Chapter 0: Preface

“This…”

Teeth clenched hard enough to shatter any moment.

Fists tight enough to draw dark red blood.

Trembling and convulsions that couldn’t be controlled.

Anger enough to turn his hair white^1

Red. Everything was red. Everything before his eyes was stained scarlet with blood.

The lush green mountain peak was stained blood-red; its very nature was swept away in a single day.

Death. All that was left was death.

What purpose did all this bloodshed serve?

Chung Myung clawed at the hilt of the sword embedded in his shoulder, drawing out the broken length of the Plum Blossom Sword.

His left arm was gone—only the torn scraps of his sleeve flapped in the wind. His legs were unwounded, yet he could barely move. His stomach gaped open with a hole the size of an infant’s head.

And yet, Chung Myung couldn’t feel the pain.

The pain of his body was nothing compared to the turmoil in his heart.

“...Sahyung^2 Jang Mun.” He discovered the discarded corpse of Jang Mun of Mount Hua Sect.

Why was it so unfair? Why were the dead unable to even close their eyes?

“Sajae^3…” Sajae Chung Gong’s bisected body haunted him.

“Sajils^4…”

Everyone was dead.

All of Mount Hua Sect’s best and brightest, who had promised to climb the mountain together, to safeguard their territory, to spread their names far and wide, had departed to a place from which they could not return.

And their Sajils followed them.

Chung Myung clenched his teeth.

Theirs was a noble sacrifice. Their death was just and glorious.

But who would dare praise their deaths? Who would dare!?

Chung Myung’s gaze locked on to the perpetrator, the one who had roused his unfathomable rage.

The Demon from the skies, the leader of the Heavenly Demon Sect: the Heavenly Demon^5.

The sight of this despicable man sat cross-legged in the sea of blood and gore evoked strange emotions in Chung Myung. Even in this hellish scene, the Heavenly Demon appeared supremely serene.

No, “serenity” didn’t suit him now. Dozens of swords pierced his body, and two spears pierced his stomach. Everyone had spent their lives to topple that demon.

The battle between the final squad, consisting only of the elite of the sects, and the Heavenly Demon ended in annihilation.

Was it satisfactory? Would the dead rest peacefully?

They would not.

Even if they did, Chung Myung couldn’t. It took everything he had left to stop the rage from stealing his rationality.

The Heavenly Demon’s pale, empty eyes opened to gaze into the blue sky.

“...Mount Hua Sect.” Three words spilled from his lips.

The words eternally inscribed on Chung Myung’s heart now emerged from the demon’s mouth.

“How unfortunate, disciple of Mount Hua Sect. If only you could get out of here, you could boast of your achievements.”

“...Shut your disgusting mouth.”

“You can still be proud of your actions. With the help of countless people, your sword finally reached my body.”

“Shut up!” Chung Myung’s stomach churned just from hearing the name of his sect from that wretched mouth.

“How unfortunate.” The Heavenly Demon was dying. Even as the greatest demon in all of time, he cannot survive his dantian breaking and his organs being ruined.

Terminal lucidity—his appearance was nothing more than his last gasps of life.

But why? Why did a dying man seem so relaxed!? Chun Ma was incomprehensible to Chung Myung.

“If I were given just one more day, I would have truly become a being worthy of the name “Heavenly Demon”. This is fate as well.”

Chung Myung gripped the sword he’d pulled out of his shoulder. The sharply forged blade cut his palm.

One step.

Another step.

At the end of a long and terrible war, Chung Myung limped towards the Heavenly Demon.

“Remember this, disciple of Mount Hua Sect.” Chun Ma’s eyes seemed devoid of emotion, even as Chung Myung approached. “This is not the end. The Demons will return. And when that happens, the world will be conquered by the Demons. The Demons can never be stoppe—”

The Heavenly Demon’s head fell to the ground.

Chung Myung crushed the head of the Heavenly Demon, eyes still open.

“It’s…”

The war was over. The world would remember their victory. But Chung Myung knew: there was no victory here. No one won this war.

Finally, Chung Myung no longer had the strength to stand. His inevitable death was coming.

Chung Myung raised his head to the sky. Even after such bloodshed, the sky was still blue, as if indifferent to the happenings of earth.

What will happen to the Mount Hua Sect? Everyone who climbed the mountain was dead. Even if anyone had survived, they were probably on their last breaths. No clan had suffered as much as Mount Hua Sect.

“Sahyung Jang Mun… I told you.”

“Don’t give your all in every task,” he’d said. Now Mount Hua Sect would be buried on this mountain. All the disciples had followed their masters to death. All that was left were the children, who knew nothing about Mount Hua Sect.

And… regret. It was regret.

Was there any meaning to what happened? Did the spilled blood of Mount Hua Sect mean anything?

“I don’t know anymore. Sahyung Jang…” Chung Myung fell onto his side.

His pure white robes, painted with a five-leaf plum blossom, splayed out before his eyes.

Innocent death.

A lonely end, with no witnesses. The great Plum Blossom Sword Saint of Mount Hua Sect was dying like a dog.

“...But your death was better than mine.” Because there was someone to weep for you. Chung Myung weeped for them.

I’m sorry, Sahyung Jang Mun. Chung Myung’s vision faded.

If he had devoted a little more of his time to training, would he have been able to save at least one person?

If he had listened to his teachers and their scolding…?

If he had truly obtained the Mount Hua Sword instead of the Plum Blossom Sword?

No regrets… But it was all regret. All he had left was regrets.

And worries for the sect.

Plum blossoms are meant to fall, and after the cold winter comes spring.

Mount Hua…

The thirteenth disciple of the Great Mount Hua Sect, the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, Chung Myung, who slayed the Heavenly Demon at the summit of the Hundred Thousand Mountains of the heavenly Demon Sect, drifted into eternal sleep.

This short anecdote was his only legacy.

Chapter 1: What The Hell Is This Situation? (1)

A dream. No, he didn’t know if it was a dream or a memory or a hallucination as he danced on the edge of death. He didn’t know if he was already dead, dying, or still alive.

All he could see was the past.

Childhood memories: his appearance from when he first entered the Mount Hua Sect; the scenes of training with Sahyung; the time he’d fled the strict sect rules and gone to see the world.

“Before a warrior, you are a practitioner. You must realize that power without ethics is just violence.”

Nagging.

Constant nagging.

It bored him. While he was a disciple of Mount Hua Sect, he didn’t fully follow the teaching. Despite his natural talent, which earned him the title of “Plum Blossom Sword Saint”, he was but a mere beginner in the Mount Hua Sect.

Why didn’t he realize earlier? Even when the teachings didn’t make sense, even when he felt out of place… everything that made him him he owed solely to the Mount Hua Sect. That was why he admired the sect so much.

He realized too late. Too late for regrets.

If only he’d paid a little more attention to the teachings, if only he was a little bit stronger, he might have been able to change that bitter ending. If only he…

“Do you regret your decisions?” Chung Myung heard the soft voice of Sahyung Jang Mun. His father, his older brother, his family—this man was Chung Myung’s goal. He wanted to follow him until the very end, but it was too late for that too.

Yes, I regret it. I regret it so, so much, Sahyung.

“There is no need for regret.” His voice exuded warmth. “It is the Mount Hua Sect after all.”

…Sahyung. It seemed to Chung Myung that Sahyung was chuckling. Forever warm and benevolent.

“Because it is the Mount Hua Sect.”

Tak!

Even then…

Puck!

Huh? What?

“Aggggggggggggghhh!” It hurts! My head! I don’t get it! What kind of pain is this? Is this what it feels like when your limbs are cut off?

“H-Heavenly Demon?” Is that bastard not dead yet? Chung Myung instinctively raised his hand to protect his head. If he wasn’t dead yet, these attacks would finish him off for good.

“Heavenly Demon?” But the voice that answered him wasn’t the Heavenly Demon, but a thick, sniveling voice he didn’t recognize.

“Huh?” When he opened his eyes, the face was equally unfamiliar.

A beggar? Beggar. A beginner—judging by the knot tied around his waist, he’d just started. A beggar among beggars.

The beggar with the grumpy, scruffy face eyed Chung Myung.

What is it? He couldn’t understand what was happening.

“‘Heavenly Demon’ – yeah right!” The beggar’s face flushed red with irritation. “You lazy bum, still sleep talking! Everyone else has gone off to beg, but you’re still here sleeping like you did something great! Yah! Do I make you laugh, huh?” The beggar hefted his bamboo stick.

Hold on… Is this kid threatening me right now? So that’s how it is.

“Huh?” The beggar was startled by Chung Myung’s sudden smirk.

It was an odd situation, but he didn’t feel like he needed to bother with context. Just who was Chung Myung, after all? He handily ranked among the top three of all the numerous swordsmen in the world. People praised his sword style as the true essence of Mount Hua Sect and dubbed him the Plum Blossom Sword Saint – the two other Great Swordsmen weren’t worthy of being his opponents. Even the Heavenly Demon, in his final moments, acknowledged Chung Myung’s swordsmanship. Disciples and sect leaders alike bowed before him.

But this beggar was making a threat? A threaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?

“Huh? Ungh? Are you laughing now?”

“Look here, kid.”

“‘Look here?’”

“I’m struggling to understand the situation, but for starters you can put that thing down.”

“Ha. Hahahahaha. Hahahahahahahaha!” The beggar could only laugh.

Chung Myung scowled. How dare he react to him like this?

And then the beggar smacked Chung Myung with his bamboo stick.

Huh. Chung Myung was dumbfounded. How dare a mere beggar do something like this, knowing who Chung Myung was? No matter what happened, he was going to fix this beggar’s attitude before the day was up.

First, he had to stop that baton! Chung Myung raised his right arm…

…What?

Huh?

Slow? Why were his arms so slow?

The baton was fast, but why were his arms reaching for it so slowly? It made no sense—with his speed, he should already be holding that stick.

Ah! Maybe it was because of his injuries? Then all he had to do was move on to his guts…

Uh? What’s that? On the edge of his vision, he saw a small hand appear, moving towards the baton at a snail’s pace.

Too slow and…

…too short?

Huh? Hands that small couldn’t stop it! This wasn’t going to work!

The stick landed squarely on Chung Myung’s head.

Chung Myung collapsed to the ground, convulsing. All of his thoughts were driven away by the skull-splitting pain.

“Kuaaaaaa!” Chung Myung clutched his head and rolled over. Even his arm being ripped off hadn’t hurt like this!

“You bastard!” The beggar laid into him in earnest. “Situation? Understand the situation? I’ll do that! But I’ll make sure you understand the situation first! If you go crazy, you go crazy! Stupid bastard! Did the heat rot your brain? The medicine for heat is getting hit, you bastard!”

“Ack! Ack! Ack! You crazy beggar! Stop right now, if not… ack!”

“Die! Die!”

“Ah—it hurts! Ack!” Chung Myung’s cries changed little by little as he was beaten.

“—You bastard! I won’t let this go! I’ll make sure to rip you—”

Smack!

“—Stop! Stop it now, please, you jerk!”

Smack!

“—Ack! Accckk! Why are you hitting me! Ack!”

Smack!

“You– beggar– ah, ack! Sorry!”

The whipping continued with no remorse.

“…save…”

Smack!

“Spare meeeee!”

As if to tell him there were no free second chances, Chung Myung was immediately beaten to a pulp.

“…Ack. He hurt my pride.” Chung Myung pulled out the piece of cloth he’d jammed into his nose.

“Ah, ahhh.” The moment he saw the red stains, Chung Myung’s face fell.

A nosebleed! Not even a nosebleed from internal injuries, but a nosebleed from being beaten! How did that even make sense? It wasn’t just the nosebleed—nothing had made sense since he’d opened his eyes.

To say nothing of his bruised eyelids, it felt like nowhere on his body was left untouched; beating someone that thoroughly had to be something of an art form. If someone hadn’t stopped him, he would have just kept goin!

Had he ever been hit like this in his entire life? Despite all the pranks he’d pulled off in the famously strict Mount Hua Sect, he had never been beaten this badly.

To suffer such humiliation for the first time at the hands of a beggar…!

“I am going to mess him up… That bastard! I’ll tear him down.” The anger and irritation roiled inside him.

Chung Myung laid on the ground. If he acted on a whim, he would only hurt his battered body.

“No, rather than that…” Chung Myung heaved himself up and stared into the river.

An unfamiliar young face greeted him. When Chung Myung contorted his face, the young man did too; when Chung Myung sighed, the young man did too.

“…How did this happen?” Why was there a different kid’s face in the water?

No, it was a nice face. The change in his face didn’t bother him—after all, the younger the better no? But it was too young. Although, better younger than older.

Besides, no matter how much he compared them, this face was a lot more charming and handsome than the old Chung Myung. He had no complaints about this new face.

But he was dissatisfied with the fact that his body was younger too.

Short. The limbs were short – not because he was naturally short or something, but because he was a child. Even worse, he was all skin and bones. Even now, he was too tired and hungry to lift a hand.

Ah, whatever!

“So…”

In summary…

“This means I’m alive.”

Maybe “I” wasn’t appropriate. No matter how hard he looked, this kid looked nothing like the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, Chung Myung. The Sword Saint was gone: his soul, and all of his memories, now resided in the body of a child beggar.

“This must be a devil’s work.”

Or maybe it was Buddhist reincarnation? Had he known this beforehand, he would have joined the Shaolin instead of the Mount Hua Sect.

He wondered if the Heavenly Demon had used some kind of disgusting magic on him. But if he could perform such feats, he would already be ruling the entire world.

Chung Myung didn’t really care what had happened, but he had to admit that everything around him was real. This was neither dream nor fantasy. His entire body throbbed with pain – the more he thought about it, the angrier he became.

“Nothing will change if I keep sitting around and thinking about it. First, I need to figure out what’s happening, and what exactly happened. Chung Myung hopped up and ran to the beggars tent.

Or he tried to run, at least.

“Kuk!” Within a couple of steps, he fell.

“You beat me hard, you bastard!” Chung Myung’s eyes rolled angrily. “No matter what happens, I’ll make sure to pay you back for this.”

Death wasn’t about to fix his dirty personality.

Chapter 2: What The Hell Is This Situation? (2)

No matter how I look at it, he seems to have gone mad. Gu Chil^1 gazed seriously down at Chung Myung. Did all the beating drive him mad?

He got hit a little harder than usual. Although Wang Cho was usually a little excessive, he’d beaten Chung Myung like he was trying to teach him a lesson—even getting attacked by a dog wouldn’t mess him up this bad. The people who normally tried to stop him didn’t even bother today, seeing how Wang Cho had absolutely manhandled Chung Myung. Gu Chil wasn’t surprised.

“So what you’re saying is… I’m a beggar?”

Was he beaten on his head or his body? A beggar, asking if he was a beggar? What madness was this? Gu Chil was certain… this guy had turned weird. No, he’d turned horrifyingly weird.

He normally slacked off, so Gu Chil knew that one day he was going to get a real beating—it was just bad luck that today was the day. That was the iron rule of the Beggars’ Union: If you don’t find food with your own hands, you either die a dog’s death, starve to death or get beaten.

Normally, people would come back to their senses after their beating. Normally. Instead, the complete opposite was happening in front of Gu Chil.

“Is it true? Am I really living in a place like this? It can’t be true.”

“…Are you blind or what?”

“Huh?”

“It shouldn’t be hard to figure it out by looking at what you’re wearing.”

Chung Myung lowered his eyes; he saw all kinds of fabrics and rags. It should have been normal clothing, but it was… rags. Any normal person would nod their head and go back to work, but not Chung Myung.

“Don’t I have a name or something?”

“Since when did beggars have names?” Gu Chil heaved a sigh. “Just a crude one. You’re Cho Sam^2.”

“…Sounds just like a beggar’s name.” Look, even his name was poor. “To be a beggar. This kind of beggar…”

The other beggar stared blankly at him.

“And age—am I around sixteen?”

“Since when did beggars keep track of their age?”

“That makes sense.”—Unlike everything else. Everything about Cho Sam had changed, from the way he spoke to the way he moved. On top of that, he had no idea what was happening around him. It was far too much to be caused by a concussion.

“Then, what year is it?”

“…Beggars count the days. You ever seen a beggar who counted the years?”

“Sounds like a true beggar.”

Gu Chil rubbed his eyes. A beggar’s life was always tired and stressful, but this was so much worse than usual.

“Then, I have one more question.”

“… You’ve been asking for a while now.”

“Do you know who the Heavenly Demon is?”

“You were mumbling about the Heavenly Demon earlier, too. Why are you suddenly looking for him?”

“Answer me first.”

“Of course I know him. Everyone knows. He was the leader of the Heavenly Demon Sect, who was defeated a hundred years ago.”

“What?”

“Boss—”

Cho Sam shot forward and grabbed Gu Chil by the collar.

“One hundred years have passed since the Heavenly Demon was slain? ONE HUNDRED YEARS? Does that really mean a century has passed since then? A centuryyyyyyy?”

“… That’s right.” Seems like Cho Sam got hit real hard.

“Tell me the truth, don’t even think about lying.”

“What good would come out of lying to you?” Gu Chil pulled Cho Sam off of him. Soon, Cho Sam’s freed hands were scratching furiously at his head.

He’s gone mad. There was no other explanation after seeing that. He wasn’t confused or rattled by the beating—he’d just lost his mind. Gu Chil had never seen someone’s face express so many shades of “flustered”.

“A hundred years, you say?”

“Do you want me to say it again?”

“…I need to head back.”

Chung Myung raised his head to the sky. He thought that seeing the clean blue sky would offer him some kind of comfort, but all he could see was the black ceiling of the tent. It was a dark as Chung Myung’s mood.

“A hundred years have passed since then?”

Gu Chil snapped.

“It’s not like you’re old or something, so why do you keep repeating the same thing!? It’s been a hundred years! The Sects had a big fight with the Heavenly Demon on top of the Hundred Thousand Mountains and took his head off! Right! It was a hundred years ago!”

“…I get it.” That was why he was so depressed.

The guy who thrashed Chung Myung earlier seemed like he was high-ranked. In that sense, the guy in front of him now could also be higher-ranked than Cho Sam.

In the Beggars’ Union, was it? Unfortunately, it wasn’t anything great—it was practically impossible for the Beggars’ Union to feed and shelter all of their people. It was said that the Union took in all beggars, but their funds were limited.

Most of the Beggars’ Union were plain street beggars. The higher-ups gave them numbers for names, and their clothes had no knots. Roaming on the streets, these beggars would have a better idea of what happened in the world of martial arts than any practitioner. Gu Chil’s words were reliable.

“Huh. Crazy. One hundred years, huh.” Everything would have changed—now it was just a matter of accepting he’d been reincarnated into the body of another child.

But… Couldn’t I have just been reborn right after my death? After a hundred years, everyone who knew Chung Myung must be dead. That aside, all the people he’d known died on top of the horrible mountain.

He was all alone.

No matter how twisted things can get, this is just too much. Then, the Mount Hua—

“Ah! Hold one—the Mount Hua Sect…!?”

When Cho Sam hopped up from the floor and started shouting at him, Gu Chil wasn’t even surprised anymore.

“Mount Hua Sect! What happened to the Mount Hua Sect?”

“What do you mean?”

“What happened to the Mount Hua Sect!?”

“Mount Hua?”

“Yes!”

“What’s Mount Hua?”

“…Huh?” Chung Myung boggled at him. He didn’t know Mount Hua? A beggar didn’t know?“

“Come on, don’t play with me. What’s the current situation of the Mount Hua Sect?”

“Mount Hua Sect?” Gu Chil tilted his head.

He didn’t know? Really? About Mount Hua Sect?

“T-the… one of the Nine Great Sects… Mount Hua Sect, you don’t know about it? Hah, you…”

“One of the Nine Great Sects? What nonsense are you spouting? There is no Mount Hua Sect in the Nine Great Sects.”

“…There isn’t?”

“Shaolin Temple, Wudang Clan, Diancang Sect, Qingcheng Sect, Kongtong Sect, Southern Island Sect, Emei Sect, Southern Edge Sect, Kunlun Sect, and the Beggars Union. There are ten now.”

“So-Southern Island Sect? Those good-for-nothing bastards are in the Ten Great Sects? Ah—no, that doesn’t matter. Then Mount Hua Sect isn’t one of them?”

Gu Chil sighed. Cho Sam only heard what he wanted to, no matter what he said. Gu Chil’s patience was wearing thin.

“Mo-Mount Hua Sect isn’t a part of the Great Sects? No, that could be possible. But you—you don’t know Mount Hua Sect? Even when a rich man becomes poor, he can last for three years with his luxuries! But you, a mere beggar, don’t know about the Mount Hua Sect?”

Calling him a beggar didn’t really capture the consequences of what he said. Well, he could starve to death.

“Does that make any sense?” Chung Myung shook Gu Chil by the shoulders. “Any sense at all? You really don’t know Mount Hua? Mount Hua? Mount Hua Sect?”

“…Mount Hua.” Gu Chil’s could feel a headache setting in.

“Right! Mount Hua!”

“Come to think of it,” Gu Chil tilted his head. “I remember hearing there was such a sect in the Shaanxi province.”

“Yes! That’s right! Mount Hua, in Shaanxi!” Chung Myung’s eyes were wide.

“From what I know, it’s doomed.”

“What?” Chung Myung’s heart stopped.

“I don’t know if there was a Mount Hua Sect in the Great Sects or not, but I heard stories about how their elite warriors were killed in the war with the Heavenly Demon. I don’t know for sure—if you want to know more, ask the others.”

What did that mean? Mount Hua Sect has fallen? Mount Hua? The Mount Hua Sect?

“This beggar, feeding me lies!”

Gu Chil turned his gaze upwards. Even when he told the truth, Chung Myung just cursed him. This was why Gu Chil hated helping people.

“No! Not a chance! I can’t believe that!” Chung Myung shoved Gu Chil away and jumped to his feet. “I need to go and see for myself!”

“Hah!” Gu Chil shouted at his back. “If you don’t come back by dinner in the evening, Wang Cho will kill you for real this time! Don’t waste your time with needless things, and get back to work!”

But Cho Sam just left.

“…What is that bastard going to do now?” Gu Chil shook his head, absolutely baffled by the change in his behavior.

“…Huh.” Was this the face of a merchant who’d lost his entire fortune? That was certainly what Chung Myung’s face looked like.

When he thought about it, with all the disciples of Mount Hua killed in the battle with the Heavenly Demon, a decline in power was inevitable. During that time, they could have been pushed out of the Great Sects. But no matter how hard he racked his brains, how could Mount Hua be pushed out and the Beggars’ Union come into the Great Sects in just a hundred years!? How did that make sense? How could beggars, who knew nothing of martial arts, be included…?

Somehow, the beggar he talked to didn’t know, so Chung Myung went asking. But no matter who he grabbed, the result was the same.

“Mount Hua? Are you talking about the mountains over there? What about it?”

“Mount Hua Sect? Did Mount Hua have a martial arts school?”

“I’ve never heard of such a sect.”

“How dare a beggar touch my sleeve—do you want your arms cut off? Let go of my sleeve this instant!”

Ah, not that last one.

No one knew. Not a single one.

“This makes no sense!” How did Mount Hua Sect turn out this way? There would always be numerous famous sects, but none would be as renowned as Mount Hua sect. It would be a bit of an exaggeration to say that all of the most famous swordsmen come from Mount Hua. Still, no one would disagree that Mount Hua was one of the three most famous, along with Woodang and Namgung.

But people didn’t know it existed?

“Argh…”

There was one positive response, at least.

“Mount Hua Sect? I think I’ve heard of it. Weren’t they famous in the past? From what I heard, they slew the Heavenly Demon and then collapsed. Are they still there?”

Collapsed? The Mount Hua Sect?

“What kind of bullshit was he spouting?” It would be more realistic to say that the Imperial palace burned down and the Emperor fled.

Mount Hua Sect has fallen! Mount Hua Sect!

Maybe I should be glad it’s me who was resurrected. Chung Myung recalled the strange expression Sahyung Jang Mun wore in his last moments. If he were alive to hear this news, he would have vomited blood and died again.

“No, no!” Chung Myung leapt from his seat. “I need to see it with my own eyes!”

Mount Hua Sect had existed for hundreds of years, no matter how horrible a state it was in. He had to see it.

“I’m going to Mount Hua!” His blue eyes blazed with passion.

This was the moment the butterfly’s wings birthed a tidal wave.

Chapter 3: What The Hell Is This Situation? (3)

Gu Chil was seriously troubled. Chung Myung left the tent screaming at the top of his lungs and then came back into the tent speaking more nonsense.

“I’m going to Mount Hua.”

Gu Chil just stared at him.

“This may sound absurd, but hear me out.”

Gu Chil actually wanted to hear just how absurd it would be. However, that was blown away by Cho Sam’s next words.

“I simply could have left without a word, but I came back to inform you because I know I received some valuable information from you.”

What a mess.

There really wasn’t a reason for Gu Chill to listen to a madman’s nonsense, but he stuck around because Cho Sam seemed so serious, and he felt bad for him.

“I will repay kindness twofold and resentment tenfold. There will come a day when I will repay the favor, so remember the name Chung Myung of Mount Hua Sect. We will meet again, and I will repay the favor that I owe you.”

His words sounded nice, at least. It would’ve been really cool if Cho Sam wasn’t bruised black and blue and dressed like a beggar.

“…Crazy talk.”

Chung Myung’s face fell.

“I know it sounds strange, but remember my words. One day, they’ll change your destiny—”

“Wang Cho is looking for you. You’re dead if he catches you.”

“Really?” They locked eyes.

“Heheheheh.” The world was full of all kinds of people. Someone suddenly reaching new heights wasn’t that great or weird in the grand scheme of things. Of course, for it to happen overnight was rather weird and frightening.

“Well, I need to get going!”

“…Come back soon. Or he really will beat you to death.”

“I’m going! Anyway, just remember: ‘Chung Myung of Mount Hua’. Remember that name!” With that, Chung Myung boldly stepped away.

Gu Chil shook his head. Life was full of twists and turns, sometimes good and sometimes bad. But if Cho Sam got caught, he really was dead.

“What am I supposed to tell Wang Cho…?”

Abruptly, the tent flap was thrown open and Chung Myung walked back inside.

What? Why was he back again? But Gu Chil didn’t get the chance to ask.

“Yah!”

“Huh?”

“What was that bastard’s name?”

“Who?”

“The one who hit me.”

“Ah… Wang Cho? Wang Cho—his real name is Jong Pal^1.”

“Jong Pal? Sounds like a beggar’s name. Tell that bastard: next time we meet, I won’t let him go.”

In Gu Chil’s opinion, Wang Cho was the one who “won’t let him go”.

“Now, I’m really going.” Chung Myung strolled out of the tent, whistling.

Just as Gu Chil thought everything was settled, Chung Myung popped back into the tent.

“Ah! What now?”

“Yah.”

“What? What now? Why, again?”

“Which way to Shaanxi’s Mount Hua?”

No matter how you sliced it, this bastard was definitely crazy.

Chung Myung ran and ran. There was not a single person in the world who would take a little beggar with them all the way to Shaanxi province.

Unbelievable… his two legs, which were so strong and reliable, felt tired. Even his heart felt weak.

Did Chung Myung ever ride a horse or carriage? Never. He could run much faster than a horse ever could, and he wasn’t nearly laid back to slow down on purpose. If you added up all the distance he ran in his previous life, you could loop the central plains ten times. That was why he’d started running without a second thought.

But he hadn’t even really stretched his legs before he was flat on the ground.

“Hack! Hack! Ugh! Ack! Oh, god! I’m going to die at this rate!”

He couldn’t have even imagined such a weak body existed. His two legs had been reduced from steel to sticks and bones, and his untiring heart was reduced to quivers.

What nonsense was this? It felt like his heart would jump out of his mouth at any moment.

“Ahhh! What kind of body is this?!” He just jumped once! Did he run for an hour or two? No! It was just a couple of minutes, but he was already gasping for breath! Just how bad was this young beggar’s body?

“Ughh.” The answers were plainly laid out before him. Putting aside his internal energy, his body alone was in quite a state—literally skin and bones, without an ounce of flesh.

And he was planning to go to Shaanxi province?

A pipe dream! He would keel over from exhaustion before reaching Mount Hua.

If he ever made it to the afterlife, his acquaintances would ridicule him. “The Plum Blossom Sword Saint, dead from exhaustion?” they’d ask.

“Hahahaha!” A mocking laugh escaped from Chung Myung’s mouth. No matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t even stand anymore.

Martial artists had great bodies, but this one was simply horrible. Chung Myung didn’t know if it would collapse from overworking or overthinking or just plain hunger! He didn’t know, so he just laughed.

“If I’m going to Shaanxi province, I need to fix this weak body first!”

But how was he to change his body? Make it healthy? He already knew the answer.

“Well, I just need to learn martial arts!”

A new start. Other people might now realize how incredible a chance this was.

Isn’t it said that those who fail to reach the top have the most regrets? Well, it was true. Even those who successfully reach the top have their regrets.

If only I had done that at that time!

If only I’d focused on learning the basics!

If only I’d practiced when the master grabbed my ear instead of running away!

If only I hadn’t gotten caught stealing from the secret alcohol stash…

No, forget that last one.

Well!

“I can do it all over again.” In the past, Chung Myung was one of the greatest swordsmen in the third generation. However, that didn’t mean he was satisfied; rather, as he got stronger and his understanding of martial arts deepened, he understood better than anyone just how inefficiently he’d practiced and how flawed his foundation was.

Foundation.

That damned foundation had cost him his Sahyung and Sajae!

Chung Myung hated the foundation classes, but he understood why it was so important when he became a disciple. After all, the foundation is what makes a man stand. A tall tower needs a strong foundation. How high the tower rises depends on how the foundation is laid. But young Chung Myung didn’t know that. No matter how much his teachers explained, he just didn’t understand. Even when he understood it, he couldn’t give it his all.

Why?

Because I’m only human. If Chung Myung was busy digging his foundation, what about the person next to him who’d already built three stories? Who wouldn’t hurry?

Besides!

“They always told me to concentrate on foundation and basics, but when I did they just praised the ones ahead of me!” Fucking power supremacy!

He could understand, though. The masters were only human too.

Everyone knew great success came from solid foundations. Still, while students struggled with their foundations, the masters were busy praising the ones with outstanding swordsmanship.

That was bearable. Mount Hua taught patience so that students were quite good at containing their emotions.

However, the students and masters had drinking parties after evening practice. What if someone starts bragging about their disciple, even at the drinking party? The drunks start bragging about their disciples as if they’re one-of-a-kind, and those who have nothing to brag about just have to sit there and take it.

That’s it. No more patience.

The next morning, they take out their frustration on their disciples.

“My Sajae’s disciple is already doing the second formation of Plum Blossom Sword!”

“That rotten man’s disciple apparently already tapped into higher internal energy! Not once have I lost to him! But now I’m losing—whose fault do you think that is? Huh? Answer me!”

“Not enough power! More power!”

With masters like that, what foundation can be laid? They were too busy trying to show off their students! It was a vicious cycle, where a Sajae’s skills were handed down to the disciples.

“However!” The current Chung Myung was different!

There was no need to rush. There was no master egging him on. Now that he’d already seen the path he had to climb, he just had to take it one step at a time.

Foundations? Others would dig into flat ground, but Chung Myung would tear down mountains. His tower would stand upon an unconquerable peak!

The first step is always important. The dantian and inner qi. In any body, the dantian was weak. As one practices, it becomes stronger and better at holding qi until it can supply the qi for your martial arts. A well-trained dantian could be the deciding factor against other martial artists.

Simply put, it’s like rolling a snowball. Imagine rolling a small snowball down a mountainside. A fingernail-sized ball becomes fist-sized and grows exponentially from there. Soon, it’s a colossal avalanche no human power can stop.

What Chung Myung needed to do was create a solid dantian to hold his qi. That meant he had to find a mountain where the snowball never stops rolling.

“Alright then!” Chung Myung looked around carefully before he began. Making a dantian for the first time was risky. He left town to find somewhere secluded, to avoid casualties. It was unlikely someone would get hurt, but why take the risk?

Here is good. Chung Myung went into the forest and sat cross-legged under the shade of a large tree.

“Now, where do I start?” There were a lot of things going through his head: all the teachings of Mount Hua, more than a dozen methods of tapping into the qi.

There was the self-healing qi.

The Plum Blossom Heart method, specific to the Plum Blossom Sword.

The internal qi, which would boost one’s qi sevenfold.

The regulating qi, said to contain all forms of energy.

The number of methods in his head would boggle most people. If he decided not to limit himself to the teachings of Mount Hua, Chung Myung could learn so much.

Yet, Chung Myung didn’t even think about it. He knew what technique he had to learn.

“Equilibrium of Six.”

For the first time, Chung Myung’s voice was clear and confident.

Chapter 4: What The Hell Is This Situation? (4)

“Equilibrium of Six”—unity. The unity of Earth and Sky and the four cardinal directions—East, West, North, and South. Six.

The Equilibrium of Six is the world, and the world is the Equilibrium of Six.

It sure had a nice ring to it.

So, what exactly does that mean in martial arts?

It’s like one of those worthless items that get tossed out of illegal stores for chump change. It wasn’t cheap, but people considered it cheap. It was the cheapest martial arts technique in the world, sold for a price anyone could afford. In short: it’s cheap.

It was supposed to be the first thing anyone should buy from the bookstore to learn martial arts. Those who don’t follow it would end up learning the same thing by self-education.

When Chung Myung was very active, the Equilibrium of Six, Right of Deliberation, and the Three Swords were famous. By the time Chung Myung was known as one of the greatest swordsmen of the third generation, the basic techniques of martial arts had revolved around Tai Chi.

So why was Chung Myung learning this cheap trick now?

Because it’s not cheap. Equilibrium of Six was one of the introductory techniques of Mount Hua Sect. All those who entered Mount Hua were instructed on the Equilibrium of Six because it could cleanse anyone’s body of impurities. Unfortunately, it didn’t make your inner qi stronger; it just made you healthier. Those who didn’t understand this despised it and cursed it so badly they wanted it removed from the teachings of Mount Hua Sect. Inevitably, newcomers to the Mount Hua Sect ended up hating the Equilibrium of Six.

But Chung Myung knew better: this was no worthless technique. If it was, Chung Myung never would have made it as far as he did a hundred years ago.

“Everything has a purpose.”

Equilibrium of Six didn’t increase strength nor qi. Honestly, when comparing the efficiency of internal qi techniques, Equilibrium was less than one-tenth as effective as other techniques.

But Equilibrium of Six was incredible for what it was made to do; the practitioner’s body would be perfectly purified.

“The basis.”—to put it simply.

The Foundation. The all-important foundation.

It was the best martial arts technique to purify the body, perfect the dantian, and perfect the body itself. However, the effects were never visible to the naked eyes, as people only noticed their dantian when using skills.

In the end, even Mount Hua gave up teaching the Equilibrium of Six. They only taught it in the introductory class because it was tradition, and even then only when asked.

What a mess. What was the point of trying to run and fly, when you’re only capable of crawling?

In his past life, Chung Myung didn’t want to cling to a technique that didn’t show him results, either.

“A hundred-fold loss. Damn it!” It was his single biggest regret. If only he’d completed the Equilibrium of Six instead of switching to a different technique, Chung Myung could have been twice as strong.

It was impossible to rebuild your foundation once the tower was built. But, thankfully, he had an opportunity to correct his mistakes. This time, he could complete it with meticulous attention to every detail. His new tower would be even bigger and more beautiful.

“Hmph.” With a deep breath, Chung Myung closed his eyes and recalled everything he knew of the Equilibrium of Six.

As he calmed down, his qi moved. With every breath, oxygen filled his body and the qi moved. First-time learners take around one month to feel the oxygen moving through their body, but Chung Myung didn’t need that time.

The energy from the air was guided by the Equilibrium of Six and settled into the lower part of his belly.

Now the real work begins. Chung Myung had no intention of loitering at the basic level of the technique. Following the path laid out wasn’t bad, but someone who had already walked the path of martial arts could never be satisfied with such a small achievement.

A little more. He focused his mind towards filtering out the impurities mixed with the qi. It was like looking at every single thread in a huge bolt of fabric and gently correcting each misaligned thread.

It was perfect.

To Chung Myung, the quantity of gathered qi was irrelevant; what he needed was a one-of-a-kind pure qi.

The qi began to fade away; from just the size of a millet seed, it became smaller and smaller and smaller. After over half a day, all that was left was a fine sliver of energy. Anyone else would be embarrassed to call this energy a “Dantian”.

“Phewwwww.” Chung Myung finally opened his eyes.

His face was bathed with sweat. His rags were drenched with sweat and thick with dust. He was already dirty, but this was on a whole new level.

“This is my first time doing it with such concentration.” Rather than difficult, Chung Myung found it refreshing. He was very pleased with the results, though calling it a Dantian was rather ambiguous.

It was weak—If you searched the entire history of martial arts, you couldn’t find a weaker Dantian than Chung Myung’s.

But Chung Myung knew: he’d taken the first step towards the perfect foundation. This little Dantian was the gateway to a whole new world. This mote of pure qi would roll like a snowball and create an unstoppable landslide.

Right. Just like…

…that bastard, the Heavenly Demon. Chung Myung’s body tensed. Even thinking about him made chills run down his spine.

He wasn’t even human. He was overpowering.

No, he was simply beyond words.

A group was assembled from the most elite from all the sects. They weren’t even after the Heavenly Demon Sect; they only wanted one person: the Heavenly Demon himself.

The result? Total annihilation.

It was no exaggeration to say that the Heavenly Demon had single-handedly beaten the Great Sects.

Perhaps… Perhaps Chung Myung would be like that this time if he did everything right.

“Okay…” Chung Myung leaped to his feet.

He managed to stand halfway before he twisted and fell on his face.

“Uh…” What? Was he faint from overworking?

“Kuuk!” He propped himself up on his arms. Or he tried, at least. His arms wouldn’t move.

“Oh?” His arms shivered as if they’d been struck by lightning. The sight of his bare arms trembling like twigs made him feel pathetic.

“Why… what now?” This shouldn’t be happening. When one learns internal qi, the body should have way more energy.

“W-wait a moment.” Chung Myung turned his gaze to his lower abdomen.

The purest qi in the world was gathered, as small as an ant… eye.

It was pure enough to satisfy even the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, and it was… almost miraculously small.

What exactly did that mean?

“No, damn it! That isn’t going to help me use my body right now! How could I forget?” Chung Myung clutched his head as he writhed on the ground.

He should have thought it through before he created it! Think! Think, Chung Myung, think! His brain was in his head, so why didn’t he think? Why didn’t he?

He could hear Sahyung Jang Mun’s voice admonishing him.

“Please think a little! Think! Why don’t you use your head when you’re doing things for the first time? Why? Your head isn’t a decoration—think!”

Had he known it would turn out this way, he would have put in a little more thought.

“I need to go to Mount Hua with this body?”

How far was Mount Hua? Roughly…

“T-two thousand miles?” He blinked blearily.

2000 miles? Any ordinary person would struggle to travel 2000 miles. But a normal child—no, a beggar with nothing to eat?

“Ugh!” Chung Myung rubbed his face. “Ah! This rotten life!”

But what was he supposed to do? He’d already created his Dantian—it wasn’t like he could have created a bigger Dantian even if he’d known. He knew what came from taking shortcuts. No more sacrificing the future for the sake of the present!

It was quite a conundrum.

“Kuuuk!” Chung Myung sighed and heaved himself up off the ground. “…What the hell is this life?”

All Chung Myung could see were hardships with no end in sight. But hardships forged heroes!

“There is nothing you can’t do with a little persistence!”

Chung Myung clenched his teeth and hobbled his way to town.

“Kuak…” Chung Myung collapsed to the ground.

There are things that can’t be done with persistence, either! And what a time to realize it.

Chung Myung had realized that there was a force that could stop him. His legs hurt, but he could tolerate pain. But there was one thing he couldn’t tolerate.

I’m hungry. Nothing could solve the hunger raging in his empty stomach.

Chung Myung wasn’t a stranger to hunger, actually. Practice sometimes requires discipline. Eating was an act of accepting external qi, but naturally, the food could contain impure qi too. Therefore, those in search of pure qi forbid themselves from eating. There were times when Chung Myung thought of abandoning his training, but he was a true disciple of Mount Hua and he was immune to hunger.

Well, that was what he thought. Chung Myung had never learned the huge gulf between choosing not to do something and not being able to do something—extreme hunger cannot be overcome with patience. His stomach felt like it was being attacked from the inside.

He managed to get out of the forest and into town, but he couldn’t do anything more. He’d practically crawled his way out of the forest.

The first life or death crisis I experience after being reborn is starvation! It was a whole new level of absurdity for him. Just who was Chung Myung? One of the greatest swordsmen of the third generation… Ah, he was tired. And hungry. He was convinced death was just around the corner.

He tried to gather qi to become a wild beast but became a worm instead.

No, when he thought about it, his body was on the verge of starvation right from the beginning. He’d only realized once he was on the brink of death.

What do I do now? He needed money to get food, and he needed to work to get money. But working in his current state was impossible.

Just then, a rustling sound came from somewhere.

Chapter 5: What The Hell Is This Situation? (5)

‘What is that?’

Chung Myung shook his head to clear his mind, only to find something shiny in front of him.

‘Huh?’

At the same time, the sound of metal clicking could be heard.

“Tsk Tsk Tsk. He’s still so young. How did he end up as a beggar?”

Clink.

Clink.

Coins started flying towards Chung Myung.

“It looks like he’s been beaten pretty badly; looks like he’ll die soon.”

“Such a terrible world. What a pitiful kid.”

‘What?’

What was happening…

‘Ah.’

‘That’s right, I’m a beggar, aren’t I? I forgot for a second.’

To everyone else, Chung Myung looked like a beggar. No, he was a beggar in his own eyes too. He was a young child who hadn’t reached adulthood yet. He was so severely beaten that his eyes were puffy and blue while blood clotted his open wounds…

And such a beggar was lying flat on the street.

“Ugh. He can’t survive without our help.”

“I can’t just watch a child suffer like that without help. What sort of person would do such a thing?”

A raggedy young beggar, with underdeveloped limbs and covered in dust, seemed to be dying.

No, it didn’t merely look like he was dying; Chung Myung was really dying.

How else could such a perfect beggar scene be witnessed from him?

Coin kept flying into view, one after another.

“Tsk. Tsk.”

“No matter how I look at him, he’s just a beggar. How did he get here?”

It seemed like the world still had kindness in it.

People were clicking their tongues as they passed by Chung Myung before tossing a few coins in his direction. Looking at the coins that came pouring in, Chung Myung couldn’t restrain the tears in his eyes.

“Oh my! He’s crying. Poor thing, it sure is pitiful.”

“Go and buy yourself some noodles with that money.”

The warmth was too much. However, the reason why Chung Myung was shedding tears wasn’t due to the kindness he received.

‘A disciple of the Great Mount Hua Sect has been reduced to begging!’

How did he fall so low?

Until just a few days ago, he was the greatest swordsman in the world. He risked his life and went to battle Chun Ma, who was about to usher in a new era of chaos. Before that, he was the most elegant swordsman that roamed the world.

But now, he was here begging. The world was finding new ways to wound him!

‘I have some pride too!’

If he accepted the money, then he would truly turn into a beggar. What a beggar he would be, a noble swordsman of the great Mount Hua who earned his living clutching the ankles of others. As if he would actually pick up the money! It was a truly impossible task for Chung Myung.

Chung Myung had a warrior’s pride. He would never give up. Even when there was a blade about to slit his throat, he refused to bend or break!

Chung Myung raised his head while clenching his teeth and shouted!

“Thank you so much! You will be blessed, sir!”

His pride was long dead.

He had to live.

“Kyaaaa~!”

Chung Myung patted his bulging belly. He looked weird, like a tadpole with a slim body that held no charm and a convex belly.

“Self~ esteem~ went to~ drain~ with the food. Better to live as a beggar~ than die!”

Due to his small stature, he couldn’t eat much.

Just three dumplings were enough to make his stomach bulge out. He still had three coins left up his sleeve.

Coins that he would have never picked up in his past life looked like treasures in this new life.

‘I never would have thought that money was so important.’

Chung Myung remembered the words of his Sahyung, who would always hold his head in agony on the last day of each month.

– Warriors need to be obsessed with wealth!

If possible, Chung Myung wanted to go back to those days and ease his Sahyung’s suffering!

‘My stomach is actually full.’

A young beggar was mouthing his complaints off to a ghost.

Chung Myung had to keep himself from crying when he thought of his hard-working, money-obsessed, Sahyung’s final moments in the battle with .

‘Anyway.’

“First, I need to live.”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

He left without a plan, and he had no idea how to get to Shaanxi.

‘I underestimated how far away 2,000 miles is.’

Chung Myung began to reflect on his actions. All of his plans revolved around the abilities of his previous body. Even though he knew that his body and the circumstances had changed, it wasn’t an easy task to adapt to his new body overnight.

In the past, he would’ve reached Shaanxi in half a day. He would have even stopped for a cold drink at an inn beneath Mount Hua, but now, heading to Mount Hua with his deprived body was a risky venture.

Even if Chung Myung could defeat any mountain bandits or beasts, there was no way he could overcome hunger.

His mind felt burdened as he realized that the journey, he expected to be easy, turned into an epic journey that could cost him the life he had just regained.

‘But I can’t just beg my way to Shaanxi.’

Chung Myung scratched his head, feeling lost.

“I need to find a way, but I need to understand what I need to find a way!”

He wasn’t aware of it when he first awoke, but a hundred years had passed since his era. It was no exaggeration to say that Chung Myung had no idea how the current world worked. But… how should he go about finding out?

“Hey!”

An average person would take more than two months to get to Shaanxi. It wouldn’t be too strange to believe that, with Chung Myung’s frail body, it could take up to half a year to reach Mount Hua.

“Hey!”

It was horrifying and frustrating for Chung Myung, who desperately wanted to see Mount Hua’s condition with his own eyes. He had to find a way, but right now, not a single thing came to his mind…

“Hey, you bastard! You deaf or something?”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung turned his head.

‘What now?’

He heard everything clearly, but he didn’t think that someone would be calling for him. There was no reason why anyone would talk to a beggar.

Three beggars were glaring down at him with ugly faces.

‘They look like beggars.’

His current life seemed to be intertwined with beggars in many ways.

“Me?”

“You? Who else could I be calling? What the hell is wrong with you!?”

The ugly beggar standing in front of Chung Myung spat on the floor.

“I don’t know what hole you crawled out from, but who gave you permission to beg here?”

Was permission needed to beg?

“You’re still a child, so I’ll spare your life. Take out everything you have, including the money you have hidden in your sleeve, and leave this place.”

The remainder of Chung Myung’s limited funds were stashed in his sleeves and in his hands…

Chung Myung looked down at his hand. They were the leftovers, the cold dumplings.

“… you people have no conscience. You bastards!”

Take this away? This little bit of food too? What was he supposed to eat!?

“You beggar!”

Whoa, a beggar was cursing at another beggar for being a beggar. It felt like he was spitting on his own face.

“Wait a minute.”

Chung Myung carefully placed the dumplings to the side.

He then stood up, stretched his hand forward a couple times, took a step ahead, then one step behind, and repeated that several times.

The beggars, who were watching the strange scene, rolled their eyes.

“What are you doing now?”

“Ah. Wait just a moment. I’ll be done soon.”

After stretching his arms and legs a couple more times, Chung Myung got up.

“It’s not entirely perfect, but this should be enough.”

After his odd routine, Chung Myung had managed to get a sense of distance and understand the length of his reach. Even with his short limbs, he managed to adapt.

So!

“You guys are about to be very upset; I have a grudge against beggars.”

“… What?”

“Don’t you understand what I’m saying? Well, that’s just how the world is. It’s messed up. Don’t be too pissed off; just accept it and move on.”

“What is this bastard talking about!?”

Chung Myung cracked his neck.

“Ah. By the way, I can’t hit very hard because my body is weak. So, you’re going to get hit a whole lot to make up for it.”

“This crazy…”

At that moment, Chung Myung lunged ahead and punched the face of the beggar standing at the front.

Ack!

A proper step. A fully extended fist that gathered strength through the gentle rotation of the waist utilizing strongly grounded legs.

Chung Myung’s fist slammed right into the beggar’s face, and the sound was like slamming a bamboo stick against a wall.

Thud!

The beggar who got hit with the unexpected blow silently collapsed on the spot.

Seeing that, Chung Myung smiled.

“You!”

Puck!

He kicked another beggar.

“I am Plum Blossom Sword Saint of the Great Mount Hua! You bastards!”

At that moment, all his accumulated resentment after reincarnation exploded.

“… esteemed sir.”

“Does a beggar look like an esteemed sir?”

“Great beggar…?”

“Should I hit you again?”

The beggars, who had their asses handed to them, whined.

‘Where did this monster come from?’

‘It hurts so much that I could die.’

A couple hits were all it took for Chung Myung to subdue these beggars. It was shocking that a child knocked out three grown adults, and it was clearly a disastrous result for the three of them.

‘It’s going to take some time to get used to this body.’

It didn’t take much to subdue them. But if he had been in his previous body, he would have turned them into rice cakes with just one finger.

But now, he had to kick, run, roll and even punch to subdue the beggars. One of them kept getting up after every hit, so Chung Myung had to slap him 38 times.

‘That Jong Pal…Cho Pal? …Whatever it was, that bastard should also be taught like this.’

Just thinking about him made Chung Myung gnash his teeth.

If only he had known how short his new limbs were in advance! If only he had the stamina to get up after being beaten, he could have beaten Pal Cho.

He was in a hurry to get back to Mount Hua, so he couldn’t even take revenge. One day, however, one day he would definitely catch that beggar and teach him a lesson.

“Men.”

“Yes!”

The three beggars jumped up. Sweat trickled down their face. All three of them looked at Chung Myung.

‘No matter how I see it, he looks like a beggar who couldn’t even lift a bag of rice.’

‘This makes no sense!’

Totally incomprehensible.

Small, weak, and thin.

On the surface, he looked weak and frail; no one expected that he could fight so fiercely. So, when they got close, they ended up seeing stars. Their fists never even touched Chung Myung’s clothes.

Chung Myung wasn’t very fast or strong, so why did they lose to him?

“Hey!”

“Yes!”

“Please give your orders! Esteemed sir! No, esteemed beggar! Ah, no!”

What’s the point in understanding? It takes time to convince someone but beating them is quick. The only important thing was that the young beggar’s punches hurt like hell.

Chung Myung glanced at the beggars and opened his mouth.

“I am just asking; do you know how to reach Shaanxi quickly?”

The beggars looked at each other and smiled. Chung Myung began to feel like there was some hope when he saw their expressions.

“Hahaha. You are asking something obvious.”

“Oh? Really?”

“If we knew something like that, why would we be begging? At least ask something worthwhile.”

“…”

Chung Myung looked at the beggars and sighed deeply.

These guys weren’t wrong. At the very least, it was his mistake to seek a path from a beggar.

“Enough. Go away.”

“Thank you!”

“Be strong!”

The beggars bowed their heads and turned around, ready to run away. No, they tried to run away.

“Hold it.”

At that moment, Chung Myung’s words froze them in place.

“Yes?”

“It is fine to flee but take out everything in your hands and pockets and leave them here.”

“…”

“You came up behind me while I was eating, so one coin… no, ten coins. Trust me, it is better than getting hit again.”

Realizing how sincere he sounded, the beggars relinquished the coins in their pockets and quickly escaped.

“Ugh, you.”

“Yes?”

“Take off everything aside from your underwear before I take them off for you.”

“…”

It was a horrific scene where a beggar was being robbed in daylight.

Chapter 6: Oh my—Mount Hua is in Ruins (1)

“Finally!” Chung Myung leaned against the stick he was using as his cane. Finally, the magnificent Mount Hua lay before his eyes.

“Finallllllyyyyy!” Tears flowed freely. How hard was it to get here? He’d brushed shoulders with death so many times and arrived using a child’s body, no different from an ordinary—no, less than an ordinary person’s body.

Of course, it wasn’t anything people usually didn’t face on their travels—mostly starvation and exhaustion. But that was dangerous too, right?

…After his terrible ordeals, Chung Myung had finally reached Mount Hua!

“…Finally.” If he wrote down his hardships, it would become a hero’s epic. Or a beggar’s epic.

Of course, Chung Myung couldn’t ignore the wear and tear on his body. Although he’d accumulated qi, the energy that should have been used to develop his body was spent walking and running. His body had not gotten stronger at all—the constant grating of his bones made Chung Myung grimace in pain.

Even his already-ragged clothes had been reduced to scraps on his body. And the dust stuck to them?

But that wasn’t important. Chung Myung had reached Mount Hua.

I’ll smash the head of anyone who says being reborn would grant a wonderful life. Chung Myung unconsciously squeezed his eyes shut.

Who you were reborn as was important. If he was reborn as a beggar without parents or a temple to take him in, he’d rather not be reincarnated.

But the suffering ends now! He’d finally reached Mount Hua! So, now he would see with his own eyes: what the hell happened to Mount Hua?

“Let’s go!” Chung Myung vigorously pushed on his stick and started climbing Mount Hua.

After a while…

“Huaaak! Huaaak!” Chung Myung, clinging to the cliff slopes, heaved like his lungs were going to burst.

“What test is this?” On this mountain? On this all-important mountain? Did it make sense for the path to be like this? He could remember the Shaolin and Wudang Sect paths overflowing with incense, but he couldn’t see a single person visiting Mount Hua.

Chung Myung stared mournfully downward. Endless cliffs stretched before his sight. Was that an exaggeration? Obviously. Nothing was endless. But he was above the clouds! This crazy mountain was so tall, he’d passed the clouds and he still had to walk!

This wasn’t a road anymore. If this was a road, then a sparrow was a phoenix. Can you call it a road if you can’t plant both feet on the ground and have to scrabble forward on your hands and knees?

“Damn it! What were they thinking, building the Sect on top of this mountain?” Chung Myung wanted to run up and investigate as soon as he’d reached Mount Hua, but it didn’t seem like he’d get the chance.

“Sahyung. Isn’t Mount Hua such an auspicious place? Isn’t that peak over there shaped like a sword? It seems like the sect established itself in a good place.”

“…Shit. Damn it.”

What? Sword-like peaks? Very sword-like. The paths to the sect cut his feet like swords.

It was said that Mount Hua was the steepest of the five mountains. It was only when he could not use martial arts that Chung Myung really understood.

“I’m really going to die.” It wasn’t a joke—he was fully convinced his life was at risk. His limbs were already trembling, and he had such a long way to go. And seeing how empty it was, he understood just how badly Mount Hua had suffered.

“Ackk.” Chung Myung groaned and propped himself against the wall.

But he couldn’t give up! What was the point if he gave up after all this way? If there’s a mountain, it’s a man’s job to climb it! Climb it, and rise again with persistence and courage!

…The truth was, going down was more dangerous.

…Really.

***

A hand clawed at the top of the cliff’s edge.

“Accckkkkkk!” The dusty white fingertips were frail, yet they lifted the rest of the body.

“Ahh! I’m going to die!” Chung Myung flopped onto his back, having barely managed to lift his body up.

“Hahh, hahh, hahh! Almost fell!”

He could see the clouds he’d put far below him. Coming this far, as a child, deserved a compliment from himself.

It didn’t go easily. It really didn’t go easily.

The good news was, he didn’t have to go down the mountain. All that was left was finding the sect.

Let’s see. Chung Myung struggled to his feet and looked around. That way—in front of him was a road leading towards the summit. From a little way along the road, he could see Mount Hua. Chung Myung’s small legs pumped. His heart shook. After a hundred years, he finally returned to Mount Hua.

“Of course, it’s only been a month since I got here.” But let’s use a hundred years, ’cause it sounds cooler.

Climbing the hill wasn’t difficult at all. His body was completely exhausted, but the thought of reaching Mount Hua gave him strength.

“Ahhh…” The sight of the roof tiles of the main gate filled his eyes with sentiment. River and mountains had changed, but these tiles didn’t; the gentle curves still capture the spirit of Mount Hua.

Right, on those old tiles—

Huh?

Old?

A tile was missing?

Chung Myung rubbed his eyes.

Was he mistaken?

No matter how much he rubbed, the scenery didn’t change. With each step closer, the half-destroyed gate became clearer and clearer.

Chung Myung ground to a halt.

The main gate was the first thing visitors saw. Even if the interior was damaged, the front gate was always kept grand and neat.

But this was the gate of Mount Hua. Its frugal and pragmatic construction exuded the atmosphere of Mount Hua. And it was at least kept neat.

But…

What am I looking at? The tiles were scattered here and there and graffitied all over. They needed to be replaced, and badly—but the cracked, blackened, unpainted pillars were even more horrifying!

S-Spider webs… They had to be removed frequently, so he could understand that. However, it was impossible to understand why they were left where they were so visible.

And the Fire Dragon Point…

“Where did the sign go? The signboard—where did it go?” Didn’t the signboard symbolize the Sect itself? Where the hell did it go?! This gate did not read “Great Mount Hua Sect”!

That was the signboard Sahyung cleaned every morning! Where did it go? Where?

Chung Myung’s legs lost strength. He barely staggered to the main gate, but he had no words left.

“From what I heard, it’s ruined?”

“Mount Hua Sect? I think I’ve heard of it. Weren’t they famous in the past? From what I heard, they slew the Heavenly Demon and then collapsed. Are they still there?”

“…Ruined?” Mount Hua? Chung Myung’s eyes shook.

“No—What kind of dog shit is this?” Others may despair, but Chung Myung struggled to contain his growing irritation.

Mount Hua, destroyed! Damn it, not something else, but Mount Hua? Mount Hua?

“Oh my. Mount Hua is ruined. Mount Hua…” No matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t deny reality. Chung Myung, battered and shaken, finally had to admit it.

“Sahyung Jang Mun! Why did this happen? Why! Why did this happen? Ah, this suffocating silence! Ughhhhh!”

Mount Hua could actually be destroyed. No matter what he heard on the way here, he didn’t hear a single thing about Mount Hua. He occasionally heard about Wudang Sect, Shaolin Sect, or even the smaller sects, but not a single word about Mount Hua.

“This is why I told you to act in moderation, Sahyung.”

“Yah. You bastard. Mount Hua is a sect. What is the meaning of warriors stuck in the mountains prettying themselves up and acting like big people? Those who ignore the difficulties of others have no right to speak about their troubles…”

“Even then, you should have held back!” The elders, disciples, and even the other great disciples were all killed in that battle. Numerous sects said they sent their very best, but there was no sect as invested as Mount Hua.

The elders who were supposed to lead the sect died, and the disciples who were supposed to succeed them… died. All that remained were the youngest disciples, who had much to learn and hadn’t even mastered their martial arts. Who, then, was supposed to carry the name of Great Mount Hua?

“…Right.” He could feel his hope shatter. He could feel it crumbling like the front gate.

Mount Hua was destroyed.

“Sahyung, sahyung! This is why I said that! Didn’t I tell you nothing would be left if we blindly followed the rules of the sect? Do you see what happened? How can you face the rest of the Sect in the underworld? Ahhh! You frustrating man!”

Chung Myung’s resentment echoed across the empty mountain.

“This is crazy. Really.”

He returned to life after a hundred years, and found Mount Hua ruined. He fought to protect this, but… if this was the result, what were they fighting for, really?

He felt the despair creeping over him.

It was then—

“Who’s there?”

—A voice touched his ears.

Chapter 7: Oh my—Mount Hua is in Ruins (2)

“Ah…” Chung Myung turned his head. There are people! After a month of travel, this was good news: someone lived in the supposedly-ruined Mount Hua.

The heavy, damaged wooden door squealed open on its abused hinges. A man in a black uniform stuck his head through the half-open gate.

“What, a child?”

Chung Myung was immediately convinced this man was a martial artist. In the last month, he had hardly ever been called a child.

“What, a beggar?”

“This beggar?”

“The beggar is traveling alone?”

“He’s a beggar.”

People didn’t care if a beggar was old or young. They were beggars just the same—but this man ignored his ragged clothes and dripping sweat and saw him as a “child”.

“You came here alone?” The middle-aged man looked around, puzzled. “How did you manage to get up here alone?”

“Uh… that…” Chung Myung stumbled over his words.

I just walked up? He wanted to say that nothing was impossible with persistence, but it didn’t seem like that would go down well in the current situation. With his skinny body, he would raise suspicion no matter what he said. There was no need to make excuses—the important thing wasn’t to explain himself but to take the lead in the conversation.

“More importantly, I need to ask you something.”

“Huh?” The man rolled his eyes. It was absurd for a child to come here all alone, much less start asking questions.

“Are you a martial artist of Mount Hua?”

“…You know about Mount Hua?”

“Am I right?”

“I am, for now?”

It isn’t too late! Chung Myung heaved a sigh of relief. It must be on the verge of ruins; he could tell that from just a glance—but it wasn’t entirely ruined, and that was the critical part.

Anyway, the legacy continues. Chung Myung resolved himself. First of all, Mount Hua is—

“Come in for now.”

“Huh?” Chung Myung was surprised by the man’s kind smile.

“The sun is going down.”

“…Oh?” Right, it was already getting dark.

“The nights are cold on Mount Hua. You’ve already had a long day—if you risk a night outside, you’re likely to freeze to death. Going down the mountain right now is unreasonable. This place doesn’t accept guests right now, but I can’t let someone who knows of Mount Hua go back alone.

Chung Myung’s eyes spun. Wasn’t this too easy?

…Come to think of it, there really was no reason for Chung Myung to be wary of him. What could a frail beggar like himself need to be on guard for?

“If no one came with you and you don’t have other plans, come in. We’ll listen to what you have to say later.”

Chung Myung was a little dazed, like something was swelling inside him.

Right. This is it. What was the meaning of making a name for yourself with a sword? Even before they took up the sword, Mount Hua Sect was famous. Hardly any traces of Mount Hua lingered, but the fires of the mighty sect were yet to be extinguished.

“Then I will trouble you tonight.” Chung Myung bowed his head.

“Come in.” The man ushered him in with a smile.

“Yes. Before that, I…” Chung Myung paused. How should he introduce himself?

I don’t know. He wouldn’t question it, would he?

“I am Chung Myung. If it isn’t too rude, may I know the name of the master?”

“Chung Myung, huh. Such a good name. I am Un Am.”

The Un family. Chung Myung’s eyes twinkled. Maybe the family changed? If it is the Un family, then this man must be the great-grandson?

Mount Hua’s Chung Myung and Un family were mutually exclusive. Neither family would exist simultaneously; at one time, it would be Chung, and at another time it would be the Uns. And since it had to have been four generations by now, this had to be the Un family.

Then he would have never seen me. The last disciples of Mount Hua to see Chung Myung were of other families, so this man named Un Am wouldn’t have known about him.

It felt like so many years had passed since he’d walked through these gates. Chung Myung had been brought to Mount Hua by Sahyung when he couldn’t even climb the mountain on his own, and now he’d come back of his own accord.

He had to take a deep breath. Considering what they’d left behind on Mount Hua and the circumstances of his return, it wasn’t strange for Mount Hua to be bare. No, on the contrary, it was expected—and it wasn’t the fault of the current people. It wasn’t their fault their seniors had been wiped out while they were still children.

In other words, Chung Myung had no right to direct his anger at these people. He should be sorry, if anything. If Chung Myung had been in the same situation, would he have struggled to protect Mount Hua? He would have left it behind and gone to the Wudang Sect. Wasn’t that just common sense?

Right. By what qualifications can I chastise these children? He was ashamed. No matter what else happened, he had to take responsibility.

“Phew.” Chung Myung finally walked inside.

Ahhh. Chung Myung had nurtured his sword in this vast hall. The cracked floor, the bluish-white stone…

“…Huh?” He rubbed his eyes. Bluish-white… no, where did it go? Why was the ground covered in mud?

Sahyung was dissatisfied by the muddy floor just beyond the main gate and decorated it with expensive blue stone. Despite being damaged by their constant practice, he never removed it.

So where did all those stones disappear to? Was the current sect leader just more pragmatic than Sahyung Jang Mun?

“Ughhh.” He could feel a headache coming.

Let’s stay calm. Calm. And calmer. What was the point of getting worked up over some blue stones?

Right. Just stones. No matter how expensive they were, they were just blue chunks of rock. Even if Sahyung Jang Mun harassed the disciples for scarring it, it was still just a stone… People are born, and so are stones; stones are born, and so are people… Ah, people and stones come and go.

Anyway!

Maybe it was sold. It was more important for Mount Hua to survive than protect the stones. Yeah, that was more important…

Let’s just calm down.

“Whew. Whew.” Chung Myung took slow, deep breaths. Thanks to those who kept the name of Mount Hua alive by selling those stones—

Where did the Heavenly Golden Palace go?

Ah, I can’t see it. What the hell? The Heavenly Golden Palace was a building, not a living thing. It couldn’t just run away, right? But no matter how hard he looked, the Heavenly Golden Palace was replaced by barren ground.

“…Uh.”

“Hm?”

“Th-there.” Chung Myung raised his trembling finger to where the Heavenly Golden Palace should have been. “T-the land there seems strange… was anything over there?”

“Ah, it seems you have good eyes. There was originally a palace in that space.”

There “was”? Where did it go?

“Haha. It isn’t a story a young one like you should hear.”

Tell me! I know this place better than you!

“I guess it’s a wound of glory. It’s embarrassing to say it, as a martial artist.”

“…Glory, my ass.”

“Huh?”

“Nothing.”

Chung Myung was at a loss. The blue stones were gone, the signboard was gone, and the best place in the sect was gone. Wherever the wind blew, it found dust.

This is Mount Hua? This? He would have believed it if you told him it belonged to those rotten bastards in the Demonic Cult.

“Acckkkkkk.”

“Are you okay?”

“Ah, no. It’s nothing. Nothing at all.” Every time he inhaled, however, he seemed to catch mouthfuls of dust.

“It’s a little…”

“Hm?”

“It seems a little… desolate.”

Un Am smiled sadly, a bittersweet expression that hurt Chung Myung.

Right… of course it would be like that. The people who protected Mount Hua, like Un Am, were the ones who suffered the most after its collapse. If they had the ability, they wouldn’t have let Mount Hua decline like this; if they hadn’t been loyal, would they have stayed even as it fell to ruin?

You must have suffered a lot. Just the thought of it weighed heavily in his heart. No matter how hard Chung Myung was taking it, it was nothing compared to the sorrow of those who protected it all this time.

“Come here.”

“…Yes.”

“When a guest comes, it is right to give them a place to rest. However, Mount Hua is a sect, and there is a law that guests must follow. I understand you might want to rest, but you must first pay your respects.”

Chung Myung nodded obediently. Un Am brought him to a place similar to a shrine. Although there were several temples of significance on Mount Hua, it wouldn’t be an exaggeration to say that Okcheon Temple was the most important. Chung Myung didn’t abandon the teachings of Mount Hua, so it was only right to enter and pray. In these trying times, he was grateful that Un Am had proposed.

And yet, he wasn’t ready to see the inside of the temple. The entirety of Mount Hua was in ruins—could the temple be any different?

Let’s not be too shocked. He took a bracing breath.

“This way.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung gathered himself and stepped into the temple.

—And then stopped. Okcheon was cut. All he could see was a portrait, an incense burner, and some small objects.

So frugal. Frugal… Chung Myung groaned and shook.

“W-where…” Where were the golden candlesticks gifted from the Jin emperor? Where were golden scrolls inscribed with the ancestor’s words?

But that wasn’t what surprised Chung Myung the most.

“T… this.” No way. No. Where did it go?

Chung Myung barely managed to raise his trembling finger towards the front.

“Huh?”

“T-there should be a flower, right?”

“A flower?”

“…Yes. A flower!”

“How did you know that?”

“I-it was there, right? Where did the flower go?”

Un Am tilted his head quizzically. There were many things he wanted to ask this child, but his contorted face begged him to answer.

“Right, there was one there. A plum blossom made of a strange white metal.”

“Yes! That flower! Where did it go?”

“Sold it.”

“…Huh?”

“It wasn’t particularly useful and didn’t fit well with the sect atmosphere, and there was a merchant who wanted to buy it. So we sold it for a good price.”

“S-sold…”

“Right. But you—”

“Ugh! Ugh! What?!” Chung Myung’s eyes rolled crazily. “Ugh…”

The White Fragrant Plum Blossom—along with the Divine Sword of Violet Dawn, it was one of the two sacred items of the sect. It didn’t glitter like gold or shine like silver, yet it was said to contain the very essence of Mount Hua.

And these crazy people sold it.

“Th-there are other things to sell! You sold it! You idiots…”

The combination of shock and fatigue finally won over him, sending Chung Myung toppling to the ground.

He could almost see Sahyung Jang Mun’s terrified figure.

Ruined. Mount Hua was ruined. Completely ruined.

Sahyunnngggg!

Chung Myung passed out.

Chapter 8: Oh my—Mount Hua is in Ruins (3)

Elder Hyun Jong of Mount Hua Sect gave Un Am a confused look.

“You mean he came up here alone?”

“Yes.”

“And then he fainted inside Okcheon temple?”

“It seems like he couldn’t even eat properly but, since he climbed Mount Hua by himself, it’s natural for him to be exhausted.”

“I guess so.” Hyun Jong smiled. The ruggedness of Mount Hua made it difficult enough for an adult to climb. The strain it would place on a child would be indescribable.

“Where is that child now?”

“I moved him to the Plum Blossom Hall. I also called Un Jin to check on him, and he said there was no problem other than fatigue.”

“That’s good.” Hyun Jong nodded. Whatever his circumstances, the kid was a guest of Mount Hua now.

“But it’s strange for a child to climb up here alone. Is there no story behind it?”

“After the visit to Okcheon, I was going to ask him—but, as you know, he fainted, and I couldn’t ask.”

“I see.”

“But…”

“Hm?”

Un Am frowned and explained the plum blossom to Hyun Jong.

“‘You sold them?’” Hyun Jong tilted his head quizzically.

“Yes.”

“He said that and then fainted? Hmm.” The Elder stroked his beard.

“Of course, I could have heard it wrong. But it is a long story. That wasn’t the only weird thing—before I could ask him anything, he asked me if I was a martial artist of Mount Hua. Doesn’t that mean he came to join?”

“Yes.”

“I wonder what he was planning…”

“Are you worried?” Hyun Jong chuckled at Un Am.

“It isn’t like that…”

“What is so strange about knowing where Mount Hua is? This sect left its mark on history. It’s no wonder people would remember it.”

“Right.”

“And he could be a descendant of a Mount Hua member.”

“Ah…” Un Am nodded. As they were pushed out of the Great Sects, many people had left Mount Hua. Few had remained to share their fate to the end. If this kid descended from one of them, they would find out.

“If you’re worried he’s here to steal something, what is there left to steal?”

“…Sect leader.” Un Am’s face fell. However, Hyun Jong didn’t see that.

“Sold it.” Hyun Jong shook his head and smiled. “Right… right. Maybe he descended from a former member since he seems to know what Okcheon Temple used to be. It must have been embarrassing for the child.”

“…Sect leader.”

“Enough. It’s true that we sold it. There’s nothing to be ashamed of.”

Maybe it’s better not to tell him. Un Am gulped. He wasn’t telling him everything the boy had said.

“You sold it! You idiots…” He wondered how the sect leader would react to those words.

“Right. Bring him to me as soon as he wakes up.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Hyun Jong lost himself to his thoughts.

Sold it. It felt like salt being sprinkled on his wounds. The ancestors will never forgive me.

No matter how much he wanted to save Mount Hua, how could he face his ancestors after selling the very history of Mount Hua? It hurt to think about…

The name of Mount Hua should not end in my time. Hyun Jong’s face darkened. It wouldn’t happen, not even in his dreams—he worked day and night to keep Mount Hua afloat. But with each day, his hope waned.

Un Am quietly stood up.

“I’m leaving.”

“Hm.”

“Ah…” Un Am stopped, just as he was about to leave. “Sect leader.”

“Hm?”

“If that child wants to join, what do you plan to do?”

“Join…” Mount Hua Sect didn’t accept disciples anymore. However, it would be different if they were a descendant of one of the disciples.

“It won’t happen.” Hyun Jong nodded firmly.

“I understand.”

“Wait.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“What’s that child’s name?”

“Chung Myung. It’s Chung Myung.”

“…Chung Myung.” Hyun Jong’s expression darkened. “Okay. You can go.”

“Yes.”

“Chung Myung…” He had the same name as one of Mount Hua’s swordsmen.

“Weird.” It was definitely weird.

“If only he were still alive.” If only the famous Plum Blossom Sword Saint had survived that bloodbath, the fate of Mount Hua would be much different. It was a meaningless daydream, but Hyun Jong couldn’t help himself.

“…So much debt.”

Hyun Jong felt so, so alone.

“You damned bastards.” Chung Myung spat curses. “You had nothing else, so you sold it?”

It was maddening. Even if they were starving to death, those weren’t things they should sell. No matter how shabby it looked, the disciples… were dead. The young kids would have… known nothing.

Right…

But even if Mount Hua was destroyed, those couldn’t be sold—

“No, this is better than being ruined.” If the ancestors had seen Chung Myung, they would have scolded him. No martial artist should be obsessed with material things. He knew that. He knew it well.

“Shit.” Chung Myung groaned.

He looked down at the mountain range. Whenever he’d felt frustrated, he would climb another mountain and look at Mount Hua. When he saw the endless peaks rising through the clouds like swords, his spirits rose. But now…

“Shit.” Everything was bad. It was all inside out. It felt like his stomach rotted whenever he saw something missing.

“The sect has declined.” Really, it was more like “collapsed” than “declined”.

“Anything of value was sold.” That meant practically everything in Mount Hua. No doubt, Okcheon was the last place they touched—after he saw Okcheon Temple, he could understand why this place was so run down. They were so destitute they’d pulled up the blue stones and sold them.

“…Right. I understand everything! Everything else is fine, but this—! “

Why are the martial arts so crooked?!

Chung Myung rolled around on the floor outside the hall. He would die if he fell off, but Chung Myung didn’t have the time to think about it.

“That old man… not even a third-rate disciple?” Talk about fate. Under normal circumstances, Chung Myung wouldn’t even be able to guess the level of Un Am. No matter how strong he used to be, he was nothing more than a kid now.

However, Chung Myung could clearly see Un Am’s level of martial arts. His senses weren’t strong, Un Am was just too weak. When Chung Myung was at his prime, Un Am wouldn’t have even qualified as a student.

“…What am I supposed to do?” He didn’t even know where to start. He knew he should start from the bottom, but it was too deep for Chung Myung to see.

Is this Mount Hua?

Do I tell them I’m that Chung Myung? They would curse him, no doubt. If he was lucky, they wouldn’t beat him before they kicked him out. Chung Myung wouldn’t believe himself, either.

But let’s say they did believe him. Assume the man was infinitely patient and asked him to prove it with his martial arts.

I don’t have the strength. Chung Myung was like a walking treasure. He had all the knowledge to revive the sect but not the power to protect himself. Chung Myung knew not everyone was as wonderful as his Sahyung. What if one of them didn’t like Chung Myung and decided to take him out? His second life would be stolen, just like that.

That’s no good, either.

“Then I’ll have to revive the sect without revealing my identity.” Or at least, hide it until he had the means to protect himself.

“…It would be easier to fight the Demonic Sect.” He spat a laugh. He had to teach martial arts to save Mount Hua and himself. He wanted to start hitting people, but…

“…If I had known this would happen, I wouldn’t have run over here.”

He owes Mount Hua. The only reason he could walk around saying he was the best swordsman in the world was because of Mount Hua. Yet, he’d given nothing back to Mount Hua, only the honor of defeating the Heavenly Demon. Thanks to that, Mount Hua was on the edge of destruction. How could he ignore Mount Hua? He couldn’t.

“Oh, Sahyung…” Chung Myung shook his head regretfully.

Up in the blue sky, he could see Sahyung Jang Mun smiling down at him.

“Still, it’s Mount Hua.”

“…Uh.” Chung Myung heaved himself up. If he didn’t want Sahyung to murder him in the afterlife, he had to make himself useful to Mount Hua.

“Damn it, who said anything could be impossible in this world?” When he’d first started learning martial arts at Mount Hua, who would have imagined he would become a great master? Everyone had thought they would be lucky if he didn’t cause trouble. Chung Myung overcame their cold eyes and became famous in Mount Hua—challenging the impossible was his specialty!

“I will make it the best in Murim!” Chung Myung’s eyes glowed with passion.

Everyone in Mount Hua shivered.

Chapter 9: Oh my—Mount Hua is in Ruins (4)

“Where did you go?”

“I was looking around.”

“…Looking around?” Un Am eyes Chung Myung suspiciously. However, Chung Myung crossed his legs and turned to gaze at the sky as if he didn’t mind at all.

Was this child always like this? The first time he saw the kid, he’d seemed extremely polite. Now it seemed like his behavior had changed.

How should he put it—he was full of bad energy?

Well, he must be. Judging from his behavior, the kid must have been a beggar for quite some time. Expecting innocence from a beggar in this world would be naive.

“Have you eaten?”

“I’m not hungry.” Chung Myung was being sincere, ironically. The condition of Mount Hua stole away his appetite—how could he overcome the emptiness he felt from looking at this place?

“Then follow me.”

“Huh?”

“The sect leader wants to see you.”

“Ah, yes.” Chung Myung nodded. He had to do this eventually; better sooner than later.

The door opened to reveal an old man sitting quietly. Chung Myung was shaken.

He certainly deserves to be called “sect leader”… The feeling of qi was enough to convince him that this man had devoted his entire life to this place. But…

But he doesn’t seem to have the courage to speak first. As a sect leader, he didn’t lack for anything, but he was lacking as a warrior of Mount Hua.

“Greetings.”

Is there anywhere as unhappy as this? Chung Myung sighed. After all he’d been through, this sect leader seemed like a toddler compared to the sect leader of his time. Here was the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, offering his greetings to a toddler.

I shouldn’t have been reborn. What was he supposed to do? Get sick and die?

Chung Myung didn’t voice any of his thoughts and just bowed.

“I am Chung Myung.”

“I am Hyun Jong.” The sect leader smiled and returned a simple greeting. “A guest has come, but we have nothing to treat you. I hope you can understand our current situation.”

“Ah, yes.”

Hyun Jong’s eyebrows twitched. Usually, you would reply, “Don’t worry,” or something like “How could an uninvited guest expect much?” But the look in his eyes and his gestures indicated this child didn’t seem to expect much from them in the first place.

“I heard you said something interesting in Okcheon Temple.”

“Hhn?”

“‘Sold it?’”

“What are you talking about?” Chung Myung tilted his head. Hyun Jong narrowed his eyes, but it really seemed like he didn’t understand what was being asked.

He really doesn’t know? A child couldn’t lie so well.

No use trying to read me, you jerk! Chung Myung smiled to himself—he was Chung Myung, one of the best liars in the world! Even Sahyung wouldn’t see through his lies or find his alcohol.

Hyun Jong simply couldn’t find any evidence that the child was lying.

“Did you not say such words?”

“I don’t remember well. The only thing I remember was being so tired I fainted…”

“Hmm.” Made sense. He’d climbed Mount Hua with his young body—the kid must have reached his limits. However…

“If you were that tired, why didn’t you say anything?”

“It is said that, when entering the gate, it is necessary to pay tribute to the ancestors…”

Hyun Jong raised an eyebrow at Un Am.

The child came here all alone, and you dragged him off to make him pray? Huh?

Un Am blinked.

No! He was perfectly fine! The kid was perfectly fine until he entered the gate—and then he passed out from exhaustion? What kind of crazy story is that?

Un Am shot Chung Myung an accusatory look, but Chung Myung’s eyes were wide and innocent.

“Hmm.” Hyun Jong nodded. “That sounds reasonable. Apologies for our inattention.”

“It’s fine.”

“Right. Another question.”

“Yes?”

“Why did you climb all the way up this steep mountain? Don’t say you came here on a whim. Mount Hua isn’t something people climb for the novelty, much less a child.”

A sharp question. But Chung Myung had his answer prepared in advance.

“Sect leader.”

“I’m listening.”

“I want to enter the Mount Hua Sect.”

“You want to enter?” Hyun Jong’s eyes narrowed.

“Yes.”

Hyun Jong stared at Chung Myung, but he couldn’t see anything from his innocent eyes.

“Does that mean you climbed up here with a purpose?”

“Yes.”

“Hmm.” Hyun Jong nodded. Mount Hua wasn’t a place for tourists.

“You want to enter Mount Hua. This means you know of Mount Hua?”

“Yes.”

“Enter.” Hyun Jong’s eyes narrowed. Chung Myung licked his lips.

It makes sense. Chung Jin was chased by the Demonic Sect and disappeared before the final battle. A missing person, not dead. Chung Jin fell off a cliff. A woodcutter found him and helped him heal; however, the injury was too severe for him to ever fully recover from. As gratitude, he took the man as his disciple and taught him the martial arts of Mount Hua—and Chung Myung is the descendant of that woodcutter!

Superb! A flawless script. The best thing was that Chung Myung had control of everything he said. This story had no loopholes, and he was guaranteed to be accepted as a member of the sect.

Even if I won’t get the same fame as in the past. He would at least be treated well, even if they didn’t think too kindly of him.

Now, ask me the reason. And then he would unfurl his script. It would be a breeze from—

“I accept.”

“Yes? Of course, the entry… what?” Chung Myung boggled at Hyun Jong. Contrary to his expectations, the sect leader just nodded at him.

“If you want to join, we should let you.”

“Huh?” No, wait. Was it so easy to gain entry into this place? A totally unfamiliar child?

“S-sect leader!” Un Am was equally shocked. “Didn’t you way we won’t accept new students?”

Yes, ask him!

“I changed my mind.” Hyung Jong grinned. “Truthfully, we aren’t in a position to accept new students—but we cannot turn our backs on a child who came all this way knowing about Mount Hua.”

“Ha… but…”

“Un Am.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Things go round and round. Whatever the child is, he came to us on his own two feet knowing of Mount Hua. Are we going to kick out those who searched us out, just because we aren’t as great as in the past?”

If someone else heard this, they might have been impressed. However, after all of Chung Myung’s preparations, it was just making his skin crawl.

What is this? Aren’t they supposed to be suspicious of someone they don’t know?

How did he even become a sect leader? No, he must have become a sect leader because he was like this.

“Ah, no… Before that, I live…”

“It’s fine.” Hyun Jong shook his head firmly. “It doesn’t matter what kind of life you lived before this. Whether you were a sinner of a thief, the moment you climb up Mount Hua your past disappears.”

Of course it did. But it couldn’t be that simple…

“N-no…”

“I told you it was fine.”

Man! It isn’t okay! Listen to me!

“Un Am.”

“Sect leader?”

“Give this child a place to stay.”

“Yes.”

“Your name is Chung Myung?”

Chung Myung nodded.

“A very nice name. A very good name. Chung Myung of the Chung family.” The sect leader chuckled. “This must be fate, too. You don’t need to get a new name for him—you might not know, but your name means a lot in Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong’s eyes narrowed.

“Would anyone be worthy enough for that name?”

“…Yes,” Chung Myung replied.

“I’ll see.”

Chung Myung stood stiffly, and Un Am escorted him away with a sullen expression.

“This way.”

The landscapes of Mount Hua caught his eyes as he stepped outside.

I’ve entered.

Entered…

Un Am interrupted his thoughts.

“The introduction ceremony hasn’t been held, but from this moment on you are a disciple of Mount Hua. You will become a vessel for the martial arts, and the youngest disciple of Mount Hua.”

“…Youngest.” Chung Myung’s eyes trembled. Youngest? Him? The Plum Blossom Sword Saint, Chung Myung, the youngest?

“Hehehehe!” When Chung Myung’s amusement leaked, Un Am couldn’t help but smile.

“You seem happy.”

“Yes. So happy. Hahahahaha.”

But why were tears falling?

…Shit.

Chapter 10: Oh my—Mount Hua is in Ruins (5)

“The child?”

“I sent him to the dorms. I think we can just proceed with the ceremony right away.”

“I see.”

Un Am stared at his feet. Hyun Jong, seeing that, gently smiled.

“You don’t seem to like this.”

“Rather than not like…”

Un Am hesitated a little, then opened his lips with a sigh.

“Sect leader, I just don’t seem to understand the meaning of your actions. Why was the child taken in? Now is the time for us to reduce the mouths we need to feed.”

“Yes. That’s true.”

“And he isn’t just some child, but one who doesn’t even have any talent for martial arts.”

“Hm.”

“Above all, I don’t feel even a single once of kindness from him. That child doesn’t seem to fit the standards of our sect. So why bring in such a kid into our Mount Hua?”

At Un Am’s points, Hyun Jong smiled.

“You think so?”

“… sect leader.”

Un Am took a deep breath. Sometimes this old man was confusing.

‘I can never understand him.’

Even after assisting this man for over 10 years Un Am still couldn’t understand him. Hyun Jong’s thoughts were too deep for him to understand.

“Un Am-ah.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Sometimes relationships come unexpectedly.”

Hyun Jong smiled brightly.

“Maybe that child could turn into a light for Mount Hua?”

“… that child is too young to be the light of Mount Hua.”

“He could be.”

Hyun Jong’s face darkened.

The current state of Mount Hua was similar to a wind chime. Holding itself up was hard and no one would bat an eye if it fell.

That was the reason why Un Am didn’t want Chung Myung to join.

How much sadness would Chung Myung feel if he was left alone right after joining? How would he feel suffering so much to get here only to be pushed back onto the streets?

“I know the situation is difficult.”

Hyun Jong opened his mouth.

“But Un Am-ah. Plum Blossoms are bound to bloom even in snow. The Plum blossoms in the harsh cold are bound to give off a sweeter scent than normally brought plum blossoms.”

“…”

“If we don’t plant seeds just because the winter has come, won’t that mean that the possibility of plum blossoms in snow will disappear?”

“… Yes.”

“Right. So go and see.”

As Un Am quietly closed the door, he shook his head as he sighed.

Each time he talked with Hyun Jong, he felt like his heart was being ripped open.

However, as of today, even after talking with Hyun Jong, his heart didn’t feel refreshed. At Hyun Jong’s words, his thoughts still stayed and mind was still fuzzy because of the current situation of Mount Hua.

The current Mount Hua couldn’t be saved.

Hyun Jong worked hard all his life but the situation just kept getting worse. If things went on like this, they wouldn’t last another year.

Whenever he thought Mount Hua, which had such a valiant history, was coming to an end, his heart would ache.

‘Where is our Mount Hua heading?’

Un Am closed his eyes.

Chung Myung blankly lowered his head looking at the clothes he was wearing.

A white robe which caught his eyes. Looking at the five petal plum blossoms engraved near the chest, he felt strange. It made his entire body tickle…

“No, this is really itching me!”

The material of the clothes was so bad that each time it touched the skin, it felt like it was grating on his skin. If he hadn’t experienced those rags on before, wearing this would have troubled him even more. The month of living as a beggar seemed to have helped him.

“Tch.”

Chung Myung frowned.

“It’s changed.”

In the past, Mount Hua wasn’t a clan with money overflowing like the Wudang sect or Shaolin sect, but still it had enormous wealth hidden in.

Of course, he couldn’t spend the money to his heart’s content because of Sahyung, whose greed for money never let anyone touch it. At the very least, he would dress the disciples of the sect with nice clothes and feed them good things.

But the clothes were all ragged now…

“What did these people do with all that money?”

There must have been heaps of money in that safe!

No, forget the safe. They even sold off the historically important items inside the sect for money, so why were they dressing the kids like this?

Not able to dress them properly, not able to teach them properly doesn’t this mean that they just wasted all the money they got?

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

“There is no such thing as a straight walking path.”

Sigh. The more he thought about it, the more his head hurt.

Expectations only lead to disappointment.

“Anyway, I joined.”

He managed to join.

The worst disaster happened, in which he ended up being the youngest of Mount Hua.

This wasn’t what Chung Myung wanted, but at least he managed to enter the sect.

There are a lot of problems which will have to be solved, but isn’t this just the first step in a thousand miles path?

No matter how difficult the task is, there is nothing that cannot be done if it is tackled one step after another. Most things in the world can be solved like this…

“But where is this place?”

That was the problem.

Where Chung Myung was located now was a hall in the past. However, it was changed in the meantime, the past appearance of the hall was turned into a dorm.

If Chung Myung’s memory hadn’t failed him, there was no concept of accommodation in Mount Hua. Those who were newly admitted into the sect would start living with their Master.

Then what was he doing now?

‘I can’t see this as a place where I stay before I enter the wings of another Master.’

No matter how he looked at it, it was a place made for the sake of humans to live.

‘Am I the only one here?’

Chung Myung came out of his room.

The rooms were lined side by side around the narrow hallway. It was different from the appearance of the past.

Chun Myung opened the door to the next room. And show clothes and other items in it.

‘is someone staying here?’

Chung Myung titled his head. ‘Who would dare to live in such a messed up room?’

“Who are you?”

Chung Myung turned his head.

‘Oh my!’

He didn’t even notice that someone was approaching him! He had made a mistake.

‘Ah. I forgot, I don’t have martial arts now.’

Even though he came to Mount Hua, he didn’t learn martial arts yet. Thanks to that, only his body got stronger after qi cultivation, which was the foundation…

Realistically speaking, the only thing he could do right now was gather the internal qi which was as small as a fingernail. Which meant it was impossible to be anywhere close to where he was in the past.

“Who are you, you bastard? Spying in on someone else’s room? A thief?”

A rough mouth.

A child who seemed to be the same age as Chung Myung. As the child yelled, more kids rushed out.

“What?”

“Jo Gul! What is it?”

The child called Jo Gul pointed to Chung Myung.

“This jerk was spying into my room.”

“Who is he?”

“Looks like a newcomer?”

Chung Myung looked at the ceiling.

‘Why did I have to come back alive?’

Was it to witness such a cruel situation?

It was heart-breaking to see the young people point fingers at him and call him what-not. In terms of age, Chung Myung was their great-grandfather.

Of course, they couldn’t possibly know that.

But how should he reconcile the meek and disciplined students of Mount Hua, to the current disciples who were using their mouths like neighbourhood gangs?

As he opened his mouth to speak to the guy with messy hair.

“What is happening!”

“Ugh!”

“Teacher Un Geom!”

At the low voice from behind, the kids began to move left and right. And a huge person came down the stairs.

Clumsiness which reflected on his face and gestures. And it was evident that this kid hurt not a single person till now.

As he was called, Un Geom glanced around with his sharp sword-like eyes, befitting his name.

“Why are you all making a fuss during your training time? Who said it was fine for you to do this?”

“No, it isn’t like that…. My uniform was dirty so I came to get a change of clothes.”

“How dare you give me excuses!”

“I apologize.”

The frightened children all backed up a step. In the meantime, they all looked at Chung Myung.

“You are?”

“Chung Myung.”

“You must be a new member of the White Plum Blossom Boarding House.”

“White Plum Blossom Boarding House?”

“This is the White Plum Blossom Boarding House. These are the dorms where the disciples of Mount Hua live. Didn’t you hear about it?”

“… dormitory?”

The man frowned.

“Don’t you know that you should speak in a respectful manner?”

“Ah, yes. I apologize.”

Calm…Calm down.

… damn it.

Once again, he didn’t think it through. The children who hadn’t even entered Mount Hua during his time would be Masters now.

‘This is so messed up.’

To have the position of a teacher, this man must be really skilled. He was sure that he would be forced to work for his life here.

“You too, come along.”

“Yes?”

“Whether you are late or early, you need to practice. It wouldn’t make any difference. It is the job of a disciple to never waste time in vain.”

Chung Myung could help but agree to the statement.

In order to change the terrible situation, Chung Myung had to strengthen himself even a day sooner. For that, an environment where he could focus on training was necessary.

The problem was that what they were trying to teach him would be basic martial arts which are useless to Chung Myung.

“Come.”

The man left first, the children followed after him. However, one of them turned back.

It was Jo Gul.

“I’ll see you tonight.”

“…”

“I’ll fix that head of yours.”

“… right, right.”

“Don’t bother thinking about running away.”

“Sure, come.”

“You really are…!”

“What are you doing!?”

The child, startled by the shout of Un Geom, responded.

“I-I am coming teacher!”

Seeing the child run ahead, Chung Myung sighed.

“I need to treat them well.”

They were all the descendants of the sect.

Of course, the way Chung Myung showed favor to the kids would be different from others.

“They deserve it.”

Chung Myung smiled as he moved.

Chapter 11: Collapsing was inevitable, you bastards (1)

“But…”

“Hm?”

Un Geom lowered his head and looked at the kid walking next to him.

‘He seems pretty fierce.’

People placed in new environments tend to be meek. It is normal to get scared when in an unfamiliar place like Mount Hua. This is especially true for someone at such a young age, but he couldn’t find that in this child.

The fast walk showed the kid’s annoyance, not fear.

Un Geom looked at him with strange eyes. When Chung Myung suddenly asked.

“When did that place called the White Plum Blossom Boarding House come into existence?”

“What are you curious about?”

“I heard that teaching is done by taking a disciple under a master, as well as lodging with them during the process.”

“Hmm.”

“It was a little strange to see everyone gathered at one place.”

Un Geom frowned at the comment.

‘He is stabbing at a sore spot.’

Traditionally what the child said was right. A newly introduced child would be taken under a master and that man would instruct the disciple about Mount Hua.

That is why Mount Hua was known to be the most dignified sect.

The reason this teaching method was broken was because of the decline of Mount hua.

“Nothing much. We just thought it would be more efficient.”

“Then does teacher also stay back in the White Plum Blossom Boarding House?”

“… no.”

Chung Myung nodded his head at which Un Geom frowned.

‘A strange kid.’

Such an answer wouldn’t satisfy the curiosity of a kid. However, this one nodded his head as if he understood… no, more like, he didn’t care.

And Un Geom wasn’t sure what the kid was thinking.

Basically, everyone who enters Mount Hua is sent to the same dorms. In other words, it was to make the newcomers be aware of Mount Hua’s teachings under Un Geom, who handled them.

He had seen quite an array of children but never such a strange kid. What should he do? He couldn’t just explain the sob story to a kid, right?

‘An interesting kid seems to have come in.’

While Un Geom was slowly analyzing him, Chung Myung had different thoughts.

‘They ran away.’

He could barely comprehend this situation.

Looking around at the entire Mount Hua, he could see at a glance how absurd the situation of this place was. Considering how he should have left behind at least three disciples during his time.

If even only three people stayed back Mount Hua wouldn’t have turned into this…

‘This means many people abandoned Mount Hua.’

The number of people couldn’t have decreased in an instant.

But it was a sinking ship. And once one person walks out, the others would soon follow.

Assuming it is okay for those masters who didn’t have any disciples they are responsible for to leave. What could the disciples with nowhere to go do if their masters who were supposed to teach them leave the sect? There was a limit to what another master could handle.

As a result, a situation would come out where there aren’t nearly enough people to teach.

“Tch.”

Chung Myung lost his appetite.

‘What to do?’

The current situation is nothing to criticize. Chung Myung was a pragmatist in the past, and unlike now, he had been quite closed off. Delivering results was more important than sticking to tradition.

If these people made Mount Hua survive by creating the new dorms, then it was overall a good thing. He felt a bit bitter, but…

‘The hearts of the children who had to make up the new dorms must have been torn.’

It was depressing as he could guess exactly how they had felt.

‘No. I don’t have the time to think like this.’

Enough of being depressed for others. What Chung Myung had to do was to not be swayed by emotions, but to remake Mount Hua the same great place it had been in the past.

Three halls unfolded in front him. A high pedestal at the top of the large vacant lot and small kids taking their place.

“Huh?”

Chung Myung titled his head.

The number of disciples was much lower than expected. Compared to the past where the ground was filled, only a handful of them were here.

“Sword!”

“Tahha!”

With the command, the swords were used and pointed ahead.

‘Oh?’

Chung Myung who looked at it wondered. Mount Hua was a liberal sect. Although it had been criticized for having a strong secular nature, they didn’t follow the martial teachings blindly. It was because they didn’t like considering the martial arts to be something to force and discipline the kids.

Thanks to that, the training hall was never actually full of disciples. Yet, it was constantly overflowing with willed people.

‘This is interesting.’

It was certainly interesting to see more than a hundred people learning the same swordsmanship.

Even Chung Myung had never gone through such type of training, except for the time when Sahyung would teach the Seven Star Sword Technique.

“To the back!”

Slash!

The sounds of a hundred swords moving at once.

Seeing that, Chung Myung exclaimed.

“Wow…”

“Isn’t it nice?”

“…”

Un Geom asked with a smile.

“No need to be shocked. If you practice hard, you will soon become like them.”

“… yes.”

Chung Myung’s answer was rather bland considering how he exclaimed a moment back.

Of course, Chung Myung’s comment had a different meaning than Un Geom assumed.

‘What are they doing?’

The further the training progressed, the more his eyes narrowed.

“Ahead!”

The children took a step ahead and then stabbed. It wasn’t swordsmanship which kids should be taught.

“That…”

“Huh?”

“What kind of sword technique is it?”

“What do you mean?”

“Ah… the swordsmanship.”

Un Geom, who understood the question, nodded his head and answered.

“The swordsmanship which they are practicing now is the Equilibrium Sword.”

“Equilibrium Sword?”

“Yes. To be precise. It is called Equilibrium of Six Sword. A sword technique which was handed down from Mount Hua’s strongest swordsmanship masters. It is the sword technique which is the basis of everything.”

“…”

“It might not be easy to learn, but if you put in effort you will surely see results. Make sure you go and stand at the back. It will be awkward for your first time, but think of it as a learning and observation period. Detailed instructions will be done within a week.”

Chung Myung walked to the back with a dull face.

‘He must have been frightened.’

Seeing that, Un Geom frowned.

‘Kids have no ambition these days.’

Right…

He glanced at the kid again.

It was strange that the kid didn’t seem frightened by holding a real sword. Even fearless kids would tremble a little when they see themselves holding a real sword.

However, Un Geom thought that it would be better to not expect too much from this child.

Meanwhile, Chung Myung who was standing at the back had a completely different line of thoughts.

‘What the hell are these crazy people even doing?’

Practical?

Learning this?

Sigh, this is knee deep shit!

This was an introduction to martial arts?

Introduction is meant to give the basics to the kids who were nothing more than blank sheets of paper.

What would happen if they decided to teach some children three thousand characters instead of basic alphabets?

Sure, the kids would be able to know the characters by heart, but would they be able to understand the meaning behind them? Of course not!

This was going to ruin the kids.

‘What good will this do?’

These people were in a hurry, so they used this shortcut method. But this was too ridiculous. What these kids were doing wasn’t that great.

But!

“It’s plausible enough to teach.”

“Eh?”

“Hm?

Chung Myung said his thoughts out loud, making all of them turn and look at him. Chung Myung who noticed it quickly shook his head, yet all the kids still looked at him suspiciously.

At that moment, the great disciple standing on the podium shouted.

“During training why are your eyes looking elsewhere!?”

“So-sorry!”

“Look ahead kids!”

“Shit.”

“Ugh.”

Children made sick noises and took their stances back up, placing their swords into pose again. Seeing that Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

It was then that the great disciple looked at Chung Myung

“You?”

“Yes?”

“Why aren’t you doing it?”

“Because I don’t know?”

“…”

“…”

The great disciple rolled his eyes and nodded his head, focusing his attention back on the group of children.

“continue. Back!”

And the command fell.

Chung Myung looked up at the sky as he watched all this. The sky was blue.

Clear without a single cloud. It was like seeing the future of Mount Hua…nothing.

‘How can I change this?’

He had a deep and long future ahead, where he will have to travel an incredibly rough road. A path only exacerbated by the fact he is alone.

Such was also the future of Mount Hua.

No money. No people. The martial arts is a mess. Changing Mount Hua is more troubling than anything.

“Sigh…”

It was then that a sharp voice rang.

“Hey.”

“… huh?”

“New here?”

“…”

To instantly recognize a new member, how weak was the current sect?

“So?”

“I’ll see you later. Don’t you leave.”

Chun Myung lost his appetite for the second time.

“Okay. But let me ask you one thing.”

“Have you lost it? Don’t you understand what I am hinting at here?”

“Fine. Just answer me and I’ll do whatever you want.”

“What is it?”

“What else are you learning here besides this?”

“This?”

“Equilibrium of Six or something.”

“After learning this, it will be the Seven Sages Sword. After that we will graduate from the White Plum Blossom and learn the Lesser Qing Sword technique.”

“Qing Sword?”

“Yes. After that we will be able to learn the Taiyi Flummox Sword technique.”

“… Taiyi Flummox Sword technique?”

“Right”

“Taiyi Flummox!”

Chung Myung was shocked.

No.

It couldn’t be.

No way!

“Hey. One more question.”

“What?”

“What happened to the Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique?”

“… what is that?”

“The Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique! It’s a technique of Mount Hua!”

The child frowned as he responded.

“What is that? Mount Hua doesn’t have that sword technique.”

“… Huh?”

“It’s my first time hearing about it.”

“Ugh.”

It was strange.

“No technique called the Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword? And people need to learn this one?”

Chung Myung’s eyes were blooming.

-leader. This Taiyi Flummox Sword is too weak in power. At this point, I don’t think removing it entirely from our teachings would even cause any rift. What do you think?

-It is a sword technique that cannot be used. Let’s just let it go…

-Still, the ancestors left it behind for…

-Are we going to teach the kids a technique which they wouldn’t use and is a complete waste of their time?

-Hm… you’re right. Let’s throw it away.

‘Sahyung!’

These kids were learning that.

Mount Hua is bound to die if it continues like this. Looks like it would fall before he could even have the chance to rebuild it.

“Who is talking again!? You people! Come out here right now.”

“Ah, sit. I’ll see you later! I mean it!”

“…”

A huge vein sprang up on Chung Myung’s forehead.

Chapter 12: Collapsing was inevitable, you bastards (2)

“Dying is better! Dying is better!”

Chung Myung’s face as he returned to the dorms was completely rotten. Nothing was going right.

People said that even if a rich man failed, he’d live three years in luxury. Judging from the current situation, it seemed like 100 years was too far-fetched. There was no way the Mount Hua sect was any better than some third-rate sect.

‘No, even a third-rate sect would do better!’

This sect has no money, and the children are in poor condition. If that wasn’t bad enough, they are full of shitty philosophy that no one understands.

Every other place would be fine, just this! This!

And that too!

‘Where did you throw away the Twenty Four Plum Blossom Swords you bastards!?’

He could understand prioritizing one technique over another because of the difficulties of the sect, or teaching abilities of the remaining instructors.

But making a technique totally disappear is a whole different thing.

Even given the fact that the previous generation was annihilated! They had left money and history behind.

“Uhhhh!”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

“What the… where should I even start?”

The term ‘total chaos’ would be used in such cases.

“Sahyung, can I even save Mount Hua?”

When he lifted his head and looked up it seemed like that old man was smiling down.

-Save?

Chung Myung grabbed a handful of soil and threw it to the sky. And went back to his dorms.

“Ow, my waist!” He said as his back hurt.

Just because they talked a little during the training that man made them train extra. If only Chung Myung was as strong as his previous life, he could go back and forth from the summit to the base of Mount Hua with minimal effort!

‘I need to hurry.’

Chung Myung lost his appetite.

At first he was going to try and figure out how Mount Hua worked and think about fixing it, but the more he found out the more troubled he felt.

It would have been easier if Chung Myung had passed onto the current time with his past body and mind.

However, right now, Chung Myung was nothing more than the youngest disciple, a beggar nonetheless, which meant the lowest level.

Could he change the position of Mount Hua?

“Sigh…” He could help let out a sigh while thinking.

Of course, he could take his time and slowly change it, however, the problem was that Chung Myung wasn’t the laid back kind. The more he saw the current Mount Hua, the more rushed he felt.

‘Even the Wudang sect must be developing at this moment.’

In general, martial arts focus on practice and repetition.

However, Chung Myung had a different idea.

The world is continuously evolving. No matter how many people in the past were geniuses, if they continue to study even the new generations will turn into geniuses. In the end they are bound to surpass the realm of those ancient geniuses.

In other words, it means that martial arts would eventually develop with the passage of time.

Just because they were Shaolin, if they didn’t constantly try to enhance their existing martials arts, that sect wouldn’t be so flourishing now. Over the years, numerous more people will come up and fill the gaps of martial arts.

Right, progress…

“Other people are making progress at this time, and these ones are forgetting what they have.”

How could he not be upset?

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

For now…

Gulp.

“…”

Chung Myung looked down at his stomach.

“Tch.”

Because he had been living as a beggar for so long, he couldn’t properly develop his body.

‘I couldn’t eat dinner.’

After all the others finished training, he wanted to eat, but Chung Myung was punished so he couldn’t eat.

In the past and now, there was nothing he hated more than fasting, things turned more difficult and annoying when he was hungry.

Chung Myung grabbed his stomach as he entered the dorms. First of all, he had to organize some things…

“Yah he is here.”

Upon entering, Chung Myung raised his eyes slightly towards those who appeared. Dozens of disciples of the 3rd great disciple were in the room.

“Yah, newbie!”

The gaze of powerless Chung Myung went towards them.

Seeing their faces, it didn’t look like they were waiting with any good intentions.

Chung Myung took a deep breath, opened his mouth, and said to Ah Gul.

“What?”

Ah Gul’s face heated up in an instant.

“This bastard must be crazy! Call me Jo Gul Sahyung!”

“Sahyung…?”

Chung Myung looked at the ceiling. Looking at the old ceiling and wooden buildings he wanted to cry.

Ah. Now he was in a position where he had to refer to these little jerks as Sahyungs.

But what could he do? He should have done something earlier if he didn’t like that.

“Yes, yes, Jo Gul Sahyung. What is it?”

“If you are new you should report.”

“Huh?”

“Don’t worry it won’t be too bad. You look too weak, I am afraid that you’d die if I hit you a bit hard.”

Laughter erupted from the sides. Everyone seemed to enjoy the joke.

Well, he understood the situation.

This is the essence of what dorm lives are. Through these types of situations, the bonds between the people grow stronger, and they learn and connect with each other.

Almost everyone giggled.

‘Nevertheless, it doesn’t feel nice.’

He wasn’t dissatisfied with this, but what he hated was the attitude of these people. Acting like it was their own gang.

Of course, when Chung Myung first entered Mount Hua it was similar, but at least they didn’t act like these kids.

Huh? What was this old man saying?

Well he was over eighty years old.

“Report.”

Chung Myung nodded his head. First of all, it will be important to handle these people.

His stomach hurts but what could he do? He was here to save Mount Hua.

“Right. What can I do?”

“Great Sahyung.” Jo Gul said as he smiled.

“Yes.”

“Great Sahyung?”

Chung Myung turned his head and saw the one called Great Sahyung. One span bigger than the Jo Gul, and definitely older.

This guy was another person under the third great disciple.

“I’ll do this.”

“Yes.”

In Chung Myung’s head, the current order of people flashed in an instant.

‘That guy is higher, but Jo Gul takes the lead.’

It was the same in his time. Although Sahyung would always help clear the problems for the sect leader.

If so, then this situation…

“Take it off.”

“… Huh?” Chung Myung’s head tilted.

Did he hear something wrong?

“I said take it off.”

“…”

Chung Myung looked around. He looked at the kids inside. Everyone was looking at him as if they were having fun.

Chung Myung’s gaze turned to Jo Gul.

“… I feel like I misunderstood… no, I think so.”

Chung Myung tried to smile.

‘Don’t get mad’

‘Let’s not get angry’

If he got angry, he would be the same as these kids.

“T-take it off?”

“Yes.”

Jo Gul smirked.

“That is how we normally get to know each other. Come on, take it off, dance, and get beaten because that is how we show our love to the new ones.”

Jo Gul’s lips turned into a smile.

“Now.”

“Huh?”

“Ah, uh feel shy.”

His pronunciation wasn’t right.

Chung Myung, who coughed up then tried to speak.

“Then… Sasuk Un Geom?”

“He’ll be practicing for the evening. You better throw away the thought of him coming to help you. Right now, we’re the only ones here.”

“I see.”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“And even if he was here, you would be fine for today. But you’ll have to live here from now on, so do you really think you’d be able to escape?”

Right. This was where he will be living.

‘Thanks.’

His thinking had been a bit wrong until now.

“Then there are no other dorms here?”

“This bastard just keeps talking. I can’t hold back anymore. Let’s get right to it.”

Jo Gul jumped up from his seat and grabbed Chung Myung by the collar.

“Once you get the hang of it, you’ll respect me as the Sahyung I’m not doing this because I hate you. We’re using this to love and put you on the right path. Get it?”

“Sahyung.”

“What? Anything left to say?”

“Clench your teeth.”

“Huh?”

At that moment, Chung Myung’s fist hit Jo Gul’s lower jaw.

Bang!

With the sound of something exploding. Jo Gul’s body soared to the ceiling.

Crack!

And he broke through the old ceiling.

Crack!

Jo Gul’s body, which was nailed into the ceiling, shook.

Everything turned quiet.

The eyes of the other disciples went wide.

“…”

“…”

Chung Myung, took a glimpse at Jo Gul, then turned and walked towards the door.

“W-where are you goi…”

Clank!

Chung Myung raised the latch and locked the door and as he turned with a bright smile on his face.

“As long as a person lives…”

“…”

“They worry about this and that. And among them, I think about one thing the most. But…”

Crack! Crack!

Loosening his head, he continued.

“Thanks to you, my thinking has turned very simple. Right, I need to start with organizing my surroundings.”

Chung Myung raised his leg and stepped on the chair next to him and shattered it. Grabbing the broken leg of the chair, he smiled.

“Hehehehe.”

And he went up to one of them.

“I grew up growing in my own way, so would I have the manners to treat my seniors rightly?”

A small hope bloomed in their hearts, he had called them seniors.

Seniors…

“Since you are seniors, I will trouble you. Don’t scream out loud. Any screaming bastard will receive double the dose.”

Ah…

They were the seniors.

“Come on, get hit and done with it. Sahyung bastards!”

Chung Myung, as if possessed, attacked the disciples.

Chapter 13: Collapsing was inevitable, you bastards (3)

“Sahyung.”

“Yes, Sajae!”

“Do it harder.”

“Yes! I will do my best!

The strength in the hands which were massaging the shoulder increased.

“What’s your name?”

“It is Yoon Jong.”

“And you are the Great Sahyung?”

“Yes, that’s right!”

Chung Myung slightly turned his head, as Yoon Jong’s swollen face came into his view.

“Still, since you are the Great Sahyung, I will treat you well.”

“Thank you!”

“Keep pressing.”

“Yes!”

Yoon Jong returned to rubbing as Chung Myung turned his head back.

The other Sahyungs were all on the floor with their heads bowed to the ground.

“You all…”

When Chung Myung opened his mouth everyone flinched. It was a strange sight to see kids above his age trembling on the floor.

“… shouldn’t you be helping out in living a quiet life? Shouldn’t you? Sahyungs?”

“Yes!”

“We were short sighted!”

Chung Myung sighed at those words.

Who was Chung Myung?

He was one of the three great swordsmen, and was recognized to be of the highest level among the three except for Chun Ma!

Wouldn’t he be able to easily handle these people?

No matter how weak he had become, these people were little kids, and Chung Myung could easily handle 30 of these kids.

“Since this was your way of accepting me, I will let this go this time. But from now on, such things should happen in a humane way. There are things which can and cannot be done.”

Everyone groaned without answering.

‘Why am I like this?’ One of them thought.

‘It feels like a Sasuk is yelling at me.’

It didn’t feel like they were on the same level as Chung Myung, as if they weren’t his peers.

Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

‘I need to deal with them.’

The more he thought about it, the more ridiculous the situation felt.

“Attention.”

As soon the word rang out, the kids got up.

“No matter how bad Mount Hua’s current state is, the kids of the most disciplined Mount Hua shouldn’t be like this.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

“You need to get back to the sect’s initial state!”

“…”

The children exchanged glances.

‘I don’t get it, how did this worm crawl in!’

‘Who was the bastard who claimed that this kid was a loser?’

‘We’re ruined! Now we all have to live together.’

Now they were staying together in a dorm.

If only they could live with their masters, like the old tradition, they could have escaped from Chung Myung. But now they were all living in a single dorm. It was like a wild tiger was thrown into a cage of rabbits!

“Tch.”

Chung Myung opened his eyes.

“Remember!”

“Yes!”

“Now, who in here is the most aware about the situation of Mount Hua, hands up!”

No one said anything.

But all their gazes turned to one side.

“…”

Seeing the gazes of the others directed towards him, Jo Gul’s eyes widened.

“hand.”

“…”

“Raise your hand!”

Jo Gul’s hand moved upwards.

‘I’ll see you later you bastards!’

It’s been many years that they had been living together. How could they sell out their own? Did they have no conscience?

Jo Gul gritted his teeth and stepped forward.

With a stiff head he looked at Chung Myung.

“Sahyung Jo Gul.”

“… Yes.”

“Even if you are a Sahyung, aren’t you being too stiff with me?”

“N-Not at all.”

Jo Gul hurried and touched his neck.

“My neck felt too stiff so I couldn’t move it like usual.”

“….”

“….”

Chung clicked his tongue and got up.

“Follow me to this room.”

“… Yes.”

“The others can rest for today. We’ll do what we need to tomorrow.”

“Yes.”

“Sahyung follow me.”

As Chung Myung moved his hand, Jo Gul followed him like a cow being led to the slaughter house.

As soon as the two disappeared, the remaining disciples rushed to Yoon Jong.

“Great Sahyung! Are you fine?”

“Do I look fine?”

“… No.”

Yoon Jong caressed his swollen eyes. The sad thing was that his swollen eyes would be fine by tomorrow, so he couldn’t even complain.

‘If only Sasuk was in these dorms, he could have stopped it.’

With his pride he couldn’t go to the man and show him the wounds. And by tomorrow morning everyone would be healed with no traces of the abuse suffered today.

In other words…

‘He planned this beforehand and as he hit us.’

The more he thought about it the more terrifying the new kid became in his mind.

“Now what do we do?”

“Do what?”

“Should we attack him once he goes to bed?”

“… will you do it?” He retorted.

“…”

Everyone went silent at that question, the image of Chung Myung running wild like a tiger roamed in their minds.

‘No. we shouldn’t do that.’

‘We’ll die if it goes wrong.’

Yoon Jong shook his head. The image of Chung Myung made his mouth turn dry.

“But…”

Someone who was lost in thought asked.

“Why was Jo Gul taken away?”

“…”

“…”

“Sit comfortably.”

“… I will stand here.”

“Don’t worry and sit, I won’t hit you.”

“It wasn’t because of that.”

Jo Gul hesitated and opened his mouth.

“I can’t seem to bend my back after being hanged from the ceiling. So standing is fine.”

“…”

Chung Myung coughed.

“So.”

“Why did you call me…”

“Talk comfortably, Sahyung.”

“… Yes?”

“It is strange to see Sahyung talk so respectfully. So speak comfortably.”

“Yes.”

“Speaking comfortably?”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung gave up.

Well, as long as they live, one day the kid would open up.

“So why did you call me?”

“Ah. I have a few questions for you. First, I’d like you to answer in as much detail as you can.”

“Okay.”

Chung Myung opened his mouth.

“So, are the children here mostly from merchant families?”

“Yes.”

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung tapped his chin with his finger.

‘Merchants.’

In the past there were many children of merchants who wanted to enter Mount Hua. However, Mount Hua never accepted anyone from merchant families as disciples.

Was it because merchants were bad?

Of course not.

They could accept beggars into the sect, a merchant wasn’t a huge deal. The problem was that the children of merchants didn’t come to become disciples. They came only to learn the martial arts of Mount Hua.

In the case of descendants of Mount Hua they would come here with the intention of burning the teachings of Mount Hua into their bones. After initiation, training and receiving guidance, one of them would become the leader of Mount Hua and lead the sect.

However, those who enter from merchant families remain solely as disciples of the sect and learn only the martial arts, after which they return back to their families.

Even out in the world, they would be respected for being a disciple of Mount Hua, but it was nothing compared to those who stayed back. The disciples who sunk down the teaching of the sect into their lives were always of support, and they would protect Mount Hua.

‘Most of them leave…’

Which meant even the three great disciples who were teaching today, would eventually leave Mount Hua.

‘What is this situation?’

If the number of disciples decreased in Mount Hua, then its name and reputation would in turn decrease.

“But Sahyungs are here?”

“What do you mean?”

“Well, there should have been rumors going around, you should have known that Mount Hua isn’t in a good shape. Why come all the way here?”

“Ah, that…”

Jo Gul scratched his head.

“Actually, my father originally didn’t like the idea of sending me to Mount Hua. However, there weren’t many sects which would accept me. Although Mount Hua has collapsed, it is still one of the many sects in the world. The connections which come from this would give me great strength and freedom.”

“Hmm.”

According to Jo Gul the kids of the merchants who came in here were common. It wasn’t bad. Ultimately it was to make themselves be valued.

If they had money or talent, there was no way kids like Jo Gul would enter Mount Hua, they would have gone to other better sects.

‘Which means even the past disciples of Mount Hua don’t have money. Which means everyone around Mount Hua is in a mess too.’

His bones felt sore.

It reminded him of the old days, with his Sahyung holding up a book and tying up his hair. At that time, he was obsessed with making money and Sahyung was a mastermind in gathering it. Thinking back, Mount Hua could have come out of the situation if they had those ledgers that Sahyung had.

People need money to live. Just because one is a martial artist doesn’t mean they could lived on eating dew.

“Hm. Then…”

“Yes.”

“Are you planning to go back to your family after learning martial arts?”

“Normally yes.”

“Is that why this place looks so sleazy?”

There was no way anyone could love this place when they came here to fulfill a temporary goal.

“I get it. Go away now.”

“Then…”

“Ah, and.”

“Yes?”

“When does the morning training start?”

“It starts at 7.”

“Tell everyone to prepare by 5 and gather them in the hall.”

“Yes?”

“5 am.”

“… Yes.”

“And have the Sahyungs know what I said.”

“To prepare for tomorrow morning and get them together?”

“What, don’t like it?”

“Why would I not like it? Trust me.”

“Yeah. I like that attitude.”

“…”

After a while, Jo Gul left the room with a subtle expression, but sadly his room was right next to Chung Myung!

Hearing the footsteps leaving, Chung Myung laid flat on the bed.

‘Even a thousand miles start with a single step.’

He didn’t remember who said that in the first place.

But the road Chung Myung had to take was a thousand miles with all kinds of messed up roads!

‘Still, it will start with one step.’

And that one step would be with these kids.

Chapter 14: Collapsing was inevitable, you bastards (4)

The next day at dawn

Woong!

Chung Myung stretched his body.

Dantian.

His dantian, which used to be small and feeble, was now in a period of noticeable growth. The energy which accumulated had grown to be clearly recognizable.

Woong!

With every breath he took, Chung Myung could feel his energy resonate and purify his body.

Bright and clean energy.

Even Chung Myung was taken aback; despite having lived for decades, he had never witnessed such a clean and transparent energy before. His dantian was now accumulating this energy. Although the size was limited and wielding enormous strength would be difficult, with time, more power would accrue, and he would be able to reach new heights he had never reached before.

“…How long will it take?”

After cultivating, Chung Myung’s face distorted.

In order to reach his former peak and even exceed it, he needed time. Mount Hua was facing its doom now; would it wait for him to gain power?

Chung Myung pushed aside and suppressed his anger as he analyzed the situation.

‘Let’s get this straight.’

The problems in Mount Hua are innumerable. If he had to pick one out, Chung Myung wouldn’t be able to decide which was most important. However, there were three things he knew.

“No money, no martial arts, and no talent.”

So, what is wrong?

Any one of these issues was bad enough, but when they were all piled on top of each other, he could feel his stomach curling in on itself.

What was the biggest problem?

‘Young talent.’

Chung Myung simplified it.

Money could be earned, and he has a wealth of martial arts knowledge that could be taught naturally.

‘So, where do we get talented youth?’

Talent wasn’t something Chung Myung could influence.

He couldn’t just go out and kidnap talented kids to save Mount Hua. And finding out who was talented and who wasn’t simply by looking at them was impossible.

If so, he would have to go for the children of prestigious families.

‘So, I need to make use of them.’

Chung Myung clenched his fists.

What would change even if he blamed himself? He had no choice but to make the best of what was available to him.

It was clear that the people here weren’t very good, and there was a shortage of teaching staff. But, if the people here are deficient, they must be taught, and if they are broken, they must be fixed.

“Of course, I never took in a disciple.”

Old memories came to his mind.

When he was old enough to accept a disciple, Sahyung asked.

-Chung Myung.

-Yes, Sahyung?

-Now is the time to take in a disciple. How do you plan on teaching your disciples?

-Do you even need to ask?

-What do you mean?

-Spare the rod, spoil the child. Should they make a mistake, they will be beaten. Even dogs will walk on their hind legs if trained to do so. I assume humans can’t be too different, right?

-…let’s talk again later.

After that, Sahyung never brought up him taking on a disciple again.

“I never expected to receive so many disciples at once.”

Chung Myung’s lips curled into a smile. If anyone had seen that, they would surely think of it as a wicked smile.

“… I am sleepy.”

“Why do we need to gather at dawn?”

“Great Sahyung. Isn’t this too much?”

Yoon Jong closed his eyes.

‘Just be quiet, will you! You bastards.’

The rules of Mount Hua are relatively strict, but the children weren’t yet forced to give up on worldly affairs. They are children from families that control their own regions, even if they are not from famous families. As a result, they can’t stand being inconvenienced and aren’t used to being patient.

Even though it had only been half a day since they had been beaten, they still let loose with their complaints.

Yoon Jong lifted his head and looked at Jo Gul. At least Jo Gul kept silent in this situation.

Well.

It wasn’t that the others didn’t understand the situation. Despite complaining, everyone did come over here as requested.

Yoon Jong stared at the dorms.

‘Where did that monster even come from?’

Chung Myung wielded a broken chair leg with a demon-like appearance, defeating over 30 kids in an instant.

Brrrrr

When he thought about it, chills passed through his body.

“… but who the hell is he?”

They were words that expressed everyone’s feelings.

“As if I could know.”

“There were more than 30 people. Is it even possible for the seniors to control a crowd like that?”

I don’t know

But what was certain was that even the great disciples wouldn’t be able to imitate what that monster did.

“That kid only joined us yesterday. He must have learned martial arts somewhere else already, right?”

“haaa, anyway. Does it make sense to be here without even having anything to eat?”

Everyone was confused.

Even Yoon Jong, who was older and lived longest in Mount Hua, couldn’t figure it out, but he knew that something was up.

“Is he going to hit us again?”

“…”

It wasn’t known who said it, but everyone went stiff upon hearing those words.

“Is that possible?”

“It could be that he wants us to remember last night’s embarrassment…”

“What if we fail?”

“…”

Worry spread among the crowd. Everyone turned their heads. Jo Gul, who was standing there, spoke.

“If you all don’t want to be hit again, then just stay quiet and follow what he says.”

“… sahyung Jo Gul”

Jo Gul was known to have the best skills among the disciples, and even he was shaking.

‘Crazy!’

What?

Get hit again?

Get hit and end up stuck in the ceiling? Jo Gul was confident in his skills. But even he couldn’t compare to this monster despite being called a genius in Mount Hua.

In the end, martial arts are something people learn. Even without sufficient teaching and good martial arts, he was confident that he could even stand toe to toe with the genius disciples of the most prestigious sects.

However, that confidence flew away after just one punch struck his jaw.

“Then, why were we asked to gather here?”

The disciples tilted their heads, looking at the strange tools ahead of them.

“Right, how do you use these?”

Long wooden rods and then a sturdy pouch, large enough to fit a person’s head, filled with something and…

“Why prepare pebbles and sand pouches?”

“Do I look like I know?”

As everyone was groaning, the door swung open.

“…”

All the clamoring mouths went silent at once and looked at the person. Chung Myung slowly walked out.

But on his face, the annoyance was evident.

‘Why does he look bothered!’

‘If you are so bothered, don’t gather us like this!’

Chung Myung stopped and then looked around as he asked.

“Is everyone here?”

“Yes!”

“Keep quiet or the Sasuks will wake up.”

“…”

Crack crack

Chung Myung stretched his neck and then said.

“Well, we are going to be living together for the foreseeable future. Though I don’t know how it will turn out, maybe we would even end up spending the rest of our lives together.”

‘I will go home even if that means death!’

‘I’ll make it down. I’ll make it down the mountain at any cost!’

Even those who had decided to live and die with the Mount Hua sect had second thoughts upon hearing those words.

“But in my opinion…”

Chung Myung smiled.

“You people are too weak.”

“…”

“…” The most insulting and disgraceful word to those who walk the path of martial arts is “weak.” Even if they were only here from merchant families to build a name for themselves, it was painful to take such an insult to their faces.

“Shit.”

The problem was that they couldn’t object to it.

These were the words of a person who beat 30 people at once without being hit. No one could deny it.

“Well, even I agree that martial arts aren’t everything in life. But, you all chose to study and learn as Mount Hua sect members. Then, you should aim to be as strong as you can be, right?”

“…”

“So, starting from today, you will practice with me every morning. It’s nice, right?”

As if that would be nice!

Someone raised their hand when they saw Chung Myung’s shameless attitude.

“What is it?”

“Do we have to do this?”

Chung Myung looked at the one who asked the question with a bitter gaze and then turned to Yoon Jong.

Yoon Jong who looked at Chung Myung flinched as he said.

“It’s…because not everyone was there at that time…”

“Ah, right.”

There were people who didn’t get hit.

Some didn’t participate in that bullying. Even if word of what happened had spread, not many would believe that and step back, right?

“You don’t want too then?”

“You seem like a newcomer, so why are you talking all this nonsense? No matter what, you should at least mind your manners.”

Chung Myung nodded at those words.

“Yes. A person must be polite. In that sense, those who have no intention of becoming strong or training. Raise your hand!”

If a hundred people gather, there will be at least one or two who don’t care, and as those one or two hands come up, others will start to raise.

Roughly a dozen or so.

“Right, right. Martial arts aren’t everything. Come on, let’s go inside.”

“Can we go?”

“Sure.”

The faces of Jo Gul and Yoon Jong went pale at those words.

‘You idiots! ‘Let’s go’ is different from ‘you go’!’

‘They are walking into a hell of their own making!’

The children, unaware of their situation, smiled brightly and entered the dorms. And Chung Myung followed them with a smile.

Tak!

The door was neatly closed behind them.

“…”

No one dared to open their mouths as they looked at the dorm.

Contrarily, there were no screams either.

But.

‘That’s…’

Yoon Jong looked at the dorm. The entire building was swaying slightly, and it was obvious what was happening inside.

A short time passed.

Kiik!

The door opened.

And from the inside, the kids sprinted out with their might as if they had seen a ghost. And then came over and took their positions.

“Tsk.”

Chung Myung, who came out, began to speak once more.

“Who among you doesn’t want to practice?”

“None!”

“Be quiet! Others will wake up.”

“None.”

“Good.”

Chung Myung clapped once and began to move.

“I, as an instructor, like to make people strong. The future of Mount Hua is bright! I will do everything I can to make you stronger.”

“…”

“Now, let’s begin.”

Seeing the sun rising in the distance. Yoon Jong tightly closed his eyes.

The future of Mount Hua was bright, but their future seemed bleak.

Chapter 15: Collapsing was inevitable, you bastards (5)

“Hm?”

Frowning at the bright light peering through the window, Un Geom reluctantly woke himself from bed.

‘These brats.’

The laws of Mount Hua were strict. In the past, when the students would share their teacher’s residence, the disciple was bound to rise earlier and wake up their teacher then prepare breakfast for him.

Although, the times had changed, and such doctrines had fallen from standards. Nonetheless, it was customary for a disciple to come, wake them, and greet them.

But today, no one came.

“Haaaa. These kids.”

Let them go for a while, and they turn lazy.

Un Geom frowned as he got up.

If any of the disciples were awake, they should have come to wake him up. That means that all the kids inside the White Plum Blossom Dorms were still asleep. No, just because they didn’t come to wake him up doesn’t mean that they must be sleeping.

‘Come to think of it.’

He remembered a new child joining the dormitory yesterday.

“Are those brats doing it again…”

He already knew that these young disciples of his would put new recruits through some form of hazing and that they were hellbent on seeing it through. As a teacher, he felt that he should put an end to it, but Un Geom was conflicted as he also believed it helped them bond together.

Jo Gul might take it too far but, knowing that Yoon Jong was there, he was confident that no problems would arise.

However, the fact that no one came over to greet and wake him meant that things had gone sour yesterday.

Un Geom furrowed his brows as he quickly changed his clothes. Putting on his robe and sword at the waist, he went out.

‘First, I’ll have to check.’

Determined, he took long strides towards the White Plum Blossom Boarding house.

Thinking that he would have to wake the kids with a huge scare, it happened the moment he turned the corner.

“Go…”

‘Out?’

Un Geom, who was about to yell, took a deep breath and choked back his words. His eyes widened at what he saw.

‘W-what is this?’

He rubbed his eyes in disbelief at the strange sight unfolding before him.

‘What? Am I in hell?’

Such a strange thought briefly flashed through his mind before he came back to his senses.

This is Mount Hua! The scene unfolding in front of him was happening in Mount Hua. But he

couldn’t understand why this was happening.

Had he gone delirious, or was he looking at something wrong?

Un Geom, who found himself rubbing his eyes once more to clear his sight, looked at what was happening again. However, nothing changed.

“_Uh…”_

A despairing chorus echoed within his ears as Un Geom stifled back a groan, unsure of how to react.

“Ugh!”

“Ah… I’m going to die. Ugh!”

“Mother…take me home.”

Un Geom stared blankly at the kids who were moaning pitifully.

“…”

Were these the same young disciples he knew?

Although their ignorance would sometimes cause anger, and their wickedness would lead to disappointment, the children he knew were still innocent kids. He always felt warmth from them.

But from the kids right now in front of him, there was no warmth of life.

‘Who are these ragged kids?’

Were these the kids he knew? No matter what he thought, these kids looked like worn-out beggars.

Un Geom peered around.

“Kuaa.”

“I am done… I am really going to die.”

Un Geom looked at the faces of the kids who were sprawled across the area.

‘Are these my disciples?’

A little rough…no, their condition was horrible, but those lying around in a beggar-like state were indeed his disciples.

‘What have they done?’

Why were the kids who were so soft yesterday in such a dire condition?

Wooden swords and strange pouches lay scattered around the ragged children.

Un Geom knew what he had to do. There was a limit to what his mind could guess, and what’s more, there were more than a hundred mouths here that could answer his questions.

“What the hell has happened here?”

As soon as he asked, the kids, who were lying on the floor groaning, looked at him.

The eyes of the half-dead disciples came to life!

“Sasuk!”

“Lord Sasuk!”

“Oh, Heavenly Lord!”

They all were speaking strangely, but it was clear that these kids were welcoming him warmly. They were even shedding tears.

It was unusual for him, whose mission was keeping the youth controlled, to see them greet him with such enthusiasm. No, it wasn’t uncommon, but this was his first time it seemed so genuine and heartfelt.

“Cough! Sasuk!”

“Why are you here so late! Why!”

“I missed Sasuk so much!”

What were they saying?

Strangely, every corner of his heart was proud looking at these kids who were always ignorant, welcoming him so fiercely. An unknown emotion flooded in.

But Un Geom soon shook his head and collected his thoughts.

‘N-no.’

It wasn’t the time for him to be impressed like this. Upon examining the youth before him, it seemed like they had fought some fierce battle; they were battered in dirt and sweat. Un Geom’s heart ached as he saw their pitifully trembling limbs and desired the truth of the situation.

“Just what happened here?”

The children, who looked like they were about to cry, hesitated and didn’t say anything when the question came—just a glance to the back.

‘Are they concerned about speaking up?’

Un Geom’s gaze followed their line of sight. There was another kid who was working hard.

“Jo Gul?”

“…No. The other one.”

“Other?”

From Jo Gul, he looked even further back.

“H-he is?”

Un Geom’s eyes seemed to widen beyond their limits at what he saw.

‘The new kid?’

What was his name? Chung Myung? What is he doing?

Un Geom tilted his head. Chung Myung was doing something bizarre. He had a wooden rod on

his shoulder with several large pouches hanging from either side.

“What is in those pouches?”

“Those are dirt bags.”

“… why dirt bags?”

He asked despite knowing why.

Weights.

Among the unrivalled ancestors, there were people who would do this.

“Gasp!”

Un Geom, who was watching, could tell that the kid’s body was getting stronger.

Despite trembling as if he would collapse at any moment, he stands up, shaking until he regains balance, and squats again.

Tuk! Tuk!

Beads of sweat poured down his chin. His whole body was drenched in sweat.

‘Will he die like this?’

Un Geom worried about his condition as he watched the child’s face, which turned a blazing red with veins popping and his expression twisted like a devil freshly escaped from hell.

There was no word more fitting than “difficult” to describe this kid, Chung Myung, as he groaned and continued to work out despite the apparent pressure he felt.

‘You’ll die like that, you brat!’

Un Geom wasn’t a generous man. In fact, he firmly believed the more rigorous the training, the better the results. Like a blacksmith hammers a sword to remove impurities, diamonds can only emerge from coal under pressure. This mindset allows him to push his disciples and strengthen their will alongside their bodies.

However, even he would say that the training of Chung Myung was harsh beyond the limits.

‘Wait, then the reason why these kids are here…?’

Was it because they were training together?

“S-sasuk! Save me!”

“We will die this way!”

The children’s bodies were drenched in sweat. The clothes they had on were soaked through and dripping with water. It gave Un Geom goosebumps to think that this was all sweat.

‘Then, they weren’t sleeping?’

Did that mean the kids were training since dawn?

“…when did you begin training?”

“Since five.”

Have they been doing this for over an hour?

“… why?”

A simple question, yet no one answered it.

‘We’ll die if we tell you.’

Everyone present was making a desperate face.

‘No way?’

No, it couldn’t be. As if that could happen.

Does that even make sense?

The kids there were the disciples of Mount Hua. Even if the sect wasn’t what it used to be, they still practiced martial arts. Among them, some kids have been here for more than five years.

Did that mean the young disciples were suffering here like this because they couldn’t handle the little new kid?

‘W-wait.’

Jo Gul was known for his outstanding skills among the children, yet even he was on the ground struggling to catch his breath.

‘What about Yoon Jong?’

He quickly scanned the area looking for Yoon Jong.

“Oh my…”

Yoon Jong was on the floor.

‘Why is he like that?’

Jo Gul was fine, but Yoon Jong looked as though his soul had escaped his body. Yoon Jong was gasping for air with his face on the ground and hips slightly raised, and tears could be seen forming in the corners of his eyes as he struggled on the ground.

“That…”

Un Geom opened his mouth and shut it again.

‘No, training is good…but.’

Wasn’t it clear what happened? The kids must have woken up early to do strength training.

Although Mount Hua is a sect that focuses on speed and finesse, basic strength training is also taught. All martial arts begin with the body as a foundation.

‘But what the hell does it mean that only one hour of training made everyone like this?’

Un Geom wiped the cold sweat from his brow.

When he glanced back, the kids were all looking at him with dazzling eyes—all with the hope that this man would solve the situation.

‘Don’t look at me with those eyes.’

It was seriously embarrassing.

“Kuah.”

Un Geom coughed as he changed his mind and looked at Chung Myung. First, he had to figure out what was happening. He would determine how to react once he knew the situation.

“Bring that kid.”

At that moment, Un Geom had firmly imprinted the name Chung Myung into his mind.

Un Geom had no idea that this would be the most important name he would learn in this life.

Chapter 16: Mount Hua is like this because of ME? (1)

“”Phew!“

Un Geom’s eyes began to gleam as he stared in a daze at the blue sky.

‘Certainly, he seemed like a normal kid at first, right?’

But this one was by no means ordinary.

‘Will he be fine?’

Chung Myung’s thick uniform was thoroughly drenched, and as the sweat poured from his body, it could be seen dripping through his clothes. With a face flushed red with blood, it seemed as if his head would burst at any moment. He struggled even to stand steady as his legs were trembling, and he could be seen biting tightly against his lip in order to keep moving.

“W-would you like to sit?”

Un Geom, who firmly regards courtesy and manners as integral to life, unwittingly suggested to

the child.

He couldn’t help it. It didn’t make sense to make Chung Myung stand after the training he went through. Looking at Chung Myung’s current condition evoked a similar feeling as seeing a young puppy left alone in the pouring rain. Pitiful.

“Ah, it is fine. Rather, I’d prefer a little water….”

“Someone get water! Now!”

“Yes!”

One of the kids, who was watching on the side, rushed to get water.

“Right. That—…”

However, Un Geom quickly fell silent.

‘What should I ask?’

He called for him to come here, but he didn’t know where to start. It was his first time being in such an absurd situation.

“What is going on here?”

He asked the most obvious question.

Chung Myung, who received the question, glanced around and opened his mouth calmly.

“It’s nothing much.”

“…What?”

“It’s just that, from today on, we all decided to exercise together in the mornings. But since it was our first time, we may have overdone it a bit. It must be because everyone was so motivated.”

‘Motivated?’

Un Geom looked at the kids behind Chung Myung. They were waving their hands desperately yet keeping their mouths sealed tightly.

However, their hands fell swiftly, and they froze in place when Chung Myung slightly turned his head towards them.

‘What sort of act is this?’

It was absurd. It was unclear how it came to this but, one thing was certain, all the disciples were afraid of this new child.

Un Geom was no fool. He had already dealt with kids and trained young disciples for ten years. He can often understand how a situation has developed simply by observing the kids.

No, it would be stranger if he hadn’t noticed what was happening, even without his experience.

‘The disciples of Mount Hua….’

Are they afraid of a newcomer?

Un Geom’s head slightly tilted sideways in confusion.

‘No. No.’

Come to think of it, the skills of these children were by no means weak. Most kids of the same age could only hang their heads low compared to Mount Hua’s disciples.

Even if it was rotting, they were still disciples of the once-great Mount Hua.

It wasn’t that his disciples were weak; it was just that this new child was odd.

“Did you say morning exercise?”

“Yes.”

“You.”

Un Geom spoke firmly.

“White Plum Blossom Boarding House has its own rules. Who told you to reduce your bedtime and practice as you please?”

Chung Myung’s expression remained unchanged as he spoke as if it wasn’t a concern.

“Then I won’t do it.”

“… huh?”

“I thought that training would be helpful. But you said no, so I won’t do it.”

“…”

Uh-what was that?

Un Geom was perplexed. This reaction was unexpected.

“Y-You thought that training would be helpful?”

“Yes.”

“Why did you think that?”

Chung Myung thought that this question was weird.

“You think it won’t help?”

“…”

“…”

An awkward air passed between them.

‘Ugh.’

Un Geom groaned to himself. He understood what this kid was saying, but Chung Myung spoke first.

“I felt that it would be enough to learn martial arts from Sasuk, but the disciples must also show effort in our own way. The essence of martial arts comes from the body, so I believed this strength training could improve our overall results. “

That was true.

The theory was correct.

“Your words are right.”

Un Geom readily acknowledged that.

“However, can you say that being forced to train under threat of coercion is correct?”

“Coercion?”

Chung Myung glanced back as he continued.

“Ahhh, Sasuk. How could I ever force my Sahyungs? When I said I was going to train, they said they also wanted to join in and followed me.

What nonsense.

A shameless lie!

But if he wanted him to speak the truth, Un Geom would have to ask, ‘Didn’t they only join in with you out of fear?’

But…

‘I can’t ask that.’

It would crush the pride of his disciples.

Yesterday, the disciples couldn’t manage one new youngster and had to be hauled out early in the morning to train in fear. Un Geom decided not to touch that sensitive topic.

And wouldn’t this situation turn Chung Myung, the youngest, into a terrifying villain who abused his own Sahyungs?

That would also hurt his disciples if mentioned carelessly.

“Th—”

Just as Un Geom was about to say something, Chung Myung spoke.

“Give me one month. I won’t let it affect our regular training, and in one month I will deliver you good results.”

‘Oh?’

Although they were discussing training, his hidden intention was slightly different.

One month.

He asked Sasuk to ignore this situation for a month and make his judgment after seeing the result.

‘Look at this kid!’

It didn’t seem like the words of a child, rather, the words of a strong man full of confidence.

“One month may be acceptable. But this training doesn’t seem that simple, can the kids really

endure it?“

“The Sahyungs all practiced because they wanted to and no one complained about it being hard.”

Chung Myung spoke brazenly as he glanced at his Sahyungs, none of which dared to open their mouths to refute him. Since no one spoke up, they must be okay with it.

‘Wh-where did this kid come from?’

While Un Geom thought, Chung Myung turned his head and asked.

“Isn’t that right, Sahyungs?”

“…ye-yes, it is.”

“We will work hard. Very hard.”

“…We worked hard today too.”

Chung Myung turned back.

“Without a strong will to grow, how could we possibly expect good results from our efforts?”

The children’s faces behind him were shocked and full of exhaustion.

Un Geom was speechless as the kids were utterly unable to speak out.

Despite only one day passing, Chung Myung had completely seized control of the disciples. Furthermore, he’s asking to allow this to be ignored for one month to show Un Geom the results of his control.

‘Come on.’

The more he listened, the more absurd it felt. Where did this little monster come from?

But…

‘It isn’t really a bad thing.’

The White Plum Blossom Boarding House had a significant issue when it came to securing training time. Mount Hua was understaffed.

And Un Geom couldn’t handle it alone. At least ten instructors were needed. But now, there were just three people who could train the kids.

As a result, they couldn’t spare much time to teach any of the disciples one-on-one. Most of the time was spent keeping the group organized, so their growth had begun to stagnate. It was evident that it would be a great help if this kid could relieve some of his burdens.

“I’ll ask you one more thing.”

“Yes.”

“It won’t be easy for you either; why would you choose to train so early in the morning?”

Chung Myung titled his head.

“I don’t understand what you mean, Sasuk.”

“Hmm?”

There was no way that this kid suddenly couldn’t understand.

“To enter Mount Hua means learning the sword, but simply joining the sect doesn’t necessarily mean we will become stronger. To become stronger, diligently training and striving for higher goals is the duty of any disciple.”

“That is right.”

“Of course, we can become stronger by following Sasuk’s teaching. But if we can put in our own effort as well the process can accelerate. It’s only natural that some sleep must be sacrificed if it means working harder to achieve our goals.”

“… right.”

It was that. There is no particular reason, only a passion for training.

‘Sect leader said we would no longer accept new students, I wondered what sort of child would receive an exception. Perhaps, a new wind is beginning to blow on Mount Hua.’

Wouldn’t it be quite worth it to bring this kid up?

His talent hasn’t been confirmed yet, but he should be able to achieve great things even without it with such motivation. Even if he’s unable to become a master, his attitude could have a good influence on the other children.

“…. You seem to be having a hard time with your training.”

“It’s because it’s my first day.”

“Still, it seems difficult.”

“The more we do, the better the results.”

Un Geom’s lips trembled as he struggled to stifle a smile.

‘This is it.’

Doesn’t this training perfectly match his own theory? It might be fine to push the others to their limits if such a kid leads them. After all, in the sect’s old days, the children would often form hierarchies not restricted solely by age.

“And, what is important when dealing with Sahyungs?”

“Be polite. Show respect and follow their words.”

He means to maintain this hierarchy while showing proper respect to his elders without despising or looking down on others.

Un Geom looked around and nodded. Unable to understand what was happening, the kids were all worried.

“Kuah.”

Un Geom coughed as he averted their gaze and opened his mouth.

“It’s quite touching that you all were ‘voluntarily’ training from dawn till now.”

“Sasuk!’

“Master!”

Shouts of confusion and shock, but Un Geom ignored it all and continued.

“If you continue to train like this in the future, you will achieve great results. This child seems to know much about training, so I will allow you to continue. Try your best.”

‘We are screwed.’

‘Wow, he is abandoning us.’

‘Look at him avoiding our gaze!’

The young kids were in a state of despair.

“Then, make sure you have your breakfast before it gets late and come out in time for the morning session.”

Un Geom slowly turned and then suddenly stopped.

“Ah, that’s right!”

Still, they couldn’t believe that this man would really throw them away so easily…

“It’ll interfere with your training, so you no longer have to come and wake me in the morning. Training comes first after all. Okay.”

Un Geom grinned and turned away.

The disciples wanted to reach their hands out to catch him, but he vanished from sight before they could even move.

“…”

Crack.

At that moment, a faint crackling sound.

It was Chung Myung, cracking his knuckles; he turned to them with a smile.

It was a smile, but the veins on his forehead were bulging, making it clear how he felt beneath his grin.

“Sasuk, help me, please?”

“…”

“It’s not like I said I was going to kill you, now my dear Sahyungs how about we have a chat in the Boarding House before having our meal?”

“…”

“Move it!”

“…Yes.”

It was at this moment that many young hopes and dreams disappeared from Mount Hua.

Chapter 17: Mount Hua is like this because of ME? (2)

“Are you serious?”

“Yes. Sahyung.”

Un Am’s face began to distort; Un Geom titled his head at the unexpected reaction.

“You didn’t know?”

“How could I have known?”

“…Huh. I thought that the sect leader brought that child in with some purpose. I guess he didn’t.”

“We can barely afford to make it through each day in our current situation. We can’t spare additional expenses trying to recruit hidden talents; he’s a tenacious child who sought us out himself.

“And he was taken in by the sect leader….”

Un Geom stopped.

This child was accepted by the sect leader, who said he wouldn’t take in any more disciples. So, he thought that there must have been some story behind it. But, the wind bringing change to Mount Hua wasn’t intentional?

It seemed that Un Am didn’t know anything more.

“Is there some secret that only the sect leader knows?”

“No. That kid really came here on his own.”

“How curious.”

Un Am said.

‘The more I think about it, the more bizarre this is.’

A mysterious boy traveled alone from afar, claiming to want to be a disciple of Mount Hua, and within a day, he’d taken hold and was enacting some sort of plot.

‘Perhaps, I’m just overthinking.’

He wondered if this kid was a spy sent by another sect to hasten their ruination, but it felt unnecessary.

First, Mount Hua was already in a sorry state, on the verge of collapse. Second, even if such a plan existed, sending a child too young to develop the necessary skills wouldn’t make sense.

And if a child with such talent existed, the sect would do everything they could to nurture and guide them rather than sending them to rot away here.

“If that is the case, wouldn’t it be better to keep an eye on him?”

“Let’s leave him be.”

“But Sahyung.”

“You didn’t stop him because you believed he could meet your expectations. Right?”

Instead of answering, Un Geom lowered his head.

“I am well aware of your hard work. It’s only natural for you to lead the disciples, but even you can’t accomplish everything on your own.”

“No. Sahyung I just…”

“It’s alright.”

Un Am laughed softly.

“It is difficult for everyone. I’m not sure what he’s thinking, but if you believe it will benefit Mount Hua, there’s no reason to stop him.”

Un Geom raised his head and looked at Un Am.

“I am not sure. That kid…”

“Un Geom.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

“That child is now a disciple of Mount Hua”

Un Geom’s eyes lightly shook.

“At times, we may be biased toward a child who comes first. However, even if he came later, all children who come to Mount Hua must be cared for as our disciples. “

“… I was shortsighted.”

Un Geom bowed his head.

“Even if he crosses the line, it won’t be too late to stop it then.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

Un Geom stood up.

“I’ll take my leave.”

“Sure.”

Un Am poured himself a cup of tea as Un Geom walked away.

‘What a strange boy.’

Indeed, an unusual child has arrived in the sect.

He’s a kid that didn’t bother trying to hide his presence despite bringing about a drastic change. Whether these changes would be a blessing or a curse was unknown.

Just one thing.

‘Change is necessary.’

What Mount Hua needed now was a new wind. Floating in the open sea without wind will leave you lost and starving. Even if the destination is unknown, you must set sail. Whether the final stop is paradise or a desolate island, it was better than dying, unmoving, in the open sea.

Un Am brought the teacup to his lips.

He hoped that Chung Myung could be the wind that moved Mount Hua

Of course, whether he can keep calm when the wind turns into a typhoon remains to be seen.

“I think I am going to die.”

“… I am already dead.”

A chorus of pained wails echoed from all around. Now, of course, those who were speaking on the verge of death were Mount Hua’s third-class disciples.

‘What fresh hell is this? A new type of torture?’

They knew it was an exercise to build muscle, but it’s not like Mount Hua neglected strength training. A solid body is the foundation of all martial arts, and even the Shaolin sect would have its own rigorous training regimen.

‘But this is unreasonable.’

Yoon Jong lowered his head and looked at the table.

Stir-fried vegetables were served as a side dish, but his hands were shaking so much that he couldn’t accurately put them in his mouth and spilled food all over the table.

“Ugh…I can’t even eat properly.”

“We have swordsmanship training in the afternoon. Will I be able to swing my sword with my hands shaking like this? If it was a real sword, wouldn’t it fly out of my hand and pierce someone’s ass? “

“…thankfully, I don’t think I have enough strength in my arms to swing with that much power.”

“Are you really thankful for that?”

Yoon Jong sighed.

‘Say it to his face. To his face.’

If they want to complain, shouldn’t they do it to his face? What good does it do to talk behind his back like this?

“There is nothing I can do.”

“Great Sahyung!”

Groans emerged from the crowd. However, Yoon Jong just silently picked up the stir-fried vegetables.

What could be done about it now that Un Geom has taken the same side as Chung Myung?

“Sahyung! In such situations, it doesn’t matter if it’s Sahyung or not….”

“But shouldn’t Great Sahyung’s opinion hold some weight?”

Yoon Jong sighed and was about to speak when a sharp voice came.

“How pathetic, what a rotten conversation.”

The crowd of third-class disciples had their eyes drawn in unison to the one who spoke.

“Jo Gul?”

There was a moment of silence before Jo Gul, who was quietly eating in the corner, began to speak in a sharp tone.

“Do you think Great Sahyung is your errand boy? Chung Myung isn’t hiding from you, if you have something to say, you can go say it to his face yourself.”

“… No, we were….”

“If you can’t speak up in person, just be quiet and eat. If you don’t eat, you won’t be able to survive in the afternoon.”

No one could open their mouths to argue after hearing what Jo Gul had to say.

Yoon Jong’s eyes met with Jo Gul’s gaze.

‘He is acting strange.’

If this were the usual Jo Gul, he would be the loudest to complain about Chung Myung. After all, he was the strongest and most vocal among the third-class disciples.

It became difficult for others to open their mouths and disagree when even Jo Gul took Chung Myung’s side.

Tak!

Jo Gul put down his chopsticks and approached Yoon Jong.

“Great Sahyung.”

“Hm?”

“Can I see you for a moment?”

“… sure.”

Yoon Jong put down his chopsticks and stood up.

The remaining disciples tilted their heads as they watched them leave.

“Are we looking at something the wrong way?”

Yoon Jong spoke first once they arrived in a deserted area.

“You look pretty pissed off.”

Jo Gul lifted his hand and rubbed his face.

“Is that how I look?”

“Your face is quite easy to read.”

“That’s the first time I’ve heard that.”

Jo Gul laughed.

“Even after all that training, you can laugh like that?”

“…. Sahyung.”

“Huh?”

“What do you think of Mount Hua?”

Yoon Jong went silent at the question. It was a sensitive subject that needed careful consideration.

“It is a difficult question.”

“I was originally planning on going back to my hometown after this. But don’t you plan on staying here?”

“Yes.”

Yoon Jong nodded quietly.

He had already decided to stay here. The other third-class disciples had yet to make their choice, but he would become an official disciple of Mount Hua and live or die with the sect.

“Do you believe that Mount Hua has any future left?”

“Mind your tongue, that isn’t something you can say so recklessly.”

“I couldn’t believe there was any hope left.”

“…”

It’s not something that should be said, yet Yoon Jong couldn’t condemn Jo Gul. He had often had similar thoughts in the past.

“Do you mean to say you’ve changed your mind?”

“… a little bit.”

“It’s changed?”

“I was forced into this training, but it made me realize. I’d never done any training that pushed me to my absolute limits until recently.”

That is true.

Yoon Jong nodded his head without realizing it. He had never done this kind of training. He always thought he was trying his hardest but never pushed himself to the limit where his body trembled like now.

“But that guy didn’t seem tired at all, even though he did twice what we did.”

Twice what we did? Along with doing double the repetitions as everyone else, Chung Myung also used more dirt bags. The intensity was on a completely different level from the other kids. Yoon Jong had checked the weights himself and couldn’t believe his eyes when he saw Chung Myung using a weight heavier than his own body.

He’s strong. He’s not just strong, but he’s younger than us as well. I don’t believe he was born powerful, so he must have grown this strong through his own efforts, right?

“You’re right.”

“Sahyung. I thought it would be impossible for me to become strong in Mount Hua. I thought I would stagnate at a mediocre level and leave; I never even thought of becoming a master known throughout the world.

“Jo Gul.”

“Listen to the end, Sahyung.”

“…”

Jo Gul gulped and continued.

“But, looking at him, I realized I was wrong. I mean, is there anyone our age who can even compare with him?”

I don’t think so.

There never will be.

Despite being the eldest, Yoon Jong wasn’t the best among third-class disciples, even still he was confident in his skills. He was sure that even if he had to face a disciple from one of the great sects, he would still be able to corner them.

But that monster flipped Yoon Jong upside down with one finger and knocked Jo Gul, who was stronger, into the ceiling.

How could another monster like him exist?

“It doesn’t matter which martial arts you learn; what’s important is how you learn. I thought it was just an empty phrase that sounded good on the ears. Seeing him, though, I realized they were honest words. Sahyung, I want to do my best.

“… I feel the same.”

Jo Gul nodded his head.

“So, Sahyung please. This may be an opportunity for our generation to experience a massive change. Even if he is a little sarcastic and arrogant, let’s follow him for now.”

Yoon Jong looked at Jo Gul.

Jo Gul had excellent skills; he had the ability to grasp the flow of things around him due to his experiences down in the world outside. If such a person became a merchant, he was bound to become successful. If such a person was speaking like this…

“Let’s do it.”

“Sahyung!”

“You are right. As of right now, nothing matters. I am someone who decided to stay in Mount Hua till the end. I will do anything I can to help Mount Hua.”

At Yoon Jong’s words, Jo Gul nodded his head.

“It’s funny though, all of this is because of the youngest just who joined us yesterday.”

“He may be the youngest, but he’s far from normal.”

“hehe, that’s true.”

The two smiled lightly and turned around; their talk was done. No matter how child-like they were, they seemed wise.

“Gul.”

“Yes, Sahyung?”

“Can we really become strong?”

“One thing is certain.”

“Hm?”

“If we can’t become strong, then we can always train harder.”

“… such comforting words.”

The two returned after this brief exchange, and until the very end, they were unaware that they were being watched.

Chapter 18: Mount Hua is like this because of ME? (3)

“For now, I have two good ones.”

Hidden in a nearby tree, Chung Myung had spied on their conversation. He was lying down comfortably with a rice ball next to him.

‘Kuak! I never used to be this merciful.’

If he entered the dining hall now, the Sahyungs wouldn’t be able to eat. He should at least let them have a proper meal; isn’t that the most humane thing to do?

Chung Myung patted his stomach and sighed.

‘I caused a bigger mess than I intended.’

Initially, he planned to lay low, but those kids came and plucked the nose hair from a sleeping tiger, so he had no other options.

What more can be done? Some things can be tolerated, but there are lines that cannot be crossed.

“There’s no changing the past.”

Thankfully, Un Geom is easy to communicate with. He perfectly understood what Chung Myung was trying to say when they spoke. Thanks to that, things were a bit easier than he thought.

Of course, he had prepared countermeasures if Un Geom didn’t understand, but that would have been more troublesome.

‘He’s smarter than I thought.’

Smart.

“… smart?”

Certainly, Un Geom understood Chung Myung clearly. However, as a young disciple of Mount Hua, looking down on his senior only to re-evaluate him as smart seemed disrespectful. But that was still a compliment, right?

“Ugh. This is so complicated.”

It seemed like it would take more time to get everything organized. His position within Mount Hua still wasn’t clearly defined yet.

But…

“Those two are definitely smart.”

Chun Myung’s eyes followed Yoon Jong and Jo Gul from a distance as they entered the dining hall.

When so many people gather, there will always be a few who stand out. In Chung Myung’s eyes, these two could be the core of the third-class disciples.

“I’ve got a good idea.”

Aren’t they quite unique? Typically, they would be on the verge of death if they were pushed that far. Complaints would pour unceasingly as they agonized over the pain. But, not these two; they desired more. Chung Myung found that quite admirable.

Especially Jo Gul.

Despite being beaten so thoroughly by someone younger than himself, he held no grudges. What’s more, it even motivated him to work harder and gave him confidence that he could grow stronger by following Chung Myung. If Chung Myung had any money left, he’d certainly gift it to Jo Gul.

“If I raise him well, he will be of great use.”

Chung Myung smirked and bit the rice ball.

Discovering talent was important, but the main priority now was Chung Myung.

‘First and foremost, body strengthening.’

The foundation was laid. There was still a long way to go, but it can be said that the most dangerous section has been passed. So now he can learn martial arts in earnest.

So, what did he need the most?

A perfect body.

Having returned to a younger body with all his past knowledge, can’t he get stronger through cultivation?

He could. However, a theory is a theory, and reality is reality. No matter how much martial arts knowledge he holds, if his body is too weak to perform, then he’ll be unable to reach his full potential.

He cannot do internal energy training with his mind alone. Only through blood, sweat, and tears will your body adapt.

For that, what’s most needed is to develop strong muscles.

Isn’t the sword of Mount Hua swift and dazzling?

Mount Hua’s sword technique requires you to swing fiercely with the strength of a hundred arms within one. The sword is beautiful, not the body. If the body is weak and unable to endure the technique, then the sword will never be dazzling.

To make plum blossoms bloom, the roots must be strong. The root of martial arts is the body.

‘I can’t just see what I want to see.’

The people are drawn to the gorgeous sword arts of Mount Hua. Thanks to that, they don’t see that there are people out there who would swing their swords to kill them too.

-Ahh, damn it! Why is this so complicated? Can’t I just stab him?

Why do I have to swing three times when I could just stab him in the face? I am going to break my wrist!

Like a swan that gracefully swims on the water, yet, below the surface, the swan’s legs flap desperately. The sword should be graceful like the swan, while the body, like the swan’s legs, is the engine that drives it forward.

So, you train and train again.

Even if you only digest a quarter of the training, after three years, they will have forged the strongest bodies and been reborn.

By then, Mount Hua might not be the world’s most gorgeous, but they would become a sect that can take down Shaolin.

Chung Myung smiled and stood up.

‘The problem isn’t the kids; it is the seniors.’

The kids will follow and get the hang of it, but he can’t treat the seniors in the same manner.

When he thought of Un Geom, he sighed.

‘He isn’t that bad.’

You could feel how hard Un Geom worked from the pressure emitted by his body.

It isn’t easy by any means for a person with no proper teacher to rise to this level. If he can receive the right instruction before it’s too late, he will be a good swordsman.

‘But how do I give it to him?’

Chung Myung scratched his head.

This was annoying.

It would be nice if he could just say it, but that would cause disaster. He didn’t have the confidence to deal with it. So, he thought of ways to naturally hand this information over…

“Kuak….”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

Since he wasn’t used to using his head and making plans, finding answers was hard.

“Should I return for now?”

To find the solution, he had to know the full situation.

He must know what techniques are being practiced and if the sect’s martial arts are being transferred properly through each generation.

Jo Gul gulped as he looked at Chung Myung sitting cross-legged.

‘Maybe I was wrong.’

Get stronger? Train?

That all sounds good, and he liked it.

But to do that, he would have to live with this guy.

‘Can I handle this?’

The more he let his thoughts run free, the more it felt like something was wrong.

“So…”

“Yes!”

“There’s no need to be tense, Sahyung,”

“… huh?”

“Is that everything?”

“Yes.”

“You can just speak casually.”

“…yep.”

Chung Myung frowned looking at Jo Gul writhing uncomfortably.

“This is really all that you have?”

“It is.”

“Really, you can rela—forget it, do as you please.”

Once he gets more comfortable around him, Jo Gul could naturally change how he speaks.

Chung Myung grabbed his head and looked at the paper.

“So, these are all the martial arts being taught?

Jo Gul nodded his head.

“Haaa, I am going crazy.”

“…”

Chung Myung moved a little as he stretched his body.

‘What is he doing?’

He suddenly called Jo Gul over and had him write a list of all the martial arts taught here. Once he received the list, Chung Myung seemed to lose his mind.

“This is all?”

He kept reciting this same line again and again like a parrot.

Sasuk had previously taught him that you need to make sacrifices to become strong. But it seemed like this kid even threw away his sanity.

“Sahyung.”

“Yes?”

“Isn’t there anything other than this? Is there possibly a restriction on what Sahyung can learn?”

“We aren’t allowed to read the techniques but just seeing them is fine. That’s all.”

“… ugh.”

Chung Myung looked at the paper again.

He had guessed it to some extent when he heard that the sect no longer had their sword techniques and replaced them with a worthless one. But this is too serious.

“No, what good would these do?”

Not a single thing on this list would help them. Were these old people deliberately trying to ruin Mount Hua?

“So, you are saying that now, the Taiyi Flummox Sword is being taught?”

“You know that already.”

“… ugh.”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

‘This is more serious than I thought.’

Having people around was indeed more important than martial arts books. But is that all? What good are people if they don’t know how to use their weapons when the enemies come? Even if they held swords, these people would be beaten while their enemies used tree branches.

Taiyi Flummox sword didn’t meet Chung Myung’s standards.

‘If only we had the Seven Sages Sword.’

Mount Hua wouldn’t be like this. The more he thought, the more troubled he felt.

Chung Myung tried to calm his raging mind when Jo Gul suddenly spoke.

“From what I hear…”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung didn’t even ask but he spoke on his own accord.

“When the Demonic Cult attacked, the west building was set on fire.”

“A fire in the west building, no, rather, the Demonic Cult invaded?”

What did the Demonic Cult attack Mount Hua for? Wasn’t their Heavenly Demon dead?

Jo gul asked him.

“Do you know of the Plum Blossom Swordsman?”

“I know.”

He knew very well. Because no one knows him as well as himself.

“Sasuk said that the Plum Blossom Swordsman helped kill the Heavenly Demon.”

“… helped?”

He beheaded that bastard! Not helped.

Chung Myung’s face brightened a little as his disciples knew about him.

“That’s what was said.”

“What? The Plum Blossom Swordsman killed that demon!”

“Huh? Who said that?”

“What do you mean who…”

Uh?

Chung Myung tilted his head.

‘Wa—wait.’

“It is impossible to say, because everyone on that mountain had died at that time. No one knows who killed the Heavenly Demon.”

“…”

Right. They all died. Chung Myung was the last one before he finally severed the Heavenly Demon’s head.

So, no one saw… yeah, no one knew….

Chung Myung understood.

‘No, then…’

For the honor of Mount Hua, he gave up his life to defeat Heavenly Demon; yet no one knows it?

What was this disgusting situation?

“Anyway, at that time, the Heavenly Demon fell, and the remaining demonic cult people went crazy and tried to push for vengeance. Despite taking a lot of damage, they climbed up and set fire to Mount Hua.”

“…”

Cold sweat began to flow down Chung Myung’s body.

However, Jo Gul didn’t notice and continued calmly.

“Even if we don’t know what happened. There seemed to be a strong grudge against Mount Hua.”

“Uh… Hm, that…”

Jo Gul may not know, but Chung Myung did.

“Haaaa.”

To sum it up.

Mount Hua was smashed after that.

‘Because of me?’

Yes?

All because of him?

“Hahahaha”

“Why are you laughing all of a sudden?”

“Hehehehehehe!”

‘Oh, my life!’

“Hahaha. Hahaha.”

Chapter 19: Mount Hua is like this because of ME? (4)

Now, he had a rough idea of the situation.

The alliance which climbed the Hundred-Thousand Mountain was utterly annihilated. However, the Hundred-Thousand mountain is the home of the Demon Sect. It wouldn’t be surprising if some of them survived the war.

Those Demon Sect survivors must have witnessed Chung Myung kill the Heavenly Demon.

“Ugh! Damn!”

Chung Myung threw away the paper in his hand.

All the people who should be recognized were dead, and not a single person he knew survived. Meanwhile, his enemies survived and came for revenge.

‘What the hell is this!?’

Jo Gul felt a chill and stepped back.

“Why are you suddenly angry…?”

“Kuaak.”

Chung Myung rubbed his face.

‘I need to calm down.’

It wasn’t something he should be angry about in front of Jo Gul.

“So, those bastards stormed in and wiped-out Mount Hua?”

“I don’t think the damage was that great. They also spent a lot of energy getting here since they came through a difficult path. Quite a few of the buildings burned down, and many of our martial arts were lost in the process.”

It was understandable.

No matter how poorly this place was maintained, it wouldn’t have fallen to this degree without something like that happening. Martial arts can still be learned without a teacher to guide you; even if you must walk through hell to succeed, it’s a hundred times better than nothing.

On the other hand, if even the martial arts were lost, it explains how Mount Hua could collapse so quickly.

“I can explain….”

It was already explained, but why is it so heartbreaking?

“Okay. I get it.”

Chung Myung stood up from his seat.

“Where are you going?”

“… a walk. I need to clear my head for a moment.”

“Sasuk will come to check on us soon. We may end up being scolded.”

“Right, right. Thank you.”

Jo Gul, looking at Chung Myung as he left, shook his head, unable to understand.

‘He is one strange guy.’

“This is crazy.”

A fire was raging within his body.

Contrasting wildly against his facial expression, which exuded a chill that seemed to freeze your soul.

He risked his life, sacrificed himself to kill that demon, and those below him destroyed Mount Hua?

What the hell are these results? Is there no retribution in this world!?

His mind began to ache as his thoughts continued unrestrained.

“Sigh…”

Now, he couldn’t even get angry at the pathetic state of the elders in the sect. After all, it was clear why this happened.

“I don’t get it; what kind of loyalty did those people have!”

If their Heavenly Demon was killed, they should have just lived cowering in seclusion. Instead, they rushed straight for revenge.

If the journey to Mount Hua hadn’t been so arduous, it might have been destroyed all the way to the roots.

“Should I call us fortunate, or were we unlucky?”

Only a few things were damaged.

“Sigh.”

Still, sitting alone on the rooftop and watching the sun fall as the night approached helped to soothe his mind.

‘That’s just how the world is.’

The real reason Chung Myung was distraught wasn’t because of what occurred to Mount Hua. He was angry because his successors had to pay the price for his actions.

If Chung Myung had lived after killing the Heavenly Demon, he could have stopped it. But he died, and the young disciples, who knew nothing, had to face the hellish aftermath. As a result, Mount Hua ended up like this.

“Tch. What can I do?”

No one could criticize Chung Myung.

It could be said that a disaster befell the sect because he killed the Heavenly Demon, but if he didn’t kill him, then the entire sect would have ceased to exist.

Chung Myung didn’t have a choice. Even if asked to relive that moment, Chung Myung would still not hesitate to sever the Heavenly Demon’s head.

But…

“It feels unpleasant.”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

“Well, the past is the past. If it’s broken, then we can just rebuild it!”

Whether or not he’s responsible, doesn’t his goal remain the same? He must revive Mount Hua and regain the sect’s former glory.

“Worrying won’t change anything. What matters is getting results!”

It will be enough if he can make Mount Hua stronger than before. It might be impossible for others, but not for Chung Myung.

It will be a little difficult, though.

No, there will be a lot of difficulties.

It may be even more challenging than cutting off the head of the Heavenly Demon.

‘But I’m in a hurry.’

Impatience is poison to a task. There’s a difference between moving quickly and trying to rush. Contemplate the job thoroughly and advance without rushing.

“Alright, let’s take it easy.”

First, let’s figure out everything that’s been lost. The best way would be to simply ask someone.

“Where is the sect leader! Come on out!”

Right. Sect leader is the right—

…Who said that?

Chung Myung’s eyes went wide as he turned to see where the voice had come from.

‘The main gate?’

There was a loud noise coming from the main gate.

‘At this hour?’

The sun was setting. Why would visitors come at this time?

“Sect leader, get out here!”

Ah, right, the Sect leader…

“Sect Leader?”

Chung Myung touched his ears with a blank expression.

“What did I just hear?”

Demanding the sect leader?

‘What crazy bastard is saying that!’

Such insolence! How dare they assail the gates of Mount Hua and demand the Sect leader! In the past, such actions would be inconceivable without enormous repercussions.

Before he’d even finished speaking, a teeth-shattering fist would have met the man’s face.

These people outside didn’t seem to be wary of Mount Hua’s power at all!

Thud! Thud

A violent banging on the gate. At the same time, the gate, which was barely in shape, began to rattle and fracture.

‘No, no, no!’

Whoosh!

The front gate finally gave in and made a strange sound as it moved. The gate collapsed to the ground and shattered as dust and debris scattered the area.

Chung Myung stared blankly at the scene, clearly dazed.

‘They broke the gate?’

The gate of Mount Hua?

What was happening?

“Let’s go in!”

Dozens of people smashed the gate and sprinted inside. All of whom ran towards the residence of the Sect Leader. It didn’t seem like it was their first time doing it.

The other sect elders stormed out from their residences at the noise.

“W–wait!”

“You can’t do this!”

But the opponents were relentless.

“Get out of my way right now! Won’t you move?”

“Tell him to come out! Sect leader!”

“Huh! Did you just touch my body?”

Chung Myung’s eyes rolled back in shock.

‘What was up with this situation?’

The intruders broke in as if they owned the place.

But the elders seemed to be struggling to block them; whenever one stepped forward, the elders would step back as if they’d been assaulted.

It wasn’t like they had strength.

No! Chung Myung could feel that the elders were stronger.

“Th—”

Before Chung Myung could understand the situation, the people pushed in and arrived in front of the residence.

“Sect leader! Come out right now!”

“Don’t even think of running away!”

“I know you are in there! I am not going to let you have your way today! Come out!”

Chung Myung was feeling dizzy.

‘What am I seeing?’

Where is this place?

No matter how horrible the downfall was, Mount Hua wasn’t a place where such things could happen.

“Kuak!”

Chung Myung felt something hit his forehead as his anger began to boil over.

“What are you doing?”

“Eh?”

One of the elders holding back the violent men asked Chung Myung and rebuked him.

“Go inside right now! Why is a third-class disciple wandering around at this time!”

“… Uh.”

Chung Myung tried to think of an excuse.

Come to think of it, no one but him was here. Despite such a considerable commotion, not a single disciple was here.

‘Does this sort of thing happen often?’

It was human nature to stick your head out and spy when there was a commotion. Nevertheless, the fact that no one came meant that a code of conduct had already been established in this situation.

Chung Myung, who only joined recently, had no knowledge about this.

“What are you doing!?”

No, even so, it wasn’t him they should be concerned about but those violent people.

“Sect leader! Come out!”

“I am not going back like this today! Hiding is of no use! Come out!”

“Have you no shame!?”

The people didn’t stop shouting in front of the sect leader’s residence.

Chung Myung’s neck began to feel stiff.

It happened then

Kiiiik!

The door creaked open with a shrill sound. And Hyun Jong, the sect leader of Mount Hua, walked out.

When he came out, the members of Mount Hua bowed to him.

“What are you doing here at this late hour?”

‘Indeed.’

While Chung Myung was getting angry at their words, the sect leader responded in a noble manner befitting his status.

He felt proud seeing the man act this dignified despite not having anyone to guide him properly.

Every movement was refined, and his words carried strong yet stable energy, which felt good to the listener, making Chung Myung feel even more relaxed.

Truly…

“What nonsense are you asking!”

“Come down! Right now!”

“Why are you acting all calm!”

Right, he’s pretending to be calm…

No!

Hyun Jong’s face stiffened slightly as he sighed.

“I didn’t run, nor did I hide. Where would I go if I left Mount Hua? So, calm dow—”

“Quiet that mouth of yours!”

Chung Myung was enraged.

Even though he spoke to them respectfully, these crazy people didn’t even bother listening.

The strange thing was how despite that, the sect leader didn’t yell and seemed flustered instead.

What sin did he commit to act so meekly?

‘Uh?’

A particular word came to Chung Myung’s mind.

“Sect leader.”

A person, who seemed to represent this group, pointed his finger and shouted.

“We have waited long enough. We can’t wait any longer!”

“…”

The calmness disappeared from Hyun Jong’s face.

‘T-that…’

Was he serious!?

“When will you pay our money back! The payment date passed long ago! We can’t wait any longer!”

Chung Myung looked at Hyun Jong with blank eyes.

Hyun Jong’s virtuous appearance vanished as he opened his mouth with an awkward expression.

“If you can give me some more tim—”

Chung Myung grabbed the back of his neck and stared toward the sky.

‘Shit.’

There’s debt as well?

A collapsing sect is all that’s left, and even that is owed to debt collectors?

‘Really.’

Tears formed in Chung Myung’s eyes. His mind was feeling as overcast as the cloudy night sky above.

‘Really, this place is full of crazy people.’

Chapter 20: Mount Hua is like this because of ME? (5)

“We’ve given you time! How much longer are you planning to take!”

“A man can only be so shameless!”

“We have waited long enough!”

Hyun Jong’s face was a bit stiff.

“I know, but….”

At that moment, a man standing quietly in the back walked forward. As he stepped forward, everyone around fell silent and took a step back.

‘Is he the one in charge?’

Chung Myung’s eyes lit up as he looked at the person ahead.

The man had the typical appearance of a merchant. A slightly chubby face, dressed in fine clothes made of the most expensive silk adorned in elaborate patterns.

‘Looks like he has a lot of money.’

Chung Myung decided to listen as the man’s mouth opened to speak.

“Sect leader. Have you been well?”

“I didn’t think that pavilion owner Kong would come here in person.”

A soft smile crept onto the face of the man called Kong.

“I wish I could meet the sect leader under more favorable conditions. I truly didn’t want to climb Mount Hua, but I hope you understand there are far too many people urging me to do something.”

“And I apologize.”

Hyun Jong lowered his head slightly and bowed. Then, owner Kong opened his mouth with a different voice from before.

“But sect leader, you must also try to understand the feelings of others. The date of our contract has long since passed.”

“Hmm.”

The one called Kong tilted his shoulders back. In Chung Myung’s eyes, it was an arrogant gesture.

“We already know of Mount Hua’s difficult situation, and we’ve looked the other way on several occasions. Nevertheless, if you keep breaking your word like this, it will be difficult to overlook anymore.”

Hyun Jong couldn’t say anything.

Although he was trying to keep a peaceful face, Chung Myung noticed that the old man’s face was twitching subtly.

It was a natural reaction.

This man, the sect leader, looked after Mount Hua for years and now suffered from debtors because of what the past sect leader did.

“According to the contract, we could demand payment for breaking the contract right now.”

Owner Kong smiled and shook his head.

“We, too, have benefited from Mount Hua’s blessings for many years; therefore, we are hesitant to take such harsh actions.”

“Owner Kong!”

“We’ve already waited—”

“Uh-huh.”

The merchants around him protested, but the man silenced them with a cough.

“If we don’t know grace, we are nothing but animals. Don’t be blinded merely by the kindness you’ve shown them. It is thanks to Mount Hua’s graces and blessings that we can live so comfortably now. Don’t forget the work of your predecessors.”

“Hmm.”

“Right.”

As everyone understood, he smiled.

“So, we are going to give you a little more consideration. We will give you seven days from now. If you don’t repay the loan taken in seven days, then we’ll take the price as per the initial contract.”

“O-Owner Kong wait for a momen—”

“Sect leader.”

Owner Kong quietly shook his head.

“No more. We need the money. We’ve already been as lenient as possible. If the money isn’t ready in seven days, we will confiscate Mount Hua as promised.”

“Kuak!”

Owner Kong turned his head at the sound that came out of nowhere and looked at Chung Myung covering his mouth.

“We’ve shown something unsightly in front of a child.”

Owner Kong said.

“This is all for today. Sect leader. I hope that we can exchange pleasantries and smile together next time we meet. Until then, farewell.”

As the man moved to leave, the other merchants followed behind him. Hyun Jong quietly raised his head to watch them pass; as if he had just survived an encounter with a fierce predator, he let loose a small sigh.

“… sigh.“

Frustrated and weak, this sigh seemed to carry an immense burden.

“So…”

Chung Myung had his legs crossed and rested his chin on his hand.

“A merchant of Hua village?”

“Right.”

“Ugh.”

Chung Myung’s head was rattling back and forth as he kept thinking. Seeing that, the other kid moved back.

‘I don’t know if he’ll attack; it’s better to avoid it.’

The reason he was explaining this to Chung Myung was very simple.

After returning to the White Plum Blossom Boarding House with great anger, he called together all the kids from the shopping district who knew about Mount Hua’s condition. Finally, the one who answered his questions was this kid.

As a result, he explained Mount Hua’s state to Chung Myung.

“Hua village is the one right under Mount Hua, right?”

Jo Gul, who was listening in from the side, asked.

“Yes, Sahyung. I remember seeing it when I was peddling wares with my father.”

“The Mount Hua sect borrowed money from Hua village merchants?”

“I don’t think that’s….”

The kid scratched his head.

Although he was in Mount Hua, there was no way that third-class disciples would know about the sect’s finances. At best, they could guess what was happening.

“That man, Kong, is the owner of Tae Hua Pavilion in Hua village. It is the largest one in Hua village, and I heard that he is working on various businesses using it as a base. He is the most successful merchant in Hua village.”

“Hmm.”

“So, if Mount Hua needed to borrow money, he was the best person to borrow from….”

Crick crack!

“Huh!?”

Jo Gul turned his head away as the color in his face turned a grim pale.

Chung Myung kept cracking his neck like a broken wood doll.

“Sajae! Calm down! Sajae!”

“Tae—Tae Hua….”

“What’s wrong?”

Jo Gul felt terrified as he saw Chung Myung seemingly lose himself in shock.

Of course, they couldn’t understand the reason for Chung Myung’s strange behavior.

Step.

Chung Myung, suddenly erupting with vitality, jumped from his seat and stared into the eyes of the other kid.

“Eek!?”

He rushed to the door with lightning speed, grabbed the kid by the collar, and asked.

“Is it true that he is the owner of Tae Hua?”

“Y–yes.”

“So, the owner of Tae Hua loaned out money to Mount Hua and now he’s trying to confiscate this ruined place?”

“C–calm down!”

“Calm down? Are you telling me to calm down?”

That bastard! Does he have any idea what Chung Myung was feeling?

Chung Myung released his grip on the kid’s collar and then scratched his head wildly.

“What’s wrong with you, Sajae?”

Chung Myung couldn’t answer that question at all. The reason was simple.

There was no way to explain it.

Because!

‘Tae Hua is supposed to belong to Mount Hua!’

Being a warrior of Mount Hua doesn’t mean that all worldly obsessions would be forgotten and neglected. Any sect without money would be unable to last regardless of their fame. Sects like Mount Hua especially needed money to sustain their massive size.

In the first place, the swordsmen of a sect focused solely on their personal growth and getting stronger. For such people, whose only focus is martial arts, it can be challenging to make money and provide for their families.

It requires a massive sum of money to feed such people. Therefore, Mount Hua employed several businesses in Hua village to work for them. One of those operations was Tae Hua.

But now, a business that belonged to Mount Hua was lending money to Mount Hua and trying to confiscate the sect for debt?

He couldn’t understand it.

Right…if what he knew didn’t match up with what they were saying, then something must have gone wrong!

“… Sahyung Jo Gul.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung motionlessly called, and Jo Gul approached him with curiosity and confusion in his eyes.

Chung Myung whispered something which only Jo Gul could hear, and Jo Gul’s eyes opened wide and stared back at him in shock.

“That?”

“Can you get it for me?”

Jo Gul stuttered a bit.

“Ah, no, I can but—”

“Then go and bring it to me.”

“… really?”

“Did you think I was joking? Sahyung?”

“I–I’ll bring it.”

Jo Gul left the room with a nervous face.

‘What is he trying to do?’

Yoon Jong curiously watched the scene as he tilted his head; Jo Gul’s reaction was weird.

Before he could think too deeply, Jo Gul was already returning while carrying something.

With a subtle face, he delivered the item to Chung Myung.

‘Cloth?’

‘No, clothing? But why would he need something like that out of the blue?’

Chung Myung, who took the clothes Jo Gul gave to him, quickly tossed aside the robes he was currently wearing.

“Ah?”

He was fully dressed in black clothing, which held tightly to his body.

“W–what are you planning to do?”

“I should ask around.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung answered.

“If I ask the Sasuks, they wouldn’t give me a proper answer and will tell me that a kid has no business knowing such stuff.”

Obviously, because that’s the correct response!

“So, I will go and ask.”

“W–wait!”

A cold sweat gathered on Yoon Jong’s forehead as he began to understand where this situation was heading.

So far, all of Chung Myung’s antics were limited to Mount Hua. Therefore, although there were problems, it was possible to remedy any issues. If he headed down the mountain, though, what sort of problems could he cause?

‘H–he needs to be stopped.’

If he was lucky, he might find the information he wanted, but…

‘As if that would happen so smoothly!’

Considering Chung Myung’s brazen behavior, he would ask right away without considering who he is talking to. This could create an even bigger problem!

If he happens to cause an incident, then the aftermath of what he’s done would be uncontrollable.

If he couldn’t be stopped here, Yoon Jong would have failed in his duties. If the adults of the sect found out that Chung Myung caused an incident, they would hold Yoon Jong, the representative of the third-class disciples, responsible as well.

But how could he stop Chung Myung?

If he could be persuaded with words, then he would have already talked him out of it.

Yoon Jong, steeped in a cold sweat, opened his mouth.

“W–what are you going to do?”

“I am going to ask them directly.”

“And what if they don’t answer?”

“Would they not?”

Chung Myung titled his head.

“I guess that’s usually the case. Still, I am pretty sure they will give me an answer.”

As if, stop it, you crazy bastard!

Yoon Jong racked his brain trying to think of a solution as he desperately thought about things that would get him a beating if spoken aloud.

“You are a disciple, right?”

“Huh?”

“You are a disciple of Mount Hua!”

Yoon Jong didn’t know why, but he felt like Chung Myung had a strong sense of pride in being a disciple of Mount Hua, so he planned on using that.

“A disciple shouldn’t do such things! We won’t be different from undisciplined groups if you do it!”

Chung Myung nodded deeply in agreement.

“You are right. A disciple shouldn’t do it.”

Clearly, it seemed to work. Yoon Jong’s face lit up with a ray of hope.

“R–right!”

“But Sahyung! Listen up!”

“Huh?”

“There is a Buddhist saying! If you meet a buddha, kill him and if you meet an ancestor, kill him!”

“…!”

“So! Being a true disciple requires you to understand this!”

He draped the cloth around his face, masking his features, and then cried out proudly.

“Sometimes, you need to know when to break the law!”

What was this crazy guy even saying!

“I am going! To be a true warrior!”

“…”

Only then did Yoon Jong realize that stopping this man Chung Myung was impossible from the beginning.

Chapter 21: Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (1)

Hua-Um Village.

Settled beneath Mount Hua, it was one of the largest villages in Shaanxi.

In the past, when Mount Hua’s name echoed loudly throughout the world, the village was full of energy, and the harmonious relationship with the sect played a vital role in that. The peddlers continued to line up to visit Hua-Um village, and those who wanted to see Mount Hua arrived unceasingly.

Thanks to that, Hua-Um village never had a shortage of customers to buy their wares, and it made a name for itself by depending on Mount Hua.

But time makes fools of all men.

Mount Hua began to decline, and its name faded from memory; as such, the life in Hua-Um village began to bleed out. However, the Tae-Hua Pavilion, the main base, still held firm. And now, on the top floor of this esteemed location, dozens of merchants were gathered.

“Hahaha.”

Huge smiles broke out.

“Sect Leader seemed flustered. Did you see that face of his?”

“Very flustered. After all, we’ve finally issued an ultimatum.”

“Of course, it was too much! The coins they took alone was 100,000 nyang! Many sects would double over at such wealth; their operations should have increased at least two-fold! We extended our hands to help because of our ancestors’ relationships, but they should have at least had some conscience and paid it back!”

“Right. A man should have a sense of propriety.”

The owner of Tae Hua, Kong Mun-Yeon, nodded as he smiled.

“Even though I am a merchant here, I must admit that it was unpleasant having to issue such commands to a place with deep connections to my ancestors.”

“What do you mean, owner Kong! Owner Kong did as much as he could. In the first place, despite breaching the contract and missing the reimbursement date several times, you still offered them several extensions and opportunities to repay their debts.”

“Right. No one can blame you for that. We should be praising you for the mercy you showed.”

“I am glad to hear such support.”

Owner Kong leaned and drank from his glass. But inside, he was ridiculing those around him.

‘How comfortable.’

Well, thankfully, he could live such a simple life.

‘Mount Hua is full of potential.’

The true power of Mount Hua didn’t come from its present force. The most important thing about Mount Hua was the history it had.

When such a clan continued to exist for hundreds of years, there were people who would build relationships with it whether they wanted to or not. At least in Shaanxi, it was difficult to find people who had no connection with Mount Hua.

The current Mount Hua is but a speck compared to its former glory; even if it disappears, few people will so much as give a damn.

But the most important thing is what would happen next.

Once people realize that Mount Hua disappeared, more and more will want to find out ‘why’. If the cause is unjust and they can’t show adequate reasoning, then this Hua village could be destroyed instantly.

Most of those connected with Mount Hua were people of high status.

‘But it will be fine.’

Because his plan was a prolonged and effective one. Mount Hua has reached a simmering boil over time, like a duck whose flesh can be torn with mere chopsticks.

“But owner Kong.”

“Yes.”

“What do you plan on doing with Mount Hua?”

“Hm.”

Owner Kong smiled.

“Mount Hua is more meaningful than you might think. It may be old and fallen, but it’s a good deal.”

“I don’t get it.”

Such idiots.

Owner Kong’s expression was nearly distorted, but he succeeded in keeping an amicable appearance.

“Don’t underestimate the power that Mount Hua’s name holds. Even if it is used as a tourist destination, many people will want to visit.”

“But…”

Yu Jong-San, who sold silk, had a crumpled up expression as he spoke.

“How much does it cost to rebuild Mount Hua? Wouldn’t it be better to get something else?”

“We don’t need anything more.”

“Hmm.”

Owner Kong pursed his lips.

“You don’t have to worry much. I don’t wish to disclose it now, but there is certainly a place which will offer enough compensation for that location even if there’s nothing left of it.”

“You think so? For Mount Hua to be loved like—”

“It is the other way around.”

“Ah…”

Yu Jong-San nodded as if he understood.

A sect that would want to erase the presence of Mount Hua would buy it for a high price just to destroy it. And they could think of a couple sects already.

“So, don’t worry. We will get our money.”

“Kuahaha! As if I was worried. We always believed in you, Owner Kong.”

“Of course! We merchants always believed and followed you!”

Kong Mun-Yeon nodded with a smile.

But his heart held different thoughts.

‘I can’t handle doing business with these people anymore.’

This was a dying land. When Mount Hua rose to fame in the world, this place flourished, but there was nothing left anymore. Because of their deep connections to Mount Hua, they had stayed, now they were slowly decaying husks, soon to be empty shells of their former selves.

In the first place, Hua-Um village wasn’t the main attraction here, so not many people came anymore. Nevertheless, the only reason they were able to stay and live was because of the money they earned when Mount Hua flourished.

If Mount Hua vanished entirely, this village was as good as dead.

‘Before it is too late, I need to organize and leave.’

If he can try and get a lot of money by selling Mount Hua, he could move and establish himself elsewhere. To do that…

“Hmm?”

At that moment, Kong Mun-Yeon turned his head.

“Who is it?”

As soon as he shouted, the guards who were there ran out.

“Who is there?”

“Is someone there?”

Kon Mun-Yeon didn’t answer and waited for the guards to come back.

Eventually, the guards returned.

“No one was there.”

“…”

When Kong Mun-Yeon didn’t say anything, Yu Jong-San spoke with a smile.

“Owner Kong. Aren’t we on the top floor of the Tae Hua Pavilion? Who could even come here?”

“Right. And if there was someone, they would have been found. Where would they even hide up here?”

Kong Mun-Yeon nodded his head.

‘Was I being over cautious?’

It could be. He wouldn’t need to wait much more until his long-cherished wishes were going to come true.

“I seem to be tired. I want to enjoy it a little more, but I think it would be right to end my enjoyment here.”

Everyone agreed with those words and got up. However, once the nerves were raging, they would rarely subside easily.

It seemed like he needed rest.

“Uhhhh!”

Yu Jong-San staggered as he walked down the street.

“Feels so good!”

It looks like he had a bit too much alcohol for the night. And his excitement hadn’t stopped.

Why?

‘So much money is about to come my way!’

The money they could get from Mount Hua is immense. The interest on the loan given to them has been compounding for so long that the initial amount is minuscule in comparison.

If just that could be recovered, he would never have to work again and could rest and play around for the remainder of his life.

Kong was an unreliable person, but he was serious when it came to matters of money. Regardless of what he planned behind the scenes, getting paid was what mattered for Yu Jong-San.

“The moon is bright… What? There is no moon? Eh.”

Yu Jong-San smiled and looked around. Instead of walking in a wide street, he had drunkenly stumbled into a dreary and lonesome alley. It was creepy.

Haha.

He wasn’t thinking straight. If a robber came over now…

“You, wait there.”

“…”

Yu Jong-San closed and opened his eyes repeatedly.

Someone was blocking the dark alley. From the black clothes to the mask. Truly…

‘Like a robber.’

He was quite small for a robber, not too scary, but his intentions were clear. Still, do robbers usually commit robbery in those clothes? Wasn’t it too obvious?

‘The clothes are screaming that he is a robber.’

Yu Jong-sang smiled and opened his mouth.

“Am I being mugged?”

“I don’t care about money.”

The robber steps forward.

“If you answer my questions, I will send you away nicely.”

“Ho-oh?”

Yu Jong-San laughed.

“It isn’t that I don’t want to give you an answer, but I feel like it would be a bit difficult.”

With those words, he raised his head.

“You see, I have a lot of people with me. Because it isn’t safe to go around alone anymore.”

Swosh!

A group of men carrying swords appeared with a slight sound. They were guards secretly escorting the man.

“I’d love to answer your questions, but I don’t think doing so will make the merchants union happy.”

The robber just looked at the man. Yu Jong-San, who had sobered up, closed his mouth, and this time, one of his escorts spoke.

“What should I do? Kill him?”

“Uhm.”

Yu Jong-San stroked his beard.

“If he came here wearing those dark clothes, doesn’t that mean he came here with a purpose and not to rob me?”

“I believe so.”

“Then, we need to hear the purpose. Capture him for me so I can have him speak.”

“Yes!”

With that, the escorts rushed forward.

“Wait a moment!”

The robber showed his palm to stop them.

“Huh?”

“See, if possible, I would like to not cause a scene. So, if you just answer what I need to know, everything will end well. So…”

“How long are you going to listen to his shit? Bring him!”

“Yes!”

The escorts surrounded the robber in an instant.

‘Idiot.’

Seeing that, Yu Jong-San turned his head away as he was uncomfortable with seeing violent scenes.

They had a contract with a large sum of money involved. So, the escorts he was handed were more capable than average. This time, the robber was unfortunate…

Kwang!

Right.

Boom!

Oh my, that poor robber.

Kwak!

Yu Jong-San frowned. It seemed too violent for one man to be hit so much.

“Didn’t I tell you that he needs to speak?”

“Uh? Really?”

“Right. I’m sure… huh?”

Who answered that?

Yu Jong-San looked back.

“…”

His guard escorts were sprawled out before him, foaming from the mouth like crabs. The robber had clearly crushed them and was steadily approaching him now.

“Language is what separates men from mere animals, yet when given a chance to speak, you chose to prove yourself a beast.”

“…”

The robber wiggled his finger.

“Come here, come on now.”

“…”

Yu Jong-San silently approached the masked man as if possessed.

“Once again, if you answer well, nothing will happen. Understood?”

“Yes!”

The answer came immediately.

“Now then.”

“… huh?”

“If you had answered like this in the first place, I would have just left, but since you tried fighting me, you need to be punished, right?”

“Huh?”

“Don’t worry. I’ll make sure you’re able to speak.”

“…”

It was a dark day in Yu Jong-San’s life.

Chapter 22: Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (2)

“…cha… unnerchand…”

“Speak properly; you sound ridiculous.”

“… I… understand.”

“Hmm.”

The robber, Chung Myung, crossed his legs as he thought.

“So.”

“Yes”

“You say the money you lent to Mount Hua exceeded 100,000 nyang?”

“… yes.”

“Hundred thousand?”

“Yes.”

“Hundred thousaaaandd?”

Yu Jong-San wanted to cry.

‘That is what I am saying, you jerk!’

If someone has a complaint, it should be resolved through conversation. But this man was bullying and abusing others like this!

“Hey.”

“Yes!”

“Even with multiple businesses joined together, it doesn’t look like you could even afford 1000 nyang. Yet, you’re saying you lent 100,000 nyang to Mount Hua?”

“Ah, that…”

Yu Jong-San, who finally understood what Chung Myung was confused about, answered with a large smile.

“You see, that’s how interest rates work. If you lend money with a high-interest rate, the interest will continue to grow until the principal balance is repaid. Hehe, it grows quickly and before you even realize it turns into—”

Hit!

“Kuak!”

Yu Jong-San grabbed his head which was hit.

“Stop being proud of it, you ass.”

“Ugh.”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

‘Well, there is no point in blaming him.’

Perhaps this debt has been accumulating for ages.

‘Right.’

It is meaningless to come and borrow large sums of money now. The time Mount Hua needed money would have been when it was collapsing. They would have required money to stop people from leaving and upholding its name.

“By the way.”

“Yes.”

“Did you say you were the silk merchant of Hua-Um?”

“Yes.”

“When did you buy it?”

“Huh? What do you mean? Our family has owned that cloth shop for generations.”

“… owned?”

“Yes. As far as I know, it was my great-grandfather who made the store.”

Chung Myung smiled bitterly.

‘Is this possible?’

This cloth store was one of those initially owned by Mount Hua.

Then?

Were all the original businesses in Hua-Um successful?

‘Yes.’

It made sense. In the beginning, this village called Hua was full of paddy fields until Mount Hua was established.

As Mount Hua kept growing and visitors increased, the village changed, and Mount Hua would use its own money to develop the village and create businesses.

Businesses that flourished in Hua-Um were all under Mount Hua.

What now? This cloth store was inherited from his great-grandfather?

Considering his age, his great-grandfather would probably be around Chung Myung’s age from when he was here in the past. Even Chung Myung had memories of going to this particular store to get uniforms for other disciples.

‘Something smells fishy.’

“I need some answers.”

“… please ask anything.”

“Then, who owns the Mount Hua Tea Shop?”

“That is owner Yu.”

“And, it has also belonged to their family for several generations now?”

“From what I know, yes.”

“Of course, the top 5 businesses in Hua-Um are the same, right?”

“Yes. All of them too.”

Chung Myung smiled at it. No need to ask more; he knew what was happening.

Once Mount Hua went down, these people must have severed their connections, right?

“Oh, my.”

No matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t prevent a sour expression from creeping onto his face.

There were two reasons why Mount Hua didn’t run the businesses directly and handed it to agents they trusted instead.

The first was that no matter how esteemed Mount Hua’s reputation was, it was primarily a sect that led disciples down the path of martial arts. If it was known to be running silk, cloth, or tea shops, then there would surely be criticism over their priorities and methods.

Secondly

–Chung Myung. What Mount Hua wants isn’t to monopolize the wealth but for all of us to live well together. Aren’t the people of Hua-Um also people who belong to Mount Hua? If we all live well together, we all will be happy; what more could anyone want?

‘This is how humans are. Sahyung!’

There is only one reason why the forefathers and scriptures emphasize that people should learn to repay kindness.

It was because humans are beings who don’t inherently seek to repay kindness.

No, actually, he was glad they didn’t pay it back. Anyone would stab their benefactor in the back if the benefits were great enough.

The sect helped these people to make a living, but instead of repaying it, they took advantage of the calamity the sect was going through and took over the businesses.

And knowing what they did was wrong, they were living happily. Putting all the burden on Mount Hua.

“Ugh.”

Puck!

Chung Myung kicked Yu Jong-San with all his might making the man roll like a marble across the ground.

“Ugh!”

Chung Myung looked at him and sighed.

‘What am I to do with this one?’

There was a good chance that Yu Jong-San didn’t even know what he was doing. He really seemed to think that the cloth business was his family’s.

‘What should I do with this?’

Chung Myung felt troubled.

Any other time, he would simply beat the man black and blue, kick the life out of him and then go back as if nothing happened, but it wasn’t that simple now.

Mount Hua is a prestigious sect.

Even now, though the name has faded, the image of Mount Hua in his time remains unchanged for Chung Myung.

Maybe the Forces of Evil could assault people without reason, but prestigious sects must behave appropriately and defend their dignity.

The day he acts unrestrained would be the day Mount Hua fell.

“Even if it is twisted, it is disgustingly dirty!”

He could see what happened, but finding the solution was complex. He had to find a way to get the businesses back without intimidating them like a thug.

Easy to say, tough to do!

“ugh!”

Chung Myung scratched his head and glanced at the man.

“Hey. So…”

It was then.

“Stop!”

“Huh?”

Hearing the voice from behind, he turned his head.

“Huh? You are awake?”

One of Yu Jong-San’s guard escorts, whom he had blown away, seemed to have come to his senses and aimed his sword at Chung Myung.

He definitely walloped the man, but he had to be stronger than the others if he regained consciousness so quickly.

“You bastard!”

The guard sneered.

“Using a cowardly surprise attack!”

Surprise attack?

Him?

Chung Myung looked at the escort with a puzzled expression.

“Hey, you ran towards me first.”

“You coward!”

“Uh, fine, fine, let’s go with what you said.”

He didn’t want to talk much with this man.

“Who are you?”

“Huh?”

“Given your skills, you certainly aren’t normal; reveal your identity.”

The absurdity of the situation grew.

If he planned on revealing his identity, would he be wearing a mask?

“What will you do when you know my identity?”

“I need to know who is going to die by my sword.”

“…what, I was the one that knocked you out just a moment ago.”

He should have just pretended to be dead; why would he bother getting up and speaking like an idiot? Now he’s earned himself another beating.

‘Did all the kids get stupid after my reincarnation?’

“If I was on alert, that wouldn’t have happened, I’ve been a guard for quite a while, and I can’t remain still after receiving such humiliation. Do you know who I am?”

“I am Jung Bin. Even if you don’t know much, you must have heard of my name.”

“Ah, sorry. I am not as knowledgeable as you think.”

“…”

Jung Bin opened his eyes wide.

Although he was here to escort for the sake of money, his name was widespread in Shaanxi. But this mysterious figure hadn’t heard of his name?

“You cheeky bastard.”

Jung Bin grabbed his sword and aimed it at Chung Myung.

“I am giving you a chance to name yourself before you die.”

“Haa…”

Chung Myung sighed deeply.

Why were there so many idiots in the current world?

“Hey, but I don’t think your current actions really fit the job description of an escort, do they? No matter how you look at it, even I seem more like a guard than you.”

“I am a good escort.”

Ah, right, sorry.

A hot-headed brainless person.

“Be prepared!”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue as Jung Bin unleashed his sword and rushed towards him.

His physique was clearly more incredible than Chung Myung’s. Their strength, speed, and internal energy were incomparable. By general standards, Jung Bin is so much stronger that even comparing them would be an insult to him.

So, was Chung Myung weaker?

As if!

Strength, speed, and internal energy.

While you may judge ordinary people by these standards, it’s not enough to apply to Chung Myung.

After all, doesn’t he have a lifetime’s wealth of experience wielding the sword and his memories as the Plum Blossom Sword Saint too?

“Ah.”

Chung Myung’s sword moved slowly. Compared to Jung Bin’s fierce slash, it seemed powerless, as if he would struggle to even hit a stationary target.

Chak!

However, that very powerless sword moved towards Jung Bin’s sword.

“Huh?”

At that moment, Jung Bin felt shocked.

As soon as the slow sword of Chung Myung came close, a tremendous force suddenly was pushed through his arm.

“Kuak!”

As his body could not handle the force, Jung Bin soared into the sky.

“Learn thoroughly and come back.”

The brilliantly shining sword of Chung Myung. It wasn’t vivid like the Plum Blossom but hazy like flower buds.

Thud!

Jung Bin’s body collapsed on the ground like a rotten tree.

“Tch.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue and went to pick up the sword.

Using the opponent’s strength against them, a kid who can’t even handle this was no match for Chung Myung.

“Learn your pla—”

It was then.

“I–Indeed!”

“Eh?”

When he turned, Yu Jong-San was staring at him, mouth agape and clearly stunned.

‘Ah, shit!’

At that moment, Chung Myung realized the mistake he had made.

Yu Jong-San had been living here his entire life. It wouldn’t be surprising for him to recognize Chung Myung’s swordsmanship, which births flower petals. Of course, since he lived here, he may recognize that it’s a technique native to Mount Hua. Though, the evidence is circumstantial.

“As expected, you are from a prestigious sect. I expected it but…!”

Chung Myung’s face in the mask had distorted.

‘Did he figure it out?’

Or maybe he would have to make sure this man never opened his mou—

“That clean and splendid swordsmanship! High-level martial arts! And above all, a gentle feeling of kindness….”

What? Kindness?

Something was wrong.

Chung Myung hesitated with how to deal with this situation; as he waited for the man to continue, Yu Jong-San confidently shouted to him.

“And at such a young age, there was only one place which could nurture such abilities! It is!”

“oh-no…”

“Southern Edge Sect!”

“…”

Chung Myung looked at the man with blank eyes.

Southern Edge Sect? Why would it be them?

“Uh?”

“Are you from the Southern Edge Sect?”

“… Huh?”

He only had to think for a moment before quickly responding.

“R–right!”

“I knew it.”

Yu Jong-San bowed.

“Ask me. I will answer anything.”

“… thanks.”

Very much, thank you very much!

Oh my.

Hahahaha!

Chapter 23: Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (3)

“Why is he so late?”

Jo Gul looked around nervously.

Dawn approached as the sun was rising in the distance, but there was still no sign of Chung Myung’s return. If Chung Myung didn’t make it before the morning, the elders would discover his disappearance.

And then there would be a riot.

The disciples of Mount Hua are forbidden from leaving without permission. What if they find out that Chung Myung snuck out while wearing a suspicious full-body black outfit?

‘It will be hell.’

He hoped that he would never have to see that.

“Calm down.”

“But Sahyung.”

Yoon Jong shook his head.

“He isn’t that stupid. He’ll be back before it’s too late, as long as there was no accident.”

And no matter how much he thought, it didn’t seem like anything could happen to that monster. At worst, he would be a little late.

“Still, doesn’t he know that people are waiting here for him?”

“Right.”

If it’s him.

As soon as Jo Gul voiced his concerns, the door swung open.

“Tch.”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong swiftly turned around.

“Sajae!”

Chung Myung opened the door and entered the room.

Chung Myung, carrying his cloth mask in one hand, began to take off his mysterious clothing as soon as he closed the door, quickly changing into Mount Hua’s uniform.

“Nothing happened, right?”

“That’s what I was going to ask. Did anything happen?”

“What would happen?”

Chung Myung had a mischievous grin.

“I was treated well and even treated others well too.”

“W-who?”

“What was his name? Yu… whatever, it was the fabric shop owner.”

“Eh?”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong were shocked at his words. Seeing their reaction, Chung Myung remembered what had happened a while back.

‘It wasn’t funny, seriously.’

Yu Jong-San, who mistakenly believed Chung Myung came from the Southern Edge Sect to clean up the remnants of Mount Hua, willingly released all the information he had.

He was trying his best to leave a good impression and gain favor.

‘Huh.’

It was good that everything worked out so easily, but at the same time, he felt bitter.

Although it was no longer among the Great Sects, Mount Hua still had a formidable history; yet Yu Jong-San clearly held no regard for it. Even after witnessing Chung Myung’s sword arts, Mount Hua’s name never so much as crossed his mind.

Regardless of whether the Plum Blossom Sword technique was lost in recent years, it was still iconic as a symbol of Mount Hua. But he lived in Hua-Um all his life and couldn’t recognize it?

Considering Mount Hua’s recent history, no one could even remember it; however, the bitterness in his heart didn’t go away.

‘Well, something bitter will always remain bitter, and it helps me see things clearly.’

He was glad that he didn’t expose his identity.

“What happened?”

“… tch.”

At Jo Gul’s question, Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

“It isn’t something for kids to know.”

“… you are a kid too.”

“Yeah, yeah. Just go gather everyone. We need to train.”

“Today, too?”

Chung Myung rolled his eyes.

“Listen. Sahyung.”

“Yes?”

“Whether pouring rain, freezing snow, or violent winds. Starting today. We won’t miss a single day of training! Heavy snow or cold winds! We will not rest for a single day even if Mount Hua collapses around us!”

Jo Gul nodded with a stiff face.

‘He’s decided!’

After all, It was his decision to follow and help Chung Myung, right? If he can get strong through training, then he would do it. Truthfully, training without rest was what he was hoping for.

“We will gather everyone. Then you will—”

“Oh, I won’t be coming.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung looked at Yoon Jong and continued.

“You know how to train, right?”

“… yes.”

“Then do it right.”

“Then you?”

“I have other work to do.”

Yoon Jong sighed as Chung Myung waved his hand.

“Right. Today we will go and practice ourselves. But you are only exempt for today.”

Yoon Jong had a slightly serious face.

“Don’t forget that this training is possible because of you. If you don’t plan to end it halfway, then you need to set the example and join in.”

“I get it.”

The third-class disciples of the White Blossom dorms were training without complaint due to their fear of Chung Myung. Even though Yoon Jong was the Great Sahyung, there was a limit to what he could do if Chung Myung was absent.

“Sure.”

Chung Myung lay flat on the bed as the two left the room.

“Now, what do I do?”

His head pounded and ached.

He was dumbfounded.

It wouldn’t be difficult to merely wipe out the enemies, but anyone who learned about it would naturally link it to Mount Hua.

If it was only Chung Myung’s reputation at stake, then there would be no reason to hesitate, but he was a disciple of Mount Hua.

And if he tried anyway, people would say it was impossible for a kid like Chung Myung to act alone. The sect would receive all the blame, and it would carry the crime of forcing children to carry out unspeakable acts.

Chung Myung wanted a better result than that. He needed justification.

“Reason… a reason… ugh.”

Chung Myung tore at his hair in frustration.

“Does any of this make sense? Damn it!”

All those businesses belonged to Mount Hua. But now they were trying to make Mount Hua pay them? His stomach was boiling in rage.

He had to prove that the businesses belonged to Mount Hua and that the merchants tried to steal them away by manipulating the ledgers.

In that case, what about the hundred thousand nyang? It could be paid back.

No, Mount Hua wouldn’t even have to pay because every nyang originally belonged to them anyway. They were the owners who made and used the money; who would ask them to pay?

So, all he would have to do was prove that the businesses belonged to Mount Hua. Then everything will be resolved…

“If it was easy, I wouldn’t be here.”

If Mount Hua still had its business ledgers, there would be no suffering now.

If there was evidence, someone would have found it; the disciples of Mount Hua aren’t fools; rather, they’re quite smart.

Looking at the situation, when the Demonic sect attacked, the ledgers and everything must have been destroyed…

“Is this also because of me?”

It hurt. His stomach hurt.

Chung Myung rolled over in his bed.

“No! Sahyung would always keep the most important things in a safe place. Safely!”

Money and ledgers! A place—

“Huh?”

Chung Myung jumped up from his bed.

Place?

Plaaaaaceee?

‘Could it be?’

Would Sahyung ever keep his books in a place that could be easily targeted?

‘Try to remember.’

Chung Myung wasn’t really interested in his Sahyung’s matters. He knew that money was needed to run a clan, but he thought that a warrior shouldn’t be attached to such things.

But seeing these kids in Mount Hua struggling to survive, he felt bad thinking of how he’d behaved in his past life.

Since Chung Myung wasn’t interested in such a matter, his Sahyung had never shown him any books. In fact, whenever he was organizing, he would often ask Chung Myung to leave before he began.

“… leave?”

Hazy memories began to resurface.

At most, there were no more than three ledgers in Sahyungs room. There must have been dozens of ledgers for a sect the size of Mount Hua. So, where were the others stored?

‘There’s somewhere else!’

There was no place to store it in Sahyung’s room.

Although he was the great elder and sect leader, his room was strangely empty; Chung Myung remembered that. There was no shelf to even keep books.

Besides, he would keep the books in a box, and there were only three held in that room. So, where were the other ledgers?

“Then, is it true?”

The rumor was that there was a secret warehouse that only the sect leaders knew about. It was a famous rumor.

Normally, Chung Myung would have investigated that rumor to know the truth, but he didn’t check it because he had no interest in it.

‘Wait, maybe…’

Mount Hua used to be a prestigious sect in Shaanxi, and sometimes strange things would arrive at the door. For example, forbidden martial arts, which none should learn, or secrets that only the sect elders know. Occasionally, legendary swords and treasures were obtained.

So, where did they all go?

If those items were here, Chung Myung wouldn’t have overlooked them.

And they weren’t sold. Some things in this sect could cause a storm if released. If the current sect leader sold them, then word would have spread widely.

Then what?

‘There must be!’

A secret warehouse where books and treasures are stored.

It can’t be far from here.

The warehouse wouldn’t be placed out in the open. So, it had to be in Mount Hua. A warehouse which no one knew about.

But could that be possible?

How would you build a secret warehouse in a sect where martial artists swarmed all over like ants?

Chung Myung slammed the door and stormed out.

There could only be one place.

First, the entrance had to be near the sect leader’s residence. If the entrance was outside, it couldn’t go unnoticed.

No one could enter without the permission of the sect leader, so it had to be there.

‘The residence of the sect leader hasn’t changed from the past at all.’

Then, is that it?

Chung Myung, who ran outside, opened his eyes wide.

There is a gentle ridge behind the residence of the sect leader.

‘If a warehouse had to be built, it would have stood out in the eyes of the people.’

However, there is one way to avoid the eyes of others.

An underground warehouse.

If they had dug out an underground warehouse near the living quarters, martial artists with keen senses could have discovered it. However, what if they had made a passage starting here and built the warehouse under the mountain?

“Other than a ghost, no one would know of it.”

Chung Myung smiled.

‘Right.’

When he thought about it, it was strange.

Usually, in other sects, the sect leader would live in the most central area.

Wouldn’t it be strange if the emperor’s palace was placed in a corner?

However, the residence of the sect leader of Mount Hua was in such a place. And there is nothing after that.

That’s all there is!

Seeing the small garden behind the sect leader’s residence, Chung Myung grinned.

“It looks like this treasure hunt won’t be too complicated.”

He felt as if he could see his Sahyung biting his lip and clenching his fist from the afterlife.

“Please understand. My dear Sahyung! Shouldn’t our top priority be saving Mount Hua? If possible, I will hand this treasure over to the current sect leader without touching it.”

If possible…If possible.

Of course, only after he got what he needed.

‘If it makes you sad or angry, then come back to life!’

“Hehehehe!”

Chung Myung smiled triumphantly.

Chapter 24: Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (4)

“Ugh.”

Chung Myung sat on the floor.

“… I feel like I’m going to die.”

It wasn’t an easy task. Although the garden was small, it was still on a mountain. And rummaging through such a place was far from easy.

Moreover, it felt like he was stealing because he was taking advantage of the dark night to avoid the eyes of the Sasuks.

‘Damn this body!’

He couldn’t adapt to it. In the past, he wouldn’t lose his breath even if he worked continuously for three days and nights. However, this weak, weak body constantly gasped for air!

It was the same when he went down to interrogate the merchant. Going up and down was ten times more difficult than dealing with that guard escort!

Moreover, with his current body, this task wasn’t easy.

“Ugh!”

Chung Myung took a deep breath and pushed his internal energy into the ground with his hands on the floor.

What was he doing in the middle of the night?

“haah, damn it!”

The warehouse was down there somewhere. But the problem was that he didn’t know where.

There was only one way. He had to check each place individually like this.

Thanks to that, Chung Myung was constantly crawling along the garden pumping out energy, searching for an empty space to find that warehouse.

Something far easier said than done.

Finding it was tough…

“This is like finding a needle in a haystack!”

Chung Myung sighed deeply.

In the past, he could instantly check an entire small mountain with his one hand. However, his current limit required both hands to only shoot a small amount of energy.

“Ugh! I am really dying!”

Moreover, it wasn’t possible to constantly use that much energy. His dantian was too small to even be called one, and it would quickly be depleted. He would have to sit down and cultivate again every time that happened.

‘What if the warehouse doesn’t exist? Am I doing something stupid?’

His body was tired, so he couldn’t keep his mind away from such thoughts. Chung Myung shook his head to blow away the clutter in his mind.

Where there is a will, there is a way.

“It must be here!”

Considering his Sahyung’s nature, along with everything else, the ledgers must be safe and sound. And there was only one way to find it.

It seemed like combing the desert to find a diamond. However, this was more like searching for a boulder on a beach. This hopeful thought was enough to keep pressing forward. How could he fail to find it?

Once more!

“Ugh!”

Once more!

“I am dead!”

Once more!

“Empty? Well, none of my business.”

Once more—

No. Hold on a moment.

“Empty?”

Chung Myung’s eyes widened. To confirm it, he squeezed out even more energy.

‘Gasp!’

He felt something unusual. An empty space below him. It wasn’t possible to determine if this space was the warehouse or created naturally, like a burrow, as his internal energy was weak.

But he was certain that it was empty.

Then?

“Spit it out!”

Chung Myung spat on the floor and stood up. And then he grabbed a pickaxe which was next to him.

“I need to see it with my own eyes to be sure!”

Now it comes down to a battle of guts!

“Kuak!”

One dig

“Kuaaaaak!”

Two digs

“Ackkkkkk!”

Three digs

Down.

Just digging down five times was enough to make his arms and legs tremble. His back hurt too.

Anyone who learns martial arts would be accustomed to suffering.

However, the pain caused by hard training and battle wounds differs from the pain of solid labor. Unfortunately, Chung Myung wasn’t very accustomed to the pain of labor.

Even if he was used to it, it wasn’t something he could do with a child’s body!

Digging in healthy land is difficult even for a healthy adult man. Besides, there are no tricks you can employ. This was something that could be done solely with strength and perseverance.

“Spit!”

Chung Myung spat out the dirt which entered his mouth.

“Come on now. Whether it’s your victory or mine! Let’s see!”

However, it would besmirch the name of the Plum Blossom Sword Saint!

“Ugh!”

Chung Myung vigorously started sharpening the pickaxe again. If there was space down there, he would find it!

Dig! Dig! Dig! Tak?

“Okay-ay-ay-ay!”

“Huh?”

Tak?

Chung Myung quickly lowered himself to the ground. Then he began to peel the soil back with his hands. After digging up the soil, he felt something under his hands.

‘Brick?’

Chung Myung’s face contorted. It felt strange on his hand, and he could see a crack in the middle; it looked like a brick.

It would be a good sight that a brick was below this place because that meant that something was created.

However, Chung Myung had a different idea.

If this place was Mount Hua’s warehouse, it shouldn’t be so poorly built from common bricks.

A brick…

‘For now, I should keep going.’

Chung Myung suppressed his disappointment. He wouldn’t be sure until he saw it. The most important thing was to see it with his own eyes.

Sha!

When the soil was removed, it was revealed that the bricks made a clear pattern. It was night, so he couldn’t see it well, but he could tell that something was underneath it.

‘Let’s see.’

Chung Myung carefully grabbed one of the bricks.

As many years had passed, the bricks were firmly attached to one another. He pulled the brick with force, yet he was careful not to break it.

Hnng!

And the brick was slowly pulled free from the others.

‘Great!’

Chung Myung carefully pulled out the brick and shoved his face into the hole he had created.

‘Okay, here is….’

Chung Myung raised his head and frowned.

There was nothing down below. All he could see was…

‘No way… ah! A hallway?’

Tightly, he clenched his fists!

He wasn’t wrong. He searched properly and found something. The place he found wasn’t the warehouse but the path which led to it. Due to his lack of internal energy, he couldn’t distinguish between a warehouse or a hallway.

But finding this place meant that he found the path to the warehouse!

‘Great!’

The moment Chung Myung raised his head and tried to remove more bricks….

Step.

A low sound of footsteps from below

‘_Gasp!’_

Chung Myung almost screamed in shock as someone was walking through the hallway.

‘Sect leader?’

He titled his head back and hurriedly covered the brick he pulled out. But there was a bigger problem.

‘Shit!’

Some light was leaking through the cracks created from removing bricks. Chung Myung, in a panic, quickly covered the bricks and then laid his body over them as he stifled his breathing.

‘Why now of all times!’

He could get caught. What would he say to the sect leader if he asked how this child found this place?

He couldn’t let himself be caught.

Step! Step!

The sound of footsteps walking through the dark hallway gradually grew closer.

‘It has to be Sect Leader!’

His appearance came into view in the dark corridor as he continued his casual pace.

Fortunately, the sect leader passed by where Chung Myung was hidden. But there was no sigh of relief. The sect leader came to a stop a short distance away.

‘A wall?’

As his eyes got used to the darkness, he could see what was inside through the hole. A large wall could be seen where the sect leader had stopped.

No. Not a wall.

It might seem that way, but it wasn’t a wall. At the end of the long hallway was a door. The sect leader stood still as he looked at it.

‘He knew about this after all.’

Chung Myung had expected him to know.

Apart from the sect leader, there was no way anyone else could know about this place. Likely, this was a secret location passed down through the generations from one sect leader to the next; or maybe he simply discovered it while living in his residence over time.

Rather, how strange would it be if the sect leader didn’t know that this warehouse existed?

This must have been where the books and treasures were kept, right?

It was then.

The sect leader quietly raised his hand and touched the door. He traced the door with his fingertips as if he was feeling something precious.

‘What is he up to?’

An action with no meaning.

However, a somber air around the sect leader made it feel as if this meaningless action carried some purpose.

As he fumbled with the door, he slowly lowered his head and remained in that position for a time.

Only then did Chung Myung realize.

It wasn’t that he was doing something.

It was that he couldn’t do anything.

Chung Myung, who looked at it, bit back his words.

Small

Weak.

The back of the Great Mount Hua Leader should always be wide and warm. But now, this man’s back was bent like that of a village chief overburdened by his obligations.

A small back that went unseen by anyone else, only within this corridor can he show his weakness; outside, he refuses to allow anyone else to see his meek self.

Chung Myung could feel the old man’s trembling.

‘Ah…’

Now he understood.

‘He can’t open it.’

Chung Myung bit his lip.

His back hurts. It’s cold and painful.

Mount Hua was collapsing.

Their name was tarnished, and their riches had been lost. Those who used to stand below them were now driving them into a corner and demanding what little they had left. Every day they grew hungrier, and their blades grew sharper.

How desperate would he have been all this time?

How miserable would it have been for this sect leader who couldn’t do anything but watch Mount Hua collapse in his lifetime?

Still, he couldn’t speak of it to anyone. Because he is the sect leader, which the people depended upon. He wasn’t someone who could lay his burdens on them.

Even if everything collapsed, he had to be firm and support the others like a massive tree that dug its roots firmly into the earth.

So…

He was in this place, seeking solace alone amidst the pain and sorrow.

Grasping at the door which held his hopes yet refused to open.

Chung Myung looked at the sect leader’s back. As if trying to engrave that image into his eyes.

The sect leader, who hadn’t moved for a while, raised his head.

He stared at the door intensely, took a deep breath, and then turned around. Slowly making his way back out of the hallway.

Chung Myung held his breath until the sect leader’s presence completely disappeared. And then lifted the brick and slowly jumped in.

“… tch.”

He bore witness to something he didn’t want to see.

‘The fault lies with me.’

Not just him; even the others during his time were at fault. The world’s future was important, but the sect’s future, this Mount Hua sect, was important too. It was important to go after the monster that arose, but they should have thought about the children they were leaving behind.

“It isn’t too late now.”

If there was a mistake, he could rectify it. From now, Chung Myung will help to return their lost years.

“Well then…”

He turned his head.

“Shall we open this damn door first?”

Chapter 25: Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (5)

‘Before that, check the surroundings first.’

Chung Myung shook his head and turned away. He had to make sure that he was ready to avoid any traps that might activate when he opened the door.

Knowing his Sahyung, he was sure that the old man would have traps if anyone other than himself tried to enter. That man was one careful bastard.

‘I don’t see anything strange.’

Chung Myung’s gaze was drawn to a hole at the top of the corridor; it seemed to confirm that some device that should have been there was missing.

It was a hole big enough to fit a child’s fist. And it wasn’t just one; there were dozens of these holes separated a fixed distance apart from each other at regular intervals.

“Tch.”

Originally, there must have been lights placed there. This hallway should have been a brightly shining one, not a dark hallway like now.

Each time the sect ran low on money, they must have taken and sold another lantern to cover their growing debts. The corridor steadily dimmed and lost its light with each challenge they faced.

What was the sect leader thinking as he looked at the dark hallway each time he entered? Was Mount Hua’s hope fading with every light sold? Did he feel that as this corridor’s light gradually faded, another path for Mount Hua’s revival would be severed?

“Ugh.”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

“It would have been better not to see this.”

Heavy. So heavy.

He knew it. Because he wasn’t stupid.

Although the sect leader and the sasuks never let the weight of their burdens show, Chung Myung could still guess how they felt. Everyone likely had trouble even sleeping properly; the weight of Mount Hua’s declining name gradually rotting away during their generation weighed heavily on their minds.

And they must have been under this kind of pressure all their lives.

‘It’s unfair.’

It wouldn’t be enough to do something alone. In fact, it was true that Chung Myung alone had raised the name and reputation of Mount Hua back when he was known as the Plum Blossom Sword Saint; but even then, the glory of Mount Hua had echoed in the ears of the people long before Chung Myung’s time.

Chung Myung clicked his tongue and moved to the door.

He was done sitting around complaining; now it was time to try and open the door.

“But… how do I open this?”

Chung Myung tilted his head.

There was no handle for the door. The long dividing line in the middle was what made him guess that it was a door; without that line, it would simply be a wall.

“And what are these lines?”

A long split in the center was a sign of the door interlocking. Then what about those jumbled horizontal and vertical lines? It looked as if someone had used the wall to practice their swordsmanship.

“… is this really a door?”

Chung Myung, who placed his hand on the unknown wall or door, quietly infused his energy into it. But he soon let go of it and backed off.

“Insane.”

The energy wouldn’t enter. With an ordinary wall, such a thing couldn’t happen. Which meant that there was something behind this door.

‘Thousand-Year-Old Cold Iron.’

At least an inch thick too.

“… all the money must have gone to this.”

It must have been incredibly expensive to bring in that precious piece of iron and use it as a warehouse door.

“That’s why the sect leader couldn’t even think of opening it.”

This was the best metal in the world. A sword forged from this ore would be a treasured blade; an armor made of this material would turn into a priceless garment with impenetrable defense.

It’s a rare treasure that holds far more value than gold at the same weight. So how was a warehouse made of such a material?

“Huhuhu.”

Depending on what you think, it may seem foolish. However, just from this act alone, you can gaze into the sect leader’s personality. To use such an expensive metal like this.

But Chung Myung could understand why the sect leader couldn’t open this place; Thousand-Year-Old Cold Iron was the most rigid metal in the world. Even Chung Myung wouldn’t be able to cut it.

If such metal was an inch thick, it would take Chung Myung at his peak in the past utilizing all his techniques to cut through it all. So, if he wanted to cut this now, he would have to be the best swordsman in the world or bring someone equally strong.

But would such an expert just kindly open the door to the treasury and walk away without touching the contents inside?

‘Absolutely not.’

A toothless Mount Hua would be easy to exploit. And those with power will take away what they want without any consideration for Mount Hua.

Mount Hua could face absolute destruction if robbers and outsiders were clumsily asked for help.

‘Sect leader’s choice wasn’t wrong. Calling in a master to avoid immediate downfall would be like calling in a tiger to avoid the wolf.’

What is inside the warehouse is essential, but even the material it is made of could attract calamity. Items that could bring in thousands of gold would incite thievery if the information was made public.

“The problem is, even I can’t cut it….”

Chung Myung’s face distorted slightly.

If it was him from the past, he could even cut it open with his bare hands. He reached the peak of the sword in the past!

“Never mind!”

He put aside all thoughts of his past life.

Chung Myung looked at the patterns on the wall. This was a door, and as his Sahyung could enter and come out, there had to be a way to open it.

His Sahyung wasn’t stronger than Chung Myung. So, his method would be…

“Uh? This is?”

Twenty-Four Plum Blossom Sword Technique?

The pattern on the wall! No! It was from a sword!

Some of the patterns resembled the Twenty-Four Plum Blossom Sword Technique. And once a clue was found, the other patterns could be recognized as well.

“This is the Equilibrium Sword technique, and this one is also the Plum Blossom Sword.”

There were lines from shallow cuts to deep marks.

Engraved on this door were the techniques unique to the disciples of Mount Hua.

‘That’s why the sect leader couldn’t open it.’

Because the Plum Blossom Sword calls for the Twenty-Four Plum Blossom Sword technique, which has been lost to the sect. Although it’s possible to recognize a sword technique from the patterns it leaves, the sect leader couldn’t learn and understand the technique just from these markings.

“This depth…”

Chung Myung let out a sigh.

The marks started with the Equilibrium Sword and Bamboo Leaf technique, followed by the Twenty-Four Plum Blossom Sword technique.

That was the way to open this door.

If the technique was spread precisely along the path, it would make the door open by itself. Chung Myung couldn’t understand how such a thing was created.

But the problem was solved.

Now, only one problem remained.

“… how am I supposed to do this?”

If it was the past, there wouldn’t be any problem. Not just him, but any disciple of Mount Hua in the past would be able to open this door without much trouble. However, the current Chung Myung was a child who didn’t properly learn the sword technique.

He could still follow the sword lines. However, it was impossible for him to put in the energy needed to unfold it at once.

“Phew.”

Chung Myung sighed deeply.

‘Nothing is impossible!’

If it was impossible, then make it possible! There were no problems in the world that couldn’t be solved.

Chung Myung gritted his teeth and put his hands together on his dantian.

“… I really didn’t want to do this.”

He didn’t want to resort to this. He didn’t want to overdo it. But this was the only method left that he could think of.

“I think I’ll end up recuperating for about a month.”

Chung Myung thought and then used his strength to tap into the innate qi, located in the deepest part of the dantian.

The true internal qi.

The power that every human has since birth.

It was different from the inner energy trained through cultivation. Even if your energy is used up or vanishes, the person wouldn’t die. Although they would feel a great sense of helplessness and weakness, it wouldn’t interfere with their life. This is because this energy is artificially cultivated by humans.

However, the true internal qi is different.

Humans who lose their true internal qi can no longer sustain life. In other words, it can be said that the true internal qi is vital for human life.

Those who have reached the peak of martial arts can use the true internal qi as their own strength. However, the true internal qi exists to sustain life; a price must be paid to utilize its power.

Excessive consumption of it would result in death.

Even if cautiously consumed, the energy will be significantly damaged, and one wouldn’t be able to lead a normal life for several months.

‘I am only going to use a little. Right, just a little.’

Wouldn’t it be meaningless if Chung Myung died before he saved Mount Hua?

Right now, Chung Myung was probably the most crucial figure hidden within Mount Hua.

Tap.

Stimulate the true internal qi. Make sure not to bring out too much. Just enough to use! Just enough to use!

The true internal qi, roused from its slumber, began to rage. It was then pushed into the dantian.

‘It is a little more than I thought.’

Chung Myung blew away his thoughts and grabbed the sword.

Is it possible?

It is!

A magnificent power was created by mixing the internal qi with internal energy and letting it flow throughout his entire body. As this energy began to flow through his unfamiliar body, his entire being shook.

“Kuak!”

A groan escaped from behind his lips. A terrible pain that made Chung Myung doubt his mind.

‘Just once! I need to do it just once!’

A black, purple color began to form on his fingertips.

He didn’t learn martial arts in this life. It was nothing more than a clumsy imitation of what he remembered from the past, and it felt even more unfamiliar because of the child-like body.

Chung Myung’s hand cut through the air like a beam of light.

A vivid trail of illusory purple light pierced the wall.

Kuak!

The sound of scratching the wall resonated in the empty hall. It was a door that had to be opened in one go since Chung Myung couldn’t handle doing it another time, but even his imitation was slow, thanks to his body’s condition.

“KUAK!”

Each time he moved, it hurt.

But Chung Myung didn’t stop and kept moving his hand. As the excessive movements continued, he could feel his muscles tearing as if they would snap at any moment; and his face was flushed and burning as though it would explode at any moment.

‘I am the Plum Blossom Sword Saint!’

If he didn’t have the ability, then he would move his body on pride alone!

Biting his lip to drive his consciousness forward. Chung Myung unleashed his final struggle.

Tuk!

His hand stopped in the air.

‘Done?’

His legs were trembling, and his heart pounded erratically as if desperately trying to keep his body together, but he didn’t have time to pay attention to his current condition. If the door still didn’t open after this, he would truly be facing a disaster.

It was then.

Kikik!

He thought he heard a strange squeaking sound! The sound of something opening.

And, the huge door ahead moved.

“ah!”

It opened!

He thought that the door would open fully, but only the lock on it seemed to have been released.

But it was…

“Aaaaghhhhhh!”

Suddenly, Chung Myung curled forward, grabbing his stomach.

Blood poured out of his small mouth. It came out with a force that couldn’t be swallowed back.

“Ugh.”

He wiped the lips with his sleeve.

It seemed that his body was injured more than he thought.

If this was the case, he would have to take at least two months rest for his internal injuries to recover.

“Haaa… reviving Mount Hua is horrifyingly tough.”

Chung Myung spit out the blood remaining in his mouth and pitifully pushed the door open in a disgraceful way using the little might he had left.

Kiiiik!

The door, sealed for ages, finally opened wide from side to side.

“Now, shall I check what Sahyung was hiding?”

With a cunning smile, Chung Myung confidently walked into the warehouse.

Chapter 26: Mount Hua gains a fortune (1)

The place was narrower than expected.

It was natural. It would have left a large hole in Mount Hua’s finances if they had created a massive warehouse out of Thousand-Year-Old Cold Iron; they would have never lasted this long.

“… he kept whining every day that he had no money. Yet he kept spending it to make things like this.”

Chung Myung felt a surge of anger, but what could he do? He could do nothing to a dead person.

Chung Myung went inside and looked around.

There were a lot of things stored here. What should he check for first?

“Money!”

Chung Myung blinked his eyes and scanned the room.

It had to be here! The slush funds which Sahyung was saving! Some shining piece of gold! Riches shining brilliantly…!

“It must be here.”

Chung Myung continued to survey the room.

Why? Why couldn’t he see them?

Chung Myung once again scoured the inside of the storeroom. No matter how many times he rubbed his eyes, however, he couldn’t find anything shiny, let alone treasures.

It shouldn’t be this way.

“N-No.”

With how frugal his Sahyung was, he must have accumulated a lot more money than any other sect leader!

It would be common sense for him to plan and keep aside a certain amount of wealth to prepare Mount Hua for any unexpected scenarios.

“But there is no money!”

A great sense of defeat came over him.

Haaa, fucking bastard. Didn’t he keep any slush funds?

Chung Myung rubbed his face.

If there had been an emergency stash of money, he could have used them for any number of schemes.

For the revival of Mount Hua, for buying drinks, and for buying more drinks…

“Ah no! I am purely focused on the revival of Mount Hua!”

“Ehh!”

Chung Myung abandoned his lingering desires and turned his head. There were things more important than wealth.

“This is it!”

Books lined up one after another on a bookshelf on one wall.

Chung Myung gulped and walked over to it.

“This has to be it.”

He pulled out a book from the middle and scanned the contents. As he read each line, a bright smile slowly appeared.

“Right!”

There can be no other way!

As expected, the books displayed on the first shelf were books of Mount Hua, which Sahyung kept. These documents were generally supposed to be stored in the sect leader’s house, but it seemed like copies were made and stored here in case of emergencies.

And there weren’t just ledgers from Chung Myung’s time, but even from the previous generations too. With just this information, he would be able to slap those rotten jerks in the back of the head.

“Those bastards are so dead!”

These ledgers were worth the painstaking effort he went through to open the door.

And on the second shelf…

“Oh!”

No way!

Chung Myung nearly screamed without realizing it.

The authentic secret arts of Mount Hu are here…

“Huh?”

Chung Myung tilted his head.

“Are these the real deal?”

Chung Myung frowned. These things were a bit different from the martial arts he studied. In Mount Hua, the secret arts, which were almost as good as dead, were gathered there!

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung scratched his cheek.

“Those foolish old bastards.”

It had been decided not to pass these down to the future disciples, but it was clear that they didn’t abandon them. It seemed that Sahyung was reluctant to completely throw them away.

Maybe he thought that it would negatively impact Mount Hua’s future if they were abandoned, so he kept them here.

If the first shelf full of ledgers showed the old sect leader’s obligations and responsibilities to the sect, this second shelf represented his compassion and dedication.

“… Sahyung.”

Chung Myung felt a rising surge of tears sting his eyes.

“Don’t worry. I will definitely revive Mount Hua to its original state.”

No, he would make it more prosperous than in the past.

Chung Myung regained his ambition and turned.

There was no rush, and it will be fine. After all, the important thing was that Chung Myung knew how to use all the techniques. It was annoying to write it down for others, but he didn’t plan on keeping the information a secret either.

And finally…

There was virtually nothing on the third shelf.

There was only a single rolled scroll.

“What is this?”

Without hesitation, Chung Myung reached out, opened it, and immediately began to read it.

[From the sect leader (Sahyung)]

If anyone is reading this, it means that the next generation’s sect leader has been decided. Sometimes, a single line of writing conveys more than a hundred words, so I leave my meaning in this humble form.

The position of sect leader within Mount Hua isn’t a position to lead.

As anyone who becomes the next sect leader would naturally come to know, the ones who lead Mount Hua are the precious disciples, and they are the ones who bring growth to Mount Hua. A sect leader’s role is to protect and support them to carry out their own will without restrictions.

Now that you are the sect leader, I hope you will put aside your own impatience and work for the sake of the sect. Mount Hua is simply Mount Hua. No one person can lead or wield it.

Remember this when you are tired from life’s difficulties and the heavy burden on your shoulders; Mount Hua will not fall.

Mount Hua is Mount Hua. Whether it declines or flourishes, it will stay as Mount Hua. As sect leaders, we merely protect the spirit of the sect in our generation.

Pray that the will of Mount Hua, which our ancestors protected, be passed onto future generations. And nurture our descendants to continue our will so that we remain eternal.

I leave you a heavy burden as the sect leader of the previous generation.

The 21st sect leader of the Great Mount Hua, Jang Mun.

[End]

“…”

Chung Myung looked at the scroll silently.

He knew.

He knew that this wasn’t a letter written by his Sahyung to him, but, weirdly, he was the person who needed to read this more than the others.

“Right… that man really nagged a lot.”

Chung Myung sighed and put away the scroll in his hands.

The other things will be returned to Mount Hua, but not this scroll.

“Okay then…”

Chung Myung turned around with a smile.

“There wasn’t much, but this should be enough.”

First, he had the ledgers, which were the most essential items. If he had them, the businesses could be retrieved. Then Mount Hua would be able to get out of the debt.

So then…

Chung Myung, who was about to walk outside, stopped walking.

‘Wait a minute.’

It was strange.

‘Why does it feel like something’s off?’

He couldn’t pinpoint what was so strange, but he felt something was wrong.

Why was he feeling that way?

“Wait!”

Third shelf?

Chung Myung turned his head.

Sect leader, his Sahyung.

Jang Mun was the 21st sect leader of Mount Hua; that man had been obsessed with neatly organizing things.

It wasn’t just the cleanliness. Even if the furniture in his room were off by a slight angle, he couldn’t stand it.

But…

Two full shelves and one empty shelf?

“No. No. That man would have lost his mind.”

He knew it because he had been with that man for a long time.

Chung Myung rushed to the empty shelf.

‘Something has to be here!’

Surely!

That empty shelf kept bothering him. Isn’t it awkward to use an entire bookshelf for just one scroll? The Sahyung that he knew wasn’t that kind of a person.

If the one who came here wasn’t Chung Myung but someone else, they wouldn’t have thought much of it. But now Chung Myung was there.

He grabbed the shelf without hesitation and moved it to the side.

‘There’s nothing else around.’

There was nothing behind the shelf except for the cold iron wall. But what about below?

It could be. The floor seemed to be covered with iron. But?

Chung Myung, who moved the shelf, put his hand on the floor and soon infused it with energy.

‘If it was the old man that I knew, then it must be here!’

If there is a suspicious place, then something must be there.

Wooong!

Nothing happened. He wondered if his internal energy wasn’t strong enough, he couldn’t feel anything.

“Maybe I am wrong?”

It was the moment when he was flustered and thought about giving up.

Tuk!

“…!”

Right!

“Ahhhhhhhh!”

As Chung Myung felt himself being sucked below where the floor once was, something gave way.

Rumble!

Eventually, with the sudden feeling of something falling, Chung Myung lost his balance and collapsed backwards, rolling away from where he stood before.

“Ouch!”

After hitting his head several times, it felt like the night stars were flashing in front of him.

‘Wasn’t it too loud?’

He instinctively turned towards the entrance. However, it didn’t seem like anyone noticed it. Although it was connected, it didn’t seem like it could be heard because of the long corridor.

More than that!

Chung Myung jumped up and ran forward.

Something opened for sure.

Chung Myung ran to observe the hole which had formed.

“Then?”

Sahyung!

“You really are a nasty bastard!”

A hidden double floor was made in case someone other than the sect leader had come in.

After all of the hard work it takes to find and open this place, nobody would have imagined that there was another secret hidden here. Even Chung Myung wouldn’t have known if he didn’t understand his Sahyung so profoundly.

Light shone from the entrance.

Light!

It seemed like the light was made to show the path to Chung Myung.

Without hesitation, he threw himself into the opening. The entrance was small, even for a child’s body. As he went down through the entrance, he found a space so small that straightening his back was difficult.

In that place…

Chung Myung stretched out his hand and decided to close the door which opened.

“Slowly. Slowly.”

He made sure that no sound came of it.

And…

Chung Myung’s eyes opened wide. His breathing became rapid, and his heart began pounding. Blood rushed to his face as excitement colored his vision.

“Hahahahaha!”

He was dying of joy~

There was happiness right in front of him.

Gold bars were neatly stacked on one side.

And various other treasures arranged at another side.

And…

“Is this my tomb?”

Even unknown gems were in there!

“Hehehehehe!”

Laughter kept coming out. Even when he tried to not laugh, he couldn’t control it.

“Uhahahahaha!”

Right, smile! Laugh!

“I’m finally rich!”

The situation which the 21st sect leader, Jang Mun, desperately sought to avoid by taking extreme measures to guard this wealth.

This was the moment when the fate and fortune of Mount Hua firmly passed into the hands of the one person who should absolutely not have it.

Chapter 27: Mount Hua gains a fortune (2)

“Hmm.”

Hyun Jong softly sighed as he watched the sunlight peering through the window.

For some, that sunlight may be the start of a pleasant day. But for those living on borrowed time, there was nothing more resentful than the sunlight which brings forth another day.

‘It’s morning again.’

Yet again, a new day has started.

Two days have already passed. And five more days were left to pay back the enormous debt.

Five. Just five more days.

Hyun Jong quietly closed his eyes.

‘Five days.’

If he could not prepare 100,000 nyang within this short period, then Mount Hua would fall into their hands.

There are three things essential in life: food, clothing, and finally, shelter.

Although they could live even if they lost their residence, those who stayed in Mount Hua would need to try and find a different way to lead their lives. Mount Hua could no longer be called Mount Hua.

There may be some who wish to carry its name and succeed the will of Mount Hua. For many years, Mount Hua was considered a prestigious sect; surely, some would wish to hold onto it.

If a towering sect with thousands of disciples one day crumbles and can only shelter a few dozen students, and if it then loses its home and is exiled, can we not say that it has been thoroughly destroyed?

Those who can’t stay here will have no choice but to disperse. There will be people who follow him for a time, but as their lives grow more difficult, wouldn’t they simply find other work?

And gradually…

‘No.’

Hyun Jong shook his head violently.

‘This isn’t the time to think so weakly.’

He still had five days left. He could protect Mount Hua if he found some way to raise the amount needed.

He is the sect leader. And he will not give up until the day Mount Hua disappears. Everyone else has the luxury to give up, but he cannot falter.

Hyun Jong raised his hand and rubbed his face.

Perhaps he could reach out to everyone who had so much as a needle-thin relationship with Mount Hua. Stories of Mount Hua’s decline have circulated throughout the world. He only needed to find one capable person who would be willing to help them.

Just one person…

Hyun Jong chuckled softly in derision.

‘Help us?’

If someone wanted to help, they would have done it already. Even when Mount Hua had higher hopes than now, not one person helped them.

And now, who would come and lend a vast sum of 100,000 nyang to a ruined sect?

‘It’s so burdensome.’

It couldn’t be avoided or ignored. But Hyun Jong had to feel the weight each day as it grew on him.

The ever-present fear that Mount Hua’s life would be cut short with his generation. He prayed and prayed that the sun would fail to rise each morning as he struggled through another sleepless night.

It was then.

“Sect leader!”

Hyun Jong adjusted his expression. No matter how depressed he was, he couldn’t show that to his disciples. Even if Mount Hua collapses tomorrow, he must be remembered as the noble sect leader who carried the woes of his students as he stood by their side.

“What is it?”

“I-I think you need to come out and see.”

“Hmm?”

Hyun Jong tilted his head.

He moved right away and went outside. Right outside, Un Geom stood there waiting with a blank face.

“Un Geom?”

Hyun Jong frowned.

It wasn’t Un Am but Un Geom. Wasn’t Un Geom in charge of the White Plum Blossom Boarding House? If he came here, it meant that something had happened in the dorms.

But what could happen in the dorms which required the sect leader’s direct attention?

Isn’t it still so early in the morning?

“What happened?”

“S-sect leader.”

Un Geom had a strange face. He seemed surprised, yet a bit exhausted too.

‘Just what could have happened?’

He knew that gathering children and disciplining them was exhausting and required patience. Being chosen for this task, Un Geom was generally a very calm and composed person.

However, if even Un Geom struggled to keep his composure, he couldn’t understand what happened.

“I will tell you about the details on the way. Sect leader! You need to see this for yourself!”

“… guide me.”

Hyun Jong followed without question.

He was curious; however, since Un Geom asked in such a serious manner, he decided to simply follow him first.

“Yes, sect leader!”

Un Geom moved quickly, and Hyun Jong followed him without delay.

‘Where are we going?’

Hyun Jong frowned as he looked around. The place they were heading wasn’t the dorms. It was a place behind the dorms, the Lotus Peak.

Why there?

However, Un Geom kept climbing up with all his might without saying a word.

‘I’ll know once I see it.’

Halfway up the path with Un Geom, he saw third-class disciples sitting, scattered, on the side.

‘Huh?’

Why were those kids here? And why were they all over the place…?

Hyun Jong’s eyes widened.

Kids were lying left and right as they kept climbing. Even though their sect leader came, they couldn’t even raise their heads to greet him and kept gasping for air sprawled out on the ground.

“W-what is this?”

Un Geom, who came to a realization, yelled out.

“You lot! The sect leader is here; can’t you show manners!”

“Leave them be.”

“But sect leader!”

“Rather, why are the children in this condition?”

“That…”

Un Geom looked around and then asked.

“Chung Myung! Where is Chung Myung?”

Chung Myung? Why was that name coming out here?

Hyun Jong looked at Un Geom with a face that said he couldn’t understand at all. Chung Myung referred to the child who recently entered the sect, so why was he called?

“I’m over here.”

The answer came before his questions were answered.

Hyun Jong’s eyes widened when he turned to see where the voice had come from.

“You, why? Huh?”

A bizarre, almost grotesque young child walked out from behind a tree.

Face whiter than a blank sheet of paper with bluish lips like a corpse. The shadows under his eyes seemed to stretch down to his chin.

He didn’t seem like a human.

It wouldn’t seem strange if that child collapsed and died on the spot.

“What happened?”

“Ah, I am sorry. I trained a little too much….’

What was that?

If a person could take on such an appearance simply by training, no disciples would have survived until now! Training should make you stronger, not weaker. Make excuses that are believable!

At that moment, Un Geom spoke.

“That’s not the point right now.”

Hyun Jong blinked his eyes for a moment.

Doesn’t matter?

“What are you talking about!”

The man in charge of looking after the children says such a ridiculous thing!

The White Plum Blossom Boarding House is the future of Mount Hua. Weren’t they the disciples who would lead Mount Hua into a new future? How could someone who was training the kids say that…

“You need to see this. This one, Chung Myung, has found something strange.”

“Strange?”

“H-Hurry, sir.”

Un Geom seemed serious.

‘What…’

If it had been someone else showing such an attitude, Hyun Jong would have yelled and cursed them right away, but he had a deep understanding of Un Geom’s character. If such a calm individual behaved in such a way, it must be serious.

Hyun Jong finally followed Chung Myung and Un Geom and went into the forest.

“What the hell is he….”

Hyun Jong couldn’t continue.

A small section of the earth came into his view; it had been dug out and held an old box within. The box was halfway open.

Hyun Jong’s eyes nearly burst from their sockets.

He could see it.

Inside the box was a shining gold light. And there was only one metal that could emit such a golden light.

But it wasn’t simply the gold that caught his attention. It was the books next to gold.

The title of the books seemed to pull his soul from his body.

[Great Mount Hua’s Hua-Um village ledgers]

A long title.

“This, this, this…?”

Hyun Jong couldn’t come to his senses. Where did it come from? Why was gold here?

He was too scared to approach this unbelievable reality. He was afraid that the items would disappear like a mirage if he reached out to grasp them.

“H-how did you find them?”

“That child found them”

“Child?”

Hyun Jong turned his head to the corpse-like figure. With a half-dying face, Chung Myung opened his mouth.

“I-I was… training at dawn….”

“What?

Listening to the mosquito-like voice, Hyun Jong titled his head. Un Geom decided to help him out.

“He seems to have come to Lotus Peak at dawn to train.”

“Training at dawn? When did you start that?”

“We started it a while back. From the day that child entered.”

“Hmm.”

From the day the child entered?

How long has it been since he joined?

‘Ah, no. I shouldn’t be thinking about such a thing now.’

He could ask for the details later.

“So, you mean you found this while climbing the Lotus peak for morning training?

“To be precise, I was too tired and decided to take a rest inside the bushes, but the place I sat on was strangely hard, and when I looked more intensely, something was sticking out. So, I dug it out just in case….”

“Oh, my!”

“But… the stuff inside was so…. unusual, so I thought that I had to inform the elders… rather than check it myself.”

“T-take your time. What kind of kid even trains so hard that they can barely speak?”

“Training… is the root….”

“I-I get it. You should go back and rest. I will check it myself.”

Hyun Jong swallowed back dry saliva as he approached the box. Trembling, he placed his hand on the box. However, what he touched wasn’t the gold, but the books next to it.

“Great Mount Hua’s Hua-Um Village ledgers.”

Hyun Jong murmured to himself as if he had lost his mind as he took the books out one at a time. His trembling hands clearly spoke to the state of his turbulent mind.

He didn’t even open the books. He was terrified that if he opened the book clumsily, it would crumble to dust before his eyes.

“Great Mount Hua Records.”

It was a book dealing with the history of Mount Hua. Although it may not play a functional role, it was still significant.

Hyun Jong carefully laid down the books and gazed at each of their titles.

“S-S-Se…”

His eyes twitched.

“Seven Sages Sword….”

His whole body shook.

“This is, is, is…. This….”

“Se–sect leader!”

“Ugh!”

Hyun Jong felt himself losing consciousness.

“Sect leader!”

“Sect leader, calm down!”

Hearing the people call for him, Hyun Jong smiled as he closed his eyes.

What came out of the box wasn’t just some wealth and books.

It was hope.

Chapter 28: Mount Hua gains a fortune (3)

“Sect leader!”

“Sect leader! Open your eyes!”

Hyun Jong opened his eyes in shock.

‘A dream?’

He got up and saw that the box was still in front of him. Fortunately, it wasn’t a dream.

“Un–Un Geom!”

“Yes! Sect leader!”

“Call the merchants. Move the box to my residence! And have the older disciples guard the perimeter.”

“Yes! Sect leader!”

“No–No! I will move it myself! Right now!”

Hyun Jong took a breath and calmed himself.

Nothing was certain yet. To accurately understand the situation, he would have to check everything first and see if the items were genuine.

But.

‘They must be genuine!’

If these things were buried here, along with such enormous wealth, they had to be genuine.

‘No, no, no! Still, I need to be certain.’

Hope and anxiety battled against one another as his emotions surged. Has he felt like this anytime in recent decades?

“Un Geom!”

“Yes! Sect leader.”

“Bring your things and come down the mountain.”

“Yes!”

Hyun Jong jumped up and then suddenly looked at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung!”

“Yes. Sect leader.”

“You have worked hard. We will discuss this later.”

“Yes.”

When Chung Myung stepped back without saying a word, Hyung Jong hurriedly lifted the entire box. Then, he made a request to Chung Myung.

“Take the other children and head back to the dorm.”

“I will.”

“Good!”

With that, Hyun Jong headed down the peak. And Un Geom followed him with the other valuables. The children who were there looked at them with blank eyes.

“What was that?”

“… huh?”

Amid the confused children, Chung Myung smiled.

‘This should be enough for now.’

The wealth and supplies contained in the box were only a portion of what was in the warehouse.

Why did he only give a portion?

It’s not Mount Hua’s, It’s Chung Myung’s….no, that’s certainly not why

‘It is because the first bite vanishes fast.’

If you give a buffet to a dying man, his body may not be able to withstand it and waste what’s been given. Rather than overfeed him, you must give him enough to sate his hunger so that he would no longer starve.

It’s not necessarily a good thing to give someone more than they need.

Chung Myung judged that the current Mount Hua couldn’t handle the burden of a large sum of wealth. It was unreasonable for them to be handed an enormous sum of money at once. All the sect needed to do was start over.

Of course, this was a trial for the sect, but it wasn’t one for Chung Myung.

Yoon Jong approached him,

“Sajae.”

“Huh?”

“We were asked to go down; shouldn’t we head back to the dorm?”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“We should”

“But why does Sajae look like that?”

“Ugh, something happened.”

Chung Myung waved his hand and dismissed the concern.

‘I know what he is asking about.’

Thanks to using his pure internal qi, the condition of his body deteriorated.

‘I should have been more careful.’

This wouldn’t have happened in the past, but now he wasn’t even in a stable body. So, everything changed when he tried to over-exert himself with a child-like body.

It was foolish to think he could control it perfectly using this new and inexperienced body. It was only natural that he ended up using more of his true internal qi than he intended.

“You look like you are going to die.”

“I won’t die.”

“Really?”

“… would you prefer that I die?”

Yoon Jong turned his head away without answering.

Huh?

Not answering? Did he really want Chung Myung to die? Such a bastard!

“You aren’t going to die anyway, so why were you expecting me to say that I hope you don’t die?”

“Expect! Expect what? Khuem.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue at that.

‘I really might be on the bed for a month or two.’

It wasn’t easy to recover from such things. Even if Chung Myung tried living carefully, he could only struggle until his body returned to normal unless he could find some medicinal pills.

“By the way, how did you find that? It didn’t seem like something normal, especially seeing how shocked the sect leader was.”

“Live a good life, and the heavens will look after you. So be a good boy from now on.”

“…”

If someone like Chung Myung was blessed by God, then the other children should already be guaranteed a blessed life. Yet, no one retorted.

Chung Myung glanced down and looked at the sect leader descending the mountain.

‘If he’s been given this much, he should be able to handle it; things will go well.’

‘If he isn’t stupid.’

“Come on, let’s go down.”

“Right. But… where are you going?”

“What?”

“To go down, shouldn’t we head down from this way?”

Yoon Jong pointed at the path leading down.

“Are you seriously asking something so obvious?

“Then, why are you walking up?”

“tch, tch, tch.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue at Yoon Jong’s question.

“Sahyung.”

“… huh?”

“To be a warrior, you need to have a flexible way of thinking. Don’t think that there is only one way down. Climbing to the top and descending the other side, there are many ways to go down.”

‘What sort of bullshit is he saying? That idiot!’

“Come on, the sect leader and the others are gone, but we still have the training to do. The last ten people won’t get their meals today. Run!”

Yoon Jong’s feet began to move as he hurriedly ran towards the peak, even before he had a chance to express his dissatisfaction. The other kids followed him, running to the top in a panic.

‘That devilish bastard!’

‘Fucking shit! I don’t think I can catch up to him!’

Seeing the kids running with their might, Chung Myung smiled.

“I will give a present to whoever finishes first.”

What should he prepare for the next time?

The items he placed in that box and gave to the sect were just a little of what he had. The wealth brought out was less than one-tenth of the wealth in the storehouse.

Chung Myung glanced up at the sky. It felt like his Sahyung was looking down at him with a distorted face.

“Ehh. Don’t tell me, you think I’m going to eat it all alone?”

Healthy! Just enough, in moderation. Right, moderation!

“heheh!”

Chung Myung smiled as he moved.

“It’s genuine.”

He could feel his heart pounding. Of course, this answer was expected, but the impact didn’t diminish even though it was expected.

Hyun Jong asked, unable to hide his trembling.

“Are you sure?”

“Yes. I am sure. The ledgers are genuine, and we also secured the deed lying underneath the gold. Sect leader.”

“Huhuh! Huhuhu.”

He wanted to speak, but words weren’t coming out. He couldn’t help but laugh in a hoarse voice.

“H-How did this….”

“We have it! Sect leader!”

“Huh… huhuhuhu.”

No matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t stop smiling.

It was said that no one knew what would happen in life, but do such precious things really happen?

What if this was discovered a week late?

He didn’t even want to think about it.

‘The heavens have not forsaken us!’

No, it’s not the heavens, but the ancestors of Mount Hua, who kept looking after and helping them.

Hyun Jong closed his eyes, unable to hide his burning passion.

“Then can we prove the contents in the ledger?”

“These certificates were issued by the nation! Of course, we can prove it! We can bring the businesses of Hua-Um under us once more and even Tae-Hua Pavilion as well.”

“Good. That’s good.”

It’s a miracle.

In just a few days, the disciples of Mount Hua would have been thrown out to live on the streets. But with these books, they could not only protect their home, but they could even recover the businesses they lost so long ago.

A jackpot!

The head of financial affairs, Hyun Yeong, laughed.

“It is improbable, but even if they are fake, we can overcome the immediate crisis. Even if these ledgers don’t work, the wealth in the box is worth well over 100,000 nyang. It is more than enough to pay it back.”

“Thank god. It’s a relief.”

“With this money, we can solve all the financial problems of Mount Hua at once. And if we can take back the businesses, we won’t ever have to worry about money again.”

He could hear such honeyed words flowing nonstop. To Hyun Jong, it sounded like the most beautiful symphony.

“That’s not all.”

Hyun Sang, the head of martial arts, smiled and said,

“This Seven Sages Sword is the real thing. I will have to examine it more later, but there wasn’t a single error written in this book.”

“Oh oh!”

“It is also encouraging that the Falling Flower Sword is correct. Although it isn’t on the same level as the other ones, it is perfect for learning along with the Seven Sages Sword. It will serve as an intermediate step into the more advanced arts.”

“R-right.”

“The Bamboo Leaf Sword seems to be legitimate too.”

He was losing it.

Hyun Jong couldn’t keep up. If he spoke now, it would only make him look stupid.

“It’s an indescribable feeling; the Seven Sages Sword has fallen into our hands once again. In the past, it was practiced as the basis for all of Mount Hua’s martial arts. Finally, it will be like it was in the past.”

“It wasn’t like that for us, right?”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“This is the treasure of Mount Hua.”

The sect leader noticed that Hyun Sang had opened his mouth to say something and then closed it, but Hyun Jong didn’t miss it.

“Is there some problem?”

“N-No. it was nothing.”

“Is it about the martial arts?”

“Not at all. They are genuine. I can guarantee that.”

“I am glad.”

As the sect leader nodded, Hyun Sang spoke.

“Wasn’t it said that a third-class disciple found them?”

“Right. A child called Chung Myung joined recently.”

“He needs to be rewarded.”

“We should give him something. Thanks to that child, Mount Hua….”

“I didn’t mean that, sect leader.”

Hyun Yeong cut short Hyun Jong’s words.

“He is a child who just entered Mount Hua. How long has it been since we saw someone have such a heart for Mount Hua?”

“… right.”

“Even if that child didn’t know the value of the books, he would clearly recognize the value of the gold and jewels. If it were me, the moment the box was opened, I would have taken a few items and hid them somewhere else. If not, I would bury the box itself and hide it from others.”

There were horrible words. But what Hyun Yeong said was the truth.

“Right. I didn’t think of that.”

“A unique child, truly strange and unique. That’s a wealth that could shake the heart of any man in Mount Hua. If I had seen it, I wouldn’t have spoken about it right away….”

“I’ll remember that.”

“… S-sect leader?”

Hyun Yeong was a bit flustered, to which Hyun Jong said.

“It is wonderful. But Mount Hua got a blessing.”

Hyun Jong smiled.

Although it was a coincidence, he was really thankful that this box was discovered at the right moment. He thought that changing his mind and bringing in the beggar was the right decision as it was going to save Mount Hua.

“Hyun Yeong.”

“Yes. Sect leader”

“Are the ledgers real?”

“I will put my neck on the line.”

“I see, then there are people we need to call right away.”

Hyun Jong’s eyes were serious.

Now was the time to punish those who tried to aim their arrows at Mount Hua.

“All those involved, bring them to Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong, the sect leader, was finally able to stand tall.

Chapter 29: Mount Hua gains a fortune (4)

“Oh my, this is tough.”

Yu Jong-San, clearly suffering, groaned aloud.

The mountain leading up to Mount Hua was so steep that even people living in the village below couldn’t climb it with ease.

Fortunately, they had escorts to help them climb the mountain; but ordinary people wouldn’t dare it.

The fact that they were climbing the mountain again less than a week after their last trek was making him uncomfortable both physically and mentally.

“Ugh.”

“Owner Yu. Be strong!”

“I am trying to be strong!”

Yu Jong-San was annoyed. Despite the escorts encouraging him, he struggled greatly to climb each step. He was being asked to climb a sheer cliff, which no ordinary person could pass through, by relying on a worn-out old rope. This was why Mount Hua didn’t develop!

‘Once I get the money back, I will never come to this place again.’

Because he didn’t want to see Mount Hua ever again.

As they climbed the cliff, a smooth and flat area greeted them. Owner Kong, who confirmed that everyone had come up, opened his mouth.

“We will take a break here.”

“Oh my. Owner Kong. That’s a good idea. My legs are shaking….”

“Owner Yu needs to work out more often.”

“Huhuhu. I am no stranger to exercise, but I don’t think my body will ever get used to climbing this mountain.”

“It isn’t that bad.”

Owner Yu shook his head and sat down on a rock.

“But owner Kong.”

Owner Pang approached Owner Kong.

“What is it?”

“Why is the sect leader suddenly asking us to come to Mount Hua?”

Those who were rubbing their aching legs all turned their focus toward the man.

“Maybe he came up with some money?”

Owner Kong smiled softly.

“Is that possible? One hundred thousand isn’t a small amount.”

Owner Kong spoke bluntly.

“But if it is borrowed….”

“There is no one in the world who would willingly lend a hundred thousand to a dying sect. A person with such a kind heart could never become rich.”

“Surely…”

Yu Jong-San shrugged his shoulders.

“Then what does Owner Kong think? Why do you think the sect leader has called us?”

“To give up.”

“Give up?”

Owner Kong looked at the summit, where Mount Hua stood.

“Likely, he must have tried to reach out for assistance and been denied at every turn. It would be distasteful to drag out the suffering until the last moment, so he called us ahead of time to concede.”

“Huh.”

Yu Jong-San clicked his tongue at it.

“This is the first time I’ve heard of someone calling their debt collectors to their door, without anything to pay, just to get rid of them more quickly. What a stiff debtor.”

“Well, he is in a difficult situation because of the debt. Still, he is the sect leader of Mount Hua; don’t speak too rashly about him.”

“Owner Kong is such a kindhearted person. How can you think so well about someone who borrowed money and hasn’t paid it back for decades?”

Owner Kong smiled.

“What I meant was for us to keep our manners. The name of Mount Hua will soon disappear; why make it more painful for them than it needs to be?”

“The whole world should know of Owner Kong’s benevolence.”

“We have such different attitudes.”

“It was nothing.”

Seeing that, Yu Jong-San clicked his tongue and thought to himself.

‘Spouting pleasantries while sitting around doing nothing.’

They were planning to confiscate the sect and kick them out of their homes; who would care about your courtesy?

‘But…’

Yu Jong-San looked at the summit.

‘Will we really get the money?’

He was always worried whether the sect would be sold for a reasonable price. Indeed Owner Kong spoke quite confidently, but any merchant would be worried when money was on the line.

But Yu Jong-San wasn’t worried about that.

‘If a member of the Southern Edge sect came here, doesn’t that mean they are interested in this?’

In the past, the entire world knew what kind of relationship existed between Mount Hua and the Southern Edge sect.

It was now a faded story since Mount Hua’s name vanished and the Southern Edge Sect ascended too high up for the others to reach.

However, the Southern Edge Sect leaders would certainly remember their rivalry with Mount Hua, right? If they continued to hold onto their resentment, then it was evident that they wouldn’t want even a fragment of Mount Hua to remain in the world.

‘Owner Kong must be thinking of selling it to the Southern Edge sect.’

Out of the total debt of 100,000 nyang, Yu Jong-San was due to receive 5,000 nyang.

How much was 5,000 nyang? Even if the money was squandered and spent frivolously, it was an enormous sum that would still be enough to leave for the next generation to live comfortably.

The long tug-of-war is finally coming to an end. Yu Jong-San’s heart began to flutter at the thought of finally getting his hands on such wealth.

‘I wonder what the sect leader’s face would look like.’

The thought of seeing that old man’s solemn face being distorted made Yu Jong-San feel a bit bitter, but he quickly suppressed the rising feelings of sympathy. After all, isn’t it true that there are no friends or family when it comes to matters of money?

“Let’s start climbing now.”

“Yes.”

All of them got up with a push, despite having a hard time, they didn’t say anything.

With their eyes blinded by money, they started to climb again.

“Each time I see it, it feels strange.”

Someone in the crowd voiced their thoughts.

“It’s just a building barely holding itself together.”

A sense of reluctance could be heard in the voice.

Falling buildings and walls and the front gate where the door had been broken through already.

An obviously ruined sect appeared before them, either destroyed by someone else or neglected for years due to bankruptcy. Still, something was captivating about it.

The weight of Mount Hua protected the Shaanxi for years.

Despite not saying a word, they all shared similar feelings.

Now, they were here to suffocate Mount Hua’s final breath. Today, the sect leader was going to finally give in.

Mount Hua, which protected this land for hundreds of years, was finally coming to an end.

“Khuem!”

“Uhm!”

Did everyone feel the weight of their actions? Everyone coughed in silence.

They had no intention of turning away from so much money, but still, they were people born in Hua-Um village. So, they couldn’t help but feel bad that they were killing their guardians with their own hands.

“Let’s go in.”

Only owner Kong seemed fine. When he took the lead, everyone hesitated and then followed him.

“Is everyone here?”

As they entered, Un Am greeted them.

“Elder Un Am. Nice to see you.”

“I am still not good enough to be called an elder. Please, just call me Un Am.”

“As you wish.”

Un Am smiled and spoke.

“The sect leader is waiting. This way.”

“Hm.”

Owner Kong frowned.

‘Are they able to pay it back?’

When they arrived the other day, the others stopped them. But now, they were asking them to come in with casual expressions.

Even if the sect leader had informed them that these merchants would come, wasn’t it strange how much their attitude had changed?

Owner Kong looked cautiously at Un Am’s back and followed behind him.

‘We’ll know soon enough. Maybe this is the true nature of Mount Hua.’

Perhaps, they acknowledged their fate and decided to meet the end in peace. Rather than look like cowards begging for more time, they’ve chosen to die standing with their heads held high.

‘I feel worried.’

Perhaps, it was because the moment he had waited so long for was finally coming true. Ordinary people tend to let their guard down as soon as their goal is within sight, but Kong Mun-Yeon is a shrewd man who becomes more nervous at these times.

As they quietly walked, they reached the residence of the sect leader. Standing in front of it was Hyun Jong waiting for them.

“We greet the sect leader.”

When owner Kong issued his greetings, the others followed.

It was the last step; he wanted to be as polite as possible.

“Welcome. You must have gone through a lot while coming up here.”

Hyun Jong smiled softly and greeted everyone.

“I am sorry to take your time. I hope you understand that I had to ask you to come up here instead of me coming down to meet you all.”

“It’s no issue at all. We are busy but not busier than the sect leader. So, it is obvious that we should come.”

Owner Kong responded with a smile.

“Rather than that, what…?”

“Haha. Such a hurry? You must have had a hard time climbing the mountain, so maybe a cup of tea—”

“Sect leader.”

Owner Kong cut the sect leader’s words off with a resolute tone.

“It is good to have a cup of tea and talk. But we are merchants, so we would like to discuss the business affairs first.”

“Hmm.”

“We merchants are people who deal with problems first and then eat or drink later. I hope the sect leader understands that.”

“Of course. I see I was only thinking of myself.”

Hyun Jong smiled and then said.

“Then, let’s get to the point without wasting time.”

“Thank you.”

Owner Kong smiled.

“I have brought you all here today to convey the position of Mount Hua.”

“Position of Mount Hua?”

Hyun Jong looked at Owner Kong.

Owner Kong was already playing out the situation in his head.

“I have tried every method available, but I haven’t been able to find anyone willing to lend money to Mount Hua. In other words, it doesn’t seem like I can repay the money within the given date.”

“Hmm.”

Owner Kong frowned at those words.

“Sect leader. We have given you enough time. We also need to earn enough to make a living. We can’t extend your deadline any further.”

“Which is why I am saying this.”

Hyun Jong made eye contact with each person.

“I know that it cannot be delayed any longer. But it is impossible for Mount Hua to make the full payment before the due date. Please understand.”

Hyun Jong bowed.

“I can’t pay back all of that money, but I can pay a portion of it. So, if anyone here would be fine with personally delaying their repayment date, it would help us greatly.

As the sect leader lowered his head toward them, everyone was shocked and embarrassed.

A strange atmosphere began to flow amidst the crowd.

Chapter 30: Mount Hua gains a fortune (5)

“Hmm?”

Chung Myung, resting on the eaves of a building from a distance, seemed to be enjoying himself as he spied on the sect leader and merchants.

“So, that’s how he plans on attacking?”

Chung Myung’s eyes, which looked at the sect leader, gleamed.

He didn’t know.

Was the sect leader seeking to push them into the hellfire, or was he giving them one last chance at redemption?

It could be interpreted either way.

However, one thing was certain, Hyun Jong, the sect leader of Mount Hua, wasn’t as simple of a man as he seemed.

‘This is how it should be.’

Didn’t he see it?

The figure of the sect leader, hunched over and trembling in sadness within the dark corridor, clinging to the door he couldn’t open.

He was the one who maintained Mount Hua, even as the burden grew, and the pain tore away at him from the inside out. He carried the collapsed sect on his fragile back without sacrificing his gentleness or dignity.

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

‘But that shouldn’t be all.’

He proved his patience. However, that wasn’t the only trait a sect leader should possess.

Of course, that is important too. But Mount Hua… no, there are certain qualities essential to being a successful sect leader in any force.

‘To remain cool-headed and composed.’

That is how a sect leader needs to be.

Although a sect is where martial artists are born, the essence of discipline is remaining calm and keeping a cool head.

Regardless of their original personality, a sect leader must have this trait. For the sake of Mount Hua, you must be able to trust your decisions with all of your mind and body, making decisions while rationally thinking out your course of action.

So, did Hyun Jong have the heart of a sect leader?

Chung Myung, lying down, rested his chin on his hands and slightly raised his body.

Crack!

The sound of bones breaking in his back.

“Ack…”

He immediately grabbed at his waist and fell back down to his original position.

‘I am going to die.’

There wasn’t a single part in his body that felt fine, probably because his body wasn’t trained properly. Even though he was constantly practicing, his body wasn’t recovering quickly enough.

He had calculated that it would be possible to restore his body in a month or two, but the problem was that he would have to endure this pain for those months. He resurrected into the body of a young, weak child and was constantly exhausted to the point of dying, and now he couldn’t even lift his body.

“Ugh… I need to do something about this.”

Chung Myung took a deep breath and shook his head.

His body’s condition could be dealt with later; first, he had to see how this situation resolved itself.

“Did you ask us to delay your repayment?”

Owner Kong frowned subtly.

This was something he didn’t expect. He never underestimated the power of Mount Hua. Dozens of sects emerge and disappear every day. So, he knew that a sect running for a hundred years wouldn’t be an easy target.

Although the situation wasn’t good for Mount Hua, it was still a sect with a long history.

But…

‘Is this all that is left of them?’

He wanted to laugh.

‘Did I overestimate Mount Hua?’

If they had potential, they wouldn’t have arrived at such a desperate situation at all.

“Sect leader. I clearly told you before that there is no way we can delay the payment any longer.”

“Don’t get me wrong. I am not asking owner Kong right now.”

“… huh?”

Hyun Jong looked at owner Kong and spoke.

“I am well aware of Hua-Um’s position. This is why I am asking all of you directly now. Even if it’s 100,000 nyang, doesn’t each of you have a different amount to receive?”

“That is true.”

“So, I am personally asking if there is anyone fine with being paid at a later time.”

Owner Kong frowned.

He didn’t understand what the man meant.

“So, you’re saying you can pay back those who can’t afford to delay any longer?”

“That’s right.”

“Sorry?”

Owner Kong’s eyes widened.

“Even if Mount Hua isn’t what it used to be, there are still those who are willing to help us. We didn’t get the whole 100,000 nyang, but we might be able to pay back a few of you. With your help, Mount Hua won’t lose its name. So, please. To those who will show mercy in Mount Hua’s current situation, in the name of Mount Hua, I will surely repay you.”

Sect leader swore again, but he had a confident expression now.

Seeing that, Owner Kong had a bitter face.

“What nonsense—”

“So.”

At that moment, Yu Jong-San, who was watching from the side, cut off Owner Kong’s words. It wasn’t intentional, but Owner Kong stopped talking and frowned.

“So, if we delay the payment date, we will still get the money?”

“Yes.”

“Sect leader, let’s be honest now.”

Yu Jong-San continued.

“We all know that Mount Hua may very well collapse tomorrow; the sect’s condition isn’t a secret, nor is it unknown to any of us, even the sect leader should understand. If we trust what you said and postpone the repayment date, doesn’t that mean there is also the risk of your sect collapsing and us receiving nothing?”

“… that is right.”

“Does that make any sense?”

Owner Kong calmed himself. It was true that Yu Jong-San cut his words off, but he was doing a fine job of cornering the old man.

Normally, owner Kong would have soothed the situation, but he didn’t do it this time. He wanted to push the sect leader a little farther.

‘It is finally done.’

Mount Hua’s long history is coming to an end.

It may seem bitter that the once-great Mount Hua sect has ultimately been crushed by the power of money, but it was more meaningful for Owner Kong who had much to gain through this.

“Owner Yu.”

“Yes. Sect leader.”

“What should I offer you?”

“… huh?”

Hyun Jong shrugged. A calm wind blew in from somewhere, and he smiled.

“There is nothing left of Mount Hua. Now, all that remains of Mount Hua is the honor of supporting Hua-Um down below for many years. All that I have to offer is Mount Hua’s name.”

“That…”

“If you ask about the risk and what to trust, then this is my answer. The name of Mount Hua. The history of Mount Hua. Wouldn’t that be enough?”

Yu Jong-San went silent.

The name of Mount Hua.

History of Mount Hua.

Right. Such meaningful words. But the people gathered here were merchants. Merchants had no reason to care about name or history, only money. Would it make money or lose money?

But to ask merchants to give him time by offering their name and history as collateral?

“Haha.”

Yu Jong-San couldn’t stop his laugh.

“Sect leader, aren’t you being too stubborn?”

“Was it too much to ask?”

Hyun Jong just asked quietly. At the heavy emotions held within his eyes, Yu Jong-San stopped laughing.

“It could be too much.”

But unlike his serious and heavy eyes, the voice which came out of his mouth was soft.

“But I would like to ask for at least this much. I believe in the name of Mount Hua, which has been protecting Shaanxi and the Hua-Um village for hundreds of years, and I know it hasn’t been in vain.”

“…”

“Let me ask the other way around. What does Mount Hua mean to you? Do you feel that there is no real value in the name or history of Mount Hua?”

No one could answer it.

Mount Hua.

Who would dare call the name lightly? Who would dare say its history was meaningless?

Now, only a few traces of the past remained, but no one would take the name so lightly. Moreover, it will be even more so for those who lived their lives at the foot of Mount Hua.

So, no one was willing to continue the conversation except for one person.

“I feel that our discussion has drifted a bit off-topic.”

Owner Kong spoke. He looked at Hyun Jong. Unlike Hyun Jong’s eyes, his eyes were sharp.

“In summary, those who wish to personally delay the payment date will be repaid later, and those who don’t will receive payment now.”

“Yes.”

“Good.”

Owner Kong nodded.

“Ordinarily, this is something that should be opposed in the name of Hua-Um Merchants Association, but I am a man with a sense of propriety, so I will allow it. Anyone who wishes to do so may personally delay their repayment. But!”

He looked back and spoke.

“You must take responsibility for your own actions. The Merchants Association will not provide any help or protection to those who delay the reimbursement date. Even if they lose their money.”

A subtle pressure.

“You may choose. Those who will be paid now stand here, and those who are fine with delayed payment, go over there.”

Owner Kong pointed to the other side.

“Is that all? Sect leader?”

“Yes.”

“Although I disagree, I shall respect the sect leader’s thoughts until the end. Although Mount Hua doesn’t have much time left, it is still worthy of at least this much respect.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“Thank you for this.”

Owner Kong frowned without realizing it. Despite his provocation, Hyun Jong didn’t change.

‘I’ll break that composure of yours.’

Owner Kong, who thought that, said.

“How is it? Unfortunately, there doesn’t seem to be anyone who can delay their repayment?”

“…”

“See.”

Owner Kong pointed behind himself. Hyun Jong looked to see the merchants. All those who met Hyun Jong’s eyes turned their heads and looked down to avoid his gaze.

“Do you need more time?”

Hyun Jong didn’t answer and closed his eyes.

“No matter how long you wait, nothing will change. No one will give up so much money because of the name of Mount Hua, which faded long ago. So, let’s stop this sect leader. Step down now. you have done enough.”

Owner Kong was intoxicated with the sense of victory.

“Now, with this….”

“Tch.”

It was at that moment.

He could hear footsteps behind him. Unknowingly, he turned back and looked.

“… Owner Yu?”

Yu Jong-San was walking to the other side with a sour expression.

He placed himself alone in the area designated for those fine with receiving delayed payments.

“What the hell….”

Seeing the absurd expression on Owner Kong, Yu Jong-San sighed.

“… look here. Owner Yu. What are you thinking!”

Kong Mun-Yeon’s furious bellow spread sharply in all directions.

Chapter 31: You bastard!? Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (1)

“Why?”

“Don’t look at me with that face. I know that what I’m doing is foolish.”

Yu Jong-San waved his hands as if he was annoyed.

“Then why?”

“Look here, owner Kong.”

“…”

“You aren’t from Hua-Um.”

Owner Kong’s face went blank.

What now?

“You arrived later and are the son-in-law of the man who owned the pavilion previously. You don’t understand what Mount Hua means to those who were raised in Hua-Um.”

“No!”

Owner Kong yelled.

What is this new shit? Why does it matter if he wasn’t born in Hua-Um?

“Look here, owner Yu.”

“Ahh. Enough. I already know what you will say.”

Yu Jong-San took a deep breath.

“I know that in a world where everything is money, even Hua-Um is for sale.”

Owner Kong looked at the man with a puzzled face. He wondered what would be said next.

“But I am a person of Hua-Um.”

“… and what does that have to do with this?”

“Those who are born and raised here grow up listening to the legends and tales of Mount Hua. We are raised being told that we must enter Mount Hua and become great martial arts masters, our names echoing across the world. It is still revered even for those of us who lack talent and can never enter. That’s how great Mount Hua was, and we grew up listening to those legends and how they protected not just the world but us as well.”

Owner Kong tilted his head. Where did this nonsense suddenly come from?

“It isn’t just me. My father and my grandfather also grew up like that. Mount Hua is the pride of Shaanxi and of Hua-Um. And…”

Yu Jong-San scratched his head and spoke.

“Not for me, but it was a source of pride for my father and grandfather.”

“… so, what do you mean?”

“But what does it make me if I am willing to destroy Mount Hua for the simple sake of money? When I enter the afterlife, will my father leave me in peace? I will be beaten for days and days like when I was a child.”

A low laugh broke out.

When Owner Kong turned his face, the laughter died down, and the others lowered their heads.

“So? For these sentiments, you are giving up a fortune?”

“Giving up what? Didn’t you hear the sect leader say he would give it back later?”

“And you believe that?”

“There is no reason not to believe. What are we going to do with that money anyway?”

Yu Jong-San spat on the floor.

“A person like you will take the money and move away. There will be plenty of ways to spend that money; if you go to places like Hangzhou, then you’ll be able to play around without any worries. But I’ve spent my whole life in Hua-Um, where will I go with the money I earn? Should I spend it all on alcohol? That’s not very fun for me.”

Yu Jong-San smiled.

It wasn’t a funny situation. He climbed the mountain enamored at the thought of receiving a large fortune. He was exhausted and wanted his money, but what was he saying now?

‘Maybe I’ve gone mad.’

He would never do this in his right mind. Yu Jong-San knew that.

But…

“You will regret it.”

“Of course, I’ll regret it. Damn it! Do you think I am saying this because I don’t know I will regret it? I know better than you! Of course, I’ll regret it!”

Yu Jong-San shouted.

“But it would be far more unpleasant to ruin Mount Hua with my own hands!”

Owner Kong looked at Yu Jong-San, confused.

The man was taking deep breaths as he got too excited.

“Look here, owner Kong. I can make enough money to provide for myself. If I protect Mount Hua now, I may get my money back later. Then I can take it and live a decent life as always. But if Mount Hua is destroyed, I will have to live in regret each day, and every time I see my money, I will be reminded of what I had done. I don’t want to live like that.”

Owner Kong clenched his teeth.

‘Has he lost his mind?’

He couldn’t understand what this man was talking about. But…

‘There is no need to understand.’

Why should he stop a man who was walking down a pit of fire with his own feet? Just one person changing his mind wouldn’t change the situation.

“Do whatever you want to. It won’t change anything if you do it alone.”

“Who said he was alone?”

Owner Kong turned his head at it.

“Owner Seo!”

Seo Mun-Jong walked up and stood next to Yu Jong-San.

“What are you doing?”

“Can’t you see?”

Owner Kong frowned.

But it wasn’t just that one man. Perhaps the words of Yu Jong-San were the trigger; five of the twenty people stood next to him.

“Oh, my god.”

Owner Kong shook his head.

‘When have I ever seen such pathetic people?’

How could people who claim to be merchants make such stupid choices?

‘No. No.’

Owner Kong controlled his expression.

‘If it wasn’t for Mount Hua, they would have never made such a choice. I suppose that’s how truly absolute their influence is here.“

If you’re swayed so easily by your emotions, you won’t be able to make the right judgments. Disrespecting the opponent was something a merchant should never do. It was the right time to think about the potential of Mount Hua, which was being displayed right now.

Owner Kong looked at the people who went to the other side. Everyone was showing signs of regret, yet they looked oddly refreshed.

‘Stupid people.’

Are they proud of not abandoning the sect till the very end?

This is only meaningful while Mount Hua exists. Even if the payment is postponed, Mount Hua won’t be able to afford to pay the rest of the merchants. They’ve lost out on a fortune due to a moment’s misjudgment.

Owner Kong decided that and asked.

“Is there anyone else who thinks otherwise?”

The others looked at Hyun Jong and then shook their heads.

“Sect leader.”

“…”

Owner Kong smiled.

“I didn’t realize that the name of Mount Hua was still so great. But that is all. The rest of us have no intention of delaying the payment date, so return to us the money we lent you.”

Hyun Jong smiled. His eyes weren’t looking at Owner Kong but the ones behind him.

“Is there really no one else here willing to help us?”

“…”

When there was no answer, Hyun Jong nodded.

“Then, it is unavoidable.”

“Sect leader.”

“Don’t rush. Owner Kong.”

Kong Mun-Yeong flinched.

Hyun Jong’s voice was soft, but there was a force he couldn’t resist.

Hyun Jong looked around at the merchants with Yu Jong-San, who smiled brightly.

“Still, it is enough that there are a few people who would side with Mount Hua. Doesn’t that mean that the world hasn’t yet abandoned Mount Hua?”

Owner Kong couldn’t say anything, and Hyun Jong loudly called.

“Un Am!”

“Yes. Sect leader!”

“Bring it!”

“Yes.”

Un Am bowed his head and walked off quickly. Seeing that, owner Kong frowned.

‘Does he really have it?’

It couldn’t be.

Just because owner Kong had tricks up his sleeve, that didn’t mean the sect leader could do the same and receive a strong backing. If there was, the information would have certainly entered his ears.

Was it a bluff?

No, that didn’t make sense either. You can only bluff when something is in the background to fall back on; the current Mount Hua couldn’t afford such a dangerous bluff.

Un Am returned before owner Kong could finish organizing his thoughts. He went alone but now came back with three people.

‘A box?’

The people seemed to be of the same age as Un Am, which meant they were elders. One of them was bringing a large box.

“Sect leader. We brought it.”

Hyun Jong pointed ahead.

“Put it down

“Yes.”

Tak!

The box was placed on the floor.

Owner Kong looked down at the chest, then back up and asked.

“This…?”

“There is a fortune in that box, check for yourself.”

“…fortune?”

“Yes.”

Owner Kong looked at the box with suspicious eyes.

‘I don’t think he is playing with me.’

The Hyun Jong that he knew wasn’t a sly man who would joke in this situation. So, was there money in this box?

Various thoughts came to his mind, but now wasn’t the time to think. A box of money was right in front of him, so why bother thinking about it?

Owner Kong approached the box as if possessed. And slowly opened the lid.

He narrowed his eyes and checked what was inside.

“This is…”

Riches?

Were the riches these books?

“Sect leader? Are you messing with us right now?”

“Would I do such a thing? I am sure I have what you wanted.”

“What we wanted?”

“You will know once you read it.”

Owner Kong calmed his emotions and pulled out one of the books. He then began to read the contents in it.

Flap!

Flap!

The sound of pages being turned at a rapid pace. His face gradually crumpled and changed various shades of color as each page was turned.

“T–this…”

Owner Kong’s face completely changed, so the merchants behind him slowly approached.

“What is that?”

“Let us see it too.”

“…”

When he didn’t answer, they glanced at the box. After confirming that several books were inside, they too reached out for them.

“What is this…?”

Each one who checked the contents grew nervous and soon became suspicious.

“Aren’t these ledgers?”

“Yes.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“It looks like old ledgers, so why are you bringing it out now…?”

Hyun Jong smiled.

“The ledgers you are looking at now were created by Mount Hua for the management of our businesses.”

“… huh? What?”

Hyun Jong narrowed his eyes.

“Owner Kong. Did you check it?”

“…”

Hyun Jong’s voice resounded clearly.

“These ledgers contain information proving that the ownership of the Hua-Um businesses which you are running belongs to Mount Hua.”

“Huh?”

“Ah, no. What do you mean? Sect leader?”

“Silence!”

Hyun Jong firmly cut off their words. And he opened his mouth to those who hadn’t come to their senses.

“Mount Hua has been so kind to you. But to think that you would repay our kindness like this. No matter how good Mount Hua is, we aren’t the kind to show kindness to rats who bite their own masters.”

Hyun Jong spoke out sharply.

“Therefore, based on these ledgers, Mount Hua will confiscate not only the businesses you have but also the property that you have accumulated under the name of the business.”

A bolt of lightning cracked through the dry sky, quickly crushing down their dreams.

Chapter 32: You bastard!? Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (2)

No one was able to speak.

It was because of the declaration which came out of Hyun Jong’s mouth. Those who understood what it meant couldn’t speak, and those who had yet to grasp the situation couldn’t open their mouths in such a heavy atmosphere.

“S-sect leader!”

“W-what are you saying? Sect leader?”

A commotion broke out.

The merchants screamed until their faces turned red, but Hyun Jong didn’t change his expression. A cold expression they had never seen from him was looking down on the merchants.

“It is as I said.”

“B-But…!”

“We don’t understand what is happening….”

It was then.

“Silence!”

Owner Kong said in a cold voice, which froze the heated crowd where they stood.

Hyun Jong and Kong Mun-Yeon locked eyes as electricity seemed to crackle between them.

“Tell Me. Owner Kong.”

The attitude had not changed, but something more had. Hyun Jong was no longer the weak pushover pretending to remain calm; even Owner Kong felt stifled at the sect leader’s change.

“This joke has gone too far.”

“A joke, you say?”

“Right.”

Their eyes stayed locked together, each trying to overwhelm the other. Hyun Jong typically would have softened his gaze, but he didn’t back down at this moment.

“I am sorry, but the sect leader of the great Mount Hua doesn’t joke.”

Hearing that, owner Kong spoke.

“Certainly, according to the ledgers, most of the businesses of the Hua-Um merchants come under Mount Hua, and if it was true that the businesses were taken over, then you can surely confiscate them.”

“You’re well aware of the situation.”

“But.”

Owner Kong smiled. But this was a different smile. It was as if he was trying to fake it.

“Isn’t that only if the ledger is legitimate?”

Hyun Jong kept staring without saying a word. And Owner Kong continued.

“How can you prove if these books which sprouted up out of nowhere are genuine?”

“What, you…”

Hyun Jong narrowed his eyes.

“Are you saying that Mount Hua faked these documents?”

“Mount Hua would never do such a thing.”

Owner Kong took a step back.

“But couldn’t Mount Hua be deceived by some charlatan? We can’t trust them unless they are verified.”

“Right!”

“That is common sense!”

The other merchants yelled.

Hyun Jong, who watched them, nodded slowly and then looked at Hyun Yeong.

“Finance head.”

“Yes–sect leader!”

“What do you think?”

“There is truth to their words.”

Hyun Yeong answered without a change in his expression, which delighted the merchants.

“What should we do?”

“Sect leader, the focus of this discussion is wrong.”

“Hm?”

Hyun Yeong smiled.

“It isn’t our business to determine if the ledgers are genuine or not. In such cases, isn’t it the government which makes such determinations?”

“Right.”

Hyun Yeong continued to speak.

“That’s why half of the books were already entrusted to the officials in Hua-Um to check their authenticity. If the books get verified, the officials will go and confiscate their businesses.”

Owner Kong’s eyes widened at that.

“Y-You already gave them?”

“Right. Why? Is something wrong?”

Hyun Yeong’s casual words made owner Kong feel like he’d fallen into a frozen lake. A cold sweat began to trickle down his back.

‘Damn it!’

If he was in Hua-Um, he could have done something, but they were now on Mount Hua, and in their absence, the officials could rush in and take over their workplace. He had no way of dealing with them while away.

‘That bastard!’

Owner Kong glared at Hyun Jong.

Hyun Jong had planned this from the beginning and gathered them here; showing the ledgers directly to the merchants simply delayed the time. Everything was going according to what he wanted.

“When did you leave the ledgers to the officials?”

“Around two days ago.”

“…. Two.”

Owner Kong gnashed his teeth.

Two days was more than enough to verify the ledgers. It was said that half of them were given to the officials, but they would certainly want to validate all of them. It was clear, the ledgers currently in the box must have already been validated.

In other words, at the bottom of Mount Hua, officials were checking the authenticity of the ledgers and were preparing to confiscate the businesses.

Mount Hua helped protect the world for generations. If the Sect leader himself requests something by utilizing the sect’s connections, isn’t it obvious how fast things would happen down there?

Perhaps there was already a commotion down there.

“Sect leader!”

Owner Kong yelled in an angry voice.

However, Hyun Jong was no longer the generous person he was a few days ago.

“Keep your voice down.”

Hyun Jong’s whole body was giving out a strong force. Even Owner Kong, who was rarely surprised, ended up bowing to him.

The name of Mount Hua.

The energy now raging from this man showed the worth of that name.

“You have no right to speak.”

Hyun Jong stared at the merchants with cold eyes. Some, unable to overcome the pressure, lowered their heads.

“A true friend is one who reaches out when things are difficult. There is no need to show kindness to those who held a sword to our throats during trying times. Go back. By the time you return, everything will already be over….”

Hyun Jong sighed.

“It is impossible to ignore how you have treated us, yet I will give permission to each of you to take a single cartload of your wealth.”

“Se–sect leader.”

They couldn’t understand just how things got to this point.

“I have shown you the greatest favor I could.”

At that time, Hyun Yeong spoke.

“Sect leader, these are the people who desecrated Mount Hua and siphoned off its wealth. Not just that, they tried to take our very foundation despite all we’ve done for them. To show favor to such people….”

“If we let go of an animal which was about to bite us, it will turn into a beast and devour us.”

Hyun Jong waved his hand at that.

“I’ve already made my decision, so we won’t be talking about this.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Hyun Yeong lowered his head.

“Go down. Shouldn’t you see with your own eyes how things are going?”

Owner Kong’s face distorted. Gritting his teeth, he glared at Hyun Jong as if he wished to kill him.

“Sect leader. You’ve been hiding such a poisonous heart behind that amiable facade.”

“Poisonous heart…”

Hyun Jong smiled.

“Sure, call it a poisoned heart. But I feel that I pale in comparison to you.”

“… I will not forget this debt.”

“Right. Un Am. Guide them out.”

“Yes. Sect leader!”

Owner Kong turned around. And without waiting for Un Am, he started walking. The merchants, who didn’t know what to do, looked at the sect leader and hurriedly began to follow owner Kong. They had to go down and check what was happening.

Hyun Jong sighed as he looked at the people moving.

“Sect leader! You worked hard!

“Hm…”

Hyun Jeong smiled at Hyun Yeong.

“Now Mount Hua is finally free. It is good!”

“Don’t relax too much. We’ve only crossed one mountain now.”

“Will there be a greater mountain than this? Now everything is set.”

Hyun Jong smiled brightly, seeing Hyun Yeong, who wasn’t sure what to do, get lost in the excitement.

It had been ages since he had last seen the head of finance so happy. Everyone in Mount Hua was carrying a heavy load on their shoulders.

‘All thanks to that child.’

It could be said that this was a prosperous time for Mount Hua.

A reward should be given, but what kind of reward should he give to the one who made this happen? He smiled.

Hyun Jong, who thought that, turned his head to Yu Jong-San and the others.

“And….”

They immediately bowed to Hyun Jong.

“Even in these difficult times, you kept our grace in your hearts.”

Hyun Jong’s attitude was different from when he dealt with the other merchants. It was soft.

“Sect leader. What will happen to us?”

“It doesn’t change that your business belongs to Mount Hua. And things of Mount Hua should be returned to us. But I will ensure that you continue to handle the business and receive payment.”

“…”

Yu Jong-San’s face calmed.

This situation was better than those who were running down the mountain now, but they were losing their businesses all the same. Wouldn’t Yu Jong-San now be an employee and not the owner?

“Then….”

The moment Yu Jong-San tried to protest, Hyun Yeong opened his mouth.

“Excessive greed proceeds a downfall.”

“…”

“It is also a sin to try and oppress others with a business that isn’t yours. Mount Hua is just giving you a chance to lessen the weight of your sins.”

Sighs came out.

All of this had resulted from greed.

‘Grandfather. What have you done?’

He was flustered again.

“Finance head.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Isn’t it true that they didn’t betray the loyalty they had to Mount Hua and helped us at the last minute?”

“It is true.”

“Let’s discuss this together. There should be a good way. Shouldn’t Mount Hua be a warm place for their close friends?”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Hyun Yeong stepped forward and told the merchants.

“Come this way. Let us head in and discuss.”

“… yes.”

The merchants followed him with complex emotions.

As everyone moved, Hyun Jong remained in place alone.

He watched Mount Hua each day, but Mount Hua now seemed different to his eyes.

The barren and faded buildings seemed to be full of vitality.

‘Does one’s perception of life all depend on how the heart is feeling?’

No, everything doesn’t simply end like that.

Mount Hua, which was touched by tragedy, has received its first blessing in several decades. The flow of life is such a strange thing; once the direction of the flow changes, it isn’t easy to reverse it simply through your own efforts.

Now that a path for a better future was opened, Mount Hua will be different from before, which Hyun Jong believed.

Perhaps today is the trigger that will bring back the forgotten glory of Mount Hua.

‘It will.’

Hyun Jong’s face, full of wrinkles, had a deep smile.

“…You, you…”

In the distance, a wrinkle-free face crumpled and disfigured itself.

“That fucking bastard!”

Chung Myung’s eyes went wide with indignation.

What? What do you mean by a cart!?

What was that calm-looking man doing?

“Come on! I will show you what a beast is!”

Hyun Jong sent the merchants away.

But Chung Myung would not let them go so easily.

Chapter 33: You bastard!? Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (3)

“Sahyung! Great Sahyung!”

“What is it?”

“Did you hear?”

Yoon Jong smiled and asked.

“Hear what?”

“The rumors circulating around, haven’t you heard them?”

“I have ears, so there’s nothing I cannot hear.”

When Yoon Jong answered, Jo Gul said.

“The merchants of Hua-Um, who Mount Hua was indebted to, turned out to be Mount Hua’s representatives in the past. All their businesses belong to Mount Hua.”

“I see.”

“There’s a riot in Hua-Um. Officials are occupying and confiscating their property!”

“I heard about that too!”

“Oh my god! Why are you so calm? Haaa! This is why I shouldn’t talk to people who want to

become elders here!“

Jo Gul beat his chest as if he was frustrated.

“Is that such a big deal?”

“It is. It’s an amazing thing! Do you know how much money it will be if all the businesses are confiscated? Putting aside the wealth, just their businesses alone, we won’t have to worry about making ends meet in Mount Hua for generations.”

“So…?”

Yoon Jong looked at Jo Gul with a slightly renewed sense of vigor.

Yoon Jong was someone who was aiming to become a Taoist in Mount Hua. There seemed to be a difference between what he saw as essential and what Jo Gul considered a huge deal.

“This seems to be bigger than I thought.”

“Oh my, sahyung. Sahyung will one day have to lead Mount Hua, and it will be a disaster if you don’t have the money to run it.”

“Hm. I should keep this in mind.”

He heard the rumors, but he didn’t think too deeply about them. He merely thought that being able to avoid paying the debt was a blessing, but it seemed like there were much more profound implications for others.

So, a new question arose.

“But how did this happen so suddenly? Why did the sect leader endure such humiliation until now?”

“Th-that…”

“Huh?”

Jo Gul’s face became strangely complex.

“They said they found some old ledgers.”

“Ledgers?”

“Right. Ledgers related to the business of Mount Hua. They found it a few days ago, so they….”

Jo Gul seemed to trail off as he quietly ended it there. Seeing that Yoon Jong couldn’t understand, Jo Gul began again.

“Found a few days ago.”

“Huh?”

“The ledgers were found a few days ago. And the ledgers had to be some sort of book, right?”

“Right.”

Yoon Jong smiled bitterly.

“It is fortunate that we happened to see some books get discovered just a few days ago, right?”

“… yes.”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong couldn’t say anything more and exchanged subtle glances.

‘That box!’

‘There must have been books inside it!’

It was too perfect to be a coincidence. Besides, wasn’t the reaction of the sect leader who checked it too extreme?

“I really want to say, it couldn’t be, but….”

“I feel the same.”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong’s faces darkened a little.

“Besides, the reaction of that idiot before it happened was….”

“Honestly, it was too strange.”

–Ouch! What is this? Why is there a stone here!

–No! My god! This isn’t a stone! Why did someone bury this here? So weird? Hehehehe. Very weird.

–Should I dig? Is it fine if I dig*? Hahahaha. Hahaha.* What could be buried here? Such a strange thing. It couldn’t be a treasure.

Yoon Jong closed his eyes tightly.

‘If you want to deceive someone, at least act properly. Damn it.’

He couldn’t forget that awkward voice. Even a three-year-old would do better than him.

‘Ah, he is up to something.’

That was what anyone would have thought.

Soon after that crappy performance, the box was uncovered.…

“As expected?”

“Right?”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong turned serious.

“Where the hell did he find it?”

“… the more we want to know, the more we end up not knowing.”

“Yeah.”

Yoon Jong shook his head.

There were too many strange details. Even if he didn’t pay attention, everything seemed suspicious.

Nevertheless, Yoon Jong isn’t very wary of Chung Myung because his sincerity towards Mount Hua is evident.

This situation was no exception. Didn’t Mount Hua benefit from Chung Myung finding those ledgers?

“Anyway.…”

It was at that moment.

“Great Sahyung!”

A loud voice came from outside the room.

“What is going on?”

“Have you seen Chung Myung?”

“Why him?”

“Sect leader is looking for him, but we can’t seem to find him. He isn’t even in his room.”

“…. Hmm?”

Yoon Jong, who tried to remain calm, went stiff, and soon his expression turned dark.

“Not there?”

“Yes. We can’t find him anywhere.”

“N-No!”

Yoon Jong jumped up and started to run towards Chung Myung’s room.

He burst through the door, slamming it open, quickly scanning the room. He even inspected the closet.

“Great Sahyung! What’s wrong?”

Jo Gul, who was a step late, asked.

“… isn’t here.”

“Huh?”

“It’s missing.”

Yoon Jong pointed to the open closet. Resting peacefully inside the closet was Chung Myung’s uniform.

“What? Did he take off his uniform? Where—”

At that moment, Jo Gul’s eyes widened.

The uniform was taken off and placed in the closet. Then the clothes which were missing were.

“D-don’t tell me!”

The black clothes which Jo Gul brought to him previously were missing.

Yoon Jong’s face contorted.

“Again… he is up to something again.”

“…”

The two of them really couldn’t tell if Chung Myung was a boon for Mount Hua or a bane.

“Huh….”

A group of men stood looking at their carts with a bewildered face. The carts contained a fraction of the wealth they had gathered.

Each one was filled with wealth to help them survive. For someone with no money, it would be a startling amount. But for those here, looking at this wealth left them with an indescribable feeling as they recalled memories of what led to their current state.

“In one day….”

Like being struck by a bolt of lightning from a cloudless blue sky

As soon as they scurried down from Mount Hua, they saw their workplaces already occupied by government officials. They were armed and surrounded their businesses with the official order to confiscate everything.

They only heard shouts from the officials ordering their men to confiscate their things.

‘What the hell is going on?’

Then, were the ledgers real?

It was shocking and seemed unfair. Who would have thought that the businesses being run for generations belonged to Mount Hua? Since it was operated by their fathers, they thought it was theirs.

But in one day, it was taken away, and they were kicked out of Hua-Um. Where else in the world could there be such an unfair situation?

Every merchant gathered wore the same dark expression.

When they saw one another dragging their carts, their hearts began to break as they looked truly destitute.

“… what the hell is this?”

“This is beyond words.”

Sighs emerged from all over.

They were exiled, but since Mount Hua informed the officials to let them take a cart full of belongings, they were given some time to gather everything. Even if they wanted food, they had to leave Hua-Um and buy it elsewhere.

“A-are we to leave like this?”

“What more can we do?”

“Protest…”

“Protest?”

The owner of Plum Blossom Inn, Jin Yi-San, looked at Jo Geum-Myeong in anger.

“Are you saying that even after watching what just happened in front of our eyes? We are the thieves! Thieves! If the sect leader hadn’t shown mercy to us, we wouldn’t have even had the chance to leave; we would have been imprisoned! How do you intend to argue their proof!?”

A few people sighed, and their shoulders drooped.

“Damn it!”

Jin Yi-San turned.

“I am leaving!”

“A-already?”

“Didn’t you hear that we would be imprisoned if we didn’t leave within an hour!? We need to get out of here first!”

In the end, they all nodded helplessly. Those who watched him slowly followed.

After traveling for some time, they were able to get out of Hua-Um with their carts. They briefly pulled their cats into the shade beneath some trees to rest.

“… for this to happen.”

“The officials who were monitoring behind us have returned too. Maybe we can get a moment of peace now.”

“Peace?”

“What should we do next?”

As they got past one issue, other problems began to come into sight.

A few of the men looked at Kong Mun-Yeong. Seeing that he hadn’t said a single word, they were tempted to make the man speak and take responsibility for what happened.

“Owner Kong!”

A sharp voice.

“What should we do now?”

As soon as Jo Geum-Myeong asked, the others began to join in.

“Say something!”

“Didn’t you say that we only needed to trust you? How did this happen?”

“We believed in you, and now we have turned into scammers and thieves. How are you going to take responsibility for this?”

At that, Kong Mun-Yeong slowly raised his head.

“…”

Everyone who saw his eyes went silent. Kong Mun-Yeong’s eyes, which had always been soft, were no longer glistening.

“Are you blaming me?”

“…”

Hearing the cold voice, they were all suppressed by his momentum and backed away.

“A-No, we didn’t mean it like that….”

“We meant… measures. Some countermeasures…”

As everyone flinched, Kong Mun-Yeong, who was overwhelming the crowd, further bolstered the momentum.

“You pathetic bastards.”

“…”

“….”

Kong Mun-Yeong got up.

“It wasn’t as if we were hoping to have a good relationship with Mount Hua! Is there any one of you who thought otherwise? Everyone must have realized this to some extent, didn’t you?”

There was no answer.

Those who still knew shame bowed their heads, but most didn’t.

Kong Mun-Yeong said.

“No need to make a fuss. For now, just endure; however, this isn’t going to end like this.”

“… do you have something in mind?”

“How can those ledger’s be legitimate?”

“…”

“They’re obviously forged.”

“W-what….”

“You must know that, with Mount Hua’s connections, manipulating the authenticity of the ledgers isn’t very difficult! He must have decided to share the wealth with the province officials.!”

“Ah!”

The merchants nodded their heads.

“Then?”

“Let’s go to Luoyang for now. We can take care of matters there. If they try to suppress us with such power, we will have to push back with greater power! I will surely punish the wicked Mount Hua and that sect leader!”

“Ohhh!”

“Right! It doesn’t make sense for them to suddenly have a bunch of books from a hundred years ago!”

“We need to uncover their crooked tricks!”

The voices of merchants grew louder.

It didn’t matter if the ledger was real or fake. As Kong Mun-Yeong said, if they can utilize great enough power, even real books would become fake.

Then getting their businesses back wouldn’t be a huge deal.

Seeing that, Kong Mun-Yeong smiled.

“So, you have nothing to worry about. I will take care of everything, so just trust and follow me.”

“We believe in you!”

“We believed you from the start!”

‘Pathetic bastards.’

Kong Mun-Yeong frowned.

They were trash, but he still needed them. It was better to have people who would follow his words than to be alone. Once he reached Luoyang, the situation would be reversed. He had a strong backer, which could give him strength…

“What bullshit.”

Then, an unfamiliar voice flew in.

Kong Mun-Yeong turned his head.

Chapter 34: You bastard!? Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (4)

‘When?’

Kong Mun-Yeong was visibly shocked. He didn’t feel anyone approaching. But someone was standing right in front of him.

‘Who is it?’

As he looked at the owner of the voice, Kong Mun-Yeong’s feelings changed from shock into bewilderment.

A black cloth clung tightly to his body, another black cloth obscured his face, and he held a sword in one hand.

“…”

It was obviously a robber!!

But…

Kong Mun-Yeong’s gaze drifted upwards. The blazing sun caught his eyes as his vision clouded over.

‘A crazy bastard?’

A robber was roaming on the streets in broad daylight. Did that make any sense?

“… what did you say?”

Instead of Kong Mun-Yeong, someone else asked. The masked man looked at the person and spoke.

“I said… cough!. Cough! Cough! Agh! What… cough…bullshit.”

“…”

Kong Mun-Yeong looked at the robber with blank eyes.

‘Is he going to die?’

Is it some old man?

A bent waist with an emaciated body made the man look like a skeleton. Every move seemed to cause his bones to ache, and what can be seen of his hidden face were tired eyes that looked old and withered.

Or was it a young child dying?

No. That couldn’t be.

“What business does he have? He doesn’t seem like a passer-by.”

The masked man coughed a few times and shook his head at the question.

“Shit. I am going to die this way.”

“…”

“Can’t you see what is going on?”

“… what’s going on?”

“A man dressed like this appears before you in broad daylight; what do you think his identity is?”

“Someone who’s gone mad?”

“…”

“… or dementia?”

“Robber! A robber!”

“Oh, you really were a robber. I couldn’t believe it.”

Kong Mun-Yeong stopped smiling.

This man claiming to be a robber looked like he couldn’t even catch a mouse.

Of course, downplaying others based on their appearance wasn’t a good idea. But now, this man’s appearance wasn’t the only problem.

Although he had a sword in his hand, no one could feel any energy from him.

And any rational man with no energy wouldn’t be walking around in those kinds of clothes. This was something only a crazy person would do.

“Look here. Old man.”

Kong Mun-Yeong waved his hand.

“It seems you’ve lost your way at the sight of wealth. It might seem like a jackpot, but don’t waste your life here. Quickly return.”

“Looking at the riches… cough! The jackpot for sure… cough! Cough! Oh! It must be you!”

“… I don’t understand what you mean?”

“Kua.”

Since the masked man couldn’t communicate clearly, he tapped on his waist a couple of times, raised the sword he was using as a cane, and pointed to Kong Mun-Yeong.

“I am not trying to steal your money. I am trying to recover my property.”

“Didn’t you say you were a robber a while ago?”

“See, you understood it so clearly despite the coughing.”

“… huh.”

Kong Mun-Yeong frowned.

Since he couldn’t rob, this robber was trying to stick around like a beggar.

“It would be better for you to leave before we are forced to take action.”

“Do you want to try?”

“Are you serious!?”

The moment Kong Mun-Yeong was about to scream, the tip of the masked man’s sword was aimed at him.

“I thought you had a brighter head on your shoulders, but it seems you don’t understand.”

Kong Mun-Yeong ceased speaking. A moment of silence passed.

Kong Mun-Yeong, who was looking at the masked man, asked in a slightly different tone.

“Are you from Mount Hua?”

At his question, the other merchants seemed shocked.

“Mount Hua?”

“What do you mean, owner Kong?”

Kong Mun-Yeong didn’t answer their questions. Dealing with the annoying bastards wasn’t important now; the masked man was his current priority.

The masked man shook his head.

“It seems you do understand.”

“You know that the talks with Mount Hua are done, right?”

“The talks with Mount Hua are done. But the talks with me aren’t over yet.”

“Did the sect leader send you?”

“Does he seem like that kind of a person?”

“… no.”

Kong Mun-Yeong knew the personality of the sect leader. There was no denying that the man was dignified and had his own sense of justice.

He wasn’t the kind to send someone to clean up after letting them go.

“Are you saying that you came from Mount Hua against the will of your own sect leader?”

“It is fine.”

The masked man shook his head.

“Because I am not in a position to listen to each and every word of that child.”

Kong Mun-Yeong’s face darkened.

‘Child?’

Although covered with a mask, he considered this man with a sloppy waist, weird body, and old-fashioned words to be quite old.

Even in comparison to the sect leader of Mount Hua, this man seemed older.

In other words, the person in front of them right now could be a former master of Mount Hua.

‘But they aren’t the kind to come out and act like this.’

He couldn’t figure it out. It was his will to never disturb his composure in front of people, but the person in front of him could be a former master.

Kong Mun-Yeong’s complexion darkened,

“I didn’t realize that former members of Mount Hua would be so petty.”

“Petty?”

The masked man snorted.

“Aren’t you being petty by pointing a sword at us and hoping to take what little we have left? What would your senior think if he saw this now?”

“… senior?”

The blue eyes behind the mask narrowed.

‘Huh? Look at him!’

‘He understands seniority in the sect?’

Senior was something Chung Myung was called in his time. Though he was quite the rouge at the time. If Kong Mun-Yeong was a simple businessman, he wouldn’t know much about seniority within a sect.

But he mentions that?

Chung Myung titled his head.

‘Something smells off.’

Something very musty. Maybe this wasn’t just done by some money-crazed people.

“Well, it’s fine either way.”

Chung Myung swung his sword.

“I don’t know if the sect leader let you go so easily because he’s naïve or if he simply hasn’t learned anything. Personally, with my temper, I would rather just break your bones and be done with it. But, for the sake of the sect leader, I will respect his decision to let you go. Leave the carts and get out of here, then I won’t catch you.”

“Hahaha.”

Kong Mun-Yeong burst out laughing.

“Old man. Do you think I left because I lacked strength?”

“Yes.”

“…”

Kong Mun-Yeong was confused.

It was weird how this old man talked. Every time he spoke, Kong Mun-Yeong would be left speechless.

“Khuem! Well, you’re mistaken. The reason I backed down was to avoid making it a larger problem. It’s not as if I’m unable to catch a man wearing a mask calling himself a robber.”

“haha. Well-spoken… cough! Cough! Ahck! Cough! Spit! Oh my…. I am dying.”

Seeing the masked man hunched over and coughing, Kong Mun-Yeong felt a bit sorry for him. If the situation allowed, he even wanted to help him.

Tears welled up in his eyes, looking at those shaky limbs and bent waist.

“… old man. If you back down, we won’t bother you. It seems like things are difficult for you too, so don’t stand up and simply head back.”

“The old man has already died.”

He was a kid now.

‘Aigoo, that pure internal qi is killing my body.’

His body wasn’t mature, so he had no choice but to use it, but he never expected the wounds to be so severe.

There was no way he could feel fine when he was supposed to be resting for three months, but he decided to go wandering the streets. He was thankful they misunderstood him to be an old man, but…

“I have nothing to say.”

Chung Myung swung his sword.

“Those who want to take a beating, stay here; those who value their lives can leave empty-handed. Back in the old days, I would have just pounced without asking a question. Recently though, I am learning to be patient, so don’t test my temper.”

“You speak well.”

Kong Mun-Yeong drew a line like he didn’t want to speak anymore.

“This is your last warning. I will not show you any more consideration.”

“I get it. Tell the people hiding to come out.”

Kong Mun-Yeong was startled.

‘He noticed?’

Following behind him were a group of hidden escorts. They were so talented that it would be difficult for even a trained martial artist to feel their presence.

“Come out.”

As the words fell, dozens of warriors appeared from the grassy terrain.

“Huh?”

“When did these people…?”

The merchants gathered close to their carts, their faces rife with fear. Of course, they couldn’t have noticed the guards following them.

“Once more!”

Kong Mun-Yeong still wanted to give the old man a chance to step down but went silent at what happened.

A sound that made his shoulders shake.

And…

Swosh!.

The warrior who jumped out the farthest collapsed suddenly. Upon seeing that, Kong Mun-Yeong’s legs trembled.

Chung Myung clicked his tongue and raised the sword.

“Anyway!”

Pak!

“Kids these days!”

Thuk!

“Talk a lot!”

Paaak!

“I didn’t act like this in my time!”

Thud!

Five escorts fell before Kong Mun-Yeong could figure out what happened. He couldn’t understand it.

“Tch.”

Chung Myung retrieved his sword, put it on his shoulder, and looked at Kong Mun-Yeong.

It may have looked cool if anyone else had done it, but now Chung Myung was weak and slumped over. Seeing him bent down, seemingly in pain, evoking a sense of misery in his movements made the onlookers feel a sort of pity for him.

“Child.”

Chung Myung smiled and continued.

“You don’t seem to know much, but none of the kids who ignored me in the old days returned with their limbs intact. You should listen well to the words of your elders. I wonder, will some old-fashioned medicine work on you?

Chung Myung walked with the sword on his shoulder, whistling.

The warriors who saw it faltered and stepped back at his approach. Completely crushed by the momentum.

“Stand back, you useless trash!”

Kong Mun-Yeong, who yelled at the warriors, grunted through his teeth.

‘Was there still someone this strong hidden in Mount Hua?’

He thought Mount Hua was just an old tiger with its teeth and claws removed. No, that was correct. The mistake was overlooking the fact that a crippled tiger is still a tiger; even without its teeth and claws, it could kill a man with its strength alone.

“I don’t know why you waited until now to appear. if you had come out earlier than now, Mount Hua wouldn’t have turned this way.”

Just as Chung Myung was opening his mouth, Kong Mun-Yeong continued.

“But, you’ve come at the wrong time. I wanted to deliver a blow to Mount Hua, but this works as well. If someone like you dies at my hands, the sect leader will surely grieve for quite some time. Prepare yourself.”

Kong Mun-Yeong raised his energy.

The grass around was ripped up and soared around in a frenzy. It was energy far greater than what a store owner should be capable of.

“Right. I knew something was up with you.”

Chung Myung’s eyes shone.

“Don’t worry; at the very least, I won’t cut that mouth of yours.”

Chung Myung walked towards Kong Mun-Yeong, while Kong Mun-Yeong ran towards Chung Myung.

Chapter 35: You bastard!? Are you from the Southern Edge Sect? (5)

There was no disrespect for the opponent.

Although Kong Mun-Yeong was a half-baked warrior, his attitude wasn’t inferior to that of a truly strong martial artist. Those who walked the path of martial arts should never underestimate their foes. Even a tiger does its best to catch a rabbit.

Moreover, there was no way he could be more alert after seeing how Chung Myung dealt with the escort guards.

But…

Something felt strange.

Tak!

As he attempted to strike with his fist, before it could even extend past his chest, it was already blocked. What’s more, it was blocked with a sword.

The robber kept blocking any movement, twisting and turning without attacking, as if playing with Kong Mun-Yeong.

“Kuak!”

He could clearly feel the flow of internal energy.

“Y-You bastard!”

He clearly attacked the masked man with a Swinging Leg attack, but the masked man had already vanished from that place.

“You’re too slow.”

“Huk!”

Kong Mun-Yeong, startled by the voice coming from behind, clenched his fist and fiercely swung backward.

But this time too.

Tak!

“Huk!”

Strength was circulated from the dantian and amplified through his waist and chest; his fists turned into raging weapons. But what happens when such weapons are blocked before releasing their momentum?

Pop!

The sound of something exploding inside Kong Mun-Yeong’s body. At the same time, his shoulder blades swelled sharply.

It couldn’t be seen with the eyes, but there was likely a rupture within his shoulder muscle.

“Eik!”

The same thing kept repeating over and over.

“Uuughh!”

Kong Mun-Yeong, seething in pain and fury, raised his energy to kill the man and swept with a powerful kick. However, the masked man didn’t seem to try avoiding it. He lightly took a step back as if avoiding an obnoxious fly.

Kong Mun-Yeong felt his feet brush past the man’s chest, the wind pressure made his clothes tremble, but the masked man was untouched.

‘What the hell is he?’

He couldn’t calm himself.

Was he fast?

No.

Strong?

No.

The masked man was neither fast nor strong. Judging from his appearance, Kong Mun-Yeong could surely deal with 10 more masked people.

But now, he couldn’t even touch the hem of the man’s clothes. It was as if a young disciple was dealing with his master, he tried all sorts of maneuvers, but none worked.

It was the same now.

His full-strength blow flew towards the man’s face, but it just brushed by with no contact. If he could even graze the man, his flesh would be torn, and his bones would be crushed; but the masked man was completely avoiding his attacks with minimal movements. As if he was playing with a toddler.

How could that be possible?

He wasn’t fast.

But he was fast.

It wasn’t an overwhelming speed. He moved slowly but perfectly and in the right direction at the proper distance.

Effortlessly and without wasting energy.

A dream of any martial artist. However, Kong Mun-Yeong felt miserable now.

It was like seeing a goblin.

He was fighting a man, but then it felt like he was kicking the air. He couldn’t touch the opponent, and he couldn’t hurt the opponent no matter what he tried.

‘This man is a monster.’

If the man was just avoiding it, he wouldn’t be so nervous. However, it wasn’t just that.

‘He is reading my movements.’

Even before he attacked, he was able to decide where to move. He was able to lead the opponent’s strength to move where he wanted. This was an excellent combination of posture and movement.

Kong Mun-Yeong couldn’t even imagine just how strong this man could be.

‘It was wrong from the beginning.’

Monsters were unpredictable from the start. Had he known such a monster existed in Mount Hua, he never would have done such a thing.

But…

“Kuak”

The masked man, who was sneakily dodging the attacks, grabbed his waist and bent over.

“Oh my. Damn this body. It hurts. It hurts.”

“…”

The masked man patted his back.

… it was a bit clumsy.

A master who was so great was gasping and tired from this little movement?

Ridiculous.

But it was happening right in front of his eyes.

The masked man was breathing heavily. And the mask around his mouth was wet, the face exposed in the cloth mask was perspiring heavily. And his back was already soaked with sweat.

He seemed to be on the verge of collapse.

Yet, he kept dodging the attacks, which flowed unceasingly.

“Kuak.”

The masked man straightened his back again.

“Tch. I wanted to play with you more, but I can’t. I am too weak.”

Kong Mun-Yeong’s face tensed upon hearing what was said.

He did everything he could, yet he couldn’t even catch a loose string of this feeble old man’s clothing. Kong Mun-Yeong was confident that if he put his strength on full display, few would be able to defeat him. He even felt he could bring down Mount Hua if he tried.

But now, he was toyed with by an old man he’d never seen before, constantly being teased.

“Why was someone like you never on the front line?”

“You don’t need to know.”

Chung Myung turned and grabbed the sword.

“Those who think only of themselves live in a strange illusion. Why should I have to answer any of your questions?”

“…”

“I’m the one who will ask the questions. For a simple business owner, your martial arts are quite strong. Why is a man with such skills running a business in Hua-Um?”

“Is there a law which says the strong shouldn’t run businesses?”

“But it’s a different story when the warrior is clearly greedy for money to the point of tricking a sect. With your level of martial arts, there are plenty of better ways to earn a fortune. Do you understand what I’m saying?”

Chung Myung’s lips inside the mask curled up.

“What are you trying—”

“Ah, that’s enough.”

Chung Myung stopped him from speaking.

“I get it, I get it, you aren’t going to tell me anyway. There is no conspiracy going around, so don’t misunderstand. I have not been commissioned by anyone, and I am not affiliated with anyone. This is all because of my personal matter. Is what you are going to say, right?”

“….r–right.”

“Hm. I thought so.”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“That’s how it usually goes. Unfortunately, those who say such things never confess easily in the beginning. Truthfully, even though your sins are great, I don’t feel the need to grind you for information. Once I separate your flesh from bone, the words should spill out naturally, but if I do that, there are bound to be additional problems.”

Chung Mung nodded to himself.

“Right, so there is the problem. Do you know what I do when I find myself in this situation?

“… how would I know?”

“We’ll make a deal.”

Kong Mun-Yeong’s eyes widened.

“Huh?”

“I said that we’ll make a deal.”

“…”

Chung Myung shook his head and walked towards the man.

“You’ve already said that you won’t speak; even if your insides explode, your mouth will remain sealed. So, we’ll make a deal. You promise to keep your mouth shut, and I promise to beat you until it opens.”

“…”

“If you change your mind in the middle and you want to talk, just raise your hand. But it would be better to think quickly. You can’t get a refund for a blow which has already struck you.”

“What nonsense!”

“Right. That is my specialty! Here I come!”

Chung Myung rushed in, closing the gap between them in an instant. Kong Mun-Yeong unknowingly backed away.

The masked man wasn’t giving out any overpowering energy. It wasn’t like the sword in his hand was scary. Even the way he ran made it feel like he would trip and fall any moment, yet Kong Mun-Yeong retreated.

But the speed he was retreating at wasn’t faster than the speed Chung Myung was running.

Chung Myung’s sword, still in its sheath, swiftly targeted Kong Mun-Yeong’s left knee. Realizing that it was impossible to avoid, Kong Mun-Yeong attempted to block his knee with his arms.

Paak!

And soon, the sword slammed into the shoulder.

“Ack!”

An unseen attack.

‘Shoulder?’

Obviously, it was aimed at the leg, so why did his shoulder get hit?

But there wasn’t much time to think about it. The sword which struck the shoulder now aimed for the head.

This time, he could clearly determine the correct angle; he crossed his arms over his head.

Tuk!

His eyes blurred over momentarily.

The world turned black for a second before color was regained. At the same time, he felt short of breath, like his neck was tearing.

“Kuak!”

Chung Myung’s sword had stabbed him in the throat. The blade was still in its sheath, so it didn’t cut his throat. Still, it was a firm lump of metal that had stabbed his throat. How painful would it be?

Tears welled up in his eyes as his body trembled.

Argh!

Meanwhile, Chung Myung’s sword came crashing down.

Shoulder, head, and waist.

Now, he was swinging the sword like he was hitting a stray dog.

What made it remarkable was that the fat man could never avoid it despite how clumsy the swordsmanship appeared. If he twisted his shoulders, his back was struck; if he tried to move his back, his head got hit.

Kong Mun-Yeong, who quickly became a mess, retreated in terror and backed away.

“M–might die….”

The fear of death began to dominate his mind. Both looked into each other’s eyes.

At that moment, Kong Mun-Yeong could tell.

Eyes.

When he saw Chung Myung’s cold and emotionless eyes, Kong Mun-Yeong understood.

He had seen those eyes many times in his life. All those who had such eyes had one thing in common.

Killers.

He didn’t know what it was, but it was definite that this man had killed countless people. Beating Kong Mun-Yeong to death would be no different than catching a fly.

As soon as he chooses to unsheathe his sword, Kong Mun-Yeong’s head would surely fly off without resistance.

‘N-No!’

He didn’t want to die. At least not here.

Then, Chung Myung began to pull his sword from the sheath. Soon after, he struck at Kong Mun-Yeong’s head with a swiftness unseen before.

“Aaaaahhhhhh!!”

Kong Mun-Yeong’s hands shone in a dazzling blue light. A massive blast erupted from his palms at Chung Myung as he wielded his sword.

“…”

Kong Mun-Yeong remained in that position with his arm outstretched in a daze.

There was nothing there.

Chung Myung wasn’t where he was supposed to be. Kong Mun-Yeong, who came to his senses, hurriedly looked at Chung Myung, who had already come closer as he was sheathing his sword.

Chung Myung opened his mouth.

“Taiyi Divine Palm technique?”

“…”

“You bastard?”

Kong Mun-Yeong’s face went pale the moment he realized his mistake.

“Are you from the Southern Edge Sect?”

His face soon became horribly distorted.

Chapter 36: A leader who is more like a beggar! (1)

“….”

Kong Mun-Yeong quickly pulled himself together. Even if he was caught in a tiger’s den, wouldn’t he be able to survive as long as he kept his wits together?

“W-whatever do you mean?”

“Ha? Look at this fool!”

Chung Myung snorted.

“Did you think my eyes are for decoration? Do I look like someone who can’t recognize the Taiyi Divine Palm?”

“…”

Chung Myung shrugged.

“Quite a coincidence. What a crafty bitch. The person operating a business in Hua-Um who led the merchants to pressure Mount Hua into the ground over their debt also just happens to know the martial arts of the Southern edge sect? The Taiyi Divine Palm technique, you’ve learned it quite well, huh?”

Cold sweat ran down Kong Mun-Yeong’s back. He was so surprised that he couldn’t even feel the pain from the beating he took.

‘Damn it.’

He should have been more cautious.

Even if his neck was cut off, he shouldn’t have used that technique. What’s more, he did it in front of a man from Mount Hua!

A fatal mistake.

But can this be called a mistake?

If the old man hadn’t pushed Kong Mun-Yeong to this extent and suddenly unsheathed the sword while beating the hell out of him, Kong Mun-Yeong wouldn’t have used the technique.

If it was a coincidence, it was the worst kind. If he aimed for this, then Kong Mun-Yeong couldn’t imagine just how nasty that old man was.

“Did the Southern Edge Sect send you?”

“…”

Kong Mun-Yeong tightly sealed his lips.

No matter what he said, it would come out as an excuse. If he could turn the situation around, even if he had to use the lamest excuse, then he would; but it didn’t seem like anything would work on this old man. So, he kept silent to ensure he didn’t give up more information.

“Huh? Shut your mouth, eh?”

Chung Myung walked towards Kong Mun-Yeong.

“Well, this is fine too. It’s a good thing to be loyal. I think you made a good choice. But there is one thing you are wrong about.”

“…?”

“Do you know what that is?”

“… what is it?”

“I won’t tell you.”

“…”

The Southern Edge sect wasn’t an easy place. Since the old days, the Southern Edge sect had been at odds with Mount Hua, but it must be admitted that it was now one of the Ten Great Sects.

There was no way for a sect of that size to do such sloppy work. That was Chung Myung’s thoughts. The information Kong Mun-Yeong knew had to be limited, and even if he knew more, there was no way to verify its authenticity.

All he had to know was that this was indeed the work of the Southern Edge sect. Isn’t that something that Chung Myung and Mount Hua should find out?

“Haaa, you bastard! Even in the past, when the martial arts world was quite grim, it wasn’t this horrible. One of the Ten Great Sects tries to steal not just other people’s martial arts techniques but also their entire sect? Isn’t that quite a scam? What an honorable sect!”

Kong Mun-Yeong, who could no longer maintain his composure, broke out.

“Right. Isn’t that better for Mount Hua too?”

“Huh?”

“You must understand it too! Mount Hua is hopeless now. Wealth? Riches? They are just additional things for a sect. Mount Hua has lost its martial arts, and it can no longer become the same Mount Hua whose name echoed in glory. It’s just a matter of it falling down later if it survives now!”

“Oh?”

Chung Myung listened to Kong Mun-Yeong’s words.

“I was trying to snuff out the dying Mount Hua’s last breaths. Again, this is something Mount Hua should be thankful for. Someone like you should know this, right? Mount Hua can no longer survive! Even the martial arts, the core of any sect, have withered at Mount Hua!”

“Who said that?”

“You don’t understand what I am saying?”

“No. Who said that Mount Hua’s martial arts have withered?”

“…”

Kong Mun-Yeong looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes.

Kong Mun-Yeong would have snorted and dismissed it if anyone else had said this. But the words coming from Chung Myung seemed to hold greater weight.

In the eyes of Kong Mun-Yeong, this man was a former master of Mount Hua.

“You bastards are trying to cut off Mount Hua’s last breath? Mount Hua is still alive and well; even if it dies, it dies. But, you piece of shit, what do you think you’re trying to do by burying Mount Hua while it still breathes?”

“…”

“Whatever, you crooked bastards always justify your actions with some twisted logic. I’d rather you people charge straight ahead and destroy Mount Hua head-on. That is the only way I will acknowledge those bitches from the Southern Edge sect.”

The closer one lives, the more likely they will bump into each other. It’s true that in diplomatic matters, you must treat your enemies as friends and keep them close.

Mount Hua and the Southern Edge sect had many similarities, and both had a strong focus on swordsmanship. Despite having different ideals, they stayed close to one another.

If two sects with similar techniques were placed side by side, one was bound to die.

In the past, Chung Myung would regularly beat the shit out of the Southern Edge sect when he felt bored. To be more precise, Chung Myung would provoke them into starting a fight.

“I am not a member of the Southern Edge Sect!”

“Is that so?”

“You misunderstood something, but the technique you saw was something I learned by accident.”

“Ah. Right. Should I tell you a surprising fact?

“… what is that?”

“I am not a member of Mount Hua either.”

“…Yes, that makes sense….”

“You—you son of a bitch!”

“…”

Chung Myung was startled at Kong Mun-Yeong’s reaction.

That was close. He almost hit him.

“Anyway, in return for showing me that technique, I will show you something interesting. If you can recognize this, it will be interesting. But if you don’t, then it is a shame.”

Chung Myung slowly stuck his sword out.

“Tell the one who sent you.”

Chung Myung’s way of speaking had changed.

The playful appearance was no more. His bent back was now straight, and the drooping shoulders had regained their form.

A perfect posture, picturesque.

Kong Mun-Yeong, who witnessed it, was shocked.

A sudden breeze began to blow over the area.

The wind seemed to carry the gentle scent of plum blossoms that filled the air.

“Plum Blossoms give off the most intense fragrance when they bloom in the snow. Although it is winter now, Mount Hua’s spirit remains unbroken. Eventually, the spring will come, and the plum blossoms will bloom in full.”

Kong Mun-Yeong saw it.

The tip of the sword which moved.

Shiver.

The movement, which began with a tiny vibration, soon grew into a great tremor, and the tremor turned into an illusory sword whose trajectory seemed to embroider the sky in a fantasy.

The tip of the sword seemed to cover the entire sky.

Vivid plum petals bloomed at the sword’s tip.

After a dreary winter, the plum blossoms which heralded a warm spring bloomed all over the mountain, painted into the world through Chung Myung’s sword.

‘This is an illusion.’

The wind blew.

The plum blossoms which covered the sky as if fluttering in the spring wind began to bloom. Eventually, the petals flew up as if swimming in the sky and landed on Kong Mun-Yeong’s head.

The petals gently swept past Kong Mun-Yeong, blowing away his consciousness like the wind. Until the very end, he didn’t know what he was looking at.

Thud!

Only the sound of him falling to the floor, unconscious, could be heard. The plum blossom petals covering the sky disappeared like a mirage.

Chung Myung, who withdrew his sword, turned around.

“Kuak!”

Blood flowed from the corner of his mouth due to overexerting himself to operate the technique. Chung Myung, who took off his mask, spit out a large surge of blood.

‘I am dying, for sure.’

He had a broken body that lacked strength. If it was the past, such a thing could have been done without sweating.

‘The foundation is good, but I still might die. Ouch!’

Chung Myung put the mask on and thought about coming up with some new countermeasures.

“Well, then.”

His gaze went to the other merchants.

“…”

They were looking at Chung Myung as if they had seen a ghost.

Why wouldn’t they?

They had never seen or heard of plum blossoms blooming in the sky due to a sword technique. No, they had heard such a feat was accomplished by masters in the past, but those warriors were dead, so they believed it to be an exaggerated legend.

However, this man brought the legend to life before their eyes.

From their point of view, as those who tried to extort money by scamming Mount Hua, Chung Myung was nothing short of a Grim Reaper.

“Who wants to be beaten first?”

“…”

“Who wants to leave?”

“Me!”

“I will go away too!”

“Please spare us!”

Chung Myung just nodded his head.

“Good. So cooperative.”

Merchants rushed out and away from their carts. But, of course, Chung Myung had no intention of letting them go so easily.

“Stop moving.”

“…”

The merchants froze in unison.

“If you just leave just like this, what am I to do about these carts? Think a little, think.”

“…”

The merchants looked at Chung Myung with eyes overflowing with injustice.

Did they even have to consider the convenience of a robber? No matter how horrible their luck was, this seemed too much.

But no one dared to speak against him.

“You.”

“Yes!”

“For now, each of you will check how much money is in your cart. Whoever finishes last will end up like him.”

Chung Myung pointed toward the unconscious Kong Mun-Yeong.

No more words were needed. As soon as the words were spoken, the merchants rushed to their carts.

“Eight hundred nyang!”

“Two thousand and eight hundred nyang!”

“It is…eight thousand….”

“What? You had that much money?”

“Is that important now?”

Some even yelled at the others. Chung Myung, who saw it, frowned.

“Hey.”

“Yes?”

“Did you include the cost of the cart and the horse too?”

“…”

“Recalculate.”

“Yes.”

Once it was done, Chung Myung nodded.

“Then, I will lend the horse, so one of you will go to the nearest town from here and get the money. I will sell these wares to you.”

The merchants looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes.

They were the sort of people who lived their lives obsessed with money, but even for them, this was the first time they’d seen such a person.

“Bring the money on a non-disclosure slip. If you put anything on the slip, I will kill you right away. Okay?”

“Yes.”

“One person will go.”

“… but.”

“What?”

One merchant asked.

“What if the one going escapes?”

Chung Myung laughed.

“What good would running away do?”

“…”

“Do you people have money now?”

“No.”

“And your businesses have been confiscated?”

“Yes.”

“Then what good will running and escaping even do? If you want to at least get something, you should come back, right?”

“… then what if they report to the government—”

“Try it.”

Chung Myung gently raised his leg and hit the floor.

Thud!

The ground beneath them cracked.

“Report it, but don’t come back with them. Run to the end of the world because I will capture that bastard even if I die. So don’t think of coming back.”

“…”

The merchants gave up on the report too.

Thinking about it, their families were here. They couldn’t just run away and leave them,

“Go.”

“… yes.”

Mount Hua was a benevolent sect.

However, there was one reason why the merchants were unhappy. Mount Hua was benevolent, but not everyone who lived in Mount Hua was.

On that day, before the sun even had a chance to set, a masked man with a money slip as thick as a book climbed Mount Hua with joy and excitement. The wealth made from the sweat and tears of many people was silently stored in a greedy warehouse.

Chapter 37: A leader who is more like a beggar! (2)

Mount Hua hadn’t changed much. The wind blowing into it was the same; the old buildings were the same.

What changed wasn’t Mount Hua but the people who lived there.

“Uk!”

Jo Gul took off his uniform. The sweat was pouring down from the uniform as he threw it off. After morning training, his entire body was steeped in sweat, and he couldn’t stay without changing clothes.

“Man, today’s training was really hard.”

“Really, it’s so much to do right at dawn….”

As he heard that, Jo Gul smiled bitterly. The people around him were also hoping to get a clean bath. Together, they washed their bodies and sweaty clothes in the ice-cold stream.

Jo Gul, who put on a new uniform, packed his laundry and said.

“Let’s get going.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

The others picked up their robes and started going up. Looking at the people walking ahead, Jo Gul had no choice but to think about it.

‘A lot has changed.’

In the past, such a sight couldn’t be dreamed of. Although the other third-class disciples were training, they weren’t passionate about martial arts. Even Yoon Jong and Jo Gul were the same.

But now, everyone was voluntarily coming out for practice at dawn. There was no end to their complaints, but they never rebelled against it.

What would one call this scene?

‘It feels like a martial arts sect.’

Jo Gul smiled bitterly. Looking at the disciples walking up, they all looked like martial artists disciples. Did that mean that Mount Hua was nothing until now?

“Why are you smiling like that?”

At the voice next to him, Jo Gul turned his head and looked at great Sahyung Yoon Jong.

“Ah, Sahyung… it is a bit embarrassing to say, but I was thinking about how everyone seems so much like true martial artists now.”

“Is that so?”

“It’s a bit of a strange thought, though.”

“No. I was thinking the same.”

“Haha…”

Jo Gul finally laughed out loud.

Not long ago, Jo Gul had never imagined that he would train to this extent on Mount Hua. He did everything instructed in his dorm, but it was half-heartedly done so he could finish and go back to resting.

Jo Gul’s goal was to pass the time and then descend and return home. No, it was everyone’s goal in Mount Hua.

Could he genuinely feel passionate about this?

Lately, it felt like something had changed. Not only him, but the eyes of the other disciples had changed too.

‘It has to be because of him.’

Jo Gul thought of Chung Myung’s weird behavior. Chung Myung was changing Mount Hua. It was clearly a small wind that most people couldn’t even feel, but it was bound to turn into a strong wind or a typhoon that would shake Mount Hua.

The result of these changes will be evident in the future.

Walking up the mountain, Jo Gul, who reached Mount Hua, straightened his shoulders and touched his chest. A faint feeling of pride began to swell inside his chest.

But then, the pride he felt flew away into the open sky.

“Hey! You shouldn’t touch that!”

“Move, move, move! We’re going to push all the materials inside and then start working! Are you deaf or something!?”

“You! If you fall there, you won’t get any pay for a month! If just the climb up here is tough, then what are you worth!?”

Jo Gul blankly stared at the figures in front of Mount Hua.

“…”

His gaze shifted from left to right.

‘What? Who are those people?’

People he had never met were walking up. Everyone had tools and materials which he had never seen before.

“You! No, not there! This way!”

It was comforting to see someone he recognized in the group of strangers. Un Am was standing among the crowd giving instructions.

“… Sahyung?”

Yoon Jong, who received Jo Gul’s gaze, walked towards Un Am with a blank expression.

“Sasuk.”

“Huh? Yoon Jong?”

“What is all this?”

“Oh!”

Un Am smiled brightly. He usually wasn’t the kind to explain such things, even to Yoon Jong, the eldest of the third-class disciples, but now Un Am was in a good mood.

“They’re workers.”

“Workers?”

“Yes. You know that many of our buildings are a bit old, right?”

“Yes.”

Not old; ancient would be the right word.

Even Mount Hua’s nameplate on the front gate was crumbling, and if a strong wind blew, it seemed many buildings could collapse. At least, the place where the disciples stayed and trained was constantly repaired and maintained. But the other buildings were left without management due to a lack of manpower.

“With our current opportunity, we plan on repairing the area. We’ll re-establish the place.”

“Uh?”

“Don’t just keep looking; go and help carry the materials. It seems like all the workers are having difficulty bringing the materials up here. Most of the wood can be acquired by cutting trees nearby, but it seems they have some wood that they can’t find nearby.

“Yes?”

“Move fast! Move already! Hurry!”

Looking at Un Am shouting with a smile, Jo Gul had a blank expression. Maybe the change was faster than he expected.

“What is going on?”

Jo Gul looked at the dining table in shock.

His hunger-soaked stomach was rumbling after carrying the materials up, but looking at the food on the table, he was more flustered than hungry.

“What is all this?”

“… am I dreaming?”

“No matter how I try to look at it, isn’t this ‘meat’?”

The other sahyungs wore the same skeptical expression. All eyes in the hall were fixed on the table. Something extraordinary was on the table.

There was meat being served.

“They really served us meat?”

“To kill a living being, cook, and serve it to us, sacred Martial artists! What a windfall!”

“Something must be wrong!”

“…”

Jo Gul smiled grandly.

In Mount Hua, there was no prohibition on the consumption of meat. Mount Hua did have a rule that condemned eating meat in the long past, but it had changed as Mount Hua developed. Vegetarianism was recommended, but meat wasn’t prohibited.

But allowing them to eat meat and actively putting meat on the table were two different things. It had been years since the disciples entered Mount Hua, and it was their first time seeing meat on the table.

“Can I eat this?”

“They put it on the table so that it would be eaten.”

Everyone looked at Yoon Jong. If that Sasuks were not there, the decision-maker would be the great Sahyung, Yoon Jong.

Yoon Jong smiled and said,

“Let’s eat. The food is getting cold.”

“Yes.”

Jo Gul sat down at a loss for words and felt a piercing gaze. All the sahyungs were looking at Jo Gul… no, to be precise, they were looking at Yoon Jong, who was next to Jo Gul, with fiery eyes.

Yoon Jong, who understood it, grabbed his chopsticks and picked up a piece of meat. And the moment he put it in his mouth.

Papapapapa!

Chopsticks came flying into the meat bowl from all directions!

Some were directly throwing it into their mouths too. When Jo Gul saw that, it seemed so absurd that he wanted to scream, but then he didn’t. Jo Gul’s chopsticks also flew like lightning.

‘If I am late, I won’t get any!’

‘Out of the way! My meat!’

‘Meat! Meat!’

Seeing the fragments of meat scattered everywhere, Yoon Jong closed his eyes.

Mount Hua.

The Mount Hua he knew was becoming strange.

“Well, the longer you live, the more changes you’ll experience.”

“Right.”

“They started construction all of a sudden, and now meat is being served for our meals. We even got two new uniforms, right?”

“Yes.”

Yoon Jong narrowed his eyes as if thinking about something. Seeing that, Jo Gul asked.

“What are you thinking?”

“I think that money is quite good.”

“Hahaha.”

Jo Gul laughed.

Even if others didn’t hear it, it felt weird hearing such things from Yoon Jong.

“No matter how much money we have, I didn’t expect the seniors to change so quickly.”

“Did you think they would purposefully keep their disciples poor? They just couldn’t help it in the past.”

That’s right.

It wasn’t that meat was prohibited; it was because meat was expensive.

“It was something that couldn’t be done because of the lack of money, so they are doing it now that they have money. But isn’t it weird?”

Jo Gul nodded his head.

“… didn’t you see sasuk Un Am who couldn’t hide the smile on his lips?”

Right.

They all saw it.

Jo Gul could swear that it was his first time seeing Un Am smile so brightly. Who could have even imagined that Un Am could smile like that?

What was certain was that Mount Hua had clearly entered a path of change.

“Sahyung.”

“Hm?”

“What do you think will happen now?’

It was a broad question, but Yoon Jong understood Jo Gul’s question.

“You should know it too, right? Mount Hua is changing.”

“Yes.”

“So, we need to be prepared.”

“Prepared…”

“It isn’t just about money. You saw it too. In that chest.”

“Yes. There were books.”

The scene where the sect leader yelled the name of some martial arts and almost fainted.

“Mount Hua is changing. We won’t be able to avoid the change. So, we need to strengthen ourselves. Then, won’t we be able to see something different from what we originally expected?”

Jo Gul nodded his head.

‘Is all of this because of him?’

Jo Gul couldn’t shake the suspicion that Chung Myung’s manipulation was what caused this whole situation. That obviously bad acting in front of the chest, Jo Gul shook his head.

“What did he do?”

“Can we know?”

Even though no names were mentioned, they both knew who he referred to.

“What’s certain is that there’s no way to predict that jerk’s actions ahead of time. We need to remain alert. If we approach this with clumsy determination, we might end up being swept away in the storm he creates.”

“Don’t worry, sahyung! I’m Jo Gul.”

“Right, right.”

Yoon Jong smiled and headed back to the dorm. A slightly different thought lingered on Jo Gul’s mind.

‘No way to predict.’

Jo Gul had a different idea. Maybe Chung Myung wasn’t someone that only disciples, but even the sasuks and sect leader couldn’t handle.

“By the way.”

“Huh?”

“Where is he? I haven’t seen him since this morning.”

“Didn’t you hear? The sect leader was looking for him today. He’s probably at the sect leader’s place.”

“Sect leader? Why was the sect leader looking for him?”

“How could I know?”

As Yoon Jong shrugged his shoulders, Jo Gul sighed.

‘I really can’t understand him.’

Chapter 38: A leader who is more like a beggar! (3)

“… are you alright?”

“Yes, cough! I am fine.”

“Are you really fine?”

“Really fine, cough! Cough!”

“You don’t look it….”

Hyun Jong’s face creased, looking at Chung Myung. He was speechlessly staring at Chung Myung; he looked withered as if he was just skin stretched over bone with a face that was pale like a ghost.

‘How bad could his health be?’

No matter how he looked at it, this kid seemed to be on the verge of starvation. It was likely that people would think that the other disciples were snatching away his food.

‘He wasn’t like this when he first came here.’

Hyun Jong turned his head and asked Un Am.

“What did the medical practitioner say?”

“That he was out of qi.”

“Qi?”

“Yes, they said that excessive training has caused damage to his pure Qi.”

“Huh!”

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung.

“Child. You practiced until you damaged your pure qi! Why would you do such a thing?”

‘It wasn’t like that.’

Training his ass!

Chung Myung hadn’t properly trained since he entered Mount Hua!

Of course, that’s all the medical practitioner could say. It was true that his fragile body tapped into the pure qi in his body and damaged it. How could a child who just began learning martial arts shatter their qi? Naturally, the only explanation was over-training.

It was a strange misunderstanding, but he decided to go along with it at this time.

“I apologize, sect leader. I just wanted to learn the martial arts of Mount Hua as soon as possible…”

“Huh, this young one is quite good.”

The sect leader nodded his head as if he began to like Chung Myung even more.

Chung Myung didn’t lie! It was true at heart!

“Eating quickly will spoil the stomach. What are we to do now that you are sick?”

“Be more careful, child.”

“Yes, yes.”

Hyun Jong smiled in satisfaction.

The child in front of him was Mount Hua’s good luck charm, and he was a devoted disciple to the core.

“Right. Did you enjoy the tea?”

“I don’t really enjoy it.’

Chung Myung shrugged it off.

‘Maybe I would enjoy alcohol.’

The tea was too strong for Chung Myung. Unlike alcohol which stimulated the throat, tea was just grassy water.

Even his Sahyung couldn’t understand why Chung Myung loved alcohol so much.

‘Is there a law that all sect leaders of Mount Hua should enjoy tea?’

In the past, too, the sect leaders loved tea. And in Chung Myung’s eyes, the long tradition of people liking it was unusual.

Sect leader carefully handed the tea to Chung Myung, and he took it with both hands.

“It is a pity you don’t enjoy it, but please taste this tea.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung quickly drank the tea in one gulp without even appreciating the fragrance.

“…”

There was a greater pleasure in enjoying the aroma of tea, but to Chung Myung, tea didn’t seem like anything more than hot water.

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung with a sad face as he put down the teacup.

“How was it?”

“It’s cold.”

“…”

There was a subtle disappointment in the sect leader’s face, but Chung Myung was being honest.

“Khum. Right.”

Hyun Jong decided to blow away the awkwardness by coughing, as his expression gently relaxed.

“I have called you here to reward you for your recent achievements. Thanks to you, Mount Hua was able to get out of this crisis. You did an amazing job.”

“I haven’t done anything.”

“How could you say that? If it weren’t for you, we would have all been on the streets right now.”

“I just happened to walk past it, and I accidentally stumbled onto that chest.”

“Huhu. What a coincidence.”

Hyung Jong shook his head.

“No, there is no such thing as a coincidence in this world. Everything is the result of a connection.”

Chung Myung nodded his head. Hyun Jong just said it to himself, but it seemed like it was directed at him.

‘I mean, at times he is extremely sharp.’

“Isn’t that right? Un Am?”

“Yes, sect leader. Also, even if it was a coincidence, the contribution made was very significant. Besides, since you weren’t greedy and informed the sect leader right away, how could we dare call your devotion small?”

“Right, right.”

Hyun Jong touched his beard.

“Yes.”

Then he looked at Chung Myung with warm eyes.

“It is only natural to give a reward to the one who made this possible. Mount Hua wishes to reward you. That was why we called you.”

“Reward?”

“Yes. Is there anything you want?”

Chung Myung was a little confused.

Was there something he wanted?

“It would be a lie to say that you could give up such wealth with no regrets. If you need, we can even return a suitable sum of wealth.”

“Money is not needed.”

“Hmm?”

Hyun Jong was a bit shocked.

“You don’t need wealth?”

“Yes. Mount Hua already provides me with food and clothing, even if I take the money, where would I use it? There’s nowhere in Mount Hua to use it.”

“Huhuhu, right.”

Hyun Jong smiled.

‘The way of Dao.’

No matter what, it wasn’t easy to give up on wealth. Just because he can’t spend it now doesn’t mean that he can’t spend it in the future.

Seeing him refuse the wealth, it seemed like he was a child with no greed—a child who was on the path of Dao.

However, Chung Myung’s inner thoughts were very different from the warm interpretation Hyun Jong had of him.

‘How much could you even give me?’

The sect leader’s secret warehouse had become Chung Myung’s personal hideout. Inside there was an amount of wealth that would drive others crazy and drop Hyun Jong’s jaw to the floor.

Chung Myung was already the richest man in Hua-Um. So, he didn’t need some minor wealth given by this sect leader.

“Then what do you want? I could allow you to learn more advanced techniques which aren’t normally allowed.”

“I don’t really want techniques either.”

“… Huh? Is that so?”

“Yes.”

“Do you find these techniques meaningless?”

Chung Myung shook his head.

“It isn’t like that. This disciple doesn’t know much, but I think there is meaning in progressing through the martial arts one step at a time in accordance with the techniques passed down by our predecessors.”

Hyun Jong was shocked.

“Is that so?”

“Yes. Didn’t you say that eating too quickly will spoil the stomach?”

“I did.”

“I think the same applies to martial arts. I will learn it slowly and progress.”

“Yes, right. You are absolutely right.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

The more they spoke, the more he liked the kid. Has a child who knows nothing of martial arts already started following the path of Dao?

‘Where did he learn all this?’

Hyun Jong couldn’t hide his excitement, but Chung Myung had a different thought.

‘Who is giving whom martial arts! You jerk!’

Still, Chung Myung struggled to determine how he would hand over the rest of the techniques he had left out this time.

It would have been better if he had given it to them all at once. However, the human mind is strange. If you give a man both a gold and silver bar simultaneously, his focus would mostly be on the gold and would think less of the silver.

The same was true with martial arts. If all of them were given at once, would they know the value of each technique?

‘I need to pay attention to every single one of these things. Sahyung, I was wrong, I’m sorry.’

He was sorry that he listened through one ear and let it spill out the other. He should have tried to understand how hard being a sect leader was.

Looking at Mount Hua through the eyes of his Sahyung, Chung Myung could imagine how difficult things were in the past.

Although it was difficult to atone for the dead, Chung Myung vowed to do his best for Mount Hua now.

“It is good that you have no greed, but it will be difficult for me. Then, there must be something you need, right?”

‘Something I need.’

What could Chung Myung need?

First, he could ask for some freedom which would let him move around more. That was more urgent than anything right now.

“Sect leader. I am not lazy when it comes to martial arts.”

“I can see that by looking at you.”

“…”

Chung Myung coughed and continued.

“But I think there’s a limit to only learning in this place. I want to see the wide world once in a while. Please give me permission to go down the mountain whenever I want.”

“Hm.”

Hyun Jong frowned a little.

“I understand your intentions, but it is against the rules of Mount Hua. Your contribution is great enough, but if we do that, others may complain that we’re giving you preferential treatment. Let me think about it.”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

“Is there anything else?”

Chung Myung, who was worried, opened his eyes wide.

“Sect leader!”

“Hm?”

“As you can see, my body isn’t great.”

“Yes, anyone can see that.”

“And the doctor said I damaged my qi.”

“Yes, I’ve heard.”

“So, could you give me vitality pills?”

“… vitality pills?”

“Yes. Mount Hua’s vitality pill. Don’t most sects usually have something like that?”

Hyun Jong laughed.

“Huhuh. Right. Vitality pill. Right. That sounds nice. Is there anything better to supplement the body and return it to its original state?”

“Yes! Right!”

“Huhuhu! Right, vitality pill. Right. The merit you put in is certainly enough.”

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung.

“Didn’t you say you wanted to go to Hua-Um?”

“Huh?”

“Of course, it is against the rules, but considering what you’ve accomplished I can grant you that much. Un Am!”

“Yes, sect leader!”

“In the name of Mount Hua’s sect leader, when disciple Chung Myung wishes to head down to Hua-Um he will not need permission from others.”

“Yes!”

“However, Chung Myung, you must keep within Hua-Um. Furthermore, you are directly responsible for your own actions and keeping out of trouble while there. Do you understand?”

“Yes. But…”

Chung Myung asked, tilting his head.

“The vitality pill?”

“Also, be sure not to neglect your training when traveling.”

“…”

“Huhuhu. Now then, go.”

“A–no. wait. Sect leader. The vitality—”

“I have high expectations for you! Keep your head high!”

“—yes.”

“Good”

“Take care. Sect leader.”

Hyun Jong smiled as Chung Myung bowed and walked out.

‘What the hell, I’m suffering out here! That stingy old man should just give me some pills!’

Huhuhu, I don’t even have vitality pills for myself; you think I could give one to you, brat?“

Chapter 39: A leader who is more like a beggar! (4)

Hyun Jong, Un Am and Hyun Sang remained in the sect leader’s residence after Chung Myung left.

“What do you think?”

Un Am smiled at Hyun Jong’s question.

“He seems to understand the path of Dao.”

“You felt the same way too.”

Hyun Jong smiled happily.

It was true that Chung Myung seemed great. Why not? Thanks to him, Mount Hua was saved from extinction. There was no enemy invasion or internal strife; instead, money caused the issue entirely. Thankfully, they were able to avoid the most disgraceful situation where Mount Hua, with its long history and tradition, lost their sect because of such a petty issue.

So, from Hyun Jong’s point of view, Chung Myung was worthy of extra care.

But now, the evaluation was unrelated to his contributions.

“Even if he is a child, there is a lot of depth in his words. His language can be rough at times, but it is understandable when considering his age.”

“Right.”

Un Am’s thoughts deepened the impression Hyun Jong had.

It didn’t feel like talking to a child when speaking with Chung Myung. It wasn’t just because of how he spoke. Rather, there was nothing child-like about him.

What could it be?

‘Am I the only one who feels it?’

He couldn’t put it into words. The scent of an experienced man came from the child.

‘I can’t explain it in any way other than the Dao.’

Un Am tilted his head slightly.

“Unlike a child, he has deep thoughts. He seems to always consider what he says before speaking. He is a smart child in many ways.”

“Right.”

“If nothing happens… it will be possible for him to lead the next generation of Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong nodded silently. He then looked at Hyun Sang.

“What do you think?”

Hyun Sang had only silently watched the entire thing until now.

“Don’t you know that I don’t have eyes for judging people, sect leader?”

“Really now, all I am asking is how you feel about him.”

“Feel…”

Hyun Sang closed his eyes.

Time passed slowly. And as he thought for a long time, he said.

“That child doesn’t seem like a child.”

“…”

“I know that children who have lived a rough life usually have deep thoughts. But that simply means they are more mature for their age; it doesn’t mean they behave as adults.”

Hyun Sang, who glanced around, continued.

“But that child isn’t precocious, he speaks and behaves like a grown man, to the point where I would like to dig in and see what’s hidden inside his mind.”

“Do you believe he’s hiding something?”

“I don’t mean it in a bad way. But…”

Hyun Sang didn’t say more.

“I understand.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“I know what everyone is thinking, but don’t worry too much. As you can see, isn’t he a child?”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

“We aren’t the kind to use people, we are here to nurture people. If it is a good seed, we help by letting them grow their talents, and if they have a problem we need to lead them to fix that problem.”

“You’re right.”

“Un Am.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“How is the construction going?”

“It is difficult to replenish all the materials due to the steep hills. We are cutting down trees as much as possible, but we can’t speed up much since it takes time to dry and trim the cut trees.”

“I see.”

Hyun Jong brushed his beard with a serious face and asked.

“Are you displeased with me, who only cares about money now?”

“Of course not, sect leader.”

“Please understand. Mount Hua is being reborn now. When a person makes a new resolution or sets a new will, they must refine their attitude and change their thoughts accordingly. This is no different for the sect itself. The sect should be re-built to obviously convey Mount Hua’s meaning and determination.”

“Sect leader is right.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“Sajae.’

“Yes, sect leader.”

Hyun Sang bowed his head slightly.

“Please finish interpreting the newly acquired martial arts books as soon as possible. However, I don’t mean to rush you. The fate of Mount Hua will change depending on how well we can pass these techniques to our students.”

“I will make sure that there is not an inch of laxity.”

“I trust you.”

Seeing Hyun Jong, who was immersed in thoughts, Hyun Sang’s face hardened.

‘Should I tell him?’

No.

Sect leader was currently envisioning the future of Mount Hua, which will continue for thousands of years. He shouldn’t be bothered by a measly story now.

‘But…’

Hyun Sang sighed.

When he discovered what happened, he felt so shocked by it. However, he couldn’t get rid of his growing doubts lately as he kept digging deeper into the process of interpreting these books.

‘For a book which was at least 100 years old, the paper was too clean and maintained.’

And there were traces of ink smeared here and there. If his suspicion was correct, then the book wasn’t from the past but recently written.

Then who?

Who could recreate martial arts exclusively practiced in Mount Hua? It didn’t make sense. If anyone could do such a thing, it would be better for them to come and directly speak to the sect leader. Then the entire Mount Hua would support the man like a king.

It means that someone was helping Mount Hua but didn’t want to reveal their identity.

Hyun Sang, shook his head.

He shouldn’t overthink.

He was worried about some conspiracy, so he reviewed the martial arts repeatedly, but no matter how much he looked, it was genuine. There was nothing wrong or misleading in there. The strange thing was that he couldn’t find anything out of place.

‘Let’s review it one more time.’

If anything was strange, he could always tell the sect leader.

“Ugh. A sect which even beggars wouldn’t come too!”

Chun Myung kicked a stone.

“What the hell did you all do with all the vitality pills left behind!”

He could guess from the look on the sect leader’s face. It was clear that there were no pills left in Mount Hua.

It was hopeless.

If they couldn’t make the pills because they didn’t have money then, now that they had money, the only answer is…

‘I would need to wait for now.’

Right. However, Hyun Jong chose to change the subject and gave permission to leave the sect instead of talking about the pills.

“Not a single thing is right here!”

His stomach hurt.

Even if someone deliberately planned to destroy Mount Hua, they wouldn’t pick such a variety of ways.

No martial arts, no pills, no people, no money!

“Not a thing goes well. Just my luck!”

He was upset, but what could he do? It was all his karma. Chung Myung licked his lips and patted his stomach.

‘Ha, what a pain in the ass.’

His body didn’t recover as easily as he hoped. He thought it would be fine dealing with the side effects, but using his internal qi in a child’s body whose musculature wasn’t complete injured him more than expected.

‘The problem is that it’s not enough.’

His body wasn’t recovering. Perhaps, it was because he kept expecting his childish body to function at the level of his previous body.

That’s it.

In his past life, if Chung Myung had heard that a child had tapped into their internal qi, he would have lifted the child and spanked him on the ass.

That was how dangerous it was.

But that was how humans are. Others shouldn’t do it, but they themselves could.

The problem he was facing was that the one disgruntled and suffering was none other than himself. Since his body was not recovering, his training slowed, and since his training slowed, his martial arts were lacking.

And he was too severely concentrating on re-building Mount Hua. If things kept going like this, it would take another half-year to recover, at least.

“I might die within half a year!”

He could have handled it in an older man’s body. But in such a young body, it was too fatal. Half a year in a young body was like a decade for him.

It wasn’t just about recovering and feeling comfortable. Now, Chung Myung was trying to build a perfect foundation. Wasn’t he still in a human body?

Children grow and change. There is an ideal time for growth; the opportunity is lost if the timing is missed. It’s necessary to build the basics and lay the groundwork for your future achievements when learning martial arts.

“I need to find a way.”

Chung Myung had a severe face.

“I need to find a vitality pill….”

A weakened qi can be healed. If it can’t be resolved with daily cultivation, he would have to find another source to repair it.

So, there are two ways.

Either receive pure qi from someone else or eat a precious vitality pill.

However, there was no way Chung Myung could find someone who would transfer qi to him, and there was currently no way he could get his hands on a vitality pill.

It wasn’t something that money could buy. Besides, wasn’t Chung Myung a child? It was impossible for anyone in Hua-Um to give him a pill.

No other way.

“Ah, really! You don’t even have dog shit for medicine! What kind of sect doesn’t have a pill! You rotten bastards!”

In the past, vitality pills were rolling on the floor of Mount Hua. It was natural to eat one pill.

And the Plum Blossom Pill?

“That wasn’t even medicine.”

The Plum Blossom Pills were so common that they weren’t treated as pills. If Chung Myung were a little stronger, he wouldn’t even bother looking for a Plum Blossom Pill.

It could be helpful for him now, but they were just useless herbs that didn’t even increase his

stamina in the past.

Chung Myung used to use them to recover from hangovers.

‘They had pretty great results.’

When you secretly drink alcohol, and the hangover doesn’t leave the body, eat a bunch of Plum Blossom Pills! Although it had no value in training and martial arts, it was the best thing for a hangover.

Of course, if Sahyung knew of his thoughts, he would have hit Chung Myung.

‘So, he hid the Plum Blossom Pi—’

“Uh?”

Chung Myung’s body, which had been walking, came to a standstill.

“Hangover relief?”

He turned his head.

“Why didn’t I think of that?”

Right! The pills!

No! no!

Right! They must be there!

Mount Hua’s troublemaker…no, Mount Hua’s former troublemaker, Chung Myung’s secret vitality pill!

“Sometimes a rotten mind is needed!”

Chung Myung giggled at his past self and started running towards a cliff in the distance with all his might.

Chapter 40: A leader who is more like a beggar! (5)

Chung Myung raised his head with a grim look. Clenching his jaw, he bent his neck up.

Little more.

Just a little more.

And a little more.

“…”

It was only when his neck was tilted to the extent that it looked like it would break, was he able to see what he wanted.

A shaved cliff.

A terrifying cliff, endlessly high with the top obscured by mist, filled his eyes.

“… crazy.”

A smile on his lips.

Dangerously Disconnected cliff was what the people living in Mount Hua called it. The highest and the most dangerous cliff, famous for being rugged even among the five mountains.

And in the middle of this perilous cliff was the place Chung Myung was looking for.

The most secretive location in the world. Very few people from Mount Hua would come here, and even less knew about the secret.

“Well, I’m the only one who knows.”

In the middle of the cliff was a small cave that couldn’t be found without climbing the cliff directly.

The steep peak was a place where the people of Mount Hua were prohibited from training. However, Chung Myung was someone who reveled in being disobedient. So, he enjoyed coming here frequently.

Then, by chance, he discovered a small cave in the middle of the cliff, and from then on, he used it as his exclusive hiding spot.

“It helped me out a lot.”

For example, drinking alcohol while avoiding the eyes of his sahyung, eating meat while hiding from his sahyung, or taking a nap while ignoring his sahyung…

“Oh sahyung.”

‘Why did you even keep me alive?’

He should have beat him to death.

Now that he had changed his position and began acting as a guardian for Mount Hua, Chung Myung could understand his sahyung’s constant lectures. If anyone in the current Mount Hua behaved like the old Chung Myung, he would beat them to death.

Even Chung Myung wanted to kill his old self.

“No, was I crazy…?”

It felt like his neck was going to break. No sane person would even consider using the middle of a cliff like this as a shelter.

And now Chung Myung has a weak and damaged body.

Chung Myung, the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, could have happily skipped his way up this cliff. But it’s impossible for Chung Myung, the third-class disciple, to climb this.

Why! Why did he have to be a child!

There was no place to step and no place to grab. The cliff was too smooth for him to move up.

This cliff was always like that.

“… I’ve had it. Really.”

He wanted to hurt his past self for choosing this place!

“Phew.”

Taking a deep breath, Chung Myung looked up at the cliff again.

“Still, I need to go!”

There was no going back.

If someone asked why, Chung Myung would answer.

“There are vitality pills in there! Damn it!”

If his memory was clear, then there should be Plum Blossom pills and many other pills in that cave!

Because that cave was where he would get drunk and sleep, the pills he used to relieve his hangovers should also be there.

‘There’s no other solution.’

No matter how much the alcohol kicked his ass in the morning, it’s still a precious vitality pill, but they were hidden in a cave to recover from hangovers.

This wasn’t something any sane person would do.

But thanks to that, Chung Myung had a chance.

Chung Myung looked at the steep cliff with a determined face and turned around. He strode into the forest on the other side.

“Phewwwwww!”

He took a deep breath.

“It’s crazy no matter how much I think about it.”

Chung Myung was now standing on top of that cliff. He came to the edge of it with a long rope, woven from vines, in his hands.

No matter how much he thought, climbing up was impossible since it was difficult to climb a smooth cliff, and the height was too much for him.

With a child’s body, it was too harsh to climb up.

Then how about descending down to the cave from the top? It must be more manageable than climbing up. But the problem was…

“It is ten times as dangerous.”

Chung Myung glanced down and gulped. He couldn’t even see the ground. All he could see was the cliff and a veil of mist hiding what lay beneath.

He stepped back and grabbed his chest.

“Ah fuck! I’m shaking.”

He enjoyed being here in the past, like walking into his own personal garden, but now it felt like the entrance to hell. How many vines did he have to combine to get himself down with a single rope? How many people would think of climbing down this cliff with just a rope?

Right now, he had to do it, no other choice or option.

“You only live once, not twice…no, this is my second life….”

Chung Myung tied the rope in his hand to a nearby stone. This was going to be his one lifeline. He pulled on the rope several times to ensure it would hold him and then stood at the edge of the cliff.

“Haaa.”

Saving Mount Hua is so difficult. He even had to risk his life like this.

“Damn it!”

Chung Myung cursed loudly and boldly started going down the cliff.

It was never easy to go down a steep cliff. It was challenging to find any stable footholds. Chung Myung leaned his body on the cliff to move slowly and attached himself to the walls.

After struggling and yelling out, Chung Myung slowly moved down.

“Ahh! Fuck! Damn it! If I had known I would have learned acrobatics!”

It was something that Chung Myung didn’t learn in the past.

It was then.

The stone ledge he stepped on as he moved down crumbled.

Tuk! Tuk!

Chung Myung blankly stared at the falling stones. The rocks bounced off the cliff and burrowed into the thick mist below.

…….Tyk!

After a long time, a noise lightly echoed back.

“… Whoa.”

It takes so long to fall to the bottom from this height. If Chung Myung fell, there would be no corpse left to find. Realizing that, he unconsciously gulped in fear.

The Plum Blossom Sword Saint isn’t afraid of anything, not even the Heavenly Demon, but that’s if the opponent was mortal. What about the ground below him? Between fighting the heavenly demon or falling to his death, it’s a no-brainer which is worse.

Imagine dying here and going to the afterlife.

How would his Sahyung greet him? He would be downgraded from the hero who killed the Heavenly Demon to the idiot who fell from a cliff.

“Shit.”

Chung Myung began to move. It was a little awkward at first, but after a few repetitions, he was moving like a lizard attached to the wall.

‘It has to be down there.’

Chung Myung, who was descending, frowned. There was a huge crack in the middle of the cliff.

‘Going inside will be tough.’

So, he would have to jump…

“Phew.”

Taking a deep breath, he looked down.

“I am Plum Blossom Sword Saint!”

Can’t be afraid of this!

He boldly threw his body. At the same time that he let go, he cried out.

“Ahhhhhh!”

He reached out and grabbed onto a protruding stone. Hanging off the rock, Chung Myung shouted.

“Ugh! I am scared!”

But thanks to the jump, he traveled a lot…

Tuk!

“Huh?”

Chung Myung looked up. The stone he was hanging onto…

“No.”

Tutuk!

“…”

No, it’s—

Help out a little, you conscience-less cliff.

Crack

The stone broke, and Chung Myung’s body began to fall.

“Oh, my god! Oh, my god!”

Chung Myung desperately swung his arms and legs in the air.

‘What would happen if I fell from here?’

Death. Certain death.

‘Am I going to die?’

Die? Chung Myung?

It was then.

Thud!

Suddenly, a strong shock was felt from Chung Myung’s waist, and his body floated into the air.

“Huh?”

The swaying rope came into Chung Myung’s sight.

‘Right!’

Tuk!

After bouncing a few times, the violent movements began to settle. Chung Myung, hanging listlessly from the rope, sighed in lament. A moment later, he burst into laughter and yelled.

“Indeed! A man must be prepared!”

He wasn’t sure if the rope would hold up well as it was made of vines, but it turned out to be strong enough since it was only holding a child’s body.

Chung Myung slowly looked around.

‘There!’

His eyes shone. A bulge that wasn’t far from where he was hanging. Below there was the hiding place of the former Chung Myung. Out of habit, he measured the rope, and it seemed like he guessed the right length!

“Kuak! Heaven is helping me out!”

Grabbing the rope, he took a deep breath. First, he was still hanging in midair from the rope. He needed to cling to the cliff…

“Ugh!”

Chung Myung began to swing his body, the still rope, then began to shake back and forth.

‘I need to find the right angle.’

Woong!

Wooong!

Chung Myung’s body, clinging to the rope, gradually swung closer and closer to the cliff.

“Ugh!”

He reached out and grabbed the cliff, but the rock was so smooth that he couldn’t take hold of it.

“Once more!”

Chung Myung moved and kicked the cliff to straighten his body. And then with both hands, he would hold the—

Tuk!

“What?”

Chung Myung’s head shot up like a thunderbolt at the sound. His eyes quickly found what he was looking for.

The rope was halfway torn.

“Ehhh”

No. That can’t be true.

Usually, the line should stay until he reaches the cliff, and then it should break…

Riiiip.

“… NOOO! UAHHHHHHH!”

Chung Myung fell along with the momentum from rebounding towards the cliff.

“Hiiikkk! I am dying! Oh, my god!”

Since he was already close to the cliff because of the rebound. Chung Myung raised his qi and tried to grab hold of the cliff.

Crack!

The bones, which were overburdened, broke.

“Ah shit!”

His wrist couldn’t handle the weight of the speed he was moving at. Desperately, he thrust his other hand with qi and held onto the cliff.

Crack!

The result was the same.

“Ah what!? They aren’t some flimsy twigs! Why are the bones breaking down so easily!? What sort of damned body was I given!?’

Live a little more!

Chung Myung swung his arms and legs like he was swimming in the air, but somehow it didn’t seem to work.

“Uah!”

If the hands don’t work, use the body!

Like a frog, he clung to the cliff; instead of his broken wrist, he held the cliff with his arms and legs.

“Ahhh! Hot! Hot!”

With his body scraping against the sheer cliff, an immense, scorching heat could be felt. Despite the pain, it worked, and his falling speed reduced dramatically.

Now, all he had to do was find that protruding cave.

Chung Myung lowered his gaze.

He couldn’t find it. Instead…

He was able to find something better than it. A much safer place than the protruding cave.

“Hehe. Land.”

It was the ground.

It was a sudden crash.

Chung Myung’s smiling body was plastered to the ground.

Thuuuuuud!

“Kuak!”

A cloud of dust scattered around. Chung Myung’s body trembled as it was buried in the dust.

“I am… alive!”

Thanks to slowing down the fall, he escaped death. However, his entire body was shattered; every single spot ached and hurt.

“Kuak!”

After struggling in place for a while, Chung Myung managed to drag his weary body up and stared at the cliff with searing, scarlet eyes full of anger.

“… I will climb you no matter what means I have to use, you damn disgusting cliff!”

Chapter 41: Because it is Mount Hua (1)

“Kuaaak!”

A dark cave.

A bandaged hand, covered in tattered cloth, pulled itself up to the lightless cave’s entrance.

“Achhhh…”

Soon after, a face which couldn’t be more distorted suddenly appeared.

“Ahhhh!”

Tak! Tak!

Chung Myung, who reached out and grabbed the floor with both hands, crawled into the cave.

“Ugh! Ugh! Ugh! Plum Blossom Sword Saint, my ass!”

What was he thinking hiding in such a place? Did his head go mad after all that training in the mountains?

‘Ah, right, the Plum Blossom Sword Saint is me.’

“Ahhhh, I’m dying.”

Chung Myung, lying flat on the floor, began to curse. When he realized that he had somehow made it into the cave, he strangely felt as if he would cry.

‘It was really close.’

Climbing up a cliff with broken wrists wasn’t an easy task. Any person with common sense would have known how dangerous it would be and given up.

Unfortunately, Chung Myung was a man who had a brain but no thoughts.

“Right! If I didn’t climb up now, it would have just wasted more time!”

Chung Myung yelled as he kept trying to make excuses for what he did as he lay on the floor, suffering and shifting around.

“Ah, this old man is dying.”

Actually, he is a child now. He gets so confused at times.

Still, somehow, he managed to live. He made a stronger rope this time; if the rope had broken again this time, he would have really gone to see the King of the Underworld.

If that happened, he was sure that the King of the Underworld would have a hard time holding back his laughter. Now he felt glad he didn’t die.

“Kuak!”

Chung Myung, who forced himself to straighten his crooked waist, looked around.

He couldn’t see anything.

Not because his body hurt that much, but because it was too dark to see anything.

“Tch. This is probably….”

He stretched out his hands and caught on to some form of fabric.

“Right.”

Pulling the cloth held in his fingertips, it was easily swept away, revealing a light that brightened the inside of the cave. Looking at the glowing light, Chung Myung smiled.

“Really, I was something else.”

The light was clear and brilliantly shining.

One cannot light a fire inside a cave. Since the cave inclined with the entrance at the bottom, it would quickly fill with smoke if a fire was ignited. No one could drink alcohol with such acrid smoke permeating the air.

To be precise, it would be possible for Chung Myung, but who would want to drink in such a place?

‘Which is why I brought night light lamps and put them here.’

How costly they were.

‘It’s one of the offerings I slipped away from Mount Hua.’

In the past, so many things came in and out of the sect; even if one or two things went missing, nobody would notice.

Of course, his sahyung and the finance minister, who had to settle the book-keeping, would have vomited blood if they’d heard his thoughts.

“What good would remembering the past do?”

Once again, with a calm feeling, he realized how ruthless the Plum Blossom Sword Saint was.

‘Ah, that’s me. I keep forgetting that.’

Chung Myung looked around at the brightly lit cave.

“Hmmm.”

Inside, which was neither large nor small, there was only one bed to lie down on, a small tea table, and a chest.

Something felt wrong. It was weird how these things stayed the same despite the years that had passed.

“Ehh. Is this how things end up?”

Suddenly, he came to a realization.

What if he had died without being revived? And someone from Mount Hua discovered this place in the future? Wouldn’t it have caused an uproar, thinking this was a secret master practitioner’s hideout?

What if someone fell off the cliff and stumbled into it?

“Ugh! The bloody cliff!”

All Chung Myung wanted was to hang out in a quiet place and drink, but the people of the later generations wouldn’t understand that and might think there was some secret hidden here.

They would think that the hidden cave was the personal hideout of a man going against the principles of Mount Hua.

“But aren’t all cliffs used for such purposes?”

Chung Myung walked towards the chest. With his hurting hands, he carefully opened the lid. The dust, which had accumulated over a hundred years, scattered through the cave as the lid was lifted.

“Cough! Cough! Cough!”

Waving away the dust, Chung Myung looked inside the chest.

The first thing which caught his eye was a bottle of alcohol. When he saw various liquor bottles stored inside, he began to salivate.

‘No, no! Alcohol isn’t important right now!’

He despairingly pushed the bottles out of his sight and then looked at the small box remaining in the chest.

‘This is it!’

Chung Myung quickly grabbed the box and pulled it out. It was a bit heavier than he remembered.

“Pheww.”

Taking a deep breath, Chung Myung carefully opened the lid. At the same time, the strong scent of the Plum Blossom Pills spread throughout the cave.

It felt as if Plum Blossom trees in full bloom filled the surroundings.

Click!

When the lid opened completely, he could see round objects filling the box. From the bottom, the box was filled to the brim with pills and sitting on top we five perfectly round snow-white items.

“Wow!”

An overwhelming sense of excitement caused tears to flood Chung Myung’s eyes.

What was filling the box wasn’t just some random cushioning materials, but actual Plum Blossom Pills!

“So crazy!”

No matter how common the Plum Blossom Pills were, who would use them as cushioning? How greedy can a person be to covet them and use them like this? If Sahyung had seen this, he would have grabbed Chung Myung by the neck.

“Be grateful I didn’t use the truly precious pills. Sahyung!”

Chung Myung was making excuses to his dead peers from embarrassment.

But he couldn’t touch the most precious pill, the Supreme Pill. Like any other sect, it was a treasured pill that could only be handled by the highest-level authority in Mount Hua.

The Supreme Pill can only be taken out with the permission of a medical practitioner and the Sect elder.

On the other hand, any of the elders in the sect can take out the plum blossom pill. Of course, there were other pills more precious than plum blossom pills, and those too could only be handled by powerful elders.

Elders like Chung Myung! The strongest and most powerful in the sect!

-The strongest troublemaker of Mount Hua!

It felt like he was hallucinating and hearing voices from somewhere.

For now, Chung Myung needed to get these things. With this, he would be able to heal his body.

Chung Myung took the white pills, the snow plum blossom pills, from the box very carefully. He used these as hangover pills in the past, but now they were precious medicine for him. To Chung Myung, these pills were more precious than money.

“Ah! I am nervous!”

Chung Myung placed the box in the chest and looked at the snow plum blossom pill in his hand.

A pure scent constantly flowed from this white pill. Just smelling it made his body feel more comfortable.

“It is said that people don’t know the importance of things until they’re gone.”

When Mount Hua stood at the top of the world, no one would even look at these pills. Only higher-tiered pills held value then.

Wasn’t that why Chung Myung was able to bring so many plum blossom pills with him?

Not just Chung Myung, it happened all over Mount Hua. It was a natural thing. There was no shortage of pills in Mount Hua, so who would pay attention to the lesser valued ones?

But now, he’s in such a precarious situation. The pills he regarded so lightly have come back with a crushing weight.

“Oh, my God. How did my life come to this?”

He’d rather die than suffer like this.

Chung Myung gathered his thoughts and sat down quickly. He would surely have enough time to lament over things once the task was done. Now, he had to recover his weak body and build more strength.

He crossed his legs as he sat down and threw a snow plum blossom pill into his mouth. The moment it entered his mouth, it melted without even giving him a chance to chew.

A fresh scent filled Chung Myung’s mouth as he began to meditate without letting such thoughts distract him.

Merely eating a pill doesn’t automatically increase your strength. Your strength can only be improved if the qi in the pills is properly absorbed into the body.

So, a subtle problem arises here.

When you’re young, you can’t fully absorb the energy even if you eat a powerful pill. This is because children lack the ability to properly operate their qi.

On the other hand, what about once you’re old enough to manage your qi?

The effects would be weakened because your body had already developed and created its own energy reserves.

Pills are only made to fill in the qi lacking in the body, not to add to what’s already full.

‘If people could get stronger from pills, then the Shaolin sect bastards would have been at it and become the best in the world.’

A young body couldn’t absorb the full extent of the qi in the pills, so what about Chung Myung?

‘I will suck it deep into the core!’

He knew how to perfectly manage his qi.

He knew the teachings of the past and had experience.

“Phew.”

Once the pill entered the stomach, the qi began to release.

Woong!

The energy was pulsating within Chung Myung’s body. He felt the great flow of qi which he hadn’t felt in a long time.

‘Nervous!’

Fill the dantian with qi and prevent the excess qi from breaking out? That shouldn’t be difficult for Chung Myung. However, what Chung Myung had to do now wasn’t so simple.

He had to fill the qi into his body to repair his innate true qi.

Chung Myung’s thick and dull mind had to act sharp like a blade. But he decided to go a step further, sharpening his mind like a needle; he perfectly controlled the pill’s qi and pushed it into the dantian.

‘Carefully. Slowly.’

Soft and delicate, as if he was handling a baby.

Inside Chung Myung’s mind, he held the qi in his hands and guided it.

However, the goal wasn’t just his dantian. It was the deepest core of the dantian. Where a pure internal qi is held in every human since birth.

‘No, I can’t!’

Chung Myung, who was about to push it into the dantian, suddenly pulled it back.

‘It’s impure.’

Pills were created by refining the excellent energy of spirit medicines found in nature. In other words, it can be said that these pills seek to extract and concentrate pure qi.

However, although this pill was Mount Hua’s pride, it was too impure to be used in Chung Myung’s dantian. If the qi inside his dantian was like pure water coming from the mountains, then the snow plum blossom pill would be akin to stagnant water.

So, he decided.

“I’ll filter it!”

If he could filter the qi, most of the impure qi could be discarded. Accepting the qi as it was, seemed meaningless. Hadn’t he come a long way to create the most complete and perfect foundation? He couldn’t ruin his progress by being hasty now.

‘Keep what’s pure and discard the rest!“

Qi circulated through his body. Gradually, it was shaved off little by little. Impurities in the pill mixed with impurities within his body and were slowly pushed out of him.

Soon, thick, dark sweat began to seep out of Chung Myung’s body.

Chapter 42: Because it is Mount Hua (2)

‘I am really going to die!’

The qi was chipped away. Chung Myung tried to make the most of what he could use, but there was nothing that could be used.

It was like trying to cut out the edible part of a completely rotten radish. The qi couldn’t reach the required standards and was pushed out of the body.

Wasn’t a pill something one used to improve the qi in their body? But now, Chung Myung was throwing it all out.

If the person who made the pill had seen it, they would have died frothing at the mouth.

‘Do you want me to lose everything!?’

This damned foundation!

Chung Myung gathered only the purest qi into his dantian, but it was far less than he had hoped for. Even a pill that was refined repeatedly to improve its quality was deemed impure by Chung Myung’s foundation.

Only a tiny portion of the qi could be used. Desperately leading the handful of pure qi, he pushed it into the dantian.

Woong!

Soon, the remaining essence merged with Chung Myung’s qi within his dantian and circulated throughout his body.

In an instant, everything changed. Chung Myung, who was sitting cross-legged, began to float.

Normally, it would be impossible for this to happen, even with a greater level of internal strength. However, because Chung Myung’s qi was so pure, this phenomenon, which transcended the amount of inner strength he had, began to occur.

Woong!

A clear, diaphanous qi went around the whole body, circulating once and again. It then began to filter out the impure energy.

‘No!’

This wasn’t what Chung Myung intended. He was thinking of recovering his lost qi, but the qi went against his will and started to regenerate his body.

Both his broken wrists instantly reset and attached as the bruises covering his body were restored entirely like they had never been there.

Shhh!

Sweat and impurities flowed from his pores like a cloud of steam. The dantian and even the blood vessels in his body began to open wider and wider.

Chung Myung titled his head.

“He-Heavenly Opening?”

The bottom dantian.

Qi, which started below the navel where the dantian is commonly located, forcibly opened the middle dantian in the chest; and even the upper dantian had opened now.

It was terrifying.

Everything in the world must follow a proper process. A child should first learn to crawl; maybe they could walk with some effort. But if a child learning to crawl suddenly tried to run, they would surely stumble and fail.

‘Need to stop it….’

The qi was thrashing about inside Chung Myung’s body. If he couldn’t control it, it would continue to rage and destroy his body.

The situation was quickly turning sour. Even if the process was helping his body heal, no one could be sure what the end result would be.

Chung Myung struggled to block the qi. However, it rebelled against his will and moved along its own path.

‘Shit, listen and stop already! You’re my energy, damn it!’

Chung Myung cursed in his mind, and the qi slowed down. It seemed like it realized who its master was.

But after a while, the qi began to run wild again.

‘Stop!’

Even if blocking the qi would hurt his body, he had to stop it as soon as possible.

Then, right when he gathered all of his will to suppress it.

-So, are you a Taoist or a martial artist?

‘Sahyung?’

It was the voice of his Sahyung echoing in his mind. Why?

No! This was something he had heard in his past life.

-Martial artists try to oppress and control the flow. But those who follow the path of Dao, let it be. You idiot. Where did your sense of logic come from? If you build a dam to stop the flowing water, it will simply flow over it.

Chung Myung’s body twitched.

-Let it be. If you leave it alone, everything will flow naturally. You wish to twist the rules of nature with the will of man? Stupid bastard. Humans are also a part of nature. How can a man compete with the all-encompassing nature?

Remembering his sahyung’s words, Chung Myung gave permission for the qi to flow freely. The moment he released control, the energy, which had been violently raging, began to flow smoothly and softly through his body.

As it circulated, the flowing stream grew larger and thicker, soon becoming a river that cascaded throughout his body.

How long had it been?

Blink!

Chung Myung suddenly opened his eyes. A supremely crystalline glare.

And…

Thud!

“Ouch!”

Chung Myung, who dropped from the air to the ground, touched his hips.

“What? Why was I floating?”

He never imagined that his body would float. He got up, rubbing his tingling butt.

“Phew. I was almost done for.”

It was dangerous. The slightest deviation would have paralyzed him or taken away his life. Falling off that cliff didn’t seem so scary now.

But the reward could be felt.

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung waved his wrist. The broken wrist was fully attached. Rather, it felt more robust than before.

It wasn’t just the wrist, either.

‘The impure qi.’

Chung Myung thought that his body had already washed away all impurities, but it was even more efficient and clean now. This was his second time removing the impure qi from his body. If he could do it again in the future, his body could reach unparalleled levels.

But the most significant changes were the meridians. It felt like his entire body was open.

Originally, his meridians were a small, thin stream flowing into a creak, but now they were wide like a river surging into the ocean.

“The internal qi has also increased.”

Considering that a year of accumulation would only increase his qi by a fingernail-sized margin, it was encouraging to improve so much overnight.

‘The pure innate qi has also recovered.’

All together.

“My dantian grew.”

For Chung Myung, the body is a vessel for his martial arts. If the dantian is small, then it will be limited. As he overcame a new wall, the dantian has grown and what it can withstand has expanded.

Right now, it was like a rat’s tail, but still, this was the foundation Chung Myung aimed to surpass his past with.

With a satisfied smile, he thought.

‘If it wasn’t for Sahyung, it would have been a disaster.’

Maybe he finally attained enlightenment after dying once. The words of Sahyung, which he always regarded as nagging, took on a new meaning and helped him when he needed it.

“I was just a swordsman.”

Not a Taoist.

Mount Hua was home to both Taoism and martial arts. But Chung Myung couldn’t call himself a Taoist.

Could he really help the current Mount Hua?

“Uhh.”

Chung Myung scratched his head. Such concerns would do him no good.

First, let’s just try something!

“If that doesn’t work, then try something else.”

Chung Myung was flustered as he walked. With each step, he was moving farther than expected but, thanks to his past experience, he adapted to it quite quickly.

Click!

Chung Myung took out the box of pills and pushed it into his sleeve.

“Tch. How unfortunate.”

Now, this was meaningless to him.

He could repair and grow his body, but the pill’s energy was only a catalyst serving as a medium for him; the pill itself did not contribute to his growth.

Compared to Chung Myung’s unique qi, it was nothing more than a lump of impurities. Things might have been better if it was the Supreme Pill.

It felt terrible to just use the pills as a medium. Anyone other than him would have experienced a much greater effect.

“Tch.”

Chung Myung hated how things were always tricky for him.

“Ehh!”

He closed his eyes to contemplate.

He didn’t need to feel bad; although he didn’t get much energy out of the snow plum blossom pill, he managed to achieve a result he couldn’t normally get no matter how many pills he took.

“I’m being greedy. Ah, Chung Myung, let’s only eat as much as you can handle.”

Chung Myung turned around…

Clank!

A couple of alcohol bottles that were in the chest were wrapped around his waist.

It’s not like he wanted to drink it. It was an action that stemmed from innocent curiosity; he simply wanted to know what alcohol aged for a hundred years would taste like.

Chung Myung, who finished taking the alcohol, stood at the entrance of the cave and glanced back.

“It feels weird.”

Traces of the past.

Mount Hua had changed so much, yet this cave remained the same. When Chung Myung was in this cave, it felt like he was taken back in time.

He missed it.

And more.

Chung Myung, who was silently looking into the cave, smiled.

‘I need to come here again some time.’

Not for drinking and playing around like in the past, but it was still a good place to come and rest.

“Well, not too often either. The past needs to stay in the past.”

He was Chung Myung, the Plum Blossom Sword Saint. However, that wasn’t who he was anymore. Now, he was Chung Myung, the third-class disciple.

Those bound by the past cannot advance into the future.

The past was a milestone that would lead his life to the right place.

“Then.”

Chung Myung walked out of the cave.

Swosh!

His body felt incomparably lighter than before, and he was able to move with far more proficiency and agility than before. His light feet slammed the cliff as he accelerated upwards.

“Ugh!”

Making multiple leaps and ascending quickly, Chung Myung made it to the top of the cliff.

“Not bad.”

A deep breath.

The fresh air on the summit lightly caressed him, then as it brushed his nose…

“Ugh!”

He felt nauseous.

It was then that he realized that his clothes were thick with filth. Chung Myung’s face frowned as he took off the clothes.

“What the hell is coming out of this body!”

Chung Myung removed his clothes, lifted them up with his fingertips, and took a deep breath.

“Oh, my god! Nothing makes sense! Where is the nearest stream?”

He would have to wash the clothes before heading back to the dorm.

Chung Myung turned and trudged down the mountain.

On that day, the innocent animals which had come to happily cool their throats in the stream had no way of knowing they would suffer a tragedy lasting several days to come.

Chapter 43: Because it is Mount Hua (3)

“Ahh. It’s cold!”

Dawn on the mountain is distinctly different from dawn on the plains.

When cold air meets the humidity of dawn, it creates a chill that penetrates the bones.

Walking through the early morning air, the third-class disciples left the dorm and headed to the training hall.

“I’m wide awake now.”

“I’m awake too, but my body doesn’t wake up at all. So tired…”

“You should have mediated.”

“Who does that at night?”

“Ah, right.”

While exchanging idle conversation, the third-class disciples took out their sandbags and stone bags from the hut prepared at the side of the gymnasium.

“By the way, how long do we have to do this?”

“Well, maybe until we are asked to stop?”

“Who will ask that?”

“You don’t know?”

All the disciples thought of one face.

‘That monster-like bastard.’

‘A scary jerk.’

Although they were all disciples of the same class, Chung Myung had completely subjugated them.

Since the training was difficult, some rebelled occasionally. However, once they were knocked into the ceiling of the dorms, they quickly settled down.

Jo Gul, the first to go against Chung Myung, and even Yoon Jong weren’t complaining, so how could the others rebel?

The disciples couldn’t even think about surpassing Jo Gul and Yoon Jong, who were better than them. From their point of view, even those two were monsters.

“But isn’t he a bit weird these days?”

“What?”

“He doesn’t look well, and he doesn’t come to train either.”

“… right!”

In the beginning, Chung Myung would participate in the training and torment the others, but he didn’t even show his face in recent days.

“Then, is it true?”

“Is what true?”

“The rumors that he had overloaded his internal qi.”

“Ah! No way!”

“No, no. Think about it. He is getting thinner and weaker each day, and he doesn’t seem to be in good health either, so he keeps skipping the training.”

“Well…”

“Maybe it would be different if he was lazy, but he isn’t. Isn’t it strange that a guy who trains three times as much as any of us suddenly stopped coming to train?”

“When you put it like that, it makes sense.”

All the disciples present were listening to the exchange.

“Then…”

Someone said something that shouldn’t have been said.

“Do we even still have to train?”

“…”

The faces of the third-class disciples suddenly hardened.

Actually, their feelings were no longer the same as they were at the start. In the beginning, they went to train because they were forced to, leaving them with aching bodies and discontent.

But now, they realized that they were getting stronger through the training. Although it was unfamiliar to physically train the body rather than cultivate their qi, they could clearly see their growing results.

Their lower body had become more stable.

Is there any greater joy for a martial artist than growing stronger? Although their bodies were tired and weary, they began to appreciate and enjoy the training.

But as soon as they heard that, the feelings they had been holding back began to take over.

‘I can’t take a leave every day, but….’

‘No, just once….’

‘Excessive training isn’t good either. I don’t think it would be bad to reduce it….’

Everyone’s thoughts changed.

‘Maybe, if Chung Myung isn’t here!’

Their poisonous thoughts continued until they reached the training hall. The early morning training, which was taken for granted, suddenly felt more annoying with these thoughts seducing their minds.

Well, they were children, so it was inevitable.

“Look, he isn’t here today either.”

“Is he really badly hurt?”

“Then… can’t we just back out?”

The decisive blow.

There were precisely three reasons why the disciples followed Chung Myung.

First, even if all the disciples rushed in, no one could take down Chung Myung.

Second, Chung Myung had the support of Un Geom, the overseer of their dorm. If a disciple steps out of line and can’t be controlled, you should bring it up with a superior, but what can you do when the superior is on their side?

And finally, Chung Myung was weirdly reasonable. When it came to training, he was a demon that would attack others and crush dissent; but he didn’t bully the others or make them do anything unreasonable to benefit himself just because he was stronger.

Because of that, they preferred how things were now rather than when they were disciplined under Jo Gul.

But now, the first of the three reasons collapsed.

‘Can’t we back out?’

‘He is already just skin and bones.’

‘Wouldn’t we win if we all work together?’

Their eyes began to shine with determination. Seeing that, Jo Gul sighed.

“Sahyung.”

“Let them be.”

Yoon Jong smiled.

“They’ll see the truth soon enough.”

It was then.

Kiiik!

Everyone’s heads turned to the side as the door to the White Blossom training hall opened. Only Chung Myung was missing. In other words, it had to be Chung Myung coming.

No one other than him could be coming here to train!

The door opened wide.

All the third-class disciples turned their heads.

“Eh! What!’

“It’s so dazzling!”

Something was shining brilliantly. Those who fought against the light and glanced at what was hidden within opened their eyes wide in shock.

Chung Myung was coming. Yep, it was definitely him.

But the man they were seeing wasn’t the same as yesterday. Clearly, Chung Myung was…

‘What is with him?’

‘Did he put oil on his face?’

‘Did he pick up some wild ginseng and eat it?’

The third-class disciples doubted their eyes.

Until yesterday, he was withered and weak; even dying wouldn’t have seemed strange, right? But now, he looked healthy, and there was a weird oil-like glow on his face.

‘We’re done for.’

‘We’ll have to train now.’

‘It was a nice dream.’

The disciples thought their dreams had flown away just as quickly as they arrived.

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung, who walked in, stood in front of them and spoke.

“Gentlemen.”

“…”

“This instructor of yours can’t help but feel sorry for you. I have been so ill that I neglected your training these days. I feel deeply responsible for this.’

“Ah. No.”

“It is fine. Things happen!”

“We are fine! We are fine too!”

They all desperately screamed at the weird words Chung Myung was saying, but he shook his head and continued with a somber look.

“No. You practiced so hard even in my absence, but I couldn’t live up to your expectations. This is definitely a mistake on my part.”

The atmosphere kept getting weirder.

‘He shouldn’t be acting like this.’

‘Is he really saying such things?’

Hearing it felt quite ominous.

“However!”

“…”

Chung Myung made a decisive declaration.

“Even if I can’t undo past mistakes, I can make up for what I did! If the training was lacking, then we need to practice more!”

“That bastard…”

“I’d rather die covered in shit….”

“I’d rather try and kill him!”

Curses quietly poured from the surroundings, but Chung Myung didn’t care.

“So, I hope that you too, do not forget that the future of Mount Hua lies in your hands, and work diligently. So.”

Chung Myung pointed up, which made everyone look where he pointed.

He showed Lotus Peak standing proudly.

“…”

“Start.”

“…”

“First come, first serve. The half who arrives last will do it again.”

“…”

“Aren’t you going to go?”

At that moment, someone shot out of the crowd like a bolt of lightning. The faces of the disciples who confirmed the person’s identity were shocked.

“Great Sahyung?”

Yoon Jong.

He was running onto the Lotus peak as if the soles of his feet had caught fire, and someone was following right behind him.

It was Jo Gul.

“No! Great Sahyung!”

“Hey! Run! Hurry!”

“If we are late, we need to run again! Run!”

With that, the rest of the disciples began to run at full speed.

“How can he recover like that overnight!”

“How could I know!”

“Sahyung! Didn’t you say we should all try going at him?”

“A gentleman should know how to embrace the right timing! Now isn’t the time!”

“Well, I am freezing to death!”

“What?”

“Sahyung! Sahyung! Run! Please!”

All the disciples began to run. Only when they did their training right would they be able to eat their meals. They would have to run on their arms instead of their legs if they had to run a second lap.

Which was why everyone struggled to get there first!

Everyone ran with tears of blood streaming down their faces. They didn’t know what happened, but Chung Myung was healthy, which meant there was no hope for them.

Their rebellion was suppressed before it even started. Looking at the backs of the running disciples, Chung Myung smiled.

“What cute bastards.”

They dare dream of rebelling?

His body had become more sensitive as he reached a higher level, so he heard everything they had said.

“Well, this is good.”

There’s a limit to what a submissive person, who only knows how to listen, can accomplish independently. Mount Hua never accepted such people. But that didn’t mean they took in overly rebellious ones either.

There was nothing worse than people who constantly complained about everything. In Mount Hua, you needed to have the ability to match your confidence if you wanted to speak freely.

“That ability, I will create it for them.”

Chung Myung smiled.

It was important to be as strong as he was in the past, but he alone wouldn’t be able to bring back the lost glory of Mount Hua. It was because Murim wasn’t influenced by a single person. Countless people rose to the top of the world through their own strength. But their names would fade if their successors didn’t manage to carry on their legacy.

In the end, for a sect to maintain its reputation and be famous, all members of the sect need to be strong.

The reason the Shaolin sect is known to be the best isn’t because of any individual person in it. Even the sect with the strongest warrior cannot defeat the Shaolin sect alone if his allies are weak.

Even Mount Hua in the past couldn’t stand against it.

‘But not this time.’

Chung Myung’s eyes shone.

In the past, he had to follow the methods of his Sahyungs and Sasuks, but this time he could rebuild Mount Hua in his colors. It will be a long and difficult journey, but in the end, it will be grander than in the past.

Of course, his Sahyung wouldn’t like this.

“If it makes you sad, then come back to life!”

After giggling, Chung Myung put his hands around his mouth and shouted.

“The last person back has to skip breakfast today!”

A viciousness that even a devil may cry over.

Chapter 45: Because it is Mount Hua (5)

The next morning.

No, it was embarrassing to call it morning.

The door to the dorms opened wide.

“It’s morning.”

“Ah, so tired.”

“Ohh.”

“I’m dying!”

It was the beginning of a day that was not so different from usual, and nothing seemed strange.

But obviously, something was different.

There was a subtle strength in the steps of those who were dragging their feet like corpses. What’s more, the fatigue-filled voices complaining weren’t the same as before.

And…

There were unfamiliar emotions in the eyes of those around.

“Come on, I should practice hard today.”

“Well, right. It will be hard.”

“It may be hard, but you have to work hard.”

Everyone went to the warehouse without a word and brought back the equipment they trained with.

‘Phew. It’s light.’

‘I seem to have a lot more energy in my body!’

‘Is it fine for me to be the only one to receive it? I feel bad for the Sahyungs.’

‘Huhuhu. Sajae Chung Myung must like me a lot to give up such a precious vitality pill.’

All the Sahyungs warily looked around.

‘If the others find out that I received a vitality pill and ate it without them, wouldn’t they be disappointed?’

‘I feel bad, but a vitality pill isn’t something that can be shared.’

‘Did anyone else get one too?’

Each of them kept thinking. Since Chung Myung told them to keep it a secret, they wouldn’t even think of saying it by mistake.

Although they all had awkward expressions on their faces, the third-class disciples of Mount Hua never thought that all the disciples had gotten a pill each.

Why?

It’s simple. Vitality pills aren’t something that can be obtained in large quantities. It would take more than a thousand gold to feed all the disciples a vitality pill. Even if you have the money, there’s no guarantee that you’d be able to find someone willing to sell so many pills.

And why would Chung Myung buy so much just to give it away to others?

‘Such a precious vitality pill was given to me.’

‘Kuah! I feel hot!’

Moreover, those who had taken the vitality pills realized the efficacy of the medicine. Warm energy constantly rose within their bodies.

The qi hasn’t even been fully absorbed yet, but just a little was enough to blow away some of their fatigue and improve their internal qi.

Their motivation was revived.

Thud!

The door to the training hall opened, and Chung Myung walked out. Seeing him arrive, the disciples lined up.

“Hmm.”

Seeing that, Chung Myung smiled.

‘Nice.’

Bright and vigorous eyes. The eyes of the disciples, which were staring at him, sparkled with a light that shone brighter than dawn stars twinkling in the sky.

Why wouldn’t they be?

For Chung Myung, it was useless to eat the vitality pills himself and selling them would be a waste. From their point of view, though, it was a priceless treasure they would normally never be able to obtain.

If the disciples knew that the vitality pill given by Chung Myung wasn’t some generic purchasable pill. But was instead made by Mount Hua in the past, the reaction would have been even more intense.

‘He turned out to be such a good guy.’

‘Kuak. The effect is so great. Such a precious vitality pill.’

‘Loyalty!’

The disciples looked at Chung Myung with warm eyes. So warm that even Chung Myung felt a bit embarrassed.

‘So, this was why my Sahyung occasionally gave out vitality pills to the ones who didn’t listen to him?’

He realized that handling people required more than just a whip.

“Now, should we get a clean start today?”

“Oh!”

Chung Myung pointed to the Lotus peak.

“Go there.”

“wuahhhh!”

“I will be number one today!”

“Move it! I am coming through!”

Seeing the Sahyungs rush for the peak, Chung Myung laughed.

‘It’s gonna be comfortable for a while.’

‘It’s strange.’

Un Geom’s eyes narrowed.

In front of him, the third-class disciples were wielding wooden swords as usual. It wasn’t any different from what he had seen so far.

However, Un Geom’s sharp eyes noticed a subtle difference.

‘The sword is stable.’

It was the same swordplay, but the sharpness and stability were different.

Un Geom’s eyes, looking at the disciples, narrowed further.

‘The lower body has changed.’

There is strength in the feet. Because greater force in the feet was applied, the upper body became more stable. Since the upper body was under better control, they could place more weight on the tip of the sword.

A good thing.

If the tip of the sword is steady, doesn’t that mean they were accurately deploying the technique? It was a significant change considering that the reason for practicing and honing the same technique countless times was to develop perfect control of their swordsmanship.

But there was one thing bothering Un Geom.

‘Is it possible for such a significant change in such a short period?’

According to Un Geom’s calculations, it should have taken more than a year for them to reach this level. It’s really short, considering they did this in a month’s time. Realistically, it wouldn’t be strange even if they took two or three years.

But…

“Ta!”

The swords cut through the air.

‘What?’

“And now!”

The advancing step on the floor was cleanly executed.

“Uh?”

Un Geom exclaimed.

It was a good thing that the disciples’ achievements had increased. But he couldn’t understand how it had happened.

‘Was it the morning training?’

Un Geom’s eyes turned to Chung Myung, who wielded his sword in the back.

“…”

That was the only reason he could think of.

He didn’t even have to think too deeply. It was after Chung Myung’s arrival that the disciples began training more. To be precise, it was after Chung Myung started the morning training.

Un Geom’s frown deepened.

‘Was the training that effective?’

Un Geom allowed the training because the third-class disciples were willing to practice on their own.

Of course, Un Geom also wanting some training time for himself was a more realistic reason.

‘I thought it would be a little more motivation for them.’

Was the effect too great? It was too extreme.

Moreover, the disciples also realized that their skills were increasing, so they were more excited than ever to engage in training.

“Hahaha.”

It felt strange.

How long had he been looking after the kids of the White Plum Blossom dorms? To finally see the disciples’ eyes shining so brilliantly?

‘This is embarrassing.’

The disciples trained so enthusiastically, but did Un Geom ever have such passion when he taught them?

Didn’t he constantly feel bothered by the work placed on him?

Un Geom sighed.

‘Even though I knew that they were Mount Hua’s disciples and that they would determine our future, I was negligent in caring for them.’

The more he thought about it, the more ashamed he felt.

Ashamed for not being the pillar the disciples needed him to be.

“Ahhh!”

The disciples’ swords all pointed to the sky in unison.

Seeing that, Un Geom nodded his head.

“Great!”

A word resonating from his heart.

“Your swords look so lively!”

He didn’t know what more to say. Un Geom’s gaze turned to Chung Myung.

It was weird.

Mount Hua hadn’t changed much in the past. But since Chung Myung arrived, constant changes have been occurring.

The financial problem plaguing the sect was solved without any fuss, and the disciples were practicing with a passion. Besides, didn’t he see that their skills were improving?

Was this all a coincidence? Or…?

Un Geom opened his mouth.

“As you all know. According to the rules, you are supposed to learn the Taiyi Flummox Sword. After seeing you all work hard, I think that I should break the rules and pass on the technique in advance.”

“Ohh!”

“Taiyi Flummox Sword!”

Un Geom smiled, seeing the disciples cheer. Rewards were given to those who worked hard, and those who received rewards worked even harder. If this cycle can be encouraged, these children would grow well to represent the Mount Hua Sect.

“So, don’t be lazy and keep practicing.”

“Yes, Sir!”

“Okay then, back to training!”

The lively words resounded through the hall, and Un Geom smiled.

It was then.

Someone approached the hall with quick steps.

“Is Un Geom here?”

Un Geom turned his head in surprise.

“S-sect leader?”

Un Geom adjusted his expression and looked at Hyun Jong with curious eyes. It was rare for the sect leader to visit the training hall.

“You’ve worked hard. I have something to speak with you about; could you spare some time?”

“Yes, Sect leader!”

Un Geom turned to the disciples and spoke.

“As for your swordplay….”

“Do it again.”

“…”

Seeing Hyun Jong arrive so suddenly, Un Geom was puzzled.

Leaving the children behind to continue their training, the two elders went to the other side of the hall, where Un Geom waited for Hyun Jong to speak.

“Un Geom.”

“Yes! Sect leader.”

“A problem has come up.”

“Huh?”

Hyun Jong took a book from his sleeve and handed it to Un Geom. Un Geom, who received it, asked.

“This is…?”

“It came out of that chest we found.”

“Ah…”

Un Geom, who noticed that Hyun Jong was beckoning him to read it, began to read in haste.

“Sect leader this… Equilibrium of Six technique?”

“Yes, it is.”

Un Geom frowned.

Equilibrium of Six was the foundational technique of Mount Hua. However, it was replaced with the True Equilibrium of Six.

“But why are you….”

“Did you see everything?”

“Yes.”

“When I read it the first time, I also hastily glanced through it because it was a hectic situation.”

“… Huh?”

“Check the last chapter. There is something written there.”

“Ah?”

Un Geom hurriedly opened it. Soon, his face contorted upon seeing what was written there.

Un Geom’s hands trembled.

A letter.

To the successors,

It isn’t wrong for one to develop and transform the martial arts of Mount Hua. Martial arts need to constantly change and develop to be effective.

But the Equilibrium of Six is the basis of Mount Hua, the backbone of Mount Hua. Transforming or changing the Equilibrium of Six is no different from changing the essence of Mount Hua.

One should keep this fact in mind.

My dear successor.

Chapter 46: Don’t be offended if something goes wrong (1)

“W-what is this?”

Un Geom, who was shocked, stared blankly at Hyun Jong. Hyun Jong gazed off at the distant mountain, seemingly at a loss for words.

“Equilibrium of Six…”

As if his mind was tangled, things seemed out of order.

The Equilibrium of Six technique is the most fundamental lesson taught in Mount Hua and was supported for many years. Just as those who hold a sword for the first time must learn to grip it, just as those who learn to read must memorize the characters first. All the martial arts in Mount Hua began with The Equilibrium of Six.

But time has passed, and things have changed. Mount Hua was no longer in a situation where they could afford to teach a slow technique with a methodical approach. They had to prepare things faster and advance quickly.

Wasn’t that why everyone put their heads together and invented the True Equilibrium of Six Sword?

Unlike the Equilibrium of Six, it can be learned faster and is more practical for new recruits.

“Sect leader. Haven’t we all come to a conclusion together that we had to move faster for Mount Hua?”

“Right.”

“But this…”

Hyun Jong let out a sigh.

“That’s why I came here to hear your opinion. As you said, it was the will of Mount Hua which redefined our foundation into the True Equilibrium of Six Sword. But the words of our ancestors are also important, right?”

“…”

Un Geom nodded his head.

It wasn’t some advice given randomly, but the words of their ancestors which laid the path for them. All sects work hard to follow the path set by those who came before.

So, how could they deny the clear will of those who built the sect?

“Hmmm.”

“What do you think?”

“How can I—”

“You teach the children of Mount Hua. When it comes to their future, I can’t help but consider your opinion. Don’t think about anything unnecessary; simply speak from your heart.”

Un Geom took a deep breath.

‘It is difficult.’

Whether to follow tradition or choose to change was something people always contemplated. Because it wasn’t a question that had a correct answer.

“Sect leader, the reason we created the True Equilibrium of Six sword technique was that we didn’t have much time in Mount Hua.”

“Right.”

In the end, the original method took time. Who didn’t know the superiority of the original technique? However, Mount Hua didn’t have the time to leisurely raise their disciples. Right now, they were on the verge of collapse, so they couldn’t opt for a slow method.

“Which is why I ask you. Do you believe Mount Hua has a future now?”

Hyun Jong frowned; this was a difficult question too.

‘Future.’

Mount Hua has just solved one of the most horrendous problems. Although it was the most urgent issue, many problems still remain.

“There isn’t an easy answer. Please understand that it cannot be answered clearly.”

“Sect leader.”

As if he had made the decision, Un Geom opened his mouth.

“Then, I am against it.”

“How come?”

“Because it isn’t easy.”

Un Geom sighed.

Although the two techniques came from the same root, they were still different. In the first place, the fundamentals that they taught were different.

The Equilibrium of Six was slow and methodical, gradually developing the individual’s foundation by advancing one step at a time. On the other hand, their new technique allowed rapid advancement and quick growth, but it lacked stability.

“Children learn quickly; these children have already learned the martial arts with their bodies. It will be difficult to overwrite what’s been taught and re-teach them from the ground up. Failure to do so properly may have disastrous results. Above all else, it takes a stable lower body and strength for the past technique. It’s too late now.”

Un Geom shook his head.

“I don’t think that the words of our ancestors were wrong. If possible, I would also like to follow their instructions. But realistically, that is impossible.”

“That’s what you really think?”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“What did you say was necessary for the Equilibrium of Six?”

“A stable lower body and strength….”

Un Geom blinked dumbfoundedly as Hyun Jong turned his head to observe the childrens’ training.

“Stable lower body?”

“…”

“Strength?”

“…”

“Their training seems to have gone well, hasn’t it?”

He didn’t train them like that.

That… Did that child do it?

Un Geom looked at Chung Myung, who was swinging his wooden sword in the back.

‘No!’

No. This situation was complicated, but it seemed too unreasonable. Chung Myung wasn’t from a martial arts family, and there was no way he could have predicted it in advance.

“It seems to me that the children wouldn’t have much difficulty in re-learning their techniques, right?”

“… Well… but the children might get confused.”

“Un Geom, isn’t it our job to manage the chaos and confusion as we lead them down the right path?”

Un Geom nodded his head.

“Is it the children who are confused, or is it you?”

“S-sect leader. Could you give me a moment?”

“Hm?”

“I want to ask one of the children.”

“One of the children?”

“It isn’t me who will be learning the technique. To truly know the best way, I think it is better to directly ask the children who will be learning the martial arts.”

“That’s a good idea.”

Teaching is something that flows from top to bottom. The ones receiving the teaching would be the children. What they think is also important.

“Then, Yoon Jong—”

“Chung Myung!”

Before Hyun Jong could finish, Un Geom called loudly for Chung Myung. Chung Myung, who was swinging his sword, flinched at the sudden call.

“Come here.”

At those words, Chung Myung lowered his sword and approached the elders.

“You called?”

“I have something to ask you.”

“Yes.”

Un Geom exhaled and opened his mouth.

“Which do you think is better, going slower and higher or faster with certainty?”

Hyun Jong, who listened from the side, had an expression of disapproval. The question was too cryptic. It wasn’t asked in a way a child would understand.

‘Ah. Right. It’s Chung Myung.’

This child certainly had a unique side to him, so maybe he could understand and come up with an answer.

As if in deep thought, Chung Myung frowned. Then, as his thoughts cleared up, he raised his head and looked at Un Geom.

“Going higher is the better choice.”

“Why?”

“Because it’s Mount Hua.”

“…”

Un Geom looked at Chung Myung with a stiff face. The corners of his eyes twitched as if the answer was shocking.

Because it is Mount Hua.

‘Huhuhuhu.’

Un Geom slowly turned his head and looked at Hyun Jong. Hyun Jong had closed his eyes. It wasn’t difficult to guess what he was thinking, although his thoughts couldn’t be entirely understood from just his expression.

It didn’t matter if the answer was right or wrong. The important thing was that the answer came out of this child’s mouth.

‘Right. We are Mount Hua.’

What they lost.

Mount Hua’s pride.

Fragments of that distant past were now flowing from the mouth of the youngest child in Mount Hua.

“Any other sect can choose the latter, but not Mount Hua. In order to restore the glory of the past and make Mount Hua’s name resonate around the world, we cannot compromise with reality.”

It was an answer which cut directly to the heart of the matter. Although Un Geom asked a cryptic question, Chung Myung answered while revealing his hidden intentions. It was something the adults should be ashamed of for trying to directly avoid.

“You mean we shouldn’t compromise because it is Mount Hua?”

“I see.”

Un Geom nodded.

“Go back and train.”

“Yes.”

As Chung Myung went back. Un Geom sighed. But before he could speak, Hyun Jong spoke.

“I am ashamed.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“To hear such words from a child. Hehe hehe. Because it is Mount Hua. Because it is Mount Hua… who in Mount Hua could even say such a thing in our current situation?”

Hyun Jong closed his eyes.

Even he, the sect leader of Mount Hua, was unable to say anything. He had hesitated to answer when questioned about the future. Perhaps, he could answer so innocently because he was a child who didn’t know.

But the important thing was that the answer had left him feeling ashamed.

“Mount Hua. Mount Hua.”

“Sect leader.”

Un Geom said.

“It may be the words of a child. But a child is someone who can’t be swayed aside by reality.”

“I know.”

“It may be difficult, but I don’t want to fall short of the child’s expectations.”

Hyun Jong let out a sigh.

It wasn’t a small matter. Determining the basic techniques of the sect was vital. But even more important was selecting the direction Mount Hua would take in the future.

The small conversation grew like a snowball urging Hyun Jong to make a choice.

A decision of which path Mount Hua should follow.

“Listen, Un Geom.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“In the name of Mount Hua, as of this moment, the basic technique of Mount Hua will be changed to Equilibrium of Six Sword.”

“I will follow your orders!”

“I will give an official order in consultation with the elders, but before the official order comes, I want you to understand it and pass it on to the children.”

“Yes!”

Un Geom’s eyes turned sharp.

Mount Hua is Mount Hua.

It can’t stay as a poor sect anymore. If they are under the name Mount Hua, they should be the best and aim for the best. Even if one is trapped within a small stream, they must wait for the day that they can ascend to heaven and become a dragon.

That was the duty of those who bear Mount Hua’s name.

“Not just that one technique. You need to consider all the martial arts of Mount Hua. Your role as the head of the White Plum Blossom dorms will be more important than ever.”

“Yes, sect leader. If we can repay the kindness we received from Mount Hua, what more could we wish for?”

Hyun Jong smiled as he looked at the kids.

‘These children are the future of Mount Hua.’

Perhaps not in Un Geom’s generation, but by the time these children take the lead, they may be able to redeem Mount Hua’s name.

For that ideal, there was nothing that Hyun Jong wouldn’t do. Perhaps, the ancestors were watching from above and smiling at him with pride.

Clearly.

‘Pathetic bastard.’

Chung Myung, who had returned to his training spot, clicked his tongue.

It seems like two elders couldn’t even come to a simple decision on their own.

‘Did you really have to ask me that? THAT? I put rice in front of them, and now they are asking me how to chew it!’

“Ugh!”

“Why are you sighing all of a sudden?”

“Do you know what I mean?”

“… nope.”

In response to Jo Gul, Chung Myung frowned.

‘I need to think. These idiots can’t do anything right.’

He decided to head down to Hua-Um.

He was worried about how these people were handling the businesses down there. If he left it to the sect leader, Chung Myung was certain Mount Hua would die for sure.

“Haaa. This sect would never make a comeback if not for me.”

“…what is with him, sahyung?”

“Leave him be. This isn’t the first or second time he’s been like this, right?”

It was a moment that caused everyone to sigh in unison.

Chapter 47: Don’t be offended if something goes wrong (2)

After a long period of hardship, peace had come to Mount Hua.

The financial problems which plagued Mount Hua the most were resolved through Chung Myung, and new martial arts were provided, allowing the sect to move forward.

Just as spring comes when winter passes, Mount Hua’s vitality was blossoming like a vibrant spring, and everyone was lost in blissful happiness… at least that’s how it should be.

“Peace my ass!”

Chung Myung’s face contorted.

The broom he was holding bent as if broken as he clenched his hands tightly.

Peace?

It is chaos!

“Uh? Calculation? T-this… wait. Jo Gul Sahyung! Jo Gul Sahyung! How much is this?”

“That! That! be careful!”

“It all depends? Huh? It depends on the items. A refund? Huh? Ah.”

The third-class disciples of Mount Hua, who had white robes on, were profusely sweating as they dealt with a rushing influx of customers.

‘Shit, shit!’

It was pure chaos.

It was good that the ledger was found, and the businesses returned to Mount Hua. Since they acquired ten new businesses that were profitable and doing well, wasn’t the only thing left to do just sit back and make money?

… that naïve thought was the beginning of all the problems.

Chung Myung hadn’t even thought about it, but these people had no experience running a proper business for nearly a hundred years. So, an awkward situation arose where greenhorns who have never earned a single penny on their own were now in charge of running ten businesses.

And the result?

As seen.

“No! I already said I ran out of ingredients a while ago! Why aren’t more coming?”

“What the hell are you doing?”

“What is that idiot doing grabbing the customers? Hey! Hey!”

Chung Myung tried to smile.

‘Do well. Do well.’

The disciples of Mount Hua, who did nothing in life but train their bodies and swords, came down to Hua-Um and were sweating hard dealing with customers.

If the ancestors saw this scene, they would have a few stern words… no, they would have grabbed the elders by their necks and flung them around wildly.

Among the disciples was Chung Myung. The customers, of course, did not respond well to his performance.

“No! What kind of tea is this!”

“Tea comes from leaves! Don’t you know what tea is? How can you call this tea?”

“How can you just mash the leaves in the pot? Where is the owner of this place?”

It was a living hell.

Chung Myung sighed as he looked around.

Well, this was better.

The third-class disciples, who began working for the first time, experienced hell. No, the people who were here to do business were going through hell as well.

A guy selling silk accidentally rips the cloth.

A man asks for a rod and gets a pickaxe.

The third-class disciples, who were only serving customers, were enough to torment the flow of business; and the upper-level staff of Mount Hua felt like they were losing their heads.

Those who have spent their whole lives on the mountain teaching now lacked the common sense of how things worked outside of Mount Hua.

“Hey, you! What are you doing! Get to work!”

“Kuak! Ah! Yes!”

Chung Myung soon began to sweep the pavilion again.

‘Sweep this, sweep that. All the customers are going home anyway!’

In Chung Myung’s eyes, he saw all the guests storming out the doors stamping and throwing dust in their wake.

Seeing their displeased faces, as if to spite his hard work, he wanted to yell.

‘Crush them completely!’

But he couldn’t do as he wanted because he was the youngest of Mount Hua.

Chung Myung just brushed dust aside with the broom and slowly fell back. Jo Gul, who was busy carrying refreshments, stood out.

“Sahyung.”

He didn’t listen.

“Sahyung~”

Jo Gul continued to act as if he couldn’t hear.

“Hey! Jerk!”

Were his ears blocked?

“Jo Gul, you bastard!”

“Yes! The third-class disciple Jo Gul… what?”

Jo Gul glared at Chung Myung. He was still just a Sajae and the youngest at that. Talking nonsense and insulting a Sahyung wouldn’t be tolerated…

“What?”

Jo Gul glanced around and then approached Chung Myung.

“Sahyung”

“Why?”

“Let’s just speak as humans, with no ranks dividing us. I’ve heard that you are the youngest son of a famous merchant. The youngest son of the continent’s greatest…something or other?”

“Continent my ass. We’re just a small merchant family.”

“Still, you have to be able to see what’s going on and understand. The youngest son of an influential family is an immature problem child, but secretly harbors an otherworldly talent just waiting to be utilized. Isn’t that how it usually goes?”

“… what the hell are you talking about?”

Jo Gul took a deep breath. He couldn’t understand what Chung Myung was trying to say.

“You see…”

Chung Myung pointed to the scene of chaos.

“How the hell did this happen?”

“Huh.”

Jo Gul sighed.

“Do you remember the people who used to be in charge of this place?”

“Yes?”

“It turns out that they had pretty good reputations. As those people moved or quit, a lot of their employees quit with them.”

“Huh? Reputation?”

Those scamming bastards seemed popular with their employees.

“Reputation? What sort of dog shit is that Sahyung?”

“To be precise, it seems that they were too thorough with their relationships and ties. Most of the employees who worked for them were their relatives or family members, so they immediately quit.”

Shit.

Is this the downside of a family-owned business? This was why professional managers… no, forget it.

“So, this is an employee issue, right?”

“That’s only the first thing.”

“Huh? Do we have more?”

Jo Gul subtly frowned and then looked around, confirming that there was no one listening in, he said.

“As you can see, the biggest problem is that the adults of Mount Hua don’t have the ability to run these businesses.”

“Is that a problem?”

“Those who live without studying and those who spend their lives on the martial arts tend to have difficulties making a living. It isn’t as easy as people want it to be. If it was easy to make money, then everyone would be rich.”

“Yeah, that is right.”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

“So, now Mount Hua is incapable of managing these businesses?”

“That’s a bit of an over-exaggeration, but it is like tying a pearl around a pig’s neck. I didn’t expect it to be this bad….”

It was then.

A loud voice was heard.

“No! I asked for Pu’er tea! Why would you bring this instead?”

“Isn’t that what it is?”

“This is Oolong tea! Sahyung! I am already in a ton of trouble; do you want me to die! How can you suddenly change it?”

“Why are you raising your voice! As if I’ve ever had to deal with such an expensive tea before! I obviously wouldn’t know anything about it!”

“Who here would have ever had the chance to drink it?”

Chung Myung shook his head.

People were fighting merely over the change of tea leaves.

“Look.”

Jo Gul clicked his tongue.

“You have to choose a good product, then you need to have good materials to make the product. If your materials are too expensive then the cost may exceed the returns, and if you choose to use cheap materials then your customers won’t trust the product.”

“… and if we start learning the business now?”

“Would you want to teach a forty-year-old geezer, with no experience, martial arts?”

“I wouldn’t.”

Jo Gul shook his head and continued.

“Honestly, I think that if it continues like this, we will be ruined in less than half a year. I don’t know what the old Mount Hua was like, but the current Mount Hua doesn’t have the ability to operate these businesses.”

“But wouldn’t learning it make a difference?”

Jo Gul looked at Chung Myung with a blank face.

“Chung Myung. Look, do you know the characteristics of our current businesses?”

“…. Uh?”

“It is all about bringing things in and selling them off.”

“Okay?”

“Silk, cloth, metals, tea etc. all of them require materials so they can be made into a product to be sold. Do you know where I am going with this?”

“If I could figure that out, wouldn’t I be rich?”

“It’s said that each material chosen can influence the prosperity of a business. Consider that. Then, if a naïve disciple, who knows nothing of the world or money, tries to purchase the raw material from a wholesaler, what do you think would happen?”

“We’ll be ripped off.”

“Not just that. They would suck the bones dry too.”

“…”

“Forget it. This was bound to fail from the start.”

Chung Myung turned his head, looked at the distant sky, and smiled.

‘Sahyung!’

He only now realized his Sahyung’s greatness. All these businesses operated effortlessly with him in charge.

‘Eh, damn it. I’d rather die than suffer.’

Chung Myung thought.

“Then, what’s the solution?”

Jo Gul looked at Chung Myung.

“Why are you asking me!?”

“Sahyung is the child of a merchant family! There must be some solution, right?”

“You idiot! If there was one, would I be sitting around like this! If I had the ability to do it, I wouldn’t be at Mount Hua at all! I would have already inherited the family business and made a fortune.”

“… is this situation that severe?”

“There’s no solution.”

Jo Gul had a bitter smile.

“At least, I would have tried to contact my home. But it’s too far away and my household couldn’t afford it. To smoothly run an operation like this we would need a giant, knowledgeable in all kinds of goods. But there isn’t anyone like that in Mount Hua.”

There used to be one.

His Sahyung.

But now?

Jo Gul spoke with a wry smile.

“If only Elder Hwang was fine, we wouldn’t have to worry about this.”

“Elder Hwang?”

“Yes, Elder Hwang.”

Chung Myung tilted his head.

“Come to think of it, this man called Elder Hwang gets mentioned frequently. Who is he?”

“A colossus.”

“Colossus?”

Jo Gul nodded his head.

“He’s one of the merchants based in Shaanxi. He handles things from Yunnan and the west too.”

“But what does that person have to do with Mount Hua?”

“He’s supported Mount Hua for a long time. It is a famous story. Because of him, Mount Hua wasn’t completely destroyed and could keep afloat.”

“…I don’t see him here.”

“Well. I don’t know but….”

Jo Gul shrugged his shoulders.

“I heard that he supported not just Mount Hua, but also many other places. Anyway, if it were him, there wouldn’t be any problems. We could have requested advice and gotten a lot of help.”

“Then, we just need to ask him for help.”

“No. Elder Hwang has been sick for a year now. There’s even a rumor that he’s in a coma.”

“Hmm.”

“So…”

“Chung Myung! Where is Chung Myung?”

Chung Myung raised his head towards the voice that was looking for him.

“Here!”

A familiar face came into Chung Myung’s gaze.

Chapter 48: Don’t be offended if something goes wrong (3)

“There you are!”

Un Am approached Chung Myung with an urgent look upon his face.

“Sasuk, I greet you.”

Jo Gul and Chung Myung bowed their heads and offered greetings.

“Right.”

Un Am slightly nodded his head and then looked at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, Sasuk.”

“I think you should head to our main mountain.”

“… Huh?”

Our main mountain?

Mount Hua?

‘No, does he think going to Mount Hua is that easy?’

What kind of errand is he asking about? Even birds could die ascending Mount Hua!

Where did their consciences go!

“Mount Hua?”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung turned his head to the side with a sullen face. Jo Gul swiftly avoided his gaze.

“No, there are so many vigorous and strong sahyungs, why me…?”

“Aren’t you the youngest?”

“Because I am the youngest, my legs are thin, and my footwork is weak.”

“You also aren’t doing anything here.”

“…”

Ah.

He didn’t like working, so he decided to clean this place instead. Who would have known it would backfire like this.

“Ugh.”

Chung Myung sighed deeply.

Now he was turned into an errand boy. How did the Plum Blossom Sword Saint Chung Myung end up like this?

“So, what’s the errand?”

“You need to deliver a letter to the sect leader.”

“Sorry?”

A letter?

He wanted to ask more but questioning a sasuk and fretting over every detail wasn’t polite. It hurts their pride if someone young, like Chung Myung, questions them.

“Yes. I will go.”

“Good. Normally, it would be fine to just wait until someone is returning and let them deliver it, but the businesses here are quite chaotic and it’s a fairly urgent matter. I hope you understand.”

Shit.

He has such a good personality.

Chung Myung would have torn their snout off if it had been a third-class disciple issuing this request.

Un Am pulled out a letter and gave it to Chung Myung.

“This is the one.”

“Yes.”

Also, Un Am kindly explained what the letter was, in case Chung Myung was curious about it.

“This is a letter from Eunha merchant guild, so treat it with respect.”

“Uh? Eunha?”

Jo Gul quietly explained.

“That’s the merchant association that Elder Hwang is a member of.”

“Eh?”

Chung Myung was shocked.

Un Am continued to explain while ignoring Chung Myung’s shock.

“This letter was sent to the sect leader because of an emergency. I happened to be in Hua-Um, so I was able to intercept it early. Otherwise, it would take another two days for it to be delivered along with the other goods to Mount Hua. So, you will have to take this and deliver it to the sect leader immediately.”

“Yes, I get it.”

“It’s urgent, so don’t delay and leave right away.”

“Yes!”

Jo Gul, who watched Chung Myung take the letter into his hands, unwittingly reached his arm out as Chung Myung dashed away towards the mountain.

“That… that!”

Then, he mumbled with anxious eyes.

“Couldn’t we send anyone else but him with that?”

“Hm? Did you say something?”

“N-Nothing at all. Sasuk.”

Jo Gul quickly said. But his eyes didn’t leave Chung Myung’s back.

‘I’m probably just feeling too sensitive.’

But ominous premonitions were rarely wrong.

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung, who was climbing Mount Hua, took the letter in his hands.

“Hmmmm.”

‘So, this is a letter from Elder Hwang of the great Eunha Merchants, right?’

‘No, since Elder Hwang is battling illness on his deathbed, this must be a letter from his subordinates.’

“Ah… really.”

Chung Myung sighed.

“Morally, it isn’t right for a Taoist to open letters meant for other people and pry into their private matters; but isn’t this letter addressed to Mount Hua where Taoists are plentiful? Whether sect leader or disciple, it should be fine for me to peek inside since we’re all family on Mount Hua. Isn’t that right, Sahyung?”

-What shit are you spewing!

“… however, my sahyung is dead, so it doesn’t matter.”

Chung Myung always touched others’ stuff.

With Mount Hua’s businesses as they are, it seems like they will remain a mess unless Elder Hwang steps in to help make things easier. But with this situation… Was there some kind of emergency in the guild?

Something must have happened to Elder Hwang.

How could he know for sure if he doesn’t peek inside, though?

Chung Myung took a close look at the letter.

An inscription on the surface clearly stated, ‘For the eyes of the Great Mount Hua Sect leader only.’

So, they say no one other than the sect leader should open it.

“It’s okay. It’s fine. To be honest, even if the sect leader was here, he would have told me what it says anyway.”

If other people were around to hear him, they would have pulled their hair out yelling at him; unfortunately, no one was around.

“Let’s see,”

A letter sealed securely with a wax stamp. No matter how carefully it was torn, marks were bound to be seen.

But it wasn’t very difficult for Chung Myung, who had plenty of experience raiding other peoples’ property.

“Well, that’s a good thing.”

Shhh!

A sharp qi rose from Chung Myung’s fingertips and accurately separated the boundaries between paper and wax. Then, as if it had never been waxed from the beginning, only a complete envelope remained.

Chung Myung opened the envelope, took out the letter inside, and began to read it.

“Let’s see….”

Chung Myung crossed his legs and scanned the contents.

Chung Myung’s face distorted. Chung Myung fought back an urge to crush the letter, neatly folded it instead, and pushed it back into the envelope with trembling hands.

He took a deep breath.

“Phew!”

After taking several deep breaths, he calmed his raging mind.

“Isn’t this that damned Demon Flower?”

Demon Flower.

Literally a demon’s flower.

Chung Myung clenched his teeth.

“There’s no way ordinary physicians can cure this!”

Because these were the symptoms of that flower.

On the surface, the symptoms are similar to being severely poisoned. Therefore, people would spend their time searching for an antidote.

However, the Demon Flower is a poison that occurs when a particular technique of the Demonic sect is used.

The reason why Chung Myung couldn’t be calm was simple.

‘Demonic bastards!’

Those bastards, who he thought had been eradicated, were alive and working behind the scenes!

‘No! No! No!’

Chung Myung slapped his cheeks to calm himself.

“The one I killed was their Heavenly Demon. I didn’t kill all the demonic bastards.”

It was natural for the remnants of the Demonic Sect to be alive. Didn’t they say the demonic sect remnants had rushed over to Mount Hua after their Heavenly Demon was killed?

There must have been some who survived the war and grew up. There would have been even more hiding out in the Hundred-Thousand Mountains. It’s no wonder they’re still around.

The problem wasn’t them being alive but them plotting something.

A blazing fire ignited within Chung Myung’s eyes.

“I don’t get it; do they still hold any grudges against Mount Hua?”

Why does everything they do damage Mount Hua?

There were so many people in this world, yet, why did they have to touch Elder Hwang?

“Ah! My head hurts!”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

‘Nothing else can be done.’

He would have to go and see it for himself.

It wasn’t possible to say with certainty based on what was written. Chung Myung would have to see it with his own eyes.

Furthermore…

“Reward! A huge reward!”

At the end of the letter, what was written shone in Chung Myung’s eyes.

According to Jo Gul, only the best of the best could join the Eunha guild, and Elder Hwang was famous even in the guild. A massive reward from such a place, he couldn’t even imagine how much it would end up being.

“I can’t miss this!”

Chung Myung’s heart skipped a beat.

Nearly a hundred years have passed, so not many would know of the Demon Flower.

If they hadn’t waged war a hundred years ago, not even Chung Myung would know of it. There was no way they could imagine that these symptoms came from a demonic technique.

Anyone who could recognize these symptoms died in the hands of Heavenly Demon and the other Demonic Sect disciples on the day Chung Myung died.

But the world doesn’t know.

‘Those who survived that fateful day might know.’

If they were alive, they would have been a sect leader. But it didn’t seem like there were any survivors. But if they’d survived, would they have passed the knowledge on? What if one of the others receiving this letter actually has a cure?

“I must have lost it! I can’t even imagine it!”

Chung Myung’s eyes flared in excitement.

Who could try and snatch away one of Chung Myung’s opportunities? …Was he really shamelessly targeting patients? But this was money… no, Chung Myung must solve this dying man’s illness for the sake of morality!

“I’m busy.”

Chung Myung grabbed the letter and placed the seal back on it. Then melted the wax a little to fix it and moved to the top.

“Let’s give this to them first.”

That way, even if Chung Myung resolved the situation, the sect leader would have some understanding of the current situation.

Hyun Jong seemed to have close ties to the guild.

The letter read thusly.

Sect leader. The long winter is over, and spring is coming. By the time this arrives, the spring plum blossoms will be in full bloom, even where the sect leader resides.

The beautiful view of Mount Hua, which I visited with my father, is still etched into my memories. I am full of desire to revisit it some time, but it is a pity that circumstances do not permit me.

Unfortunately, I am ashamed to be writing to you like this in hopes of a request. I am contacting you because my father’s condition keeps worsening with the passage of each day.

As you know, my father has been in bed since last year as his health began failing. Considering his age, it was understandable. But strangely, in recent days, other symptoms started to appear instead of the usual signs of old age.

Father is currently unconscious and unable to move. His body is dyed red, and a black light or something ominous circulates on his forehead while his heart beats erratically.

We, the Eunha Guild, invited various people to check on my father’s condition, but no one made a proper diagnosis.

So, as if grasping at straws, I’m trying to find some clue about this illness by sending these letters out to anyone I know is capable. If you know anything about my father’s symptoms, we would appreciate it if you could contact us back in any way.

I promise to give a massive reward in the name of Eunha Guild to those who provide information that would help improve my father’s health.

Waiting for a reply.

Hwang Jongi, the minor Lord of Eunha Guild.

Chapter 49: Don’t be offended if something goes wrong (4)

“Kuak.”

“I can’t do this anymore.”

The third-class disciples groaned and passed through Mount Hua’s gate.

It was impossible for them to do business in Hua-Um. These Taoists needed to achieve peace through meditation; they couldn’t relate to those obsessed with worldliness and fleeting desires.

“Everything is fine, but….”

It was understandable.

They also understood how important money was and how hard it was to earn. Until recently, weren’t they forced to endure by surviving off only porridge due to a shortage of money?

Even if they were Taoists, it was impossible to live off the bark of trees and cultivation alone. Whether it was a mountain, a field, or a city, people needed money.

So, they had no complaints there.

The problem was…

“Can’t we just get a dorm in Hua-Um? What kind of treatment is this?”

“If we have to go up and down Mount Hua each day and night, I really might die. Sahyung…”

Yoon Jong closed his eyes tightly.

Usually, he would have yelled at the children to stop their whining, but he didn’t say anything because even he was out of breath now.

“… think of this as training….”

“What kind of training….”

“If not, go to sasuk directly and ask him.”

“…”

Everyone shut up immediately at that.

It wasn’t because they were afraid. It was because their suffering was insignificant compared to the hardships of their elders.

They only did it today, but the elders had been going up and down the mountain every day for the businesses.

“Sahyung. I have no time to train these days.”

“We are here to learn martial arts, not do business. If it was going to be like this, I’d rather have stayed home and not joined Mount Hua at all.”

Yoon Jong sighed as the whining kept going.

“I know what you are trying to say. But things don’t always work the way you want them to, right? That’s just how it is, so endure for now.”

“… Yes, sahyung.”

“Alright.”

Still, everyone nodded their heads. Yoon Jong sighed once more in secret.

‘That’s what I said, but when will this situation get better?’

He couldn’t imagine.

No, it wasn’t that he couldn’t. In Yoon Jong’s eyes, things wouldn’t get better; rather, they would worsen.

Fortunately, the merchants who sided with Mount Hua came to their aid. Otherwise, they would have already experienced dramatic losses.

For things to get better, the path to improvement must be visible. But Yoon Jong could only see bad things.

‘Sect leader must have a plan.’

As Yoon Jong continued his thoughts, he flinched.

‘I’m worried about Mount Hua.’

Until recently, that was rarely the case. Although he was one of the third-class disciples, he barely worried about Mount Hua. It was because he had always thought that even if Mount Hua collapsed, he could simply go elsewhere.

But before he knew it, he had grown seriously concerned for it.

This is all part of the change that occurred after he showed up…

“Sahyuunnngggg!”

Yoon Jong closed his eyes tightly.

‘Everything has been changing for the better, but why does that guy keep getting more and more immature each day?’

Yoon Jong looked at Jo Gul, who was running towards him.

“Sahyung! Sahyung! We are in trouble!”

“Calm down. You are Taoist so don’t rush and be—”

“C-Chung Myung…”

Chung Myung?

The moment that name came out of Jo Gul’s mouth, Yoon Jong’s face turned a ghastly pale.

It was truly amazing how one name was enough to shake another to their core.

“No! You need to see this! Hurry!”

As Jo Gul started to run ahead, Yoon Jong followed behind without saying a word.

‘What is he up to this time?’

Yoon Jong didn’t have time to think. He ran with all his strength and followed Jo Gul into the dorms, swiftly rushing into Chung Myung’s room.

“Not here?”

An empty room.

“Is he out?”

“No, that isn’t it! Look at this!”

“Huh?”

This?

Yoon Jong narrowed his eyes and looked at where Jo Gul pointed.

‘A sheet of paper?’

A sheet of paper was left on the bed with a message written on it.

Something came up, so I will be away at work for a few days. You can handle it. Also, if you skip training, I will fold your spine backward, so don’t even think of skipping out!

“… this crazy bastard.”

Yoon Jong’s hand trembled.

What? A few days?

Did that mad man think that he could run around anywhere he wanted?

“W-what do we do, Sahyung?”

Yoon Jong sighed.

“First, we need to make sure the others stay silent about this.”

“… but if he gets caught…”

“Even if we go and tell them, it won’t change anything. He said he’ll be back in a few days, so we need to try and hide his absence until then.”

Unless it was the same as today, when someone came searching for him specifically, nobody would notice if Chung Myung went missing for a short while.

“What will happen if we get caught?”

“Are you worried about that?”

“Yes, aren’t you worried about it?”

“… I’m worried about something other than that?”

“What?”

Yoon Jong sighed and spoke.

“I’m worried about how many days he will be gone and what new mess he is going to cause this time.”

“…”

Jo Gul, at a loss for words, agreed in his mind.

“Huak! Huak! Huak! I need to take a breather!”

Chung Myung sat down on the tree trunk next to him to catch his breath. He ran a great distance straight from Mount Hua without resting and was out of breath. It seemed like he would die.

“Oh! How far have I fallen from my prime!?”

He could jump from one mountain to another in one step. He could even jump from one side of a river to another in two jumps!

If it had been him in the past, it would have taken less than two hours to reach Xian city from Mount Hua. It would have been like taking a leisurely walk.

However, Chung Myung couldn’t do it at his current level, so he had to run like a crazy dog, sweating until his body hurt.

“Oh my… If I could have just one glass of cold water, life would be worth living.”

Each time this happened, he would think of the past. Taking a deep breath, Chung Myung raised his head and looked at Xian.

“It’s been a long time since I’ve been here.”

Although Hua-Um developed quite a bit, it cannot be compared to Xian city.

Xian was the largest city near Mount Hua. As a result, whenever there was a need to visit a big city, the first place anyone would consider was Xian.

Chung Myung, feeling alive and rested, stood up while reminiscing.

“Quite a lot used to happen here.”

Ordinarily, the disciples of Mount Hua wouldn’t come here.

The reason was simple. The closest faction to this city was actually the Southern Edge sect.

Southern Edge Mountain, home of the Southern Edge sect, was only a few kilometers away from here. So, their disciples would often come here when they were bored.

What would happen if the disciples of both Mount Hua and Southern Edge met?

‘One of the two will be destroyed.’

Southern Edge Sect and Mount Hua weren’t on good terms.

No, it’s not enough to say they simply weren’t on good terms. They just couldn’t bear being close to each other; they were closer to being enemies.

Why do we have such a bad relationship?

It has to be asked the other way around… what reason do we have to get along?

Like neighboring nations don’t have good relations, the big sects never liked getting along with their neighbors. First, there are always border disputes and interests to be contested. Not to mention a constant competition to recruit local disciples with talent.

Above all, when asked who’s mightier, swords are drawn and wielded before the question finishes escaping their lips. It’s a matter of pride.

Moreover, both Mount Hua and Southern Edge were from the same province, and they even had the same kind of teaching, which focused on swordplay.

‘Haha. The ancestors must have had similar personalities. Maybe they thought that if they settled their clans near one another their descendants would get along.’

Well, that may be what they thought, but the successors came to regard each other as enemies.

As a result, Mount Hua had no choice but to reluctantly get along with the Southern Edge Sect.

At least, until Chung Myung appeared.

As everyone knows, Chung Myung has quite a temper and is more than a little rebellious. The more his Sahyung tried to stop him, the more he wanted to come to Xian.

Were there disputes?

Of course.

‘I hit them a lot.’

Chung Myung wasn’t such a boor that he would visit the city just to pick fights. At that time, he only focused on eating one more piece of meat and drinking one more glass of alcohol.

He couldn’t enjoy himself and indulge in drinking and dancing within Mount Hua because of his ever-present Sahyung’s watchful eyes keeping him tied down. But, he could avoid his Sahyung’s nagging by hiding in the city.

However, those Southern Edge fools seemed to enjoy fighting rather than drinking and dancing. After being beaten by Chung Myung once or twice, whenever they found out that Chung Myung was in town, they would come rushing after him.

Chung Myung acknowledged the Southern Edge sect’s tenacity as well. Regardless of how many times they were beaten to a pulp, they would always come back, chasing after Chung Myung in greater and greater numbers whenever he showed his face.

Even when Mount Hua was in the midst of collapse, weren’t they still trying to drag Mount Hua down tenaciously?

“So…”

Chung Myung glanced at his clothes. He couldn’t take off his uniform because he was in a hurry. The plum blossom symbol embroidered on the chest stood out brilliantly.

Should he get a change of clothes?

Chung Myung was a little worried.

“Eh, whatever.”

He doubted that he would run into those damn bastards in this wide city. It isn’t like they would be searching for him as they did in the past.

“It’s not like anything will happen.”

Once he got to the Eunha Guild, he wouldn’t have to worry about this sort of thing.

“And then I can get my money!”

With a sinister smile, Chung Myung crossed into Xian.

Completely unaware of the storm he was about to create.

Chapter 50: Don’t be offended if something goes wrong (5)

Hwang Jongi couldn’t hold back his disappointment.

‘So, you’re saying that it can’t be helped?’

Hwang Mun-Yak was Eunha Merchant Guild’s prominent leader and Hwang Jongi’s father. With every passing day, Hwang Mun-Yak’s health continued to deteriorate. Until recently, he was at least conscious, but a couple days ago, he ceased even waking up as the severity of his symptoms increased.

An unconscious man couldn’t even eat food to nourish his body.

If this continued, it was clear that his breathing would end within a few days.

In a hurry, Hwang Jongi had invited influential people the world over. Now he had even begun to seek help from prominent Taoists, whom he had a relationship with, but not a single answer had come back yet.

Today, he had a glimmer of hope when a figure of the Sichuan Tang family, who boasts about their knowledge in poisons, came to him. However, what happened had left Hwang Jongi wallowing in disappointment.

“It is difficult.”

Unsurprisingly, Hwang Jongi sighed at the negative comment he heard.

“Are you saying that even the sect known as the ‘master of poisons’ is unable to help my father?”

“It is true that we pride ourselves as the foremost experts on poison in this world. We can assist in matters related to any poison.”

“But?”

“But, your father’s malady isn’t caused by poison.”

Hwang Jongi narrowed his eyes at this statement.

“Even after seeing these symptoms, you’re saying that?”

Tang Myung, the elder of the Tang Sect, shook his head.

“Although the symptoms are similar, this hasn’t been done by poison. There seems to be a fundamentally different cause.”

“Ugh.”

Hwang Jongi’s complexion darkened to the point where it couldn’t get much darker.

Even though he invited the best and most influential people in their fields and wielded his financial power to promise the greatest compensation he could, he still couldn’t find someone to cure his father’s illness.

“Are you certain that this isn’t simply his age catching up to him?”

“These symptoms aren’t natural.”

“Then, then what the hell is going on?”

Tang Myung slightly lowered his gaze, visibly troubled.

Seeing that, Hwang Jongi sighed.

“I am sorry. I know that you did your best, I am just a little frustrated.”

“I am sorry for being unable to help.”

“Not at all. Forgive me for not seeing you off.”

Tang Myung got up and left outside with a bitter expression.

“What am I supposed to do?”

Hwang Jongi held his head as he mumbled.

His father’s illness was getting worse day by day. How could he stop this? Despite having so much money, was he unable to do anything for his father?

‘What sin did my father commit for this to happen?’

Hwang Mun-Yak had devoted his life to helping the poor. He knew that Heaven’s will is not necessarily executed in retribution, but wasn’t this too harsh?

To die after suffering from an unknown disease for over a year…

Suddenly, there was a knock on the door.

“May I come in?”

“Ah… yes. Elder.”

The door opened, and a man came in. It was a white-haired man in an impressive white uniform.

“I just saw Elder Tang Myung leave.”

“Yes.”

“Young master, I am embarrassed to keep saying the same thing, but now is the time to admit it. The only way to save Elder Hwang is through Taoist Ritual.”

Hwang Jongi’s face grew bleak upon hearing what was said.

“I understand what the elder is saying, but I don’t want to rely on it just yet.”

“Young master. Didn’t I tell you? The elderly’s symptoms are because he went against the flow. He collected too much negative qi and twisted his foundation. If you can make the decision to let us handle it, there might be a chance.”

Hwang Jongi turned his head and looked at the man.

The man nonchalantly continued as if the gaze piercing him wasn’t burdensome at all.

“It isn’t common for the sect leader of the Great Southern Edge Sect to personally offer help. This privilege is only being extended to you because he is Elder Hwang of the Eunha Merchant’s Guild. Time is running out. Please, don’t do anything you will regret.”

“… I wish to wait longer.”

“No use.”

The man clicked his tongue. It was as if he considered Hwang Jongi’s actions to be pathetic.

Hwang Jongi bit his lower lip.

The reason he ignored this man’s rude remarks was simple. This man here was the Southern Edge Sects’ Elder, Ki Mok-Seung.

The Southern Edge Sect has been famous as one of the Ten Great Sects for a long time, and in recent years, their name has soared to even greater heights throughout the world. He wasn’t sure about this generation, but Hwang Jongi was sure that this sect would occupy the highest peak at the top of the world within the next few generations.

Besides, Xian is a place that has been under the influence of the Southern Edge Sect since ancient times. With the elder of such a sect offering to help them, Hwang Jongi couldn’t afford to sever their ties and had no choice but to refuse politely.

‘They will probably ask for a fortune in return.’

Giving money wasn’t the issue.

If they could really save his father, he was willing to give up all his possessions. However, if they had the confidence to save his father, they wouldn’t have asked for the payment in advance but would ask for it later after truly saving him.

Having lived his life with his father as a merchant, Hwang Jongi knew what the other party would aim for in this situation.

“We haven’t yet received replies for the letters I sent out. I will make a decision after receiving the responses.”

“This is really frustrating. How could they cure this disease when all those doctors and healers you’ve already invited failed? Did you not hear a word the Tang sect elder said?”

Hwang Jongi’s eyes twitched.

This man spoke as if he had heard the conversation between Hwang Jongi and Tang Myung. He might not have realized, but didn’t this man just admit to eavesdropping on them?

‘Shameless.’

Hwang Jongi sighed deeply.

Unfortunately, he lacked the confidence and strength to the point that out now. If Hwang Mun-Yak’s condition deteriorates further, his role in the Eunha Merchants will shrink. Then, it would be necessary to maintain a relationship with the Southern Edge sect, which holds great influence within the city.

Even if that meant that he would have to use a lot of money.

“I ask for a little more time. It isn’t that I lack faith in the Southern Edge Sect. It’s because, as a son, I hope to do something more for my father.”

“There isn’t much time left. If he dies, you shouldn’t forget that it was the result of the young master’s vain obsession.”

Hwang Jongi clenched his fist.

“I’ll keep that in mind.”

It was then.

“Young master!”

An urgent voice came from outside.

“What’s going on?”

“Mount Hua! A man has come from Mount Hua.”

“Mount Hua?”

“Yes! From Mount Hua!”

Hwang Jongi’s eyes trembled.

He did send a letter to Mount Hua. However, since there wasn’t much to expect from a sect on the verge of ruin, he sent the letter rather late.

Judging by the time, the letter must have only reached them one or two days ago. Yet, they already sent someone here?

‘Perhaps?’

Did they know something about Hwang Mun-Yak’s symptoms and decided to send a person rather than a letter?

Hwang Jongi, who saw a ray of hope, was about to get up from his seat when he heard a cold voice.

“Mount Hua?”

Ki Mok-Seung’s eyes opened wide. His expression hardened by the word Mount Hua and then let loose a harsh voice.

“They’re merely a ruined mess, what can they even do! How dare they come here!”

Hwang Jongi bit his lip.

He knew that Ki Mok-Seung was speaking with his sect in mind, but Hwang Jongi had the impression that this man was speaking as if the Southern Edge Sect was already in control of the Eunha Merchants.

“Young master. There’s no need to meet such people. What does Mount Hua know that would allow them to cure this?”

Hwang Jongi’s face hardened.

“Even so, they traveled here after receiving my call for help. Do you think that I would send them away without even properly greeting them?”

“You need to listen to me—”

“Elder.”

Hwang Jongi cut him off.

“This is the Eunha Merchants Guild. Don’t forget that this isn’t the Southern Edge Sect.”

“Ahem!”

Ki Mok-Seung tried to hide his discomfort, but Hwang Jongi ignored it and got up. He hurriedly opened the door and went outside.

‘We never know.’

No one in the world could even name the disease; even famous sects had given up on helping them. Then, maybe, just maybe, the answer would come from an unexpected place.

Hwang Jongi came out and looked around.

“Where are the guests from Mount Hua?”

Hwang Jongi’s subordinate deeply bowed while responding.

“At the entrance.”

“Are you saying that you left visitors who traveled from afar at the gate? What sort of disrespect is that! No matter how horrible the situation within is, such rudeness is unacceptable!”

Hwang Jongi yelled with a fierce bellow; the subordinate didn’t ask for forgiveness and simply looked at the gate.

“I was going to ask him to come… but I couldn’t understand that situation at all….”

“Move. I will go there myself.”

“Young master. But…”

Hwang Jongi’s face hardened as he moved. He didn’t like his subordinate’s awkward attitude.

‘Since when did the Eunha Merchants Guild divide their guests according to status?’

If his father was conscious, he would have scolded everyone involved.

Those who do business should treat everyone equally. Elder Hwang’s theory was that those who divided customers by their names and status weren’t qualified to do business.

People might say that the might of Mount Hua had weakened, but it was rude to ask them to wait at the gate when they came to help!

‘Um! I need to set things straight!’

Hwang Jongi resolutely moved to the entrance.

Soon, a small child, leaning with his weight on one leg, came into his sight at the entrance.

‘Well, it is Mount Hua.’

The pure white robe and the plum blossom pattern on the chest. This kid was undoubtedly a disciple from Mount Hua.

Hwang Jongi looked at Chung Myung and spoke.

“We have been rude.”

The young man raised his head slightly.

“No, well, you were.”

“I am Hwang Jongi of the Eunha Merchants Guild. It was my negligence for not properly educating my subordinates, so please hold me responsible.”

“It’s fine. I didn’t come here hoping to be treated well.”

Wasn’t this answer a bit too old-like?

Hwang Jongi continued, maintaining his expression.

“Thank you for understanding. But what about the others in your party?”

“I came alone.”

“Ah, I see. The party… sorry?”

Hwang Jongi shook his head.

“What are you saying?”

“I said that I came alone.”

The young man shrugged his shoulders, smiled mischievously, and spoke.

“I have a way to cure Elder Hwang, so please guide me in. Oh, and I’d like to check out the huge reward that you mentioned. Is that fine?”

“…”

Hwang Jongi’s eyes trembled.

Who the hell was this little bastard?

This was the first meeting between Hwang Jongi of the Eunha Merchant Guild and Chung Myung.

Chapter 51: Haha, what a great person has come (1)

“Alone?”

“Yes.”

“So… you came alone?”

“Yes, that’s what I said.”

“Yes…”

Struggling to understand what was happening, Hwang Jongi looked back at the entire situation.

Repeating the same words and the same questions in his mind. He awkwardly makes eye contact with his subordinate.

‘Didn’t he say that just now?’

And then nodded with a slightly awkward face; it seemed like the child did come alone.

Hwang Jongi turned his head and looked at the child in front of him.

He had all sorts of thoughts racing through his mind.

Was Mount Hua looking down on the Eunha Merchants?

Or was there a reason they sent this child? If not…

“Hahaha!”

At that moment, a peal of loud laughter was heard approaching from behind.

“How ridiculous! Young master, didn’t I tell you? There is no need to meet with Mount Hua!”

Ki Mok-Seung.

He had followed Hwang Jongi to the front gate and continued to speak while struggling to stifle his laughter.

“What were they thinking by sending a little boy for help? They knew nothing but wanted to make use of this opportunity. They were too embarrassed to come in person, so they sent a child instead. Such petty tricks!”

Hwang Jongi’s face hardened.

It was obvious that Ki Mok-Seung disliked Mount Hua just from his words, but now Hwang Jongi was beginning to think the same.

‘Is Elder Hyun Jong of Mount Hua a man who would do such a thing?’

The Hyun Jong that he knew was always a gentleman, despite being in trouble. It was unlikely for that man to send in a child alone.

But was this a new reality?

“Young man. Did you really come here alone?”

“Yes.”

“… you mean that Mount Hua has sent you, a young Taoist, alone?”

Young Taoist?

Chung Myung sighed deeply.

‘To be treated like this, because of this young body.’

There was a time when Chung Myung was Mount Hua, and Mount Hua was Chung Myung.

‘Eh. I’d rather die than suffer like this.’

But he could understand the reaction. A child, who isn’t even a physician, comes and says they’ll cure diseases that the best doctors in the world failed to treat.

So, he controlled himself.

“Young master?”

“Y-yes.”

“My name is Chung Myung, a third-class disciple of Mount Hua. I received the letter the young master sent to Mount Hua. I have a clue about the symptoms which were written in the letter, so I came to visit.”

“All alone…”

“It was an urgent matter, so I couldn’t wait for the others to come. Isn’t the elderly in critical condition?”

That was true…

Hwang Jongi, who stared at Chung Myung, couldn’t bring himself to trust that face. But he recalled a part of Chung Myung’s words and hardened his face.

“You said you have a clue about my father’s condition?”

“Yes. That’s right.”

Hwang Jongi clenched his fist.

‘This is the first time someone said it outright!’

So far, so many people had come, but not one person had an idea of what was happening.

‘Maybe?’

At that moment, he heard a snort from behind.

“Huh. That young child is already misleading you. How can a child know something that the great masters of the world don’t? Young master! You can’t listen to him any longer.”

“But…”

“Young master, do you believe that little brat?”

Hwang Jongi bit his lip.

At that moment, Chung Myung, who was listening, spoke out.

“By the way.”

“Huh?”

“Who the hell are you? To keep referring to me as a brat?”

Ki Mok-Seung looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes.

“Are you asking me?”

“Is there anyone other than you who used the word brat?”

“Huh. You arrogant brat! Does this mean that the disciples of Mount Hua can’t even recognize the uniform of the Southern Edge Sect? I know that Mount Hua isn’t doing great, but I didn’t think they would be taking in such idiotic disciples.”

“Ah. Southern Edge Sect.”

Chung Myung just shrugged his shoulders.

“Well, you were speaking as if you knew what you were talking about, so I thought you were a physician. So, do you have a cure for Elder Hwang’s condition?”

“Elder Hwang has fallen ill because he went against the Dao. If we can perform the Taoist Ritual to relieve the anger of heaven, he will be healed cleanly.”

Chung Myung smiled at it.

“Oh. That could be true.”

Hwang Jongi’s face contorted at it.

But the words which flowed from Chung Myung’s mouth were completely different from Hwang Jongi’s expectations.

“Then we need to hurry up and call for the Wudang sect or the Kunlun sect.”

“… what?”

“Isn’t this ritual thing what they specialize in?”

Ki Mok-Seung frowned as he spoke with a slightly flustered face.

“T-there is no need to go that far. Isn’t the Southern Edge Sect right here?”

“Ehh. Everyone knows that both the Southern Edge and Mount Hua Sects aren’t good with rituals. If you are going to do a ritual, it would be better to get a proper expert. If it was me, I would prefer the Wudang sect.”

“…”

Hwang Jongi’s face darkened.

‘Who is this child?’

The child then whispered to Hwang Jongi.

“The Wudang sect tends to value trust, so donate a little and they will come to you right away. If you want to do something, then aim for the best quality. From a good place. A place that’s cost-effective too.”

“…”

Ki Mok-Seung let out a furious bellow from his anger-flushed face.

“Shut up! This brat is constantly making fun of adults! Did your elders teach you this?”

“Ah, yes, yes. Sorry.”

Chung Myung calmly picked his ears.

It was blatantly disregarding Ki Mok-Seung, but the man could do nothing but tremble in anger.

If he was the elder and he couldn’t even bear the anger and lashed out, then it would be a disgrace for the Southern Edge Sect. Wouldn’t that be enough for the people of the world to point their fingers at them?

No one could tell if the child was doing this intentionally, but he was adept at pulling on every nerve.

“Young master. Kick this brat out right now!”

Hwang Jongi sighed at those words.

“Elder. This is the Eunha Merchant Guild. Not the Southern Edge sect. it is up to me to decide how I will treat my guests.”

“Are you still saying that after seeing how this child acts?”

Hwang Jongi ignored Ki Mok-Seung and looked at Chung Myung.

‘I want to believe him.’

If he came here to cheat them, then the child wouldn’t be acting so proudly. But there was a bit of suspicion.

“Young Taoist.”

“Yes.”

“I am not saying this because I don’t believe you….”

“It is fine. You can’t simply believe someone outright.”

“… thank you for understanding. May I ask a few questions?”

Hwang Jongi asked right away. Chung Myung also felt that it was understandable for the other man to be suspicious.

“Yes, by all means.”

Hwang Jongi gulped and continued.

“Young man. You said a while ago that you had some clue about my father’s condition, can I hear a little bit about it?”

“It will be a bit hard to say.”

“hehe!”

Afraid that Chung Myung would say something, Ki Mok-Seung snorted. Hwang Jongi felt embarrassed at the absurdity.

“Instead, can I ask something?”

“What is it?”

Chung Myung asked.

“I heard that Elder Hwang often traveled for the sake of business, right?”

“Yes.”

“Then, he must have stopped by the Qilian Mountains before growing ill. Right?”

Chung Myung spoke brimming with confidence.

Hwang Jongi was taken aback, his eyes opened wide, as he looked at Chung Myung and said.

“No, he didn’t.”

“…”

Chung Myung tilted his head slightly.

“Huh?”

“That never happened. Father had never gone up those mountains.”

“… Ah, is that so?”

Chung Myung seemed flustered, and Hwang Jongi’s expression began to turn gloomy, so Chung Myung hastily said,

“Then, he must have been attacked in the upper parts of the Mountains before, right? Did he experience a crisis of some sort?”

“My father hasn’t been attacked at all in recent years. At least, not for five years.”

“Uh? Not that too? Ah, shit, then what?”

“…”

Hwang Jongi narrowed his eyes.

“Really? That can’t be right.”

Hwang Jongi could hear Ki Mok-Seung laughing from behind.

“That’s strange. Where did he get beat up?”

Beat up? This crazy bastard!

Was this child even in his right mind?

It was at the moment the hope Hwang Jongi saw in Chung Myung disappeared, Hwang Jongi’s eyes turned cold.

Chung Myung spoke in a panic.

“W-wait! Is that true? Well, I can still fix him.”

“… Young Taoist.”

Hwang Jongi sighed, and without missing the moment, Ki Mok-Seung came in.

“Didn’t I say that they were nothing now? Mount Hua was always made of rookies who liked to dazzle the others’ eyes. Isn’t that something you can see from this one’s overconfident form?”

“Please refrain from speaking like that, elder.”

Hwang Jongi dissuaded Ki Mok-Seung and spoke to Chung Myung.

“I understand the will of the young Taoist to come and help, but my father is very ill right now, and I don’t have the time for this. I hope you can understand my current position too—”

“His entire body turns red as if he’s boiling but his body shivers as though it’s cold. When you press his skin with your finger or hand, the pressed part turns white and then quickly turns red again. Until he lost consciousness, he complained about the cold as if he was in a frozen cave because of the uncontrollable chills! Furthermore, the black spots are not only the glabella, but also the back of neck and crown of his head.”

“…”

“Should I say more?”

Chung Myung smirked.

“H-How did you know?”

Hwang Jongi’s eyes widened. The face and form of Chung Myung were so confident that he couldn’t doubt him anymore.

“Ah… I came from a long way; I am a little thirsty.”

“What are you waiting for! Get water right now! No, get cold water! Right now!”

The subordinate didn’t even answer and ran inside with all his might. Hwang Jongi’s gaze and attitude had changed towards Chung Myung.

“We can’t do this here, please come inside.”

“Haha. What a great person has come.”

“Hurry! Please!”

Chung Myung inflated his chest and followed Hwang Jongi inside. Ki Mok-Seung, who was watching from the side, exclaimed urgently.

“Young master! Those are typical symptoms of those who suffer from harmful qi! Knowing that doesn’t change anything!”

Hwang Jongi narrowed his eyes.

“Are you saying that a black qi gathers on the crown and back of the neck of those who have been affected by harmful qi flow?”

“… that.”

“This is a matter of the Eunha Merchant Guild. We will not tolerate any more interference than necessary. If you interfere one more time, I will personally have to take this up to the Southern Edge Sect.”

“Uhm.”

Ki Mok-Seung sighed and took a step back.

His eyes looked at the child; Chung Myung had puffed up cheeks, clearly trying to hold back his laughter.

“Y-You… brat!”

Ki Mok-Seung felt heat rising all over his body. He wanted to tear the child apart, but what could he do? As Hwang Jongi said, this wasn’t the Southern Edge sect but the Eunha Guild. No matter how much of an elder he was, he couldn’t act arrogantly here.

“You brat! If you cannot treat Elder Hwang properly, I will personally strike you down!”

All he could do was shove Chung Myung and walk away furiously.

After a little while, Hwang Jongi spoke with a bitter smile.

“I am sorry. Young Taoist. Strangely whenever Mount Hua comes up, the Southern Edge Sect seems to lose all reason.”

“It’s fine.”

“Ah- please understand….”

“Who’s to blame? It was all my sins to begin with.”

“… huh?”

Chung Myung shrugged.

‘Maybe I shouldn’t have beaten them so much?’

At this moment, the perpetrator from a hundred years ago sympathized with the victims a hundred years later.

Chapter 52: Haha, what a great person has come (2)

“No… that—”

“What is it?”

“You see, there’s a proper order to these things.”

“Isn’t this the most urgent matter?”

“I’ve come from so far away, and I’m hungry.”

“When the treatment is done, I will prepare a feast.”

“… I have no power to move.”

“You can sit.”

Chung Myung glanced at Hwang Jongi. His eyes were burning.

Hwang Jongi finally caught hold of a rope while he was drowning, and that rope was Chung Myung. If he couldn’t fix elder Hwang, he wasn’t going to let Chung Myung go.

Chung Myung lost his appetite.

“Then, let’s go and see—”

“Hurry!”

“… okay, okay! Don’t rush me.”

Chung Myung turned his head and looked at the bed. Lying on the bed was a man covered in a thick silk blanket.

“Well.”

Checking the man’s face, Chung Myung narrowed his eyes as his forehead creased.

‘It certainly is the symptoms of the demon flower.’

He would have to take a closer look to be sure. Chung Myung moved closer and removed the blanket.

Seeing the scene before him, he frowned subconsciously.

Hwang Mun-Yak’s withered and skinny appearance couldn’t be hidden despite the loose clothing on his body.

The old man’s throat had dried up, as each ragged breath he took seemed to walk a tightrope between life and death.

‘The situation is more serious than I thought.’

Chung Myung rubbed his chin.

‘The demon flower is one thing, but this wasn’t done properly.’

If he had been subjected to a highly trained demonic art, then he wouldn’t have lasted a year. Even those who rigorously trained all their lives would be unable to survive for three days.

These are not symptoms an elderly man could endure.

Then…

“I’m going to check his pulse.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung reached out and grabbed elder Hwang’s wrist.

He then inserted a little bit of qi. As Chung Myung’s pure qi left his body and entered elder Hwang through his wrist, the blackened veins and red tint on his skin began to retreat.

‘This.’

Chung Myung frowned.

The symptoms were clearly that of the demon flower. However, they were awkward symptoms that would never come from properly trained Demonic sect members.

Chung Myung released the old man’s hand and touched his chin as if he was in trouble.

Hwang Jongi couldn’t hide his nervousness as he saw Chung Myung’s strained expression looking like that. Anyone would struggle to remain calm if their last hope showed such a serious reaction when examining a patient.

Finally, unable to bear it, Hwang Jongi opened his mouth.

“… how is it?”

“Eh, so…”

Chung Myung scratched the back of his head.

“Is it tough?”

“No. I don’t think that treating it would be difficult.”

“Right. It is fine. Everyone has be—huh?”

Hwang Jongi’s body trembled.

“What was that…?”

“Treating this shouldn’t be too difficult.”

“Really? Are you sure?”

“Yes. But I can’t rush into it right away. Some preparations will need to be done.”

“Preparation like…”

“First of all!”

Chung Myung had a sly smile.

“Let’s eat.”

“…”

Crunch! Munch!

Chung Myung was cutting and chewing everything around him to shreds. Hwang Jongi was aghast at the absurd sight unfolding before him.

He had met many Taoists in his life while building relationships with others, but this was the first time he had seen a Taoist so obsessed with eating meat.

Even now, the long-torn leg of the duck which entered Chung Myung’s mouth re-emerged as a desiccated bone robbed of all its flesh.

Not just that.

Gulp! Gulp!

As soon as the glass was filled, expensive Yeontae liquor disappeared down his throat.

“Kuaaah! Euu! This is it! This is life!”

“…”

It was the first time Chung Myung had tasted such delicious alcohol.

Hwang Jongi would have normally laughed, saying that he’d met an interesting person today, but the current situation kept him from enjoying himself.

“That… young Taoist?”

“Eh? What?”

Chung Myung asked with meat filling his mouth, Hwang Jongi, taking a deep breath to calm himself, continued.

“The preparations… when will they be done?”

“I’m preparing now.”

“What do you mean?”

“Ah, nothing serious.”

Chung Myung put down his chopsticks.

“The treatment requires a lot of stamina, so it is important to be well fed. Plus, the chef here is really great.”

Obviously, he is.

Because the chef was the best in Xian.

“I only got to eat small meals and rice in Mount Hua; this is so good.”

Chung Myung patted his stomach.

“Are you done?”

“No. This is just the beginning.”

“…”

Was there a tapeworm in his stomach?

It was said that Mount Hua was going through difficult times, but this one seemed too hungry… no, even if he was starving, wouldn’t his stomach get full after a while? Surely, there must be a limit to what a human’s stomach can hold?

This was a Taoist who surprised people in many ways.

“You didn’t come here just to eat, right?”

“What are you saying?”

“Well, Taoists are people who move with a purpose.”

“Those who cultivate the way of Dao live according to the flow.”

“Well, the flow here is too fast….”

“This is a moderated flow.”

What?

Hwang Jongi sighed, knowing he couldn’t win over this child.

“Young man. I understand that it’s rude to rush you when you are here to help us, especially after a long journey. But shouldn’t you also consider the feelings of a son whose father has been bedridden for over a year?”

“I am already considering it.”

Hwang Jongi jumped out of his seat!

“Look here! Young one! My father—!”

“Isn’t dying.”

“—what did you say?”

“He isn’t dying. So, sit down.”

Chung Myung casually poured another glass of alcohol and drank it down.

Seeing Hwang Jongi’s angry and confused expression, Chung Myung decided to speak.

“I’ve already taken some measures to ensure he won’t die, so there’s no problem. It will take some time to cure him completely, but we’ve already overcome the first important hurdle.”

He’s been treated?

When?

“There is a saying that the faster we move ahead, the more we need to think back. Healing your father now is not that important. What’s really important is to understand why he fell ill in the first place.”

“… you really treated him?”

“Did you think I was scamming you?”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders and continued.

“If you have any doubts, go and check. I’m sure the dark qi on his forehead will have dissipated by now.”

Hwang Jongi stared intently at Chung Myung and nodded his head.

“I do not doubt you. However, I think it’s good to be certain, so I will check right away.”

“Please.”

Hwang Jongi quickly went outside. A short while later, he burst through the door, slamming it open as he stared at Chung Myung with incredulous eyes.

“W-what did you do?”

“I treated him.”

“When?”

Chung Myung didn’t reply and casually pointed to the seat opposite him.

“Aren’t you going to sit?”

“…”

Hwang Jongi looked at Chung Myung suspiciously.

While living as a merchant, he’d met an uncountable number of people, but this was his first time meeting such a person.

He’d met many children, but this child seemed more like a seasoned old man.

‘As if an old man’s soul resided within a child’s body.’

That’s impossible. Instead, this child must have experienced countless events unsuited for his age. Otherwise, it was unlikely for a child to handle such situations with ease.

‘Can I trust him?’

But there is no reason to not believe. As he confirmed, his father did show signs of recovery.

Whether or not he knew what Hwang Jongi was thinking, Chung Myung continued to pour another glass of liquor and spoke.

“If you don’t want to sit, then stand and answer. I have a few questions for you….”

Hwang Jongi sat down.

“Who is the person closest to your father?”

“Closest?”

“Yes. A person who guards Elder Hwang. A person who follows him dawn till dusk. Otherwise, someone well trusted, the last person to be suspected of anything untoward.”

“… why are you asking that?”

“Let’s just say that it’ll be necessary for the treatment.”

Hwang Jongi tilted his head.

“Of course, it is me. It is my job to serve my father.”

“Except you.”

“Except me…”

Hwang Jongi, who thought deeply, shook his head.

“I don’t know. Father was a man who worked a lot. So, of course, several people were around him or looked after him. There are at least five people who meet your standards and often stay around him.”

“A lot more than I thought. Hmm.”

Chung Myung scratched his cheek.

But then shrugged his shoulders and smiled.

“If there are five of them, finding out which one it is won’t be easy.”

“Find out what?”

“Are you really asking because you can’t understand? Eh. No, right?”

“…”

Hwang Jongi’s face went stiff. He didn’t ask because he was unaware of the truth. It was because he didn’t want to admit it.

“You mean, someone did this from inside?”

“At first, I thought that it was from outside, but looking at Elder Hwang, I don’t think that was the case. From my point of view, this was a betrayal from the inside.”

Hwang Jongi’s face went stiff.

“Please refrain from such words, Young Taoist! All members of the Eunha Merchants are like family! They have been together with us their entire lives, and they all respect my father! They—”

“Or not.”

“—Uh?”

Chung Myung patted his full stomach.

“If we suspect them and they’re truly innocent, then it’ll all be fine anyway, right?”

“… that is true.”

Chung Myung yawned.

“So don’t worry. We will investigate and find out.”

Hwang Jongi just nodded his head.

Seeing that, Chung Myung clicked his tongue and thought.

‘He is pretty naïve for a merchant.’

Chung Myung knew just how poisonous humans can be.

He’d seen monks who preached mercy give into a rage and go mad and watched innocent Taoists plot the most efficient way to slit a person’s throat.

Human beings are two-sided.

You can be an angel to someone and the devil to another.

‘Well, that’s beside the point.’

The important thing was that a person wanted to kill Hwang Mun-Yak.

Judging from his condition, the culprit clearly has poor comprehension of the Demon Sect’s technique. The problem was that, even though it couldn’t do much damage to Hwang Mun-Yak at first, over time and prolonged exposure, he became gravely afflicted.

Even if someone had knowledge of the demon flower, they wouldn’t be able to tell how the symptoms originated unless they had seen it with their own eyes, like Chung Myung.

‘The culprit must be well hidden.’

Luck was on his side.

If Chung Myung had never seen the contents of that letter… no, if he hadn’t even heard of this Elder Hwang earlier that day, then Hwang Mun-Yak would have been destined to die.

‘Kua. This is a good deed.’

Save people and make money.

“How do you plan on investigating?”

“I am already doing it.”

“… Hm?”

Hwang Jongi asked with a blank face.

“You are doing it?”

“Yes.”

“You’re eating food, but you say you are investigating?”

“Ah. Not that. The fact that I am in a room with the young master is enough for the investigation.”

Hwang Jongi couldn’t figure it out.

“Just watch. Soon a lot of fun things will happen. Young master, be sure to keep your eyes open. Ah, there is one more thing you need to do.”

“What is it? I’ll try my best.”

Chung Myung picked up the bottle next to him.

“One more bottle.”

“…”

“Quickly.”

“…”

A flood of tears was concealed within Hwang Jongi’s heart.

Chapter 54: Haha, what a great person has come (4)

Lee Song-Baek frowned.

Regret? Did he just say regret?

‘What a fearless child.’

Usually, Lee Song-Baek wasn’t the sort of man to judge someone based on their age or status. But this young kid from Mount Hua seemed too self-indulgent.

‘No matter how good he is.’

He isn’t even old enough to understand just how significant the difference between his sect and the other sects is, yet he is out here speaking such things.

How could he hold his head high and say such shameless statements knowing that his sect was at the bottom?

‘Let’s stay strong.’

Lee Song-Baek sighed and continued.

“You’re saying you agree to spar?”

“Yes.”

A blunt but calm answer.

Lee Song-Baek opened his mouth and asked.

“What is your Taoist name?”

“Don’t have one. I am Chung Myung.”

“Chung Myung, Chung Myung it is.”

He already knew it, but he still asked for his name.

“Look here, disciple Chung Myung. I’ll give you a piece of advice. You may think that nothing is wrong with what you’re doing, but the world’s affairs aren’t determined solely by one person. I suggest you return to Mount Hu—”

“Aren’t we going to fight?”

Lee Song-Baek flinched.

Chung Myung yawned as if he was bored and then said.

“It seems like the Southern Edge sect fight with their mouths. Why did you say you wanted to fight, only to waste my time talking?”

“…”

Lee Song-Baek smiled.

‘My discipline is lacking.’

Feeling the desire to destroy that wretched bastard soar.

“There’s no need to rush. We will start now.”

As Lee Song-Baek grabbed the sword, Go Hwi gently grabbed his sleeve.

“Sahyung. You intend to do this yourself?”

Lee Song-Baek looked back at him.

“You don’t have to do it, Sahyung. I’ll do it.”

“No.”

“Sahyung.”

Lee Song-Baek answered with firm eyes.

“There is a minimum courtesy we must show to the opponent. I am the most mature of us here, so fighting against me won’t be too shameful for that child.”

In the end, Go Hwi sighed and stepped back.

‘Anyway, Sahyung is too much.’

He was in a position to become a great disciple of the sect.

“The Southern Edge Sect’s Lee Song-Baek wants to spar with Mount Hua’s Chung Myung.”

“Ah, wait a minute.”

“… what now?”

Chung Myung titled his head as he looked at Go Hwi and said,

“Lend me your sword.”

“…”

Go Hwi’s eyes widened.

‘Borrow my sword? How could a disciple from a once prestigious sect be like this?’

When entering a sect that teaches swordsmanship, the first thing one learns is to never let another person lay hands on their sword!

“Are you saying that disciples of your sect don’t even carry their own swords?”

“Well, I am sorry for not expecting a fight.”

“Mount Hua is…”

“Don’t bother if you don’t want to.”

Chung Myung turned around.

“I’ll check and see if there is anything, like a stick, worth using instead of a sword….”

Lee Song-Baek frowned.

“Lend him your sword.”

“Sahyung!”

“Do you want people to say that disciples of the Southern Edge sect fought a disciple of Mount Hua when he didn’t even have a proper sword?”

“…”

Go Hwi sighed deeply at Lee Song-Baek’s words. Soon after, he took off the sword tied to his waist before throwing it to Chung Myung.

“Thanks.”

Chung Myung took the sword, held it in one hand, and looked at Lee Song-Baek.

“Let’s get started, shall we?”

“… won’t you unsheathe it?”

“I am not planning on killing you or anything. It’ll stay like this. You can unsheathe yours if you want too though.”

Lee Song-Baek closed his eyes.

‘Shit! Shit!’

The more he talked to this kid, the more it felt like all his years’ worth of mental training was disappearing.

Lee Song-Baek closed his eyes, took a deep breath, and raised his sword.

Initially, he planned to just scare him off, but now he thought it wouldn’t be enough. Aside from his personal feelings…

‘Judging from the way he talks and the way he acts, he won’t understand until he’s been broken apart.’

Lee Song-Baek, who judged Chung Myung’s character through the short conversation, was ready.

“Don’t let your guard down.”

“Yeah, yeah.”

Chung Myung lifted the sheathed sword.

Seeing that, Lee Song-Baek frowned.

“You had better do it right. My hands are strong and fast. It will be too late to regret after you’ve been struck.”

“Excuse me.”

“Hm?”

Chung Myung sighed deeply and said,

“Hurry up, will you? What are we still standing around for? Come at me.”

“… you!”

Anger deeply covered Lee Song-Baek’s face.

“I’ll change that attitude of yours!”

In the end, he threw away all the manners a Taoist had to have and flew towards Chung Myung.

Phat!

The clear and simple sword of the Southern Edge Sect.

Among the Ten Sects, each sect was famous for their swordsmanship or their Taoism with distinct characteristics of their own. The Wudang Sect’s sword is known to be soft, Mount Hua is splendid, and the sword of the Southern Edge Sect was serious.

A heavy sword, excluding all changes and tricks, very much like the past, struck towards Chung Myung’s neck.

Chung Myung slightly raised his sword and blocked the attack.

Kang!

The blade and sheathed blade collided, producing a sharp metallic sound.

“Tah!”

Lee Song-Baek swung his sword again, this time aiming for Chung Myung’s flank.

Fast and strong. Even if there was time for a counterattack, no one would have the courage to counterattack due to the sword’s immense force, which desired to split his waist in half.

Kang!

And again, Chung Myung lowered his sword to block the attack.

He hesitated.

Chun Myung, who couldn’t handle the weight of the heavy sword, took a step back.

Lee Song-Baek noticed this slight hesitation and swung his sword to drive Chung Myung further into a corner.

“Whoa.”

Go Hwi, who was watching the match, smiled leisurely.

“Sahyung seems quite angry. He doesn’t seem to want to end this.”

“Huh?”

“That kid just kept saying whatever he wanted and ended up pissing off Sahyung. Tsk tsk. You really need to judge who you can and can’t afford to offend.”

“Is Sahyung scolding that child now?”

“Yes. He can finish this match whenever he wants to, but can’t you see that he’s trying to hold back? I’m sure that kid must feel like shit right now just trying to survive Sahyung’s onslaught.”

As said, Chung Myung was constantly moving back and forth.

Looking at the sight unfolding in front of them, Wei Han-Su titled his head.

“Doesn’t it seem like he’s blocking a little too well, though?”

“That’s the great thing about Sahyung. What would people say if Sahyung took down a child in an instant?”

“Ah…”

“He quickly grasped the child’s limitations and pushed him with enough strength and speed to just barely continue blocking. He doesn’t even need to hit him to teach him a lesson.”

Go Hwi looked proud while saying that.

“Honestly, he doesn’t need to go to such lengths to educate that kid. That kid should be thankful for this lesson. You too, stop doubting Sahyung.”

“Yes!”

Go Hwi clicked his tongue.

‘It’s hard to believe that someone as gentle as Sahyung has gotten so angry. Well, anyone would get angry at that child’s attitude. I just hope Sahyung doesn’t get too excited.’

However, despite the thoughtful appreciation of the crowd, Lee Song-Baek, who was attacking, was giving it his all to beat Chung Myung.

Kang!

‘Blocked again?’

It was strange.

It shouldn’t have been blocked.

Contrary to what Go Hwi was saying about controlling his speed and strength, Lee Song-Baek was constantly accelerating.

‘So why am I being blocked?’

Chung Myung’s sword wasn’t fast. It wasn’t slow, but also not fast enough to make the opponent wary.

However, even with that, he could block Lee Song-Baek’s sword.

That slow sword seemed to pre-emptively arrive and patiently await where Lee Song-Baek would strike.

‘I haven’t even thought about where I’m going to strike, but he’s already there. What the hell is going on?’

Could he read sword movement?

No, he wasn’t at that level.

There was no way a young disciple of Mount Hua could read swords, and even if he could, it would be impossible to do it in action.

To block his sword with that slow sword, it was as if he could read minds… no, even before Lee Song-Baek decided on a path, that kid was moving his sword.

How could such a thing be possible? Was he a ghost?

“Ahhh!”

Lee Song-Baek groaned as he swung his sword.

No matter how much he looked at the child, he judged that he couldn’t be any older than fifteen years old. Considering his age, he should be around his younger brother’s age. However, such a child blocked Lee Song-Baek’s sword without any difficulty.

His sword was one of the most renowned within the Southern Edge Sect!

‘Impossible!’

Lee Song-Baek’s sword began to shine with qi.

Clearly, the spar began with only a little strength, but now he had unknowingly induced internal qi as his strength rapidly rose.

Swosh!

A strong gale gushed out from the sword.

Kang!

Lee Song-Baek’s sword, which was lightly surrounded by internal qi, couldn’t push away Chung Myung’s sword.

Wall.

It seemed like a wall.

No matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t get through it. It felt like a wall made of hard steel.

“Eik!”

Lee Song-Baek swung his sword as hard as he could.

“Hyat!”

Seeing the wind fluttering around Lee Song-Baek’s sword, Go Hwi screamed.

“Sahyung! Don’t overdo it!”

Go Hwi’s shrill voice echoed clearly in Lee Song-Baek’s ears.

’Ah! What did I do!

Lee Song-Baek quickly called back his qi. The heavy internal energy dispersed from the blade as the momentum lowered, and what he swung was a barren sword that was merely a bit faster than normal.

However

Kwaang!

There was an explosion from out of the blue as Chung Myung’s body shot back like an arrow in flight.

“Huh?”

He was stuck to the wall.

Slide!

Thud!

There were cracks spread like spiderwebs along the wall that Chung Myung struck. His body slowly slid down before settling on the floor.

“…”

Lee Song-Baek was in shock.

“Sahyung!”

Go Hwi ran to him in panic.

“What did you do?”

“Ah-No, I…”

Obviously, he recalled his qi from the final strike.

Even with all his might, he couldn’t cause a scratch on Chung Myung. It made no sense for the child to be pushed back so much without the sword even striking him.

It was then.

“Ughhhh.”

Chung Myung, who collapsed on the floor, convulsed, and suddenly began to spurt blood from his mouth like a fountain.

“Heeeiiikkkkk!”

“Uhhhhhh!”

Everyone was frightened and ran to Chung Myung. Only one person, Lee Song-Baek, stood rooted in place as the color drained from his face.

“Puaaah!”

Blood soared like a fountain rushing out.

Wow… who would imagine that blood could spurt out of a person’s mouth like that.

Anyone with eyes would believe that Lee Song-Baek was at fault for this.

“Sahyung!”

“…”

Lee Song-Baek couldn’t understand what was happening.

“Cough! Cough!”

Chung Myung’s mouth was dripping with blood. He clearly appeared to be injured severely. It wouldn’t be too strange even if he flopped over and drew his last breath.

Just when Lee Song-Baek managed to regain his senses and was about to run to Chung Myung.

“What the hell is going on here!?”

Everyone’s eyes turned to the voice.

Lee Song-Baek had no choice but to tightly close his eyes with a grim expression.

With a face full of anger that he had never seen before, Hwang Jongi was glaring at him.

Chapter 55: Haha, what a great person has come (5)

“I asked you! What the hell is happening!?”

Hwang Jongi’s voice rang out loudly.

Confused and panicked, the disciples of the Southern Edge Sect didn’t say anything and stared blankly at Hwang Jongi.

What could they say?

Cough. Cough.

“…”

Right now, what they needed most was an excuse, but the blood pouring from Chung Myung’s mouth would render any excuse invalid.

In this hopeless situation, not even the grandfather of Zhuge Liang’s grandfather could find a suitable excuse to help them escape.

Hwang Jongi looked at Chung Myung lying on the floor and cried out.

“Hurry! Bring a physician right now! There must be a member of the outer house who hasn’t left yet! What are you doing!”

“Yes! Young master!”

One of the servants following Hwang Jongi rushed to the outer garden. Hwang Jongi strode closer to Chung Myung, who was down.

“…”

The disciples of the Southern Edge sect hesitated as they opened a path for him.

Hwang Jongi knelt down and examined Chung Myung’s condition. Anger violently surged in his heart as his face distorted in rage.

“You people dare claim to be righteous!”

At Hwang Jongi’s words, the faces of the Southern Edge sect disciples darkened.

“Are you saying that this is how one should act against a child? I thought the Southern Edge sect would be dignified at least, but how am I supposed to understand what just happened in front of my eyes!”

Lee Song-Baek’s face turned pale.

Would he be able to make it out of this alive?

He never intended to hurt him like that.

‘I even called back the internal qi!’

Lee Song-Baek was standing still without a word. But one thing was certain. Hwang Jongi’s expression left no room for excuses.

The servant came running back with a physician in tow at that moment. As soon as the physician approached the wheezing Chung Myung, his face stiffened.

“Ugh!”

With his stiff face, he spoke.

“Hurry and move him inside! Come on! His insides are a total mess, so be careful! Careful!”

The Southern Edge Sect’s disciples tried to assist them upon hearing that.

“Stand back!”

Hwang Jongi wouldn’t allow them to touch Chung Myung’s body. Hwang Jongi stared at them with blazing red eyes and called for his servants.

“What are you doing!? Did you not hear my words!?”

“Sorry! Young master!”

The servants carefully embraced Chung Myung. Blood, gushing from his mouth, dripped down to his chest and settled on the floor.

“Careful! Careful!”

The physician clung tightly to Chung Myung and headed to the main house. Hwang Jongi and the other disciples watched as Chung Myung was moved.

As the fading figure of Chung Myung finally disappeared., Hwang Jongi turned his head.

“I will never forget what happened today.”

“Young master!”

“Leave.”

Lee Song-Baek’s face turned pale.

The Eunha Merchant Guild was necessary for the Southern Edge sect. Wasn’t that why even their elders came down here?

If their relationship was now in trouble, the aftermath wasn’t something the sect could afford.

As Lee Song-Baek was about to say something, a voice came from behind.

“What is all this?”

It was Ki Mok-Seung. He approached with a puzzled look in his eyes.

“Young master, what is all this? Is that blood….”

Ki Mok-Seung, who was speaking, went silent. The floor and the wall were broken, and he could guess what had happened.

‘These stupid bastards!’

Ki Mok-Seung’s gaze fell on his disciples. He sighed after seeing Lee Song-Baek, who couldn’t even meet his gaze.

“Young Master. If some accident has happened, we—”

“Are you calling this an accident?”

“—Young master.”

“The person who was here to treat my father was horrifyingly injured by your disciples. Can you call this an accident? An accident is something which happens unintentionally, am I wrong?”

Ki Mok-Seung looked at Lee Song-Baek.

His look conveyed a deeper meaning to Lee Song-Baek. Since he was the one who caused this, he should settle the matter himself.

Lee Song-Baek, who understood, bit his lip and stepped forward.

“Young master. There seems to be a misunderstanding.”

“A misunderstanding?”

Hwang Jongi exhaled in anger.

“It would be better that you call me blind. I saw with my own eyes and heard with my ears, so what could I have misunderstood?”

“I never used much force against him. There is something—”

“Look here.”

Hwang Jongi stared at Lee Song-Baek with cold, sunken eyes.

“Do you think that overextending your hand is the problem here? Why did you, a disciple of the Southern Edge sect, have to wield your sword against a child from Mount Hua in the first place?”

“It was a simple spar.”

“Spar?

Hwang Jongi shook his head.

“I might not be familiar with the ways of warriors, but I know that spars are done between those who hold equal levels of strength. You say that you were sparring when you went against a child who was barely half your age?”

No one said anything.

If the spar had ended without accident, there wouldn’t have been anything to say. However, with it resulting in an injured and bleeding child, there was no talking their way out of taking responsibility.

“I won’t say much. Take your disciples and leave.”

“Y-Young master, listen to my wor—”

“I said to leave….”

“…”

Hwang Jongi looked at Ki Mok-Seung and said,

“I won’t press the issue farther out of respect for the relationship we’ve shared with the Southern Edge sect for so long. But now, I don’t want to see the faces of your disciples here. Please leave this place for today.”

In the end, Ki Mok-Seung just slowly nodded his head, unable to speak up.

“I will. Young master, this was an unfortunate accident, but please remember that the Southern Edge Sect hopes for Elder Hwang’s swift recovery.”

“I wish that to be the case. But it doesn’t seem like that anymore.”

Hwang Jongi returned toward the main house. Ki Mok-Seung, who observed Hwang Jongi’s departure, turned his head to glare at Lee Song-Baek.

“Elder, I…”

“I won’t say much. This is your fault; you deal with it. Go and ask for the young master’s forgiveness at any cost, solve the situation, and then return. I will return to the Mountain with the others.”

Lee Song-Baek’s face turned pale.

How could he possibly ask for forgiveness from the young master in this situation?

This was more like a punishment than an order. But looking at the frigid expression on Ki Mok-Seung’s face, he could only stay quiet and comply.

“… I understand.”

Ki Mok-Seung looked at Lee Song-Baek for a long time without speaking and then turned around.

“We’re leaving.”

“Yes. Elder.”

The disciples all looked at Lee Song-Baek and then followed after the Elder.

Watching them leave, Lee Song-Baek bit his lip in frustration.

“How is his condition?”

“… it’s not so good.”

“Hmm.”

Hwang Jongi’s face darkened when he received the physician’s diagnosis from the general head. Seeing his bleak expression, the general continued.

“According to the physician, his qi meridians are completely strained and in a dangerous situation. For now, they are trying to control the qi, but they can’t guarantee a complete recovery.”

“Does that mean he won’t die?”

“It seems like it.”

“Thank goodness.”

Hwang Jongi sighed in relief.

Mount Hua’s disciple came to Eunha Merchant Guild to help and was beaten to death by the Southern Edge sect?

This was something he hated to even think about.

Moreover, Chung Myung had come to treat his father. Of course, the fault lay in those who assaulted him, but even the Eunha Merchant guild would be ridiculed for allowing it to occur at all.

For Hwang Jongi, personally, this was intolerable.

Chung Myung was the only person who managed to improve his father’s condition so far. Maybe, he was the only hope at ever having his father back.

Attacking such an important person and injuring him so… this would have never happened if the Southern Edge Sect had even a modicum of respect for his father and his guild.

‘That Southern Edge sect has become so arrogant!’

Normally, he would have tried to see both sides of the situation. But when he thought about their attitude and Ki Mok-Seung’s words, it was difficult to trust them any longer.

Hwang Jongi coughed several times in discomfort and looked at the general.

“Then, how long will it take for him to awaken?”

“He should be up in two or three days….”

“Hmm. In the meantime, I only pray my father’s condition doesn’t worsen.”

Hwang Jongi let out a deep sigh.

He thought he had finally found a way to help his father, but this had to happen. It seemed like the heavens had turned their backs on him.

The general head, who glanced at Hwang Jongi’s expression, carefully spoke.

“But Young master….”

“Hm?”

“Will this child really be able to cure the Elder? I’m not that confident in him.”

“Is there anything we lose by believing him?”

“That is true, but….”

Hwang Jongi spoke firmly.

“Of the many people we called for, none have been able to figure out father’s disease. But this child from Mount Hua could list the symptoms without even looking at my father. Didn’t my father’s condition improve a little too?”

“Yes.”

“This isn’t some vague belief that I have in him. I feel like Heaven is trying to help us a little. Anyway, we just have to ensure that this small child recovers properly. Don’t hold back on supporting him.”

“I’ll keep that in mind. Then, I’ll take my leave for now.”

“Yes.”

The general head bowed and got up from his seat.

“Hmm.”

Hwang Jongi, who watched him leave, let out a low sigh.

Wheeze

Wheeze

A low, feeble breath escaped from the corner of Chung Myung’s bedridden mouth. His face was pale and tired, seemingly devoid of blood, which showed how precarious his condition was.

It was slow and quiet with no consistent rhythm, but it continued, nonetheless. However, it wouldn’t be strange if he stopped breathing entirely.

Wheeze

Only the short and weak breathing filled the room when a strange silence followed.

Click!

The door opened with a slight sound. And then, nothing happened for a while.

Did a few minutes pass?

Kiik!

The door began to open carefully.

Before long, a man carefully snuck his way in. A cautious movement, not even letting his footsteps make a sound. The room was blanketed in total darkness, leaving it impossible to recognize who had entered.

The man snuck in like a cat hunting for food as he came to Chung Myung’s side.

Wheeze

Wheeze.

The sight of Chung Myung breathing weekly with a pale face caught the eye of the silent intruder.

The mysterious figure, staring at Chung Myung’s face, slowly raised his hand.

Their fingertips were dyed an eerie black as if coated in ink.

“I have no grudges against you; just think of this as the price for disturbing my work.”

The man mumbled to himself, then slammed the blackened hand towards Chung Myung’s neck.

At that moment

Grab!

Chung Myung, who should have been exhausted and tired, suddenly pushed aside the blanket and grabbed the man’s wrist.

“Ugh!”

Chung Myung looked at the man with a tired complexion.

“…”

A strange smile on his face, the most wicked and triumphant kind.

“I got you, you son of a bitch!”

Chapter 56: Are you really a Taoist? (1)

“I got you, you son of a bitch!”

Chung Myung smiled as he got up. The man tried to retrieve his wrist from Chung Myung’s grasp but was unable to free himself from the firm grip.

“You!”

The man quickly raised his other hand to strike Chung Myung. But, at that moment, the door burst open wide, and the room lit up.

It was Hwang Jongi.

Step step.

He walked in with a very stiff face and spoke with a heavy voice.

“What are you doing here? General?”

“…”

Beon Ja-Bok, the general head of Eunha, looked back in shock as Chung Myung held him in place.

“Y-Young master!”

“I am asking you what you are doing here.”

Beon Ja-Bok’s expression contorted.

“I just wanted to check the condition of the small—”

Chung Myung interrupted and continued to answer for the General.

“Ah, you wanted to check my condition and kill me?”

Chung Myung waved the hand he was holding.

“You’ve misunderstood….”

“Misunderstood? I like misunderstandings, too.”

Chung Myung jumped to his feet.

Beon Ja-Bok stared blankly at Chung Myung with wide eyes.

“I-It was clearly a serious injury….”

“It must have been a misunderstanding. I was fine from the beginning.”

“… you were unconscious.”

“Oh. I haven’t been sleeping well recently, so I just happened to be overdue for a nap.”

Beon Ja-Bok gnashed his teeth.

“You deceived me.”

“You shouldn’t say such a thing. You need to insist that it was a misunderstanding as much as possible. If you say things like that, then everyone will think you were up to something.”

“You!”

He struck Chung Myung with his left hand. However, Chung Myung neatly avoided his attack, released his other hand, and jumped off the bed.

Without looking back, he walked over to Hwang Jongi.

“Look, didn’t I tell you he would come out?”

“… Hm.”

Hwang Jongi nodded with heavy eyes.

“I didn’t believe what you said, but I have nothing to say after seeing this. Of all things, I never expected the general head, whom I believed in the most, would act like this.”

Hwang Jongi shot a soul-freezing glare at Beon Ja-Bok.

Meeting his gaze, Beon Ja-Bok knew that no excuses would work. He stared at Chung Myung with a stiff face.

“How did you come to doubt me?’

“I didn’t.”

“… what?”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders.

“I didn’t know who the hell the wrongdoer was. You must know I’ve only been here for a few days. I just assumed the culprit would come to kill Elder Hwang’s savior if he thought I was injured and in need of recovery.

“… what if I hadn’t come?”

“You didn’t have a choice.”

Chung Myung smiled.

“It’s hard to kill the first time, but the second time comes much easier. Plus, if you kill me now, you could shift the blame onto the Southern Edge Sect. How would you willingly miss such an opportunity?

“So, you planned this with the Southern edge Sect?”

Chung Myung looked at him and said

“Nope.”

Beon Ja-Bok’s distorted face suddenly went blank.

“You didn’t?”

“Yep, they just happened to pick a fight with me. I was thinking about how to solve this problem, but they came and created a nice situation.”

Beon Ja-Bok bit his lip.

“Internal wounds! I don’t know about anything else, but the physician said that you were severely injured!”

“If I couldn’t even deceive a normal physician, I wouldn’t have bothered planning this thing. You keep asking such obvious questions.”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders.

“You have a lot of questions, but I have no obligation to solve your curiosity. What’s important is that you fell into the trap, and I found the man who tried to kill Elder Hwang.”

“Hahaha!”

In the blink of an eye, Beon Ja-Bok looked at Hwang Jongi.

“Young Master. Surely you don’t believe that little child, right?”

“… is there a reason for me not to believe him?”

“Aren’t you normally the most rational one? Isn’t there something more important than what the child is saying?”

“More important?”

The man nodded and continued.

“Yes. Just because I tried to harm this child, that isn’t proof that I tried to hurt the Master. Why would I do such a thing? Think of how well the Master has treated me all this time; why would I bring him harm? Young Master, isn’t that why you never suspected me?”

“Hmm.”

Hwang Jongi frowned at it.

It was an obvious excuse, but he wasn’t wrong.

“Then why did you try to kill the young Taoist? Why did you hide the fact that you learned martial arts?”

“That child was deceiving the young Master! Even you were seduced by his words into thinking he could help your father! How can that child help him?”

“Then you should have persuaded me!”

“Would you have listened to me? Wouldn’t you disregard me? It is easier to fool a man than it is to convince them they’ve been fooled! Killing that child was the only way to bring you to your senses!”

In an instant, there was a murmur.

Hwang Jongi turned his head.

The servants who had gathered there after the commotion began were whispering amongst themselves. Their words couldn’t be heard but judging from their expressions, they seemed to think that Beon Ja-Bok’s reasoning wasn’t wrong.

That was how persuasive his words were.

“Are you done talking?”

However, Chung Myung took a step forward.

“…”

Beon Ja-Bok stared at Chung Myung.

“It is true that I tried to kill him, but I never tried to hurt the Master. You—”

“Ahhh.”

Chung Myung waved his hand and cut off the ongoing speech.

“Enough. Enough. I don’t want to know the reason, and I don’t want to hear excuses.”

“What…?”

“I’ll just have to beat him.”

Before anyone could react, Chung Myung rushed towards Beon Ja-Bok.

Aiming for Beon Ja-bok’s head, he stretched out his hand.

Chung Myung’s hand began to emit a sharp and intense light as it rang with a shrill slicing sound. Beon Ja-Bok, who could sense the power within this strike, moved to counter the assault.

Kwang!

Both hands crossed as Chung Myung retreated.

“Now, attention, please!”

He casually lifted his arm.

“T-that!”

Everyone saw the outstretched hand and doubted their eyes.

The hand which had been hit clearly turned black. Then, slowly, Chung Myung’s entire wrist turned red.

Chung Myung began to speak as the onlookers stared aghast, waiting to hear what he had to say with bated breath.

“Demon Hand.”

Chung Myung waved his hand to make sure they were all looking at him.

“Normal people cannot withstand a single hit, and their entire body turns red as they slowly die. Of course, this man isn’t very proficient, but even at his level, he can kill people. Especially if the opponent is an old man who never once trained in martial arts, it would be even easier than eating a piece of rice cake.”

“…”

While Beon Ja-Bok was desperately struggling to organize his thoughts and plot some way out of this situation, Chung Myung said,

“Of course, if you can pinpoint another person who frequently has close contact with Elder Hwang and is able to infuse him with demonic qi, then feel free to name him.”

A decisive blow.

Anger surged in the eyes of those who witnessed these events. Who would continue to trust this man who shamelessly betrayed their Master?

The hand Chung Myung was showing had similar symptoms to what Elder Hwang’s entire body was like.

“Y-You! A bastard who doesn’t even appreciate the grace shown to you!”

“How dare you try to assassinate our master and then act so shamelessly?”

“I won’t calm down even after I beat him to death!”

As everyone’s mood changed, Hwang Jongi no longer hesitated.

“Capture him!”

At his enraged voice, everyone went silent.

“Right now, subdue that man! If he resists, kill him!”

At his command, the servants rushed into the room. Beon Ja-Bok, who was tense, decided to fight.

“Ack!”

“Ugh!”

Those who entered the room were swept away by the power of Beon Ja-Bok.

“Damn it! It was almost over!”

He looked at Chung Myung with venomous disgust.

“If it wasn’t for that little brat!”

“Who are you calling a brat?”

Chung Myung pursed his lips.

He wasn’t a brat, nor was he little, but he hated being called that.

“A little while more, and he would have been done! If I had known this would happen, I would have killed you right away! If you hadn’t planted those thoughts into that stupid young Master….”

“Ahhh.”

Chung Myung waved his hand.

“Well, of course, you must have something to say, but let’s talk about it later. For now, let’s finish this quickly. I am a bit sleepy since I was rudely woken up from a nice nap.”

“What?”

Beon Ja-Bok exploded.

“Hahahaa! You arrogant brat! I don’t know how you knew, but do you think you can defeat me with your pathetic martial arts? You? Defeat me?”

“No.”

“… Huh?”

“Why would I bother? There are other people here to do that. There.”

Chung Myung pointed to someone behind him.

Everyone’s eyes shifted to where Chung Myung pointed.

“… Me?”

Lee Song-Baek, who was staring blankly at this perplexing situation from behind, pointed to himself.

“Me?”

“Oh. The youngest hero has come to subdue the bad man! Please take care of yourself!”

“Ah, wait, me?”

“Who else?”

Chung Myung’s eyes were wide open as he asked, and Lee Song-Baek quickly understood the situation. Looking back, since all the disciples were dragged back to the sect, he was the only one here.

“W-why me…”

At that moment, Lee Song-Baek felt it was unfair. However, Chung Myung gestured somewhere with his chin. Lee Song-Baek looked and saw Hwang Jongi staring at him.

‘Ah, right!’

A chance to rectify his mistake! Looking back, it no longer seemed like what happened to Chung Myung was a mistake, but that didn’t matter now!

“The enemy will be dealt by the sword of the Southern Edge Sect!”

As Lee Song-Baek drew his sword and rushed forward, Chung Myung clapped his hands and cleared the way.

“Wooow! Such heroism!”

He wanted to quickly take the man down, but Lee Song-Baek had appeared behind him, so he offered him the opportunity.

Leaving the battle between the two men, Chung Myung approached Hwang Jongi.

“One matter has been resolved.”

“… it isn’t over yet.”

“He’ll capture him soon enough. He is still a famous disciple from the sect; there’s no way he’ll be defeated by someone who hasn’t even properly mastered the martial arts.”

“Not properly mastered? He definitely injured your hand….”

Chung Myung showed the hand to Hwang Jongi.

His hand, which was black, first turned white and then red.

“…”

“I didn’t lie. It is true that he learned the Demon Hand. I just exaggerated a bit to show what happens when he uses it on one person for a long time.”

“Huuu…”

Hwang Jongi let loose a deep sigh.

“Are you really a Taoist?”

“Of course.”

‘The greatest and most experienced master in the world at that.’

Don’t believe me?

It is the truth!

Chapter 57: Are you really a Taoist? (2)

The general wouldn’t last much longer…

No, actually, he was lasting a lot longer than expected.

Lee Song-Baek, who had confidently jumped into the fight, had been fighting desperately for more than an hour to take him down.

He didn’t know whether it was a tense battle that made the others sweat, but it sure made Chung Myung yawn.

‘I thought he’d take him down right away. Should I have just done it myself?’

However, watching Lee Song-Baek sweating so profusely, Chung Myung couldn’t bring himself to say it out loud.

In the meantime, the tired hero was smiling triumphantly as if he was proud of himself despite taking an hour to defeat the general.

‘Wipe off your sweat at least….’

“Huh, the man.. kuak… the man… took him down.”

Hwang Jongi nodded, looking at Lee Song-Baek, who was trembling in exhaustion and spoke.

Seeing his trembling legs and ragged breathing, Hwang Jongi felt pity and couldn’t stay angry at him.

“You’ve worked hard. The Eunha Merchant guild will never forget this help.”

“Tha-thank you… thank you.”

“Get some rest.”

Worried that Lee Song-Bael would collapse, Hwang Jongi excused him, and he dropped down and sat without even answering.

Normally, Hwang Jongi wouldn’t have felt much gratitude for Lee Song-Baek after all that occurred. But seeing his feeble appearance, which gave everything to subdue the enemy, he let himself forget the bad deed he did in the morning.

Hwang Jongi glanced at Chung Myung.

‘I don’t know what to say about this situation.’

Has it really only been two days since Chung Myung appeared here?

Yet, he solved the problem, which persisted for over a year in just these two days.

‘Was this a problem which could be solved so easily?’

No way.

Hwang Jongi knew it.

Everything in life seems simple in hindsight. If this was such a simple scenario from the beginning, why hadn’t a single one of the world’s experts been able to solve the issue?

‘It’s as if an old expert resides within that little child.’

But that was impossible.

“I think it’s almost resolved now.”

“Why did the general head target my father?”

“I don’t know.”

“Didn’t you do this because you had some guess at the reason why?”

“No, I didn’t.”

“….”

Hwang Jongi was dazed.

Chung Myung calmly spoke as if he guessed what Hwang Jongi was thinking.

“It’s the government’s job to make him reveal the reason. My job is just to solve the problem and receive the reward. Speaking of which, you do have the reward prepared, right?”

Normally, no matter how hard one worked, they wouldn’t so brazenly ask for compensation. Humans value their pride.

However, Chung Myung didn’t have any pride to take care of.

At one point, he was the famous Plum Blossom Sword Saint, the best of the Mount Hua Sect. Now though, he was just the youngest of Mount Hua’s third-class disciples; he didn’t have to care about saving his face.

Although it was a bit absurd, Hwang Jongi quietly nodded his head.

“Of course. But you forget one thing. The problem hasn’t been solved yet. I never asked you to find the assassin but to help my father recover and get out of his bed. Right?”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

“That comes next.”

A more confident voice than before.

Hwang Jongi replied in a firm voice.

“I promise my support to Mount Hua, even if it means turning the guild upside down and going against the world.”

As if moved by the heartfelt words, Chung Myung grabbed Hwang Jongi’s hand tightly.

Hwang Jongi smiled brightly as if he guessed that Chung Myung’s heart was moved.

“You don’t need to be so moved. This is least—”

“Are you kidding me!?”

“… huh?”

Chung Myung’s face contorted.

“The reward should be given to me, not Mount Hua! Are you saying that I do all the hard work, and they reap the rewards!?”

“…”

Hwang Jongi was speechless.

It seemed like this child was more insane than he thought.

In front of Hwang Mun-Yak lying on the bed, Chung Myung stood there with a dry mouth.

Now, so long as the treatment succeeds, everything will be solved. After that, he would be able to return with his reward.

Everything was handled perfectly.

Nothing so far was difficult. He liked that he even got to bully the Southern Edge Sect in the process. That was his favorite part.

But there was one problem…

‘Honestly, I’m not entirely confident.’

Till now, everything was something he could do. But to be honest, it was impossible to know whether or not it was possible to fix the old man.

If it was Chung Myung, the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, he wouldn’t have to worry about it.

No matter how ferocious the demon flower was, in the end, it was caused by demonic qi. It would be enough to simply erase all the demonic qi in the body to get back to normal.

But the current Chung Myung was still lacking strength.

He was very small, had little qi, and was a lot more disadvantaged.

With that, there was no guarantee that he could stop the spread of the demonic qi inside Elder Hwang’s body. On the contrary, if he carelessly touched the demonic qi, then the weakened body of elder Hwang would die instantly.

“Will this work?”

He wouldn’t know without trying.

Chung Myung’s stomach twisted as he approached the man.

If he wasn’t sure of the results, there was only one thing to do.

Elder Hwang would surely die if left alone. No matter how severe the sickness, wasn’t it the basics of the path of Dao? One must never leave a man to die just because you lack ability.

“If something goes wrong, don’t resent me.”

If it goes well for the elder, then it goes well for everyone.

Chung Myung took a deep breath and placed his hand on Elder Hwang’s dantian. Slowly, he pushed qi into elder Hwang’s body.

The qi sleeping deep within Chung Myung slowly began to flow.

Chung Myung’s qi was like a leisurely flowing river. Sometimes a violently raging river, and sometimes a gentle sea embracing the world.

However, one thing about the current Chung Myung’s qi was different from his past.

Crystal clear.

Clear and spotless. It was clear without impurities, like pure water flowing through deep mountain valleys.

The clear and bright qi rushed into the body of Elder Hwang, which was filled with demonic qi.

Woong.

Elder Hwang’s body slightly convulsed.

The dark skin, corrupted with demonic qi, began to lighten as the vile energy retreated as Chung Myung’s energy flowed in.

‘Oh?’

Chung Myung found that shocking.

‘This is interesting.’

He had quite a bit of experience handling demonic qi, but this was his first time seeing this phenomenon.

What made this qi demonic?

It was called demonic qi because it reverses the flow. Demonic qi penetrates into other people, corrodes their bodies like a virulent poison, and aggressively pushes away any other qi.

But now, the demonic qi in Elder Hwang’s body was running away like a beast on fire rather than rushing at Chung Myung’s qi.

‘Then maybe…’

It would be possible!

No-no!

‘How much trouble did I have to go through to collect this! This should definitely work!’

If it hadn’t been for Chung Myung obsessing over the purity of his qi, he would have gathered more than ten years’ worth of qi already.

However, the amount of internal qi filling Chung Myung’s dantian was less than a year’s supply. Even this was only possible thanks to that miraculous pill.

Yet somehow, this tiny amount of qi he’d gathered was overpowering the demonic qi gathered in the elder’s body.

‘This is something I hadn’t expected.’

At first, he was simply trying to lay a pure and perfect foundation so that he could rise to a higher level than in the past. However, as time advanced, his obsession with pure qi grew stronger, and his progress slowed.

Just when he was thinking about whether he should release that obsession…

‘When I think about it, this is only natural.’

Pure qi is basically the opposite of demonic qi. The pure qi contains the power to purify all unclean things in the world. This energy was basically divine when compared to demonic qi. It was the purest and more perfect form of energy.

So, the demonic qi would naturally be unable to approach it.

The vicious demonic qi began to be neutralized in an instant.

Chung Myung felt it a bit ridiculous seeing the demonic qi turn to nothingness.

As he neutralized the demonic qi in Elder Hwang’s body, he began to clear his meridians and radically purified the body.

‘What is going on here?’

Cleansing the body and purifying meridians is something that would normally only be attempted with powerful medicines and only by strong warriors. How difficult would it be to purify an old man’s body which had several decades of impurities and decay?

But now, the young Chung Myung wasn’t using any pills but was merely washing away the demonic qi in the old man’s body with his own qi.

The problem was that Chung Myung did not intend this result.

Wooooooong.

Hwang Mun-Yak’s body began to tremble slightly. At the same time, his body began to turn both white and black at the same time. The area which had been purified from the demonic qi was white, while the areas which still remained tainted were dyed black.

The demonic qi was desperately trying to resist, little by little.

‘Just a little more!’

Elder Hwang’s body had turned into a battlefield. Even though he was unconscious, his entire body was trembling, and blood dripped from his lips.

Chung Myung clenched his teeth when he saw the dark red blood come out.

This was not a battle between Chung Myung and the demonic qi.

This was a battle of whether or not Hwang Mun-Yak could survive until the demonic qi was eradicated.

‘I need to end this quickly!’

Considering Elder Hwang’s condition, any hesitation could get him killed. It was better to leave everything to the heavens and make a quick gamble.

Chung Myung, who had made up his mind, raised his qi.

He pushed the last handful of qi into Hwang Mun-Yak’s body. Thick drops of sweat started to flow down Chung Myung’s forehead like rain.

In elder Hwang’s body, Chung Myung’s qi began to heat up the demonic qi. It absorbed the qi, neutralized it, and dissolved the impurities.

At the same time, Hwang Mun-yak’s narrow and cramped meridians began to expand and widen.

The demonic qi, which had been fiercely resisting, lost its force and began to rush to one location. Chung Myung, who saw the direction it flowed, was startled.

‘A-No, no!’

The head.

The demonic qi, which had no place to go, flowed in the opposite direction of the dantian, where Chung Myung was injecting qi.

Elder Hwang’s head was dyed black and started to swell.

Like it was about to explode!

Chapter 58: Are you really a Taoist? (3)

The demonic qi all gathered in Hwang Mun-Yak’s head as if it were ready to fight.

‘I can’t touch it.’

It was becoming a pain in the ass.

If Chung Myung behaved clumsily and caused a collision in Elder Hwang’s head, he’d be off to greet the reaper. No, maybe now, the grim reaper was already behind Chung Myung, patiently waiting for him to make a mistake.

Then, what if it was left alone?

‘That’s even worse.’

Elder Hwang’s lower body was purified entirely, but that wasn’t necessarily good news. The purified body would accept demonic qi from the head at a quicker rate.

It would happen much like ink diffusing into clear water.

If he advances, the man dies. If he retreats, the man dies too.

The beleaguered Chung Myung hesitated to make a decision for a while.

‘What do I do?’

‘What can I do?’

Normally, he was the sort to charge forward, but what if his recklessness caused someone harm?

He agonizingly pondered over his decision and bit his lip.

‘Then….’

He can’t charge forward, and he can’t retreat either, right?

Then, he’ll just ignore both options!

Chung Myung shifted all of his qi to one side of his body. A cornered mouse would even bite a cat, and a soldier forced against a cliff would fight to the death.

But what if there was room to escape? The rat would run, and the soldier would retreat.

‘Now, here’s a place for you to escape.’

Chung Myung opened a path.

There was nowhere to run away in Elder Hwang’s body, but there was still somewhere else. There was only one place left to escape.

That was to Chung Myung’s own body.

As soon as Chung Myung pushed his qi to one side, the pressured demonic qi began surging forth, searching for an empty vessel to occupy. The elder’s body had become unsuitable. Finding the connection between the two, the Qi rode along Chung Myung’s arm and invaded his now empty body.

“Uh…”

A groan leaked out.

A tingling sensation rushed through his arms and spread all over the body in an instant. His eyes began to blur with terrible pain, and his consciousness faded.

“Kuak!”

Chung Myung recovered his qi from Elder Hwang’s body. Then, he began to spread it through his own.

Kwakwakwa!

There was the sound of his bones creaking and crashing down.

The demonic qi, left with no place to go, began a fierce struggle. However, Chung Myung’s internal qi suppressed the demonic qi, like an occupying force, and mercilessly cleansed it.

Every part of the body seemingly turned into a battlefield.

Bang! Bang!

A roar echoed inside his body. With each explosion, unbearable pain tormented him. However, he bit his lips with bloody eyes.

Lose consciousness here?

‘Don’t make me laugh!’

His pride as the Plum Blossom Sword Saint wouldn’t let him.

Chung Myung stood still and waited till it stopped. Chung Myung’s qi attacked the remaining demonic qi fighting until the bitter end.

Kwakwakwang!

Thousands of exploding voices echoed.

His vision turned white as his consciousness faded. Chung Myung closed his eyes. His qi could subdue the demonic qi, but it was strongly resisting.

One round. Two rounds.

He scanned his body and, as if satisfied with his ability to cleanse it, his qi moved and then returned to the dantian.

Only after thoroughly checking his entire body did Chung Myung wake up.

“Kuaaak. I almost died.”

No joke, it was perilous.

This demonic qi wasn’t something he could have handled at his level. Even the slightest mistake would have cost either Chung Myung or Hwang Mun-Yak their lives.

‘This time, it was really dangerous. I’m not going to do this ever again.’

Chung Myung gently rubbed his dantian point.

“But it seems that it’s increased a bit.”

There was no particular reason it would increase, but it just felt like it had.

“… isn’t it still just a rat tail?”

The qi was just the size of a small pepper. It was still a tiny fragment of what he once had, and he wasn’t sure when it would grow into a large surging river.

Chung Myung sighed and turned his head to look at Elder Hwang. His face was slightly flushed, perhaps because the poison had disappeared. His health seemed to be recovering quickly.

Right.

It wasn’t just the demonic qi that had been washed away. When the pure qi was pushed into him, it wasn’t a body reconstruction, but the cleansing seemed like it increased his life expectancy by about 10 years.

“Tch.”

Thinking that he ended up doing good things for no reason, Chung Myung clicked his tongue and approached Elder Hwang.

“Uhhhhh….”

It seemed like the old man was regaining consciousness. His eyes were trembling as he slowly opened them.

Elder Hwang’s eyes, which had been shaking back and forth with no focus, began to settle on Chung Myung.

“Who… are you?”

Chung Myung smiled brightly.

“Me? A divine Taoist.”

“…”

Elder Hwang, who was weak, trembled.

“I must have died and gone to hell.”

“…”

What the hell was that?

After Elder Hwang regained consciousness, Eunha was quickly cleaned up.

Beon Ja-Bok, who tried to assassinate Hwang Mun-Yak, had planned to kill Hwang Jongi next if his plan succeeded. He would have then moved on to his children as well. If the entire family’s bloodline died in the same manner by some incurable disease, then the public would believe it to be bad luck or a curse on the Hwang family, and Beon Ja-Bok could avoid suspicion.

In fact, the plan worked pretty well. If Elder Hwang had died suddenly, everyone would have suspected malfeasance; but since he suffered for nearly a year, no one guessed that it was an attempted murder.

Didn’t they even receive confirmation from the Tang family that he wasn’t poisoned?

If Chung Myung hadn’t arrived, the Hwang family would have died according to plan, and their fortune would have been stolen.

Beon Ja-bok revealed everything. He was the son of a merchant that used to rival the Eunha guild; he spoke with tears in his eyes as he told a heart-rending tale of his pitiable life. Well, that’s none of Chung Myung’s business, though.

“If you commit a crime, you should be punished. Where in this world could you find a person without some tragic experiences?”

The only thing Chung Myung was interested in was the demonic qi. However, he said that he simply found a corpse deep in the mountains when he was out journeying.

Chung Myung felt like his spirit was siphoned away.

‘Well, there was no way those demonic sect people would have been this sloppy.’

No, they would have handled it carefully and quietly. After all, weren’t they the type that would kill others if they were bothered?

In conclusion, it can be said that everything went well, the culprit was found, the elder was cured, and it was confirmed that the Demonic Sect wasn’t involved.

With that, Chung Myung, who helped the Eunha Merchant Guild, was treated as their VIP.

A VERY important guest.

“Hmm.”

Elder Hwang sat down lightly.

“Father, you still need to be careful with your body. You just got out of bed.”

“It’s okay. I was indeed laid up in bed for a long time, but I feel even more energetic than before I fell ill.”

“Still…”

“Don’t worry.”

Hwang Jongi looked at his father with questionable eyes.

Even so, Elder Hwang didn’t back down. He might look like he would collapse any moment, but he was overflowing with energy.

“More than that.”

Elder Hwang raised his head and looked at Chung Myung.

“… disciple Chung Myung… right?”

“Yes. Didn’t you see me before?”

“It seems like you’ve changed a lot since then.”

“Ah. I ate quite well.”

Chung Myung scratched his head with thick sausage fingers.

Those who saw this scene were subtly shaken.

‘His size doubled in three days.’

‘How the hell did he eat so much in three days that his clothes are about to burst.’

‘I can even see oil flowing down his skin from the fat. Why did he even bother joining a sect?’

Everyone shook their heads at the sight of Chung Myung, who had grown twice as big as before in just 3 days.

Elder Hwang was the only one who, fortunately, maintained his composure. As if to show how great of a merchant he was.

“I should greet you first.”

Elder Hwang prostrated flat on the spot. Hwang Jongi, startled at the sudden action, tried to lift him up. But, when he saw his father’s stern gaze, he backed away without a word.

Elder Hwang bowed again and opened his mouth.

“Thanks to the disciple, my life was saved. I am forever indebted to you.”

“Ehhh. Get up, please.”

Why didn’t he get up?

At Chung Myung’s words, Hwang Mun-Yak slowly stood up and smiled.

“I’ve heard the story from our servant. If it wasn’t for you, I would have been dead. Even animals know the grace which saved them. If I was born as a human, yet forgot grace, then I would be worth even less than an animal.”

‘Oh. He’s so eloquent.’

Right. That’s right.

Hwang Mun-Yak said quietly, looking at Chung Myung.

“I don’t believe there is any way in this world to repay this life-saving favor, but I want to do the best that I can. If my benefactor wants something, please speak without hesitation.”

“Ah. Something I want.”

“Yes.”

“Haha. How could a Taoist seek rewards for helping to save others? If someone were to learn about it, they would mock us.”

“I do not discriminate against anyone. If I shirk away from showing grace simply because the one who saved me was a Taoist, I will be ridiculed. It is unacceptable for me.”

“I understand your feelings… but it can’t be helped. It would cause me trouble since I came here without getting the sect leader’s permission.”

“… without permission?”

“Yes. It was urgent, so I didn’t have time to request permission.”

Elder Hwang looked at the young Taoist in front of him with watery eyes full of affection.

How could he not be moved when this child had crossed his sect gates and risked himself to travel and save him?

“You did that much!?”

“As I said, it was urgent.”

Elder Hwang was moved while Hwang Jongi narrowed his eyes.

‘He looks rather relaxed for someone who came here without permission.’

But he didn’t speak in front of his father.

Elder Hwang nodded his head and spoke with an exuberant voice.

“I will handle that problem for you. Furthermore, I won’t tell the sect leader, so tell me what you want—”

“Is that a promise?”

Elder Hwang titled his head at Chung Myung, who interrupted his words.

“—What?”

“I want a promise that you won’t tell the sect about this.”

“Ah… of course. I’m a merchant, so I will….”

Again, before elder Hwang could finish speaking, Chung Myung pulled out a book from his sleeve.

Hwang Mun-Yak stared at the book with a puzzled expression.

“What is that book?”

“Ah. It’s no big deal. I find my memory failing me and growing fuzzier as I get older.”

Getting older?

This child?

Chung Myung smiled and shook the book.

“I wrote it down.”

“… what?”

“You wanted me to tell you what I wanted, right?”

“Right.”

“So, I wrote it all down.”

Ah.

So.

… that book? …All of it?

Chung Myung licked his finger, turned the page, and spoke with a smile.

“Now, shall we get started?”

“…”

“Now?”

“…”

Hwang Mun-Yak felt that he might have made a big mistake for the first time.

Chapter 59: Are you really a Taoist? (4)

“Father?”

Hwang Mun-Yak opened the door and nodded slightly, looking at Hwang Jongi as he entered.

“Is your body alright now?”

“Hm. It’s hard to believe, but my body feels so light that I could fly away. I feel ten years younger.”

“That is quite… strange.”

“I’m not sure how to put it into words, but I feel as lively as I did in my youth.”

Hwang Jongi looked confused.

The fact that his father, who was sick in bed for a year, had recovered was something to celebrate. However, it was strange that his sickly father’s body had recovered so quickly after lying in bed for so long. Even more bizarre was that it had grown stronger and livelier with no side-effects from the moment he recovered.

“Anyway, I am fine, for now.”

“Stop saying such things.”

Hwang Mun-Yak waved his hand,

“That young man’s ability is so amazing. It’s like I have received his grace.”

Hwang Mun-Yak remembered the first words Chung Myung said to him.

-Divine Taoist

‘It isn’t something I misheard.’

If Divine Taoist was a term used to refer to those who follow the Dao and can do things that normal humans cannot, then there was nothing more fitting to call this child aside from that.

Wasn’t he living proof?

“So, what is it? You probably aren’t here just to check my health, are you?”

“It might not be what you expect, but I am still your filial son. Isn’t it natural for children to take care of their parents’ well-being?”

“Don’t say such childish lines and get to the point. We don’t have much time.”

Hwang Jongi bowed his head.

Although Hwang Mun-Yak had only recently gotten out of bed, he still had a merchant’s insight.

‘Indeed, he is my father.’

Discussing his concerns would resolve his worries.

“Father. No, Guild Master.”

“Do tell me, young master.”

By changing their titles, the conversation would no longer be bound by personal feelings between family members but rather fellow guild members.

“I heard that you have issued an order to cut back on our dealings with the Southern Edge Sect?”

“I did.”

“And haven’t you promised quite a bit of compensation to Mount Hua too?”

“Yes.”

“Father, The Southern Edge Sect is still a powerful sect in Shaanxi and Xian. It is dangerous for us to cut back our dealings with them and join hands with Mount Hua, which could collapse at any moment.”

Hwang Mun-Yak nodded his head without answering.

“I understand that it is only natural for the Guild Master to feel grateful to the young Taoist. However, the promised reward is excessive, and it’s dangerous for us to deepen our relationship with a crumbling sect. Please allow the businesses to continue as before.”

Hwang Mun-Yak lifted his teacup and looked into it with deep eyes.

Taking a sip of tea, he closed his eyes as if wanting to slowly savor the aroma wafting from his cup.

How long was it?

Hwang Mun-Yak quietly put the cup down and opened his mouth with a slightly more serious voice than before.

“Young master.”

“Yes, Guild Master.”

“What is the duty of a merchant?”

“That…”

Hwang Jongi thought for a bit and opened his mouth.

“It is a duty of a merchant to run a business that is upright and just, to make trades and contribute to the nation and the world.”

“Huhuhuhu.”

Hwang Mun-Yak nodded his head with a satisfied smile.

“Young master.”

“Yes!”

“You have such a silver tongue. That sounds fine.”

“… Master?”

Hwang Mun-Yak firmly said.

“A merchant’s duty is to make money. Sometimes, it is fine for a merchant to violate the law and even morality in order to pursue wealth, isn’t that right?

Hwang Jongi bowed his head.

“… right.”

“If you want to do the right thing, do it with the money you earned. If you want to help others, you can help them with that money. There is no rule or morality in the act of a merchant making money. There is only efficiency.”

“Then what are we doing?”

With that said, wasn’t Hwang Mun-Yak’s current choice strange? Anyone could see that he was reducing their dealings with the Southern Edge Sect who was climbing to new heights while leveraging aid to Mount Hua, which was collapsing.

It wasn’t strange that if the Southern Edge Sect finds out about this, they will also cut off their relations with the guild.

“Did you forget how I made all this money?”

“I do remember. But…”

Hwang Mun-Yak’s method of making money was simple.

To find the value of items that others ignore and distribute them, or to find and support the most undervalued products.

Whether it is a sect, a union, or a group.

Hwang Mun-Yak had grown Eunha using that methodology, and now it was the best in Shaanxi.

“You mean to say that you’re investing in Mount Hua this time?”

“That’s right.”

“Guild Master, there has been a clear reason for every investment so far. But, I don’t understand this move with Mount Hua.”

“Haven’t you seen it for yourself?”

“… are you speaking about that child?”

“Right.”

“But…”

Hwang Jongi bit his lip slightly.

Chung Myung is great. There was no denying it, but only Chung Myung was good. The ability of one person doesn’t lead to greatness for the entire sect, and even more so if it’s a kid.

“With that child, I can foresee that Mount Hua will evolve. Maybe we will see them become stronger than expected. But Guild Master, no matter how much I think about it, I don’t think that one child will be able to grow Mount Hua strong enough to compete with the Southern Edge Sect. Doesn’t this seem a bit meaningless?”

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled brightly.

“Do you think so? I beg to differ.”

“… Guild Master.”

“Young master. Merchants must always look behind the scenes and not at the picture that is shown upfront. Eunha may have once been the most important alliance to the Southern Edge sect, but now we are just one of their aides. How much longer do you think this will last?”

Hwang Jongi looked blankly at Hwang Mun-Yak.

He hadn’t thought of it until now, but looking back, wasn’t Ki Mok-Seung’s attitude too oppressive and overbearing?

Even if the Guild Master was lying sick in bed, how could he dare to act so recklessly if he had any respect for the guild?

“The Southern Edge Sect has no room to grow now. Of course, they will continue to grow, but it will be at a slow pace. Though, that isn’t the case for Mount Hua. Mount Hua will experience explosive growth; if we can maintain a good relationship with them, then the benefits we can reap will be unimaginably large.”

“However, Guild Master, I don’t think there is any guarantee that Mount Hua will make it big.”

Hwang Mun-Yak narrowed his eyes.

“Hwang Jongi.”

“Yes! Father!”

Their way of addressing each other changed again.

“You sound like a child. A merchant does not wait for a reason to move. We need to create a reason.”

“…”

“We don’t have to wait for Mount Hua to grow. We need to make it grow. If we can succeed, we will be able to leap to become one of the top five Guilds of the land, not just of Shaanxi.”

“That is a difficult task. If we fail, there is no going back.”

“hehe. When the body becomes healthy, the mind becomes younger. So, what if we fail? Then we’ll just have to start over again. You don’t want to waste the wealth we have?”

“…”

“It is scary and unfortunate too. But I will be more ashamed if I’m unable to make more money than what we have.”

Hwang Jongi nodded his head.

His father had made up his mind, so any conversation would be meaningless.

“I’m still skeptical. However, if my father thinks so, then I will trust and follow you. I will help Mount Hua grow so that I can clear these doubts I have.”

“It feels good to hear that.”

Hwang Mun-Yak chuckled. Though, Hwang Jongi’s words didn’t end there.

“But.”

“Hm?”

Hwang Jongi frowned and asked.

“Aren’t the wealth and rewards you’ve given the young disciple a bit excessive?”

“There’s a reason.”

“Yes?”

Hwang Jongi looked at his father suspiciously.

To which his father answered with a question and a bright smile.

“What do you think about that young disciple?”

“Are you asking about his growth?”

“Yes.”

Hwang Jongi pondered over and over and then opened his mouth.

“Considering his heart and determination, he will, of course, have an important position in Mount Hua in the coming future….’

Hwang Jongi spoke carefully.

This wasn’t something that could be said lightly.

“Anyway, he will play a key role.”

“No. He is already playing a key role.”

Hwang Mun-Yak shook his head and continued.

“I have lived my whole life as a merchant. I have met many great merchants and warriors, but he is the only one who has embarrassed and left me in awe like this. Why should we waste our time searching for an Imoogi hoping to rise when there’s a dragon preparing to ascend right in front of us? There is no way we can let him go.”

“Is he that good?”

“You will find out soon. This sort of genius can’t be understood by an ordinary person’s reasoning. Don’t try to understand; just watch. There will come a time when you will end up accepting it naturally.”

Hwang Jongi nodded.

He still couldn’t understand, but since his father said it, he decided to accept it.

But one question remained.

“Then why did you give such excessive rewards?”

“He is normally the disciple of a sect, and he has his own reasons for coming here after learning that someone is sick. Of course, he didn’t come here solely out of sympathy for the sick. But his nature is good; there is no need to doubt that.”

“Hm.”

Hwang Mun-Yak spoke with a subtle smile, different from before.

“The wealth and rewards he has received now will become an indelible burden on his heart. Especially as he is young, the burden will be more intense. If his feelings of gratitude become shackles that bind us together, then this is a cheap investment to make.

“Cheap?”

“… actually, he took five times more than I expected. He was like a viper.”

“…”

Hwang Mun-Yak’s face flushed with irritation.

“No, how can someone so young want so much!? Damn it, if I knew that I would be ripped off like this, I’d rather pretend to be sick and send him back! He tore me apart! That young boy, he doesn’t even know to ask in moderation. Just because I asked him what he wanted, I ended up nearly crying my weary heart out….”

“Father, calm down. Someone might overhear.”

“Ahem.’

Hwang Mun-Yak pushed down his true feelings and sighed a couple times.

“Anyway, if he appreciates and accepts us as close allies who live and die together, we’ll have nothing to lose.

“I understand. A close alliance like friends.”

“Right, of course. He’s a good friend.”

Hwang Mun-Yak and his son smiled at each other.

Chapter 60: Are you really a Taoist? (5)

“Hehehe. I caught a pushover!”

Chung Myung laughed softly.

“No, it’s unreal, aren’t these people supposed to be merchants? They’re really going to give me so much just because I saved one person?

Money!

Wealth!

Riches!

Ahh! Didn’t all his ancestors say that money is the best?

He was already one of the wealthiest people in Shaanxi after he robbed his Sahyung’s warehouse, but it was always fun to see his wealth increase.

“But it wasn’t so much.”

He was just joking when he asked for half of their wealth. Just a quarter of their wealth would call for celebrations.

Of course, they wouldn’t have given such wealth to Chung Myung out of gratitude alone. They may have offered their entire fortune when Hwang Mun-Yak was still ill, but the situation and rewards would naturally change once he recovered.

It’s common knowledge that people change their minds before and after a situation resolves.

Nevertheless, to give so much wealth to Chung Myung without complaint, there must be some ulterior motive.

However, even if they wanted something from Chung Myung, Chung Myung wasn’t the kind to easily comply.

‘I just won’t do it.’

If Chung Myung was an average child, he might feel burdened receiving so much wealth, but unfortunately for Elder Hwang, he was no child.

Rather, he was more like an ancient fossil from the past.

If they had known, they would have taken a different approach.…

“Anyway, everything has been resolved.”

He rescued Elder Hwang, and in return, he promised that they would help Mount Hua. He will also head to Mount Hua with Chung Myung as soon as the preparations are done. So, it can be said that everything here was settled.

There was just one thing left…

Chung Myung smiled and looked at the person approaching.

“Hey, are you feeling well?”

Lee Song-Baek.

The second-class disciple of the Southern Edge Sect approached Chung Myung, who was lying on the wooden floor and stared down at him.

“What is it?”

Lee Song-Baek looked at Chung Myung and then answered.

“I need to return to my sect soon.”

“Ah, that’s good. It must be lonely being here all by yourself. Congratulations.”

“Thank you.”

Lee Song-Baek didn’t turn back after saying that. Seeing him standing there blankly, Chung Myung asked.

“Is there anything you want to say?”

At those words, he faintly smiled.

“Disciple.”

“What?”

“I understand that you set me up in order to solve this problem.”

“Huh?”

“I mean, the results were good, so I can understand what happened.”

Chung Myung sat up and looked at Lee Song-Baek.

“It would be strange to call what you did a trap. Wasn’t I the one who initially sought to trap you?”

Lee Song-Baek smiled.

“So, you aren’t going to blame me?”

Chung Myung smiled.

‘This kid has a strange personality.’

Kids these days were different from the old days. All the sects which came in contact with Chung Myung were anxious and hostile towards him.

Because of that, he never bothered checking the personalities of the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples.

“Well, what do you want to say?’

“It doesn’t matter if I’ve been humiliated, put in danger, or played by you. It all happened because I was lacking.”

Lee Song-Baek spoke with a stiff face.

“The only thing which bothers me is the time we crossed swords. I still don’t understand what happened.”

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

“So?”

“If you allow, I would like to spar with you again. This time, I have no hidden intentions like the last time and am sincerely requesting you to spar.”

Chung Myung scratched his cheek.

‘Look at this.’

He thought that this kid was going to start another fight. It was strange that he was okay with being played by Chung Myung.

He thought that the kid would charge at him like a wild boar. Instead, he chose to bury his grudges and ask for a spar to understand what happened.

‘I don’t think he’s just looking to get beat up.’

This was quite a funny reaction.

“Hm. what do I do?”

Sparring means comparing each other’s skills. From Lee Song-Baek’s point of view, it could be meaningful to learn something from Chung Myung, but for Chung Myung, there was nothing to gain from Lee Song-Baek.

So, there was no reason to accept the request…

“Well, fine.”

But there was no reason to reject it either.

Chung Myung stood up and pointed to the yard.

“There?”

“Let’s go where people can’t see.”

“Phew. I am scared. Are you trying to be sneaky again?”

As Chung Myung pretended to slit his throat, Lee Song-Baek sighed.

“Young disciple. I’m not a fool. It is shocking, but I know that your skills are superior to mine.”

“Oh?”

Chung Myung looked at him with interest.

“Didn’t I tell you? I want to know what happened last time.”

Chung Myung smiled.

“You will regret it.”

“Even then, it is fine.”

“Yes, well. Then let’s go.”

When Chung Myung moved, Lee Song-Baek followed him with a firm expression.

Lee Song-Baek exhaled a low breath.

He was nervous.

Lee Song-Baek wasn’t nervous even when he became a Sahyung, nor when he fought with his fellow disciples or Sahyungs. However, looking at Chung Myung in front of him, he felt his pulse race as his heart pounded in his chest.

‘Small.’

He carefully thought about it; this disciple was still a child.

It was embarrassing to call Chung Myung a child, but that doesn’t change that he was at least ten years younger than Lee Song-Baek. He was young enough to be the son of one of the elders.

‘There is at least one generation gap between us.’

A generation gap meant the difference between a teacher and a disciple.

This meant that Lee Song-Baek, a second-class disciple, could take a third-class disciple under him like Chung Myung. Of course, it was difficult for him to actually take one in because he had to concentrate on his training.

In other words, he was now holding his sword against someone young enough to be his disciple.

But what was this?

This pressure?

He recognized Chung Myung as an opponent and stood against him, but an immense pressure he had never felt before weighed him down.

‘Why am I so nervous?’

It was like standing against one of the elders. There was no way a child could be at that level, though.

In fact, not once had he felt Chung Myung trying to use his internal qi. Yet, it felt like a fierce opponent was standing on the other side.

Biting his lip, Lee Song-Baek tried to re-ignite his fighting spirit.

‘I need to check this with my own eyes.’

And he looked.

‘He seems to have good senses.’

Chung Myung was quite interested upon seeing Lee Song-Baek, whose sword was already shaking.

Right now, Chung Mung poses no threat to Lee Song-Baek. However, Lee Song-Baek was unable to relax, as if a mighty warrior was peering down at him.

Pretty sharp senses.

‘He might one day become the Southern Edge Sect’s Supreme Sword.’

In the past, when Chung Myung was that age, were there people of the same caliber in the Southern Edge Sect?

Well. Not sure.

It was a time when Chung Myung held no interest in others. He was too busy sharpening his own sword skills and trying to avoid getting caught by his Sahyung for doing the wrong things.

Even then, he couldn’t think of anyone in the past that could match up. A person with great senses meant greater potential to grow.

He might not stand out much right now, but as he gets older and trains more, he will begin to advance several times faster compared to the others. He could even become the Southern Edge Sect’s Supreme Sword in the distant future.

But the sad thing is…

‘He was born into the same era I was reborn into.’

Chung Myung gently raised his sword.

Should he teach Lee Song-Baek a lesson?

“Are you coming?”

When Chung Myung shook his head and pointed the sword at his opponent, Lee Song-Baek shuddered and backed away slightly before pulling his sword forward with clenched teeth.

The fact that he was still standing there showed how desperately he was trying not to back down. After taking several deep breaths, Lee Song-Baek struggled to open his mouth.

“Can I ask you one thing before we start?”

“Yes. Anything.”

“Who is Young Disciple?”

“… I am Chung Myung of Mount Hua.”

Lee Song-Baek clenched his teeth.

“How are you so accomplished? You clearly can’t have been learning the sword for a long time.”

‘I learned the sword for a hundred years now, you bastard.’

Chung Myung hated how his age was always being used against him.

He didn’t like it as, in the past, Chung Myung was a lot stronger than he was currently.

It had been less than a year since Chung Myung started training, and he progressed slowly as he chose to build a stronger foundation.

However, he had already focused on polishing his sword for over ten years in the past and reached a point that no one dared to challenge him.

So, there’s nothing to be flustered about.

“The world is inherently unfair.”

“…”

“But that doesn’t mean that you don’t have a chance either. The important thing is to believe in your own path, isn’t it?”

“Are you saying that if I believe in my sword and work hard, I will be able to defeat you someday?”

“Ahh. Could be.”

Chung Myung waved his hand.

“But it is fine. You won’t be ashamed if you can’t win against me. Rather, you will understand that it is an honor to have shared a duel with me.”

“Weird. Too weird.”

Lee Song-Baek’s eyes sunk in.

As they talked, it seemed like he gradually relaxed a bit.

“Be careful. I know that I’m not good enough, so I’ll do the best I can from the start.”

“Sure.”

Lee Song-Baek slightly twisted his sword.

Seeing that, Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

‘What is this?’

A small change in the sword’s movement. The Southern Edge sect values precision and sharpness. There was no way they could twist the sword like this. Showing the blade and moving it in front of the opponent is mainly used in the Illusion Sword technique.

Right.

A Mount Hua sword technique.

“I will deal with you using the Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword.”

“Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword?”

Chung Myung tilted his head.

Did the Southern Edge Sect have such a technique?

Normally, they had the Thirty-Six Movement Tanxia Sword. It seemed like something new had been invented in Chung Myung’s absence.

“Here I come!”

“Yes.”

“Ahhh!”

Lee Song-Baek screamed and rushed towards Chung Myung.

Chung Myung had a gloomy look as he watched this approach.

‘What do I do?’

Should he trample on the juniors of the Southern Edge sect? Or teach them kindly and help them grow?

‘Tch, no matter how bad my personality is….’

If the opponent was an elder or a great disciple, the situation would be different, but now it was a child. The priority was to teach…

It was then.

Lee Song-Baek’s sword changed.

It wasn’t fast, but heavy. Not flashy, but colorful.

A change that was entirely different from the Southern Edge sect’s methods, which Chung Myung was familiar with until now, unfolded.

Upon seeing the change, Chung Myung’s face contorted like a demon in a fury.

“This—”

Chung Myung’s wooden sword swung furiously.

Kwaang!

Lee Song-Baek coughed up blood and fell back in just a few seconds.

However, Chung Myung wasn’t satisfied, so he grabbed Lee Song-Baek by the collar and pulled him close to his face.

Seeing Chung Myung’s demon-like visage, Lee Song-Baek struggled to breathe.

“You, where did you learn that technique!?”

“Co-Cough. T-that…”

“You…”

Chung Myung bit his lip.

Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique.

What bullshit!

Those words may deceive those who don’t know any better, but Chung Myung wouldn’t be deceived.

The change was dull and clumsy, but the basic form of the sword was something Chung Myung knew very well.

‘Plum Blossom.’

The sword of Mount Hua. A sword representing Mount Hua. A sword that was the essence of Mount Hua.

Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique.

The Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique, which was lost in Mount Hua now, was unfolded in the hands of Lee Song-Baek.

Chapter 61: Sect Leader! That one is the God of Wealth! (1)

“W-where did I learn—Cough.”

Blood gushed out of Lee Song-Baek’s mouth. Seeing that, Chung Myung sighed and let go of his collar.

‘I went a bit too far.’

Even if it was unacceptable for Lee Song-Baek to use that technique, there was no way he could treat this child like that. Lee Song-Baek didn’t have the ability to create a new technique.

“Tch.”

He stretched out his hand and hit Lee Song-Baek on the back of his neck.

Tak!

As Chung Myung’s qi entered Lee Song-Baek’s body, his trembling subsided, and he let out a sigh as his expression eased.

Confirming that he had calmed down, Chung Myung stood up and looked at the sky.

Chung Myung, who had been looking thoughtfully at the sky for a long time, asked.

“Is that the Southern Edge Sect’s new technique?”

“… yes”

“Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique?”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung smiled bitterly.

‘They twisted the name?’

This was nothing short of open provocation towards Mount Hua, who knew what would happen if they learned about this.

‘No. That’s not it.’

These people claimed it as their own and displayed the technique openly. Most likely, the current Mount Hua wouldn’t even be able to recognize it for what it was.

This was making a mockery of Mount Hua.

If Chung Myung hadn’t appeared, Mount Hua wouldn’t have known anything even after watching the men of the Southern Edge Sect use their sect’s technique.

The evil man who made this sword was the only thing clawing away at Chung Myung’s mind.

“Who all learns this sword art?”

“…”

“What, are you overthinking it?”

Lee Song-Baek nodded.

“From the second-class disciples.”

“From the second-class. So, the first-class, second-class disciples, and the elders have all learned this sword?”

“I heard that the elders didn’t learn it. Those who are learning are first and second-class disciples.”

“They haven’t learned….”

As his words trailed off, Chung Myung’s eyes lit up with a fearsome glint.

If one of the elders had invented this new technique, they would have definitely transmitted it to the first-class disciples below them.

‘Then…the person who completed this sword technique is still in the sect?’

This was good news.

If the man who committed this crime was already dead and buried, then who would be left to receive retribution?

‘I don’t know who it is, but I will make sure that he pays the price for this!’

Chung Myung gritted his teeth.

There was no need to think.

When the Demonic Sect invaded Mount Hua, the Southern Edge Sect must have come to help. The invasion was too brutal. If they had decided to stand by and simply watch their neighbors’ downfall, then they would have been criticized by the rest of the world.

‘They pretended to help, but in reality, they stole techniques from Mount Hua.’

Not everyone had done this. However, some people took advantage and did something that shouldn’t have been done when Mount Hua was burnt down.

Maybe…

‘I don’t even know if the downfall is because of that Demonic sect.’

Crunch!

Chung Myung clenched his jaw and ground his teeth together.

The more he thought about it, the more he couldn’t stand it.

“These bastards…”

Chung Myung risked his life to save the sects from danger, and this is how they returned the favor to Mount Hua?

Moreover, wasn’t this just plain greed?

People make mistakes. It is in their nature. Let’s say that someone from the Southern Edge Sect came to help Mount Hua and was blinded by greed and made a mistake in a moment of weakness.

Then wasn’t it the duty of the sect to correct it?

The sect should strictly rebuke them and return what was stolen, not create new martial arts from it. And they have even named the technique Snow Flower? Were they mocking Mount Hua?

“What a load of shit.”

Chung Myung grunted, looking at Lee Song-Baek.

“You!”

“Uh? Ah.. yes!”

“Don’t learn this.”

“Huh? Why?”

“I said don’t, so don’t! You bastard!”

Chung Myung hit Lee Song-Baek on the back of his head.

He whimpered as he held his head.

“Tch.”

Chun Myung, who felt irritated, looked at Lee Song-Baek and spoke.

“This is unattainable.”

“…”

Lee Song-Baek looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes. However, he knew this was the truth.

If Lee Song-Baek hadn’t come and asked to spar again, then it may have taken Chung Myung several years or longer before learning about the Southern Edge Sect creating this technique.

It can be said that Lee Song-Baek helped him.

Chung Myung is a man who repays grace shown and never forgets grudges held. Although indirect, this grace was a bit much to ignore.

“The Southern Edge’s martial arts are centered around the basics. They seem slow and heavy right now, but it gets stronger once the sword is sharpened and polished. If you hope to achieve greatness, stop learning this right away.”

“But the elders say that this sword is one step ahead of our existing sword technique.”

“Of course, they would say that.”

Because not a single person must have managed to fully master the Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique.

Brilliant techniques advance quickly yet stagnate further in development. When a person who focuses on their foundation and honestly trains the basics and a person who learns complex and flamboyant techniques fight one another at a superficial level, then the flamboyant one will win every time.

‘No, doesn’t the Southern Edge sect understand….’

“Ah…”

Chung Myung sighed.

‘I think I know.’

The main culprit behind all of this might be Chung Myung himself.

The Southern Edge Sect must also be proud of their own sword techniques. However, Chung Myung, who they hated for decades, died in the battle with the Heavenly Demon Sect. The Southern Edge never once defeated Chung Myung.

Then was the sect weak?

Absolutely not.

‘If they were weak, they would never occupy a spot among the Ten Great Sects.’

On the contrary, the Southern Edge Sect had many geniuses. Throughout the history of the Southern Edge Sect, they always had talents blooming within.

These geniuses existed in Chung Myung’s time too, but these geniuses all crashed head-first into the great wall that was Chung Myung…

‘No wonder they were skeptical about their techniques.’

Idiotic people.

‘If I had been in the Southern Edge Sect, then I would have been the Southern Edge Supreme Sword.’

It’s not the martial arts that matter. No, martial arts are essential, but the person who uses and wields the technique matters most.

“Well…”

At that time, Lee Song-Baek glanced at him and opened his mouth.

“I shouldn’t learn the Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique?”

“Yes.”

“But…”

Lee Song-Baek hesitated to speak, to which Chung Myung glanced at him and said in a severe tone.

“Your path cannot be defined or set by others.”

“…”

Lee Song-Baek looked at him with a different expression.

“Some decisions require you to heed advice from others, but the real decisions in life need to be made by oneself alone. Neither the words of an elder nor mine will help you.”

Chung Myung turned around, and without hesitation, he started to walk towards the Eunha Guild.

“W-wait!”

Chung Myung stopped and slightly looked back.

Lee Song-Baek bowed.

“Thank you for your guidance.”

“Well, it was nothing.”

Chung Myung waved his hand and moved on.

Lee Song-Baek kept looking intensely at his moving figure and took a deep breath.

“I feel like I met a Divine Taoist.”

Meanwhile, Chung Myung’s face flushed red in anger and cooled.

“The more I think about it, the more rotten you bastards are!”

How dare they steal Mount Hua’s technique. And copy it? He wanted to run over to the Southern Edge Sect right now to crush it down.

“Ahh. Sahyung. This is how the world is. Instead of properly repaying the favor, these bastards did this bullshit. Do I have to put up with this?

-What can you even do aside from putting up with it?

It seemed like his Sahyung was laughing while looking down at him.

“Ah, if only I was as strong as I used to be….”

If Chung Myung was the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, then the elders of the Southern Edge sect would have already been dead. Unfortunately, he was just a third-class disciple.

‘I need to get stronger faster.’

It was that same feeling again.

This was a world where strength mattered, and those without power couldn’t do anything. Even if the elders of Mount Hua knew of this, could they do anything about it?

No.

The strong had the privilege to enjoy power, and the weak had to stay silent. The current Mount Hua didn’t even have the strength to accuse the Southern Edge sect.

“Only for now.”

Chung Myung gritted his teeth.

“But the time will come.”

Eventually, Mount Hua will regain its former glory. Chung Myung would make sure of that for as long as he lives.

If there was one thing he confirmed today, it was that Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect are completely incompatible.

Since the Southern Edge Sect had crossed a line they shouldn’t have, it was impossible for Chung Myung to even try and get along with them.

Even if the others wanted to, Chung Myung wouldn’t tolerate it.

“I need to get stronger faster.”

He needs to get stronger, but so does the entire sect. If Mount Hua grew stronger, things would change, and they wouldn’t need to be so restrained.

Chung Myung had no intention of making Mount Hua rely on him alone. He was going to bring the entire sect to power this time.

That way, those insolent fools can be adequately punished.

‘Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique….’

It’s well made.

It’s a clumsy copy of the Twenty-Four Plum Blossom Sword. However, they didn’t simply modify Mount Hua’s technique and ignore their own. Instead, they thought deeply about how to blend the Southern Edge Sect’s martial arts together with Mount Hua’s technique.

There were traces of the Southern Edge Sect’s sword arts within it, and the technique’s speed was also adjusted to harmonize with their martial arts.

It wasn’t just a copy, but the creation of a full-fledged martial arts technique…

“Which is why it’s so troublesome.”

A playfulness that couldn’t be hidden appeared on Chung Myung’s face.

“I’ll leave you alone for now but will slowly scorch you soon enough.”

Just sitting around watching didn’t fit Chung Myung’s character. If his enemy was going to be defeated, then he needed to be the one who brought his enemy to their knees. It wasn’t his style to wait around for their destruction.

“You crossed the wrong person.”

Chung Myung looked to the south and clicked his tongue while gazing at the mountain in the distance.

“I will make sure you pay the price for touching Mount Hua without showing grace, Southern Edge Sect.”

Then he turned around and walked back to the guild.

But, at this time, Chung Myung didn’t know.

The opportunity to punish the Southern Edge Sect, which he thought would be in the distant future, would come quite soon.

Chapter 62: Sect Leader! That one is the God of Wealth! (2)

Mount Hua was in a state of turmoil.

Seven days had passed since a third-class disciple had suddenly disappeared from Mount Hua. This was a huge thing.

Of course, when Mount Hua collapsed, there were more than just one or two who escaped at night. But this wasn’t something common anymore.

Thanks to that, the atmosphere in Mount Hua was horrendous.

“… could he have been in some kind of accident?”

“Accident?”

“It doesn’t seem like he is going to come back no matter how long we wait. But, I don’t see any reason for him to abandon Mount Hua, right?”

“Right.”

Yoon Jong nodded his head.

Jo Gul had said it. Chung Myung had no reason to leave Mount Hua. If he had even the slightest intention of doing so, then he wouldn’t have given away that pill.

Did he give away such precious medicine just to leave Mount Hua immediately after?

Rather, maybe he gave them poison and left before it could take effect.

But….

“If Chung Myung doesn’t have a reason to abandon the sect, but he still hasn’t come back after all this time… doesn’t that mean something bad happened to him?”

“Gul.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

“No matter how hard I try, I just can’t imagine him getting into an accident.”

“…”

“Can you imagine it?”

“I can—”

Chung Myung’s smiling face flashed through Jo Gul’s thoughts. Of course, not a warm smile but a wicked one.

‘Ehh. No way.’

Even if he was thrown down a cliff and then an even bigger cliff, Chung Myung would find a way to survive even in hell. It was impossible for him to not come back.

“Then, what happened?”

“It would be nice if it was something which could satisfy the elders. They seem quite angry.”

“Yes…”

“Sasuk Un Geom has been summoned to the sect leader’s residence again. I’m worried something bad is going to happen.”

“Sigh.”

Yoon Jong frowned and turned his side.

‘What the hell is going on with him?’

Even though he thought everything would be fine, Yoon Jong was strangely worried about Chung Myung,

“Isn’t he too arrogant!”

Hyun Jong frowned at the sharp voice.

“It has been seven days and nights already. This is the first time a third-class disciple has been away for such a long time without permission.”

“Hmm.”

“This isn’t something we can overlook. Now, the sect is finally re-establishing its foundation, what will others think!?”

When the head of finance, Hyun Yeong, raised his voice, everyone nodded. Clearly, this wasn’t something to overlook.

It was then that Hyun Sang, the head of Martial Arts, spoke.

“Now now, calm down, Sahyung.”

“How can I be calm now?”

“Why are you thinking about it like that? What if the child has gotten in some accident? He might need help right now.”

“Accident? What are the odds of an accident happening on Mount Hua? Even if it’s true, he walked out on his own two feet. Does that mean that it’s our mistake?”

“He may have lost his footing….”

“… Ummm…”

Realizing that this possibility made sense, Hyun Yeong immediately closed his mouth.

Mount Hua is indeed a steep mountain. It was common for people to trip and get injured. Even skilled warriors would occasionally get into danger; it wouldn’t be strange if a third-class disciple died.

“Shouldn’t we search the Mountains? If he is injured….”

“Right, we should search.”

Hyun Jong, who was silent, answered with a heavy voice.

“We can certainly not rule out that possibility.”

However, Hyung Yeong didn’t give up.

“Even so, we cannot let this slide. Isn’t this only a problem because a third-class disciple left Mount Hua on his own accord? Why was that child even given permission?”

Hyun Jong’s face slightly hardened.

It was none other than Hyun Jong who gave Chung Myung the authority. Now, Hyun Yeong was saying that the sect leader had given too much freedom to the child.

“There was a reason for that.”

“Reasons exist everywhere. Order can only be kept by following the rules of the sect.”

“Finance head.”

“Sect leader. This is something that shakes the basis of Mount Hua. Since when did Mount Hua give special privileges to children? He’s not even a great disciple, only a third-class disciple.”

“That’s enough.”

“…”

Hearing the heavy and cold voice, Hyun Yeong kept his mouth shut.

If he said anything more, it would cross the line. He also didn’t want to fight with the sect leader.

“… sect leader. I went too far. I didn’t mean to blame you.”

“I know.”

Hyun Jong took a deep breath.

‘What is happening?’

No matter how much he thought about it, he couldn’t understand why Chung Myung would do such a thing. Did he give him too much authority?

‘Did I misjudge that child?’

Un Geom, who silently watched the proceedings, opened his mouth heavily.

“Sect leader.

“Go on.”

“I will call the disciples and organize a search party. We will search through Mount Hua and the village below as well.”

“Hm.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“You should.”

“After finding Chung Myung, I will return. It was my mistake to not discipline him properly.”

“How could it be your fault? You aren’t even his mentor.”

“I am the mentor for all the children.”

“But…”

Hyun Jong, who was about to speak, shook his head and closed his mouth. If he said anything more, it would imply that the dorms were under no one’s guidance.

“It isn’t your fault. It is mine for putting too much trust in that child.”

“Sect leader, it’s not like that.”

“The important thing right now is not to find who is at fault. It won’t be too late to discuss the right from wrongs after finding that child. It would be a pity if we were unable to save him because we wasted too much time here, wouldn’t it?”

Everyone bowed their heads.

Even if there was a mistake, no one could deny Hyun Jong’s heartfelt concern for the disciple.

“Un Am.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Organize a search party with you as the head. We need to provide all the support we can in order to find that child. First, we will find him and then—”

At that moment, a loud voice interrupted the meeting from outside.

“Sect leader!”

Hyun Jong’s forehead twitched.

“I am in a meeting right now—”

“The child is back! Chung Myung is returning!”

Hyun Jong jumped up from his seat; there was a sense of relief which he couldn’t hide on his face.

“How is his condition?”

“Yes. He looks fine. But—”

“Enough. I will go and see for myself!”

There was nothing wrong, which meant there was no accident. Hyun Jong was glad to hear that he was safe.

“Wait, sect leader.”

However, Hyun Yeong didn’t let him leave.

“What?”

“Sect leader.”

Hyun Yeong glanced around at the people around him and opened his mouth.

“I understand that the sect leader cares for that child. Considering all that he has contributed, it is natural for him to receive such treatment.”

Hyun Jong narrowed his brows.

“What are you trying to say?”

“Sect leader. Do not spoil the child too much.”

“…”

“Punishment isn’t only a tool to govern the sect, but also to nurture the people properly. If he isn’t punished appropriately for what he did, then that brat will never realize what he did wrong.”

Hyun Jong sighed.

“You think I don’t know that? Don’t worry. I’m the one who wants to raise him more righteously than anyone else. If the child is safe and well, he will be punished for half a month….”

“That won’t do.”

It was Un Geom who cut in.

“The crime of not returning to Mount Hua is serious. He should be imprisoned for at least half a year.”

“Un Geom, he’s only a child, a third-class disciple.”

“If this was something the second-class disciples did, it would be a year. Please punish Chung Myung appropriately according to the offense committed.”

Hyun Jong closed his eyes tightly.

The position of sect leader doesn’t exist so that he can impose his will on others and decide everything. It was a position that gathered everyone’s opinions to come to a decision.

“… do the others think the same?”

“Yes.”

“Sect leader. Don’t hate us. We do treasure the child’s talents, but that’s the reason we are being strict.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“I know.”

Hyun Jong walked outside without loosening his stiff face. All those who were seated stood up as well.

Un Am sighed as he watched this happen.

‘What did you do? You foolish child.’

Only Un Am understood how much Hyun Jong cherished Chung Myung. So, no one except Un Am knew how he was feeling.

They nearly reached the entrance and saw Chung Myung entering the gate.

“That…”

Un Am and Hyun Jong’s faces were burning up.

No injuries. It was good that Chung Myung was uninjured, but he should have at least been self-reflecting on his sins. Yet, the child’s face showed no signs of regret at all.

Why is he walking tall with straight shoulders and acting so confidently?

“You brat!”

Hyun Yeong screamed.

“Huh?”

Chung Myung, who noticed so many elders approaching him, tilted his head.

“Where are you all going?”

“You idiot! Where do you think YOU are going?”

“To see the sect leader?”

Hyun Yeong, who was screaming, looked at Chung Myung, who bowed to Hyun Jong.

‘Th–that guy?’

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Is there a reason why you left Mount Hua?”

“Yes. Sect leader. There were unavoidable circumstances.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“Explain. If your explanation doesn’t convince us, you will be punished accordingly. Mount Hua’s laws are strict.”

Hyun Yeong couldn’t stand being there.

“How dare this third-class disciple be this arrogant! If you can’t give us a proper reason, I guarantee you’ll suffer extreme consequences! Sect leader favors you so much, but this is how you repay his kindness!?”

Chung Myung looked at Hyun Yeong and scratched his head.

“No, it isn’t like—”

“You! Speak properly!”

Firmly, an answer came from behind Chung Myung.

“Don’t behave like that, please.”

“Huh?”

Only then did they realize that Chung Myung wasn’t alone.

“Elder Hwang?”

“E-elder Hwang?”

“Didn’t we receive a letter saying that you had fallen ill?”

Hwang Mun-Yak, who entered the gate, looked at everyone. Then observed the sect leader.

And he bowed.

“It is nice to meet you again, sect leader. How have you been?”

“Elder Hwang. It’s been so long since I last saw you. I heard that you weren’t feeling well; I am glad that you seem to have recovered.”

He pretended to be calm, but Hyun Jong was shocked.

‘H-how is he here?’

Wasn’t it just seven days ago that they received a letter saying he was going to die of some serious disease?

Yet, Elder Hwang was here and looked to be in perfect form. He seemed like he was the same as the last time they met.

“Sect leader. Don’t be so angry. My life was saved thanks to this young disciple. He saved both the Eunha Guild and me too.”

“Y–yes?”

“It is Mount Hua’s grace which looked after Eunha. Which is why I decided to come here and give my thanks in person.”

“… what on earth?”

Everyone looked at Chung Myung.

Chung Myung only grinned and shrugged.

“Well, that’s how it turned out.”

‘Ah!’

‘This brat!’

‘Somehow, it only makes me angrier.’

Chung Myung was still the best when it came to pissing off his elders.

Chapter 63: Sect Leader! That one is the God of Wealth! (3)

“So…”

Hyun Jong couldn’t hide his shock. It was the same for everyone in the room.

There were only two people who remained composed.

One was Hwang Mun-Yak, sitting opposite Hyun Jong, and the other was Chung Myung, who was made to kneel and reflect.

“That child… you’re saying that Chung Myung cured Elder Hwang and prevented a crisis in the guild?”

“Yes.”

“Huh.”

Hyun Jong looked at Hwang Mun-Yak and Chung Myung alternatively.

It was unbelievable.

Although he was a disciple of Mount Hua, Chung Myung hadn’t been here for more than three months. He had little time to learn and was barely more than an average child.

How could it make sense for this child to accomplish such a formidable feat?

“Elder, is this really true?”

Hwang Mun-Yak frowned at Hyun Yeong’s question.

“Do you think I would lie to you?”

“O–of course, that’s not the case.”

Hyun Yeong backed off; the power of the Eunha Guild was so frightening that Mount Hua couldn’t afford to offend them.

Moreover, this man had consistently supported Mount Hua in the past. Without Hwang Mun-Yak, Mount Hua would have collapsed long ago. Doesn’t that mean he should be catered to as a guest of unparalleled importance?

Even if Hyun Yeong held an esteemed position as the finance head and elder of Mount Hua, he couldn’t treat Hwang Mun-Yak carelessly.

“I don’t believe that you would do such a thing.”

Hyun Jong frowned slightly, looked at Hyun Yeong, and spoke.

“It wasn’t our intention. I will apologize for what was asked, Elder Hwang; please don’t be too upset with us.”

“Well.”

However, his displeased expression didn’t relax.

He wasn’t really bothered by their behavior, but he needed to keep the others in line. A merchant who engages in trade shouldn’t be too friendly. Even a small gap should be exploited as an opportunity to challenge the opponent…

“Kuak!”

Hwang Mun-Yak coughed when he glanced at Chung Myung, who showed a displeased look on his face.

‘Come on now.’

A third-class disciple is the one saving his elders from being scolded too harshly. Where in the world would you see a sight like this?

Hwang Mun-yak couldn’t ignore the signals Chung Myung was sending him and softened his expression.

Un Geom spoke up.

“I don’t understand.”

Hwang Mun-Yak looked at him and asked.

“Who are you?”

“I am Mount Hua’s Un Geom. I am in charge of the dorms the disciples reside in.”

“I see, and Un Geom, you are saying that you don’t believe my words?”

“That’s not the case. I just have a fundamental question. Apart from everything else, does Chung Myung even have the ability to cure such ailments?”

“…”

A reasonable question.

Everyone looked at Elder Hwang and Chung Myung with doubt in their eyes. Hwang Mun-Yak was speechless and also looked at Chung Myung. This wasn’t something the two had discussed.

“That isn’t difficult.”

“Can you explain?”

“Yes. As you all know, I was a beggar, right?”

“Yes.”

“Beggars usually pick up anything and eat everything they can get their hands on, so they often get sick and poisoned.”

“What are you saying! If that was the case, then the Tang family could have helped treat Elder Hwang a lot earlier.”

“Yes, but you see beggars end up poisoned in unexpected ways. Most are unaware of how to relieve traditional poisons, but beggars are much more capable when it comes from something edible.”

Taking a deep breath, he opened his mouth.

“Five Shade Grass is a plant that is found in most places. It is very similar to mugwort, but it has poison in it. Birds also often eat it and get poisoned. Once consumed, the poison begins to afflict you after a couple of days, then comes a long period of suffering and eventually death.”

Everyone was engrossed in his words.

“However, the way to detoxify it is simpler than one might think. Even if you take the person to a physician, they won’t be cured, but feeding the person a ground radish will help them recover.”

“So, Elder Hwang was poisoned with the Five Shade Grass?”

“Yes. The symptoms were very similar, so I tried it out, and he recovered.”

“No…”

Hyun Sang, who was silent until then, began to speak.

“I’ve heard a similar story. The Beggars Union is known to have the most efficient poison remedies.”

“Well, is that so?”

Chung Myung laughed internally as he saw the others questioning whether to believe it or not.

‘Ask away, you bastards.’

There was nothing to worry about, even if they went and asked the Beggars Union to check the authenticity of the information. Everything he said was true.

War was fought against supply. Getting supplies to the front lines on time was the most difficult thing in the world. So, those on the front line would often pick up anything that could be eaten, and there are many cases of people getting sick.

The incident he spoke about was something Chung Myung had actually experienced in the past. It was the Beggars Union that had helped him.

What happened to Elder Hwang had nothing to do with this, but what do the sect leaders even know?

‘It sounds reasonable enough.’

Life is like that.

“Such a thing exists?”

“Then we can’t do much. Should we really cause a fuss over Chung Myung being a few days late when someone’s life was hanging in the balance?

“You did a great job!”

Everyone looked at Chung Myung in admiration.

“Sect leader.”

Un Geom spoke.

“If this is true. Then, rather than punishment, shouldn’t a reward be given instead?”

“Uhm. Indeed, you are right.”

Hyun Jong’s eyes widened a little.

“But sect leader.”

Un Am raised a slight objection.

“It is a great sin to disobey the sect leader’s order and not return, no matter how righteous his intentions were, what he did was wrong.”

“Are my orders more important than a man’s life?”

“… that…”

“Are you saying that we should praise a disciple for leaving a person to die as long as they return punctually?

Un Am went silent.

“Mount Hua is a sect which pursues justice. What can take priority over saving people’s lives? Are my petty orders more important than life?”

“I was short-sighted.”

Un Am bowed his head.

Meanwhile, Un Am and Hyun Jong exchanged glances. Un Am was the first to speak, and Hyun Jong expressed his anger, so people wouldn’t bring this topic up anymore.

Hyun Jong, who realized Un Am’s intention behind asking this question, gave a quick glance at Un Am and looked back at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Well done.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung bowed his head.

As soon as the situation was settled, Hwang Mun-Yak decided to speak.

“The Eunha Guild and I have been greatly blessed by Mount Hua. No, to be precise, I was helped by Chung Myung, but he said that it was all thanks to the teachings of Mount Hua and gave credit to the sect.”

“Oh!”

“That child.”

“It’s the Path of Dao, seriously!”

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled.

‘Everything is taken care of.’

However, it was impossible to speak the truth. From his point of view, it was better to let Chung Myung and Mount Hua be one.

It was hard to hold back his laughter as he looked at the face of Chung Myung, who brazenly accepted his elder’s praise.

“And so, to repay the kindness I received, I would like to make a small investment in Mount Hua.”

“Investment?”

“Yes. Though perhaps the word investment isn’t right. More like support. An investment has to be returned, but there is no need for such things if it was given in the form of support, right?”

“Y-You have already given so much to Mount Hua….”

“Sect leader.”

Hwang Mun-Yak looked at Hyun Jong.

“If I was planning to end it there, I wouldn’t have bothered coming here with my family. I want to pour all of myself into Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong’s eyes trembled.

“E-elder Hwang?”

Despite Hyun Jong’s surprise, Hwang Mun-Yak only smiled.

“We brought our people so we can take this slowly. What Mount Hua needs and what we can do will all be discussed.”

“Thank you! Thank you very much, Elder Hwang.”

“There’s no need to thank me. I will fall short no matter how much I try since life cannot be measured with money.”

Hwang Mun-Yak and Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung at the same time.

Hyun Jong spoke with a cheerful smile on his face.

“You’ve brought a blessing over Mount Hua, and now you’ve even helped spread the name of Mount Hua. I’m almost ashamed.”

“Don’t say that. If I hadn’t learned anything here, would I even be able to do that?”

Hwang Mun-Yak was shocked.

‘Look at this silver-tongued devil.’

His words flowed smoothly like oil on an even surface.

“Then, apart from the finance head and Un Am, the others can leave and rest.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Everyone stood up.

“And Chung Myung, I will call you later, so don’t go too far.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung bowed his head slightly and went out with the others. As soon as they exited, the head of Martial Arts, Hyun Sang, patted him on the shoulders.

“You worked hard. It was a great job.”

“Well, I didn’t do anything too great.”

“What you did was amazing. How can it not be a huge deal? Huhuhu. It’s amazing enough to save a life, but it was even Elder Hwang’s life! Really, a shooting star must have come to Mount Hua!”

That shooting star was Chung Myung himself.

He was the only star here.

Chung Myung sighed, seeing these people giving all the credit for what he did to some random luck.

Right, right. What can I do when they’re so happy?

At that moment, Un Geom came.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, Dorm Master.”

“I know you did a good job, but it is true that you handled it poorly. You were in the wrong, especially for leaving Mount Hua without a word.”

“I was in a hurry, so I didn’t think about it.”

“That’s possible, but be careful next time. What you did this time was more dangerous than you thought.”

“Yes. I will be careful.”

“It is true that you disobeyed the sect leader’s order. You can’t always use the excuse that it was unavoidable.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung bowed his head.

His lips were pouting.

‘Why is this child so inflexible?’

However, Chung Myung, who was thinking all sorts of twisted thoughts, felt relieved when he looked up and saw Un Geom’s lip twitching and struggling to hold back a smile.

“Ahem. Well, you should be careful and keep up the good work.”

‘Look at him.’

The others all approached, patted him on the shoulder, and congratulated him. The existence of Elder Hwang in Mount Hua held a deeper meaning than Chung Myung thought.

He is a person who provides money.

And those with money are the best.

“It seems like Mount Hua’s luck is finally turning around. Good fortune keeps finding us lately.”

Luck?

Everything was because of Chung Myung.

Chung Myung sighed secretly.

‘Ah, Sahyung. My back is starting to hurt now.’

He seemed to hear his Sahyung laughing at him from the sky.

Chapter 64: Sect Leader! That one is the God of Wealth! (4)

Mount Hua was in chaos.

No, it was already in a state of turmoil, but now it was in a fuss for a completely different reason.

“Elder Hwang was saved?”

“Who is elder Hwang?”

“The greatest merchant of the Eunha Guild. Even if all the merchants of Hua-Um gathered, they wouldn’t be able to go against Elder Hwang.”

“Huh? Is he that great of a person?”

“That’s what I’m telling you.”

The third-class disciples were all in either disbelief or shock as they spoke.

“Chung Myung saved someone that important!?”

“Wow! This is really….”

“Weird.”

“I know.”

“Why would he….”

It was good news, but the third-class disciples were all confused.

With this, Chung Myung’s position was bound to rise, and it was clear that the adults in Mount Hua would favor him more. Wasn’t Chung Myung already being protected by Un Geom and the sect leader?

And now he’s going to get another level up?

Jo Gul smiled.

“I wondered what he was getting himself up to.”

He is really a ghost-like man. Maybe the heavens were helping him?

“Isn’t this too much, Sahyung?”

“Well….”

“Doesn’t he have too much luck on his side?”

Yoon Jong looked at Jo Gul and spoke.

“You think it was luck?”

“… you think it’s something else?”

“It isn’t luck. It’s skill.”

Jo Gul titled his head. Yoon Jong started to explain when he saw his companion’s confusion.

“It was Chung Myung’s skill that gained him the authority to go down to Hua-Um village, that’s why he got picked to deliver the letter. What would we have done in that situation? All we could have done was inform our elders of the situation and perform our usual duties in Mount Hua.”

“…. yeah.”

“What’s more, there was no guarantee that Elder Hwang would survive his treatment either, but he took a chance because of his skill. If things had gone poorly, Elder Hwang might have died, and Mount Hua would have been ostracized as a sect that tried to take advantage of a wealthy guild only to cause a catastrophe instead. It’s a situation in which even the sect leader can’t move about recklessly. “

Jo Gul nodded his head. What Yoon Jong said was true.

“Everything looks easy when you see someone else do it. You only realize how difficult something truly is when you must do it yourself. Focus on developing your skills instead of discussing luck. Luck may provide you with opportunities, but if you lack the skill to capitalize on that moment, then it’s all a waste.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

Jo Gul sighed low.

‘Sahyung is starting to nag more and more these days.’

In the past, Yoon Jong was the kind that would step aside from any situation.

Although he was sitting in a symbolic seat as the eldest of the third-class disciples, he wasn’t someone outstanding and never tried to make use of his position.

Like water, he would often just go with the flow. Lately, though, he felt more and more like a Sahyung.

He’s changed since he decided to achieve something in Mount Hua.

It was the same with Jo Gul.

The others went silent and fell into contemplation at Yoon Jong’s words.

However, Yoon Jong’s words weren’t finished.

“But I am worried.”

“About?”

“The process and result were achieved through his skills, but it is also true that his position has increased….”

Chun Myung had already made several contributions to Mount Hua. Now, he made another major one, so what level would his status rise to?

“I am sure that something else is bound to happen.”

“…”

Chung Myung being vicious like a snake isn’t the problem here.

The problem was that this vicious person was diligent.

“Sigh.”

“Just what sin did I commit in my previous life?”

The White Plum Blossom Boarding House was filled with sighs.

“Elder Hwang decided to take over the businesses in Hua-Um.”

“We’re fortunate.”

“If it’s Elder Hwang, we can trust him.”

Hyun Jong tried to suppress his excitement.

‘I am so glad that I can’t even make tea!’

It wasn’t easy to stabilize his hands, which were trembling in excitement.

Hwang Mun-Yak offered to manage their business without any charge. He even promised a huge amount of compensation, saying that he would repay the favor he had received.

He simply placed two conditions.

Instead of accumulating wealth inside Mount Hua, the money earned would be utilized for the development of Mount Hua.

And the other was to give preference to the third-class disciple, Chung Myung.

The first condition was no problem.

Hyun Jong had no intention of storing the wealth away. Mount Hua wasn’t in a position where it could leisurely accumulate wealth. They would have to pour money down the well before it would become stable enough to hold water.

The problem was the second condition.

‘Preference is too vague of a term.’

It was a natural request to expect from Elder Hwang, Chung Myung had saved his life. As Chung Myung is a disciple of Mount Hua, it can be said that Elder Hwang was repaying the favor by investing in Mount Hua. Yet, he had a special interest in Chung Myung himself.

The problem came from the term ‘preferential treatment.’

‘What are some ways we can give such treatment to a third-class disciple?’

That was what made Hyung Jong’s head hurt.

If he soberly evaluated the achievements made by Chung Myung, it was strange that he hadn’t been rewarded properly.

But wasn’t Chung Myung already receiving privileges that even the great disciple couldn’t have?

‘At a time like this….’

Hyun Jong looked at Un Am.

Un Am looked at Hyun Jong too and opened his mouth.

“Hmm, this is a good thing.”

Un Am drew in the crowd’s attention, looked around at them, and continued.

“The reason Elder Hwang asked is because Chung Myung has saved him from a horrible end.”

“Well.”

“Yes.”

“He’s such a good child. How does he choose to only do good deeds? Is he a spirit?”

“He’s truly on the path of Dao.”

“Tell me about it.”

“Hm?”

Un Am coughed once to gather attention from those talking about the child.

“Then, shouldn’t we reward that child again?”

“Well, yes. He should be rewarded.”

“He does deserve it.”

Everyone nodded.

“Hmmm, so what kind of reward do you think would be fine? Let’s all give our opinions.”

Seeing that things had gone the way he wanted, Hyun Jong smiled.

Wouldn’t it be nice to have a disciple that only brings fortune to Mount Hua and receives appropriate rewards in return? Of course, such things were a blessing to Mount Hua.

“Considering that he’s a third-class disciple, why not teach him a martial art which he normally couldn’t learn as a third-class disciple?”

“Oh?”

Hyun Jong looked at Hyun Sang.

This was certainly preferential treatment for the child.

“After I finish studying them, why not let Chung Myung learn the Seven Sages Sword and the Falling Flower Sword? That would certainly make him happy.”

“That’s a great idea. Sect leader?”

“I agree.”

It was a very warm atmosphere. Hyun Jong smiled and nodded his head.

“Then, as we discussed….”

“No…”

At that moment, someone interrupted Hyun Jong’s words.

Hyun Jong slowly turned his gaze and looked at the source of the voice.

Finance head, Hyun Young.

He decried with a face full of anger.

“Sect leader! It makes no sense to give that child this kind of reward!”

‘Ah, what now!’

This discussion was going to be another pain in the ass.

Although Hyun Jong was the sect leader of Mount Hua, Hyun Young was also an elder and a member of the financial side. He couldn’t easily ignore the words of Hyun Young and do what he wanted.

“Finance head, what now?”

“That’s your reward? What kind of reward is that?”

“Huh?”

“Do you think that if you give that child martial arts, he’ll be happy? He’s already busy training every day at the dorms, and you want to give him more to learn? That’s not a reward; it’s punishment!”

What?

What is this?

Why did it seem like the conversation went in a strange direction?

Amid everyone’s confusion, Hyun Young looked at them with fire blazing in his eyes.

“That is no reward! A reward must be something that you give another person wholeheartedly. What kind of reward is this!? When you give a reward, it needs to be significant enough to feel a certain reluctance to part with it! Do you understand what I’m talking about?”

What was this man even saying?

Hyun Jong looked at Hyun Young with eyes that were full of bewilderment as he couldn’t figure out what was happening. Wasn’t Hyun Young the one who hated Chung Myung’s the most and said he had to be punished at all costs in the previous meeting?

Why did he suddenly change his position?

At last, an excitable voice erupted from Hyun Young’s mouth.

“Do you think this is some normal contribution!? Thanks to that child, Elder Hwang was saved, and the money is flowing into Mount Hua—No, Mount Hua is being supported! Elder Hwang even said that he would even manage the businesses for free… FOR FREE!”

Only then did Hyun Jong understand why this was happening.

Hyun Young was the head of finances.

Someone who had to take care of the maintenance of Mount Hua. To put it bluntly, it was a position that needed to manage the money within Mount Hua.

Really, it could be expressed in one word,

HELL

How horrible must it have been to manage the finances for a ruined sect? However, thanks to him, Mount Hua was able to survive until now.

‘No more.’

There was no one willing to aid a ruined sect, and debtors kept coming to collect.

Then, when the situation became dire, Chung Myung solved the problem.

Although a large chest of money was found, money would disappear quickly once it found a use.

What the finance head wanted wasn’t money, which would run out when used, but stable income, which could be invested each month with the businesses running well.

How happy must he be? After all, Chung Myung saved Elder Hwang, the person Mount Hua needed the most in order to steer them towards the best outcome. From his perspective, he would support Chung Myung even if he needed to wait on him hand and foot for over a month.

Hyun Young was red when he shouted.

“Give him a proper reward! That way, he will bring more nice things to us!”

“A reward isn’t an investment to earn back later….”

“Anyway!”

Hyun Young, who was excited, even stopped Hyun Jong from speaking.

“Sect leader! That child, he is a God! He’s the God of Wealth! You need to give him a proper reward and keep using him to earn more money! Do you get it! Huh?”

“…”

“Do you know just how much money he’s earned this time? All these other idiots are gathered here, but not a single one among them has even brought in a penny! Such bastards! But this child is a wonderful bastard! Right? Do you understand? Say yes?”

Hyun Sang got up from his seat and then hugged Hyun Young from behind and started pulling him out of the room.

“Sect leader! Reward him right! A huge reward!”

As he was dragged out, Hyun Jong sighed.

“I hope you all understand. He’s gone through some tough times.”

“… we understand.”

“Actually, there isn’t anything we can do. Considering the hardship that he’s endured.”

“How difficult must it have been….”

“Sect leader.”

Un Am cleared the atmosphere and spoke.

“Finance head is right. Chung Myung needs to be rewarded properly. I especially like the idea of giving him what he really deserves.”

“Well, that’s right.”

“If we look at this situation calmly, Chung Myung’s achievements this time cannot be compared to what he did previously.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head.

“But last time, it was pure coincidence. So, the disciples will also try to see what kind of reward Chung Myung receives this time.”

“Yes.”

“I want Chung Myung to be given a proper reward so that all disciples understand that those who achieve great deeds for Mount Hua will be awarded appropriately.”

Everyone nodded their heads, and Hyun Jong said.

“Then, what should be the reward?”

No one could answer.

“First of all….”

It was Un Am who spoke.

“He likes going down Mount Hua, so I think it might be good to have him be our liaison with the Eunha Guild.”

“But wouldn’t that just be turning him into an errand boy? Is that even a reward?”

“Elder Hwang is fond of Chung Myung, so he will treat him favorably each time.”

“Ah, that is true.”

Hyun Jong nodded his head. It was a good idea.

As soon as one opinion came out, the others began to express their thoughts as well.

“Why not give him a Plum Blossom Sword in advance? Wouldn’t the child like that?”

“What use would the Plum Blossom Sword be to a child who still trains with a wooden sword? Why not give him a new uniform? Embroidered with golden thread.”

“What’s the point of wearing gold-lined threads when food is scarce? Let’s just give him something to eat or let him take something from the library.”

“Do you think Chung Myung is like you! You think we should just give him food as a reward?”

“Then we’ll give him pills!”

“There are no pills in Mount Hua!”

“Then buy some! We have money!”

It was then.

Thud!

Hyun Young kicked the door open and shouted.

“Just give him money! What are you all racking your heads for when we have money to give! You frustrating old bastard! Shut up and give him money for… um! Um! Um!”

Hyun Sang covered Hyun Young’s mouth and dragged him out again with an awkward smile.

Tak!

“…”

“…”

“…”

Hyun Jong closed his eyes.

‘It is true that good things have constantly been happening lately….’

But the more Mount Hua grew, the stranger it became.

Maybe it was just his imagination?

Chapter 65: Sect Leader! That one is the God of Wealth! (5)

Hwang Mun-Yak sat opposite Chun Myung and sipped his tea.

Chung Myung frowned slightly as he looked at Elder Hwang.

It was Hwang Mun-Yak who began the conversation.

“How is it?”

“You say the strangest things from time to time.”

“There is nothing wrong with asking.”

Hwang Mun-Yak’s eyes shone as he gauged Chung Myung’s reaction. He felt a subtle sense of incongruity as he looked at Chung Myung.

‘I, Hwang Mun-Yak, am speaking on equal footing with a child like this?’

It wasn’t a matter of arrogance, but considering what Hwang Mun-Yak had achieved in life, sitting like this with a third-class disciple would usually be unthinkable.

Nevertheless, Hwang Mun-Yak was now alone with Chung Myung. Not as a benefactor who saved his life, but simply because he wanted to deal with Mount Hua’s third-class disciple, Chung Myung.

“Aren’t we in the same boat now?”

“Boat…”

Chung Myung smiled brightly.

“It was luck that I saved Elder Hwang. Being on the same boat is a bit too much.”

“I have no desire to be on the same boat as Mount Hua.”

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes and looked at Elder Hwang.

‘Look at him?’

Isn’t he being a bit too honest?

“To be precise, without you, Mount Hua is of no interest to me.”

“You are overestimating my worth.”

Hwang Mun-Yak curled his lips at Chung Myung’s modesty.

“Young disciple. I am a merchant. I have been a merchant all my life, and I will be one until the day I die. As a merchant, the only weapon I possess is my eye for people.”

“…”

“If my eyes were wrong, I would have already been in ruin. Even if I have merely been lucky enough to avoid failure till now, I would surely fail one day. There is nothing more upsetting or regrettable than that, but if my eyes are correct….”

Hwang Mun-Yak looked at Chung Myung.

“Wouldn’t good fortune be in the future for both Eunha and Mount Hua?”

Chung Myung lightly scratched his cheek.

“Well, don’t say anything about being on the same boat. I’m not fond of such phrases.”

“Why?”

“People who speak such words are often the first ones to put a knife in others’ backs.”

Things like this happened in the past.

Countless people praised and shed tears for Chung Myung and Mount Hua as they went to save the world. But none of them had shown kindness to Mount Hua in the end.

So how could he like these words now?

“I don’t like such phrases either. From a merchant’s perspective, a boat is something you can get on and off at any time.”

“Yes, I suppose so.”

“But.”

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled.

“Although, if our destination is the same, then there is no need to get off the boat. After all, if both parties row the boat together, won’t it be easier to reach our destination?”

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung looked at Hwang Mun-Yak with serious eyes.

“Yes. There is nothing wrong about that.”

Hwang Mun-Yak’s eyes shone.

‘I am sure.’

He confirmed this.

It didn’t matter what the outcome of this conversation would be. It would be great if Chung Myung would cooperate, but even if he didn’t, as long as the negotiations with the sect leader were completed, Eunha Guild would support and take advantage of Mount Hua.

Nevertheless, Hwang Mun-Yak wanted to speak privately with Chung Myung to confirm this point.

‘In this child’s head, Mount Hua is already developing. He has already determined that Mount Hua will develop, without fail.’

What tremendous confidence.

However, this self-confidence didn’t feel like it came from simple child-like pride, ignorant of the world. Rather, a sense of senility could be felt from Chung Myung.

“Young disciple.”

“Yes.”

“The Eunha Merchant Guild will do its best to support Mount Hua. You know what that means, don’t you?”

“What, you are breaking up with the Southern Edge Sect?”

“That’s right.”

“I think it is a bit disrespectful to expect a reward for something we didn’t request from you.”

“I want nothing in return. I just want you to know.”

“Yeah. Sure…”

‘You just wanted to let me know, sure.’

It wouldn’t cost a thing.

“I’ll be sure to come and visit you often in the future.”

“Yes. Sect leader said that if there was a need to send someone to Eunha, I’d be the one to go.”

“That’s quite the good news. I hope to see and speak with you soon. Haha.”

“Yes, of course. Hahaha.”

Both people chuckled at the same time and looked at each other.

In their hearts, both had completely different thoughts.

‘This quick-witted little prick!’

‘How dare you try and take advantage of me. I’ve handled countless fools like you in my past life!’

They were facing each other with smiles, but sparks were flowing between them.

“Young disciple.”

“Yes?”

“This is the gamble of my life.”

“That’s something a young man should say.”

“Well, I think I’ve gained a new life after you helped me. It wouldn’t hurt to bet on a new life.”

“But you don’t really care about that.”

“Perhaps I just wanted to say it then.”

Hwang Mun-Yak stood up. Then he looked at Chung Myung.

“I will only say one word of advice in return for saving my life.”

“Yes.”

“Young disciple. You certainly are excellent. Even if you searched every crevice of the world twice over, you might not find someone more capable at your age.”

“Thank you for your kind words.”

Do you want to find a person like Chung Myung? It’s not just those his age; there’s absolutely nobody like him in the entire world!

Who else could come back from the dead like him?

“But I think that young disciple needs to stay hidden a little longer. The world is a scary place. All sorts of ghouls and ghosts dance around, and there are many demons around us. As soon as you reveal yourself, they’ll rush towards you.”

Chung Myung had a bitter smile.

“You speak too highly of me; I am just a kid.”

“I told you all that I wanted to say. Okay then.”

Hwang Mun-Yak turned around and walked away.

“Ah, one minute.”

“Yes?”

Hwang Mun-Yak turned around again; Chung Myung had a subtle smile on his face.

“I need you to find out a few things for me. Could you please help me out?”

Hwang Mun-Yak also had a subtle smile as he nodded.

“Sure.”

Tak!

Hwang Mun-Yak closed the door behind him and Hwang Jongi, who was waiting, approached him.

“Did you have a good conversation, father?”

“How did the discussions with the village below the mountain go?”

“From today on, we have decided to place subordinates within Hua-Um. If we support and distribute the goods, we will be able to stabilize the businesses before ten days are up.”

“That’s quite long.”

Hwang Mun-Yak said.

“Even if you take a loss, settle the matter within three days. Now isn’t the time to pursue profit. We need to show our abilities here.”

“Yes.”

Hwang Jongi couldn’t hide his curiosity and asked again.

“The young disciple is…?”

“… Hm.”

Hwang Mun-Yak glanced back at the door he had left behind with a subtle expression.

‘That child is a monster!’

He couldn’t understand what that child was thinking. Even though he took on a child-like appearance, Hwang Mun-Yak began to doubt whether even that was real or fake.

“Mount Hua…”

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled.

“I’d rather call this place the Dragon’s Lair.”

“Uh?”

“Nothing. Let’s move.”

Hwang Mun-Yak walked out whistling.

Dragon Lair.

Where a dragon lives. There was no need to guess who the dragon was.

“Jongi.”

“Yes, father.”

“I’ve changed my mind. Maybe we should put everything on the line in Mount Hua.”

“…”

Hwang Mun-Yak was strangely excited.

Merchants don’t live on money but information. Money was just the result of utilizing the information in the proper manner.

He realized before anyone else that a dragon resided in Mount Hua. This information was so great that even Hwang Mun-Yak couldn’t estimate its value.

‘If I use this information well, the Eunha Merchant Guild might very well rise to the top of the world!’

It won’t be easy, but wasn’t this worth a try?

“There must be a lot of work to do. Let’s go now.”

Hwang Jongi silently followed his father, unable to understand the situation.

At the small hill behind White Plum Blossom Hall, a pair of eyes were watching them.

“Uh.”

Chung Myung watched the two adults as they set off from Mount Hua.

“That old man just doesn’t quit.”

Dealing with Hwang Mun-Yak was different from dealing with Hyun Jong or the other elders of Mount Hua. Of course, the elders of Mount Hua were diligent and wise, but they were Taoists who lived their lives away from the real world.

Hwang Mun-Yak lived in the secular world his entire life, so he was a lot more calculating.

“Whatever, it all worked out.”

He was able to solve the issue. Hwang Mun-Yak would continue to help Mount Hua in the future.

The weakest part of Mount Hua has been bolstered.

Wealth?

No.

Hwang Mun-Yak will make sure that Mount Hua’s name is heard around the world once again. Since Mount Hua is a martial arts sect, it was necessary for them to claim their identity in the right way.

Chung Myung looked up at the blue sky and grinned.

“Well, one problem is solved, Sahyung! How was that? Do you think I did well?”

The visage of Chung Myung’s Sahyung could be seen smiling down at him from among the clouds.

As if to say,

‘You idiot. It serves you right! Now, do you understand how hard it is?’

That was what that old man seemed to be saying.

“This is still the first step.”

There was a long way to go.

Mount Hua’s biggest obstacle has been overcome, there was no immediate concern remaining that the sect would vanish, and they had even gained a fair bit of wealth. With that problem solved, the next focus would be their martial arts.

If the Southern Edge Sect has lost their identity and forgotten their roots, then what about Mount Hua, which doesn’t even have roots? He had to restore Mount Hua’s martial arts back to their peak.

Chung Myung raised his body up.

“Ugh. When will the kids grow up!?”

Looking down at Mount Hua, the scene seemed to leave him feeling pleased. Even though it was only a little, Mount Hua had begun to change.

Chung Myung laid down again.

“Sahyung, Sahyung. I should have listened more to Sahyung’s constant nagging. Now I understand Sahyung’s worries.”

Chung Myung closed his eyes.

He could envision the old days when he hid away from his Sahyung as he chased after Chung Myung, ready to discipline him.

His appearance had changed, but so did the years.

Mount Hua is Mount Hua.

Right. It was still Mount Hua.

It was a day when the long winter had passed, and the first spring plum blossoms bloomed in Mount Hua.

Chapter 66: Don’t worry! I’ll make you win! (1)

The power of the Eunha Merchant Guild was genuinely shocking.

The people of the Eunha Guild showed that they could stabilize and overhaul the Hua-Um businesses within a short few days. A feat that Mount Hua was unable to do despite using all their disciples.

Thanks to that, a buddha-like smile wouldn’t leave Hyun Young’s face as he strolled around.

Most of the time, that smiling face would lead to…

“Have you eaten?”

“Yes, Elder.”

“Good, good.”

Hyun Young patted Chung Myung’s hair with a loving smile more benevolent than anyone else. Honey seemed to drip from his eyes.

“Eat a lot. Eat a lot and go somewhere else to earn more good things.”

“…. What?”

“No, I mean, raise Mount Hua’s reputation.”

“…”

The third-class disciples were all stunned in shock. Hyun Young, who was normally like a venomous serpent, laughed and stroked someone’s hair.

Chung Myung felt like a sacrificial lamb being fed before the date of its killing.

‘I feel like I’m being trained indirectly.’

Hyun Jong and now even Hyun Young were all smiles. They were so happy that youthful black hair had begun sprouting under the years of gray!

‘They must be quite old.’

Although they looked young for their age, considering that they were distinguished martial artists, they still seemed far too worn and withered. Those who had suffered so much during the prime of their lives now had a massive burden lifted off their shoulders.

Hua-Um settled down, and the elders regained their laughter.

Time began to flow like water.

The disciples of Mount Hua also embraced the flow of time, feeling the stability that came to Mount Hua for the first time in decades.

And while everyone was enjoying such a peaceful life, the third-class disciples were dying.

“Ahhhhh!”

“Oh, myyyyyyy God!”

The third-class disciples, carrying stones the size of a human body, moved their tired bodies as sweat poured like rain from them. And did push-ups with all kinds of screams.

“Ackkkkk!”

“M-My waist…”

However, there was one thing that was different. The swearing, which used to be directed at Chun Myung, has been replaced with cries of agony.

“I am dying!”

“You won’t die. You made it this far without dying. Straighten your back!”

“No, I am really going to die…!”

“You just have to do it two more times. Now, this is the last one. Once more! Okay! This is the last one!”

“Acck!”

With another push-up somehow completed, one of the disciples gasped and cried.

“A-Are we going to die like this?”

“You aren’t going to die. Nobody has died yet.”

“… Ack.”

At first, they just started their training because Chung Myung asked them to…well, more like forced them to. They started this training to avoid missing their meals or being beaten.

However, after repeating this for several months, they realized something.

‘This works.’

No, it’s not enough to say it works. To be precise, it changed everything. At first, they could only endure this training because of the pill Chung Myung gave them, but now they could feel the effects of their training all throughout their bodies.

First, their lower body was rigid and stable; their swords would no longer waver. Also, their stamina had gone up, and their entire body felt alive and energetic.

Even though they were previously unmotivated, they all had a martial artist’s spirit at the end of the day. Weren’t martial artists the sort of people who would become motivated once they recognized their own growth? They wouldn’t even hesitate to chew a living snake if it meant improving themselves.

Who would complain if all it took to improve their condition was simply lifting some stones?

The screaming voices increased as the training carried on, and over time the disciples, who used to carry bags of sand, were now lifting heavy stones.

The most notable of which was Jo Gul.

“Ahhhh!”

Jo Gul lifted a rock twice as large as the others. Seeing that, everyone bit their tongues.

“Is he doing this without using internal qi?”

“Seems like it.”

The way they spoke changed. It was only a few months, but they had all grown a bit taller, and their shoulders widened.

Jo Gul had changed so much that people would blink twice before recognizing him. He used to be on the smaller end of the third-class disciples but was now taller with a solid muscular frame.

Yoon Jong looked at the shocked disciples and smiled.

‘It’s a strange thing.’

When they first started training, Yoon Jong held a lot of worries within his chest.

Basically, Mount Hua’s sword is a swift one. Mount Hua’s sword style was to pressure the opponent through myriad changes based on the speed and tempo of the user.

That’s why Yoon Jong initially thought this training method, of simply increasing strength, would interfere with Mount Hua’s sword arts.

Somehow, their swords seemed twice as sharp since their training began to bear results.

Thanks to that, they achieved a new level of understanding of the sword arts they had been taught.

Viewing their swordsmanship in a different light, they were now learning the Falling Flower Sword.

It was a little tricky, but Yoon Jong was more than satisfied with it.

The Falling Flower Sword and Seven Star Step differed from what they learned before. The deeper they delved, the more mysterious the techniques seemed. They were martial arts which convinced them that they would become stronger once they mastered them.

So, they were all excited.

‘One more!’

“Uhhhhh!”

“Acckkkkkk!”

“Wow, your bodies are getting so big that your swords seem like chopsticks!”

“Hehe. Please! Bring me another sandbag!”

Yoon Jong couldn’t help but feel like the disciples of Mount Hua were becoming more like a den of bandits.

It was indelible to see the fragile disciples gradually turning into hulking muscular beasts.

“Sahyung. It’s time to eat!”

“Yes.”

In the past, everyone looked forward to the end of the training, but now they each set their own training plans and push themselves harder, often training overtime on their own.

It was Yoon Jong’s role to manage their plans so that the disciples wouldn’t be overtrained.

“Now, let’s head inside. We should wash up, eat, and get ready for morning practice too.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

“First, finish what you were doing.”

“Um, yes.”

Yoon Jong was looking around and glanced at Jo Gul.

“But where is Chung Myung?”

“He hasn’t been coming to training much lately, right?”

“Yes.”

Since the third-class disciples became more motivated to train by themselves, Chung Myung didn’t join in with them as often.

“It’s not like he is sleeping either; he wakes up before anyone else. So where is he even going?”

“How could we even know? Actually, isn’t Chung Myung the busiest person in Mount Hua right now?”

“… Yeah.”

It was true.

After a series of events, Mount Hua was revived. Visitors, who had never come to Mount Hua before, began to frequent the sect, and the businesses recovered from Hua-Um had been re-integrated, so the sect was steadily earning money.

Following that, Mount Hua itself was even being renovated, with maintenance laborers also coming and going constantly.

In the meantime, Chung Myung was moving back and forth between the Eunha Guild and Mount Hua.

“Sahyung.”

“Hm?”

“How strong do you think we are?”

“Well.”

Yoon Jong tilted his head.

Strength is relative. In order to know how strong they were now, they had to understand their past strength. But they didn’t really have a standard to measure by.

They only knew that they had gotten stronger, but it was difficult to judge how strong they became since they were all growing together.

“Wouldn’t I be at least twice as strong as my past self?”

“Only twice as strong?”

“I don’t know. It’s a bit abstract. What’s certain is that I’m confident that I could defeat at least three of my former self.”

“That isn’t enough.”

“Huh?”

“You know. The conference is coming up.”

At that, Yoon Jong frowned.

“Yes.”

“We need to get much stronger.”

“… right.”

Yoon Jong smiled bitterly.

“Let’s ask Chung Myung to give us some new training.”

Jo Gul resolutely nodded with a sullen expression.

“What do I do now?”

Chung Myung headed towards the mountain’s peak. To become strong, he had to train.

Chung Myung had achieved perfect synchronization between his body and sword in the past. With the memories of his former life, he was able to somewhat reach similar results with his current body, but he hadn’t been able to accomplish perfect body and sword unification like he had in the past.

There was no shortcut here. He must constantly swing his sword to resolve the dissonance felt between body, mind, and sword.

However, the problem was that Chung Myung couldn’t do this in front of others. If he were to train properly in front of others, their entire worldview would be flipped upside-down, and it would draw unnecessary attention to himself.

“Yep, I would rather die than suffer!”

So, he chose to practice in a location beyond the prying eyes of others.

These days, Chung Myung climbs the mountain at dawn, swings his sword on the peak, and then comes down.

‘How am I supposed to do this?’

There was no problem climbing the mountain; the problem was that it wasted a lot of time.

‘I don’t have enough time to spend like this.’

He had to keep an eye on the third-class disciples, manage the businesses down in Hua-Um together with the Eunha Guild, and gently appease the sect’s elders, who sometimes act strangely.

But more importantly, he was sure of one thing.

‘I don’t have the time to relax.’

If he was given 100 years, then Chung Myung would someday enter the realm of the Plum Blossom Sword Saint and naturally become stronger than his past self. As Chung Myung gets stronger, Mount Hua will naturally get stronger too.

But the world isn’t such an easy place.

There are bound to be people who will target Mount Hua; they will do anything to become stronger even without a specific goal in mind. Because a sect that flourishes will be seen as competition to be stifled and snuffed out.

Somewhere down the line, interference will appear, and people will come to pick a fight.

What if he takes his sweet time to train and ends up encountering an enemy he can’t defeat?

Besides, doesn’t Mount Hua already have a lot of enemies?

Chung Myung shook his head.

‘I need to get stronger as soon as possible. I can only handle so much.’

Chung Myung couldn’t afford to neglect his training. He had to climb as quickly as he could. Lying and waiting wouldn’t make him stronger; he would have to clench his teeth and work hard….

“Huh?”

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

Someone was here.

An uninvited guest appeared at the location Chung Myung had trained for the past month.

‘Who would be here at this time…?’

He cautiously approached the peak and peered at the figure that was wielding their sword in the moonlight.

The tip of the sword drew a smooth line through the night sky.

Soft but powerful. Flashy but elegant.

The sword which rose from the ground embroidered the sky and slowly descended like falling flower petals.

An elegant sword dance.

It was a dark dawn before the sun had even begun to rise. A woman was performing a sword dance under the moonlit night sky.

Her white robe, ebony hair, and silver sword shone in the moonlight.

“Like a moon under a moon….”

Chung Myung was engrossed in her dance.

The mysterious woman’s sword appeared to melt into the moonlight.

Fragile, yet unshakable. The sword seemed like a Plum Blossom. Right. The old sword of Mount Hua.

Chung Myung fell into a bizarre state of fascination.

The ancient sword arts of Mount Hua, which he thought he would never see in this era, were unfolding in front of him.

It wasn’t a question of what swordsmanship they chose to master; it was a question of what it meant to wield the sword at all.

Yes, like…

“Who’s there!?”

A sharp voice interrupted his concentration as the woman rushed toward him.

‘Huh?’

The woman quickly appeared in front of Chung Myung and sharply stabbed her sword.

“Uh?”

A fierce sword lightly touched Chung Myung’s neck.

Chung Myung sighed lightly, staring blankly at the sword on his neck.

‘I would be better off dead!’

How could he let a child catch him off guard? His reputation as the Plum Blossom Sword Saint is over.

“Who are you? I don’t remember seeing someone like you here before?”

‘That’s what I want to say!’

Who the hell is this woman?

Chapter 67: Don’t worry! I’ll make you win! (2)

The woman stared at Chung Myung with cold eyes.

In the meantime, Chung Myung managed to understand a couple things about the person before him.

First, this woman belonged to Mount Hua.

She had Mount Hua’s pattern engraved on the chest of her uniform to prove it. Only the disciples of Mount Hua could wear this.

Second.

‘Tch. Any man would be mesmerized by her.’

She is pretty.

In his previous life, Chung Myung had been all around the world. To remain un-swayed by mortal pleasures and always maintain a stable mind was what the Dao was all about. However, it was impossible for Chung Myung, who was famous for being a delinquent master of Mount Hua, to remain stuck in one city for very long.

It had been the same before he rose to fame. He was someone who would hit the people from the other sects constantly.

After that, he struggled very hard to raise the reputation of Mount Hua through a cooperative effort and beat up everyone who tried to cheat him or Mount Hua.

Right. Even in the old days, he proved that Mount Hua’s sword was the best in the world by defeating the masters from all the famous sects.

Of course, it wasn’t intentional.

‘They always started it.’

It wasn’t Chung Myung’s duty to develop Mount Hua’s reputation. That was the role left to the elders of the sect. However, the role somehow became linked to Chung Myung and his Sahyung. Thanks to that, Chung Myung was dragged around all over the place.

Even then, he had rarely witnessed a woman as beautiful as this mysterious disciple in front of him. Although, there was a feeling like a flower that hadn’t yet fully bloomed, making him wonder how it would look when it finally blooms someday.

Ebony hair, eyebrows, pure white skin, and perfectly clear, large eyes were impressive.

If Chung Myung had been a child with no experience, he might have been overwhelmed by this beauty by now.

The problem was that Chung Myung was an old man who suffered and saw too much of this world to be swayed by mere beauty.

“Who are you?”

“A human.”

“…”

The sword moved closer to his throat.

Ah! Shit! She doesn’t know how to joke!

“Mount Hua’s uniform.”

Her gaze fell on the chest of Chung Myung as he spoke.

“I don’t remember seeing your face. Who are you?”

“It’s my first time seeing you here too.”

The woman narrowed her eyes.

“A third-class disciple?”

“Yes.”

“Third-class disciples aren’t allowed to go outside the sect gate after sunset.”

“I’m exempt from that rule.”

“… What?”

“The sect leader gave me permission.”

Chung Myung’s brazen retort added a chill to the woman’s face.

“The sect leader?”

“Yes.”

“To a third-class disciple?”

“Yes.”

“A lie.”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders without answering.

“Go and confirm it yourself. Do you think that a disciple of Mount Hua would lie using the sect leader’s name?”

The woman’s eyes slightly shook. She seemed to believe there was some truth in those words.

“So put this sword away first. It might hurt someone.”

“…”

The woman lowered her sword. She couldn’t confirm if Chung Myung’s words were genuine or not, but she couldn’t continue to threaten him after he used the sect leader’s name.

But

“It’s wrong to watch other people’s training.”

“This is where I regularly trained until yesterday, but then someone I don’t know suddenly appeared. If I can’t investigate and determine who they are, then what do you think I should do?”

“You should have come out the moment you noticed someone.”

“A stranger I’ve never seen before suddenly appears near Mount Hua, and you want me to reveal myself without determining their intentions?”

The woman gently bit her lip. Her white face turned a slight shade of red; it seemed like she couldn’t argue back.

‘She isn’t very good with words.’

Her sword was sharp, but not her tongue, apparently. With a face like that, she likely didn’t get dragged into many fights.

‘Such a disgusting world.’

Good-looking people live such comfortable lives.

“What is your name?”

“Chung Myung.”

“You received a name from the sect?”

“No. My name is Chung Myung.”

“… a third-class disciple needs to have Chung attached. But it isn’t a sect name; it’s your own name?”

“Yes. Even if the sect gives me a name, I will keep it as Chung Myung.”

“Ah…”

Shit. This woman was dumb.

“I am Yu Yiseol.”

“Okay.”

Yu Yiseol stared at Chung Myung without saying a word.

“What is it?”

“I’m a second-class disciple, I am Baek, and I am your senior.”

Huh?

Chung Myung titled his head.

‘There were people of Baek?’

No, of course there were. Mount Hua names each generation of disciples as such: Chung, Myung, Hyung, Un, Baek.

It was natural for someone to have the title of Baek. Then, the next title after Baek would return to Chung, like a circle.

In other words, it was normal for there to be disciples who were named Baek after the seniors named Un.

‘I just didn’t see any of them, so I forgot about it.’

The naming is done right away based on their age since problems can arise if there are age differences among the disciples. Therefore, depending on circumstances, sometimes a name gets skipped too.

Since Mount Hua’s situation was so complex, he thought that a couple names were skipped, but there was someone with Baek?

“It is the first time I’m hearing about this.”

“You are the youngest of Mount Hua, right?”

“Yes, right.”

“Didn’t your sahyungs tell you?”

“Uh… well…”

There was no way that his sahyungs, whom he constantly bossed around, would ever volunteer such information to him.

‘It’s my fault.’

Chung Myung, who was easily convinced, nodded his head.

“There must have been some misunderstanding. What could be done?”

Someone with the Baek name appeared. From Chung Myung’s point of view, a few more pieces were added to Mount Hua’s board.

“Is that the end?”

“What?”

“What about your greeting?”

Chung Myung’s face contorted.

‘I don’t get it. What is this brat saying in front of this old man!?’

Being young is a sin! It really is a horrible sin!

“Yes. Nice to meet you.”

Chung Myung roughly greeted her with a voice holding no emotion.

‘Go away now.’

He had to train, too. He didn’t want to waste the day just because someone else occupied his training place! The sun was about to rise too!

“… what a weird kid.”

Who?

‘Me?’

Yu Yiseol started at Chung Myung and spoke with a chilly voice.

“I am going to check with the sect leader to see if what you are saying is the truth. If you lied, you had better be prepared for the consequences.”

Chung Myung replied.

“By all means, go.”

“…”

Yu Yiseol started at Chung Myung without a word for a long time and slightly shook her head.

“Really weird.”

“…”

Chung Myung wanted to spit those words back at her.

With her sword sheathed, the girl glanced once more at Chung Myung and began to descend. As her figure disappeared in the distance, Chung Myung sighed as he gazed at the rising sun.

“Ah, my fate.”

Being treated like a child was horrible.

“And my training time is also over!”

He could still train if he wanted to, but his mind was going through so many questions he was certain that it would only be a waste of time.

‘Whenever I train, it ends up like this. So much time is wasted just going up and down the mountain.’

Chung Myung bit his lip.

Maybe it was time to find another training ground?

“What’s with this atmosphere?”

Chung Myung tilted his head as he looked at the disciples having their meal.

It was the first time after Chung Myung thoroughly beat everyone that such a dark and gloomy air lingered about. He never thought he would have to see this, which was why he was confused.

“You’re here?”

Yoon Jong waved to him and called him over.

Chung Myung took his meal and went to the table where Yoon Jong and Jo Gul were seated and asked as soon as he sat down.

“What’s with this mood?”

“… our seniors are back.”

“The Baek bastards?”

“Oh? You know them?”

“…”

Chung Myung had lived his whole life in Mount Hua, you idiot!

“Anyway, so what? What’s wrong with them coming back?”

“First of all, don’t call the Baek disciples’ Baek.’ It’ll get complicated if they hear you say that. we might be scolded too.”

“Me? Or you?”

“… Ah, I need to think about that.”

Yoon Jong had a wry smile.

“The seniors have been in closed-door training away from Mount Hua. In the past, their training centers weren’t well maintained, so they couldn’t do any large-scale closed-door training here.”

“So, they went to another sect to train?’

“… not exactly. I don’t think they went just anywhere.”

“Anyway, so what? What about them is making these kids so gloomy? Do they have bad personalities? Do they bully and beat the other disciples?”

“Unlike someone else, the seniors don’t beat us.”

“I wonder who that ‘someone else’ you’re referring to is.”

“… Let’s move on.”

Yoon Jong was flustered when Chung Myung called him out, but Jo Gul quickly took the lead to change the subject.

“It’s because of the conference.”

“What? Isn’t a conference just for meetings?”

“No, this is the Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect’s conference.”

“What’s that?”

Jo Gul sighed.

“Once in a while, both the sects come together. Now, we have a competition every two years to compare each sect’s achievements against one another.”

“Ah, I feel like I heard about this somewhere…. When did this start?”

“Don’t know. I know that it’s been happening for a long time.”

Yoon Jong said,

“I heard that the first conference was organized to occur once every five years. Back then, the goal was to foster friendship between both sects. That changed little by little over time, and it’s now become an event where the second and third-class disciples get together and compete in the name of their sects.”

“Compete?”

“Don’t say it’s to compete….”

The answer came from elsewhere.

“It’s called being beaten one-sidedly.”

“Even now, where I got hit still hurts.”

“How can we survive again this time? After seeing what happened, even the seniors went to train for our sake. This is so crazy.”

Looking around, Chung Myung sighed.

“Ah. Since the elders fighting would cause trouble, they push the fighting onto the second and third-class disciples? And we have been beaten all this time?”

“Right. To avoid repeat suffering of our past humiliation, the seniors went into closed room training and only just got back. In other words, the time of the conference is drawing near.”

“Is that so?’

Chung Myung’s lips curled into a smile.

“Well, we’re going to compete with the Southern Edge sect, huh?”

The Southern Edge sect?

That one?

Whether he wanted to or not, each situation lately only made Chung Myung hate the Southern Edge Sect more.

In the past, there was a bit of pity, but after knowing that they copied Mount Hua’s sword technique, Chung Myung couldn’t even sleep in peace!

“Competition…”

In the past, such things never happened.

At that time, Mount Hua was the best, and the Southern Edge Sect wasn’t great, so such things didn’t happen.

But now that Mount Hua was weak, were those bastards trying to use these claims of friendship to promote their strength?

It wasn’t even funny to hear.

‘A friendly meeting with Mount Hua?’

Chung Myung’s eyes shone.

No matter how lame Mount Hua is now, it was Chung Myung’s child. Only he had the right to destroy it, not some other sect.

“And those second-class bastards!”

“Chung Myung, please. They are seniors; just call them seniors. Please.”

“Fine. Then those senior bastards!”

“…”

“Are they sure they can win?”

“… that’s a bit….”

Yoon Jong couldn’t readily answer. Closed-room training was meant to focus on the parts that a disciple lacked, but it was difficult to guarantee how strong they had gotten. Also, despite their achievements, winning still seemed like a distant dream.

“Then.”

Chung Myung gritted his teeth.

“Then we need to win!”

“What?”

“Sahyungs! Are you ready to do anything to win? Even take poison!? Or break your limbs and bodies!? If you can do something to beat those bastards and make a name for Mount Hua, you are all prepared to die, right!”

No, that doesn’t sound right…

Wasn’t Chung Myung pushing it too far?

“Don’t worry! I’ll make you win! I’ll turn you all into the best!”

Well, this man never really followed the path of Dao.

‘Just go to the Green Forest Mountain and turn into one of their bandits already. Why is he even here?’

Well, this is a mountain too.

Haha.

Hahahah!

Chapter 68: Don’t worry! I’ll make you win! (3)

“The second-class disciples are coming back.”

“Hmm.”

Hyung Jong sighed heavily.

It was good to hear that the children who left for closed room training were returning, but it was unpleasant to think about what would happen soon afterward.

“How far away are they?”

“Some seem to have already reached Hua-Um village, and some are yet to arrive.”

“I see.”

Hyun Jong raised his head and looked at Un Am.

“Sect leader.”

“Speak.”

“Why was the conference being held so soon? Wasn’t it originally scheduled to be held in half a year?”

“The Southern Edge Sect sent us a letter requesting it. This time they wanted to hold it earlier.”

“Can’t we ask them to postpone it?”

“That’ll be difficult.”

Un Am sighed.

“Mount Hua is in high spirits right now. Everything is going well, and we can live without worrying about food or our stability. Everyone is smiling brightly. Compared to a few months ago, it’s a remarkable change.”

“Yes.”

Hyun Jong agreed.

The most significant difference was that Mount Hua was full of energy now.

Those who once lived without knowing what tomorrow would bring finally saw the faintest glimmer of hope. The children’s smiling faces brought warmth to the hearts of the sect leader and other elders.

“But, we are still a martial arts sect.”

“Yes.”

“We did recently rediscover some of our lost martial arts from the books that were found, but it isn’t yet the time to see results.”

Hyun Jong nodded without saying anything. What Un Am was saying was correct.

Mount Hua could overwhelm the Southern Edge Sect in the past, but now Mount Hua wasn’t great. Only recently did they find their lost martial arts and gain new hope.

‘That too, just a small glimmer of hope.’

They had a long way to go.

Now, they were able to survive and solve their financial woes. However, to regain their former fame and glory, they would need to regain their former martial might.

But could martial arts be learned overnight?

Absolutely not.

“If the conference ends in the same result as before, I’m worried that the disciples will lose their newfound hope and turn into defeatists with no motivation.”

“Un Am.”

“… yes. Sect leader.”

“Do you think I don’t know that?”

Hyun Jong shook his head and continued.

“Would avoiding it or pushing it away make any difference? If we avoid it, will it quell the disciples’ doubts and produce positive results? This would have to happen one way or the other. If I ask to postpone it, then wouldn’t the disciples believe that their own sect leader lacks faith in them?”

“That…”

Un Am bowed his head.

“There is no shame in losing. If you lose despite your best efforts, it is unavoidable. They will simply have to work harder next time. But delaying the conference to avoid a loss is something we should never do.”

“I was short-sighted, sect leader.”

“I fully understand your concern. But… it would be difficult to postpone this conference for many reasons.”

Un Am sighed.

‘I ended up saying something useless and disturbed the sect leader’s mind.’

In such times, Un Am always wanted to be of help to the sect leader.

“Really, wouldn’t it be nice if the second-class disciples can achieve good results?”

“Right.”

Both Un Am and Hyun Jong knew that wasn’t an easy task.

The Southern Edge Sect was once under their feet, but now the gap between the two sects is unimaginably wide. The weight of being second-class disciples from the Southern Edge Sect compared to those of Mount Hua was as different as a large boulder compared to a feather.

The disciples did their best during closed-door training but winning would be difficult.

‘At least, it would be nice if they don’t fall too easily.’

Hyun Jong’s heavy heart sank.

“Un Am.”

“Yes.”

“These children are returning after a long period of hard work. Make sure to prepare some good food and alcohol.”

“But…”

“It’ll be okay for the children to have one day of rest after all their training. Shouldn’t those children also get to experience how Mount Hua’s circumstances have changed?”

“That is true. I will prepare them without fail.”

“Okay.”

“I will leave then.”

Un Am got up and was ready to leave.

As Un Am left the room, Hyun Jong quietly got up and opened the window. Looking out, he sighed.

‘The Southern Edge sect.’

It was like a thorn was stuck in his heart. He took a breath and hoped that thorn would be cut off before it pierced in further.

“It is difficult. Difficult.”

The Winter was long, and Mount Hua’s spring still seemed far away.

“We can win?”

Yoon Jong and Jo Gul gathered in Chung Myung’s room.

If someone else had said something like this, they would have ignored it, but Chung Myung’s words held a different weight to them.

Both Yoon Jong and Jo Gul knew. Chung Myung would never speak in vain. No matter how absurd it was, he accomplished the things he said he would.

“We?”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue, looked at the two, and answered.

“Not now.”

“Huh? Even if we are this strong?”

“Sahyungs have gotten stronger.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung raised his thumb and index with a minuscule gap between them and said,

“About this much?”

“…”

“…”

“Ah. Joking. It isn’t that much.”

“I knew it!”

“Of course.”

Chung Myung doubled the size of the small gap from before.

“About this much.”

“…”

“…”

Jo Gul’s face, which turned red, unable to hold it, yelled.

“Hey! We’ve been pushing ourselves to the verge of death to change so much. Does it make sense to say we only grew that much!? I can feel it in my body!”

“It’s only been a few months since you all started, and you were already on the verge of death?”

“No, but we are definitely stronger than before….”

“Even if an acorn grew three times in size, would it compare to a full-grown tree?”

“Tch.”

Chung Myung made an honest evaluation.

The growth of the third-class disciples was terrifying. Growing at this rate was something Chung Myung never expected. They were forced into this training and still managed to achieve great results. Imagine what kind of growth they would have if they trained whole-heartedly!

But…

‘They aren’t there yet.’

Compared to the third-class disciples of the past, these guys had a long way to go. But the Southern Edge Sect was the same as before.

Mount Hua may have lorded over the Southern Edge Sect in the past, but their skills had waned compared to their days of glory. On the other hand, the Southern Edge Sect hadn’t changed. Even if their abilities were similar to the past, it was still too much for Mount Hua. Even defeating a third-class disciple would prove problematic in the coming conference.

‘But maybe these two?’

As for Jo Gul, it seemed like he would have a chance to win. Yoon Jong needs to be a bit more refined.

Only two of the third-class disciples. Still, this was good.

“Then, how do we win?”

“It will be fine.”

Yoon Jong frowned.

“The conference will begin in just a few days. If we couldn’t win after months of training, what could we possibly do to catch up before they get here?”

“Which is why I asked.”

“… asked what?”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“If you are prepared to die.”

“…”

No, that…

“Did you hear what you said?”

“Does that matter? What’s important is if you are prepared.”

“No…”

The moment Jo Gul was about to say something, Yoon Jong interrupted him and said,

“I am resolute.”

“Sahyung!”

Jo Gul raised his voice, but Yoon Jong didn’t even look in his direction.

“I don’t know about the other Sahyungs, but I am ready. I am sure most of the others are willing as well.”

“Sahyung, do you know what you’re saying…?”

“I know.”

Yoon Jong seemed determined.

“It doesn’t matter. If I die right now, at least I’ll never have to see that situation again. I can still see those disgusting bastards standing over us and laughing in my dreams.”

“… that’s true.”

These two experienced the tragedy of the conference two years ago. It wasn’t simply a defeat but a disastrous experience.

How could they put their feelings into words?

“If I could return that humiliation, I would be willing to risk death. It isn’t something that I want to live with. I’d rather turn around and go down the mountain than go through that again.”

Jo Gul nodded his head.

Yoon Jong’s words roused Jo Gul’s memories of their previous humiliation. He also felt that he would do anything to avoid repeating that experience.

“Well, yes. Then I’ll stand with you, Sahyung.”

“I believe you.”

“Great.”

Chung Myung smiled.

However, Jo Gul felt uncomfortable.

“But Chung Myung.”

“Yes?”

“How will we do it?”

“Ah, it is nothing. I am just going to change the way that we practice.”

“How?”

Chung Myung replied.

“Practical test.”

“Huh?”

“What you’ve been learning, you should be able to apply it. I will show you how to use your body.”

“…”

Jo Gul’s eyes shook slightly.

“Uh… how to use it?”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders.

“You know that all martial arts are learned with the body. Get ready. We’ll start right away this evening.”

“…”

The two disciples felt a hunch that something was going wrong.

Late at night.

The third-class disciples gathered in the training hall.

“No, do we really have to gather at night like this?”

Jo Gul pouted and grumbled.

Now, there were no elders unaware that the third-class disciples trained at dawn.

At first, some expressed their concerns about the practice, and some were skeptical. Now that it had been ongoing for months, though, everyone just accepted it.

Un Geom even recognized the effect and informed the other elders to prevent interference.

They could practice freely in the morning, but now Chung Myung even wants to train at night?

“What the hell is he trying to do, Sahyung?”

“I don’t know.”

Yoon Jong shrugged.

Everyone complained, but not a single person walked away.

Everyone understood. Although Chung Myung’s training was radical, it was the most effective.

If Chung Myung said he would make them stronger, then he would do that.

“Is everyone here?”

At that moment, Chung Myung approached the hall.

The third-class disciples looked at him with a mixture of excitement and anxiousness.

They were sure that something crazy would come at them again, but they knew that it would lead to further growth if they could persevere.

The third-class disciples had all come to trust Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung. But this time, the training is….”

It was then.

Shhh!

Chung Myung unsheathed the sword at his waist.

“…”

A real sword?

… Uh?

It looked like a real sword.

Even if an ordinary person was holding a real sword, that was enough to make one feel frightened.

However, seeing a crazy younger disciple with a sword gave their pounding hearts a sinking feeling.

“Ah, training?”

Chung Mung asked calmly and slowly approached them with the real sword.

“It is nothing much. Just that…”

His lips twisted into a smile.

“All you have to do is die once. It isn’t much, right?”

… what!? That crazy bastard!

Chapter 69: Don’t worry! I’ll make you win! (4)

Chung Myung’s gaze slowly shifted from left to right.

The people receiving Chung Myung’s gaze couldn’t even make eye contact with him and quickly turned away their gaze.

‘Don’t look him in the eye.’

‘Shit! I got caught!’

The third-class disciples desperately turned away from Chung Myung. Just by looking at his gleaming eyes, it was obvious that they wouldn’t be able to back out if they got caught.

“You…”

An eerie voice that seemed to crawl its way out from the depths of hell emerged from Chung Myung.

“I don’t want to see you losing to those Southern Edge bastards!”

His eyes were gleaming with madness!

‘I might pee here!’

‘What am I supposed to do if he comes at me with that insane look on his face!?’

‘He looks even crazier today than normal. Is it because it’s a full moon tonight?’

Even if everyone else accepted defeat, Chung Myung would never admit it. The other may think that it’s reasonable to lose to the Southern Edge Sect, but Chung Myung would never be able to sleep if they suffered defeat at their hands. How could he live peacefully without punishing those idiots that stole the Plum Blossom Sword technique?

“Sahyungs, you need to win. I will make it so that you win.”

“…”

Everyone was desperate to escape from this demon.

But even when there were so many people, why wasn’t there at least one person who could speak up?

“But…”

It was Jo Gul.

With a blank face, he looked up.

“What do you mean by that? To die once?”

“Oh?”

Chung Myung smiled when he heard the question.

“Sahyung. Sahyung, come to me”

“… Me?”

Jo Gul raised his finger and pointed to his face.

“Yes.”

“…”

Jo Gul looked around and saw all the other sahyungs happily nodding their heads.

Jo Gul stood blankly with his mouth agape as the feeling of betrayal rushed over him.

‘You traitors!’

Was there no such thing as companionship? Before Chung Myung came to Mount Hua, there was strong loyalty among them. Just when did this place turn so harsh?

“Come here! Quick, quick!”

“Great Sahyung.”

Jo Gul looked back at Yoon Jong for the last time, who lightly coughed and spoke.

“Go already.”

“You son of a….”

He stopped himself from cursing.

In the end, Jo Gul bowed his head and trudged forward like a cow being led to a slaughterhouse. Yoon Jong’s eyes fell on Jo Gul.

Chung Myung looked at Jo Gul and said,

“You said you wanted to fight them, right?”

“… yes.”

“It might be a bit strange, but….”

Chung Myung chuckled. It was an eerie sight to see his chilling smile illuminated by the light of the moon as he held a real sword.

“Sahyung is already strong enough.”

“… Huh?”

“It’s not like your training until now was done in vain.”

Jo Gul frowned.

“So, we aren’t too far from the Southern Edge Sect?”

“That would be a no.”

Chung Myung quietly shook his head.

‘Wasn’t Lee Song-Baek known to be one of the strongest second-class disciples?’

Seeing how the other disciples treated Lee Song-Baek, he was definitely strong. If he had to assume what level of strength the third-class disciples would have based on that…

‘It’s similar to what I thought before.’

Jo Gul can compete fine, and Yoon Jong might need some luck on his side. But the other disciples had no chance.

Of course, the competition can change rapidly depending on their individual physical conditions and luck. But, unless heaven’s luck falls on them, the other third-class disciples of Mount Hua cannot overpower the Southern Edge sect.

“Although, it isn’t because sahyungs are weak.”

“… what is it then?”

“You’ve reforged your body, but you are doing the same things you did before.”

“Huh?”

Body?

Jo Gul looked down at his body.

‘My body did change.’

Thanks to Chung Myung’s weird training and the medicine he gave out, the third-class disciples became so strong that they could compete at a higher level.

Just seeing the muscular frames that everyone had developed brought a smile to his face.

Of course, it wasn’t just good to look at.

After adapting to the training, the disciples realized that their bodies had become stronger than in the past. Their swords moved faster in their hands, and their lower body was as strong and stable as a boulder.

“But it’s the same thing. Is there something wrong with what we are doing now?”

“That’s what I’m going to be telling you from now on.”

Chung Myung smiled and approached Jo Gul.

Kuk!

Chung Myung’s sword scratched against the ground with a grating sound. Jo Gul gulped and stared at his approaching figure.

“Sahyung.”

“Yes?”

“Why are you learning the sword?”

“… that…”

In the Mount Hua sect, there could only be one answer to that.

One controls the body and sword to eventually reach the greatest understanding of Dao. A sword is a tool along the path to achieving the highest peak of the Dao.

‘There is no way this guy wants that answer.’

If he decided to say nothing, he would be insulted.

So…

“Isn’t it to beat up our opponents?”

“Wow!”

Chung Myung clapped in applause.

“That’s a shocking answer from Sahyung. It’s really unsuitable for us Taoists, but that is the correct answer for a typical swordsman.”

… it would have been better to give the obvious answer.

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“You’re half right. It’s to win. So, what should we do to win with the sword?”

“Shouldn’t we grow stronger?”

Knowing that no matter what answer he gave would lead to him being verbally thrashed, Jo Gul answered right away.

“Right.”

However, Chung Myung agreed with Jo Gul’s statement.

“You just need to be stronger. If you are stronger than the opponent, you will win. But this means things might be a little different.”

“… I don’t understand.”

“It’s simple.”

Chung Myung smiled brightly and raised his sword.

“From now on, Sahyung and I are going to fight. Sahyung, use every possible means to overcome me. I will only swing my sword once.”

“… really?”

“Yes.”

Jo Gul frowned.

‘Isn’t he ignoring my strength too much?’

Jo Gul was already used to dealing with Chung Myung. He knew better than anyone that beating Chung Myung was impossible no matter how hard he tried.

But this fight was a different story.

No matter how wide the gap between them is, it would damage his pride to lose to Chung Myung when he would only do one slash.

‘I need to show him how strong I am!’

Jo Gul clenched his teeth and raised the wooden sword.

“Are you going to continue with the real sword?”

“Yes.”

“…it might hurt someone.”

“Maybe.”

Why wasn’t he giving a clear answer?

Was he going to cut Jo Gul or not?

Jo Gul shook his head to clear and calm his mind.

“Can I start?”

“Oh?”

As Jo Gul confidently raised his wooden sword, Chung Myung smiled.

“You seem to be quite confident, Sahyung.”

“Thanks to you, I trained myself to death!”

“Hmmm.”

Chung Myung smiled as he lifted his sword.

‘Confidence, that’s good.’

Those who wield the sword need to be confident. People who don’t believe in themselves have difficulty showing their abilities.

But…

‘It is a little too early.’

The third-class disciples are still just chicks. As Mount Hua has been developing at breakneck speed lately, it was natural for the disciples to be excited. But now wasn’t the time to be confident; it was the time to solidify their basics.

Chung Myung had to show them that.

Jo Gul stared at Chung Myung with a fierce glare.

“Be prepared!”

“Huh?”

“This isn’t personal in any way! Haaaa!”

Jo Gul charged and jumped towards Chung Myung. His eyes were burning furiously in contrast to his words that no personal feelings were involved.

It was flustering that he was showing so much killing intent.

‘Did I do something wrong?’

The others would be dumbfounded and pissed off if they had heard Chung Myung’s casual thoughts, but fortunately, no one could.

Chung Myung silently dodged Jo Gul’s swift sword strike.

“Haaa!”

However, Jo Gul’s sword began to make a dizzying change.

Falling Petals Sword.

Even though it had been less than a month since they started to learn this, Jo Gul was able to skillfully wield it. In harmony with the Seven Star Steps, the Falling Petal Sword was so sophisticated that those who didn’t know the sword stood in awe.

‘He sure is talented.’

Chung Myung looked at Jo Gul with renewed vigor.

Judging by the innate talent in the sword, Jo Gul was second to none in Mount Hua. Judging by his talent alone, he was even on par with Lee Song-Baek.

‘However.’

Chung Myung smiled.

Aren’t plants supposed to grow stronger when they are stepped on occasionally?

This wasn’t a selfish thought; it was purely for the sake of Jo Gul’s growth.

Chung Myung tightly grabbed his sword.

“Isn’t he doing quite a bit better than what we expected, Sahyung?”

“… better?”

“Yes. It seems like sahyung is pushing Chung Myung into a corner.”

Yoon Jong smiled bitterly.

“It sure does look like that.”

“What?”

“It looks like he’s pushing Chung Myung into a corner, but not once has he been able to land an attack on him.”

“Ah…”

While the others paid attention to Jo Gul’s sword, Yoon Jong paid attention to Chung Myung’s movement.

Footwork?

No, it wasn’t that.

Chung Myung wasn’t using any special footwork or techniques. If the opponent came close then, he would back away, and if the enemy attacked, he would slip past their moves. With one step at a time, he steadily dodged everything as if he could read Jo Gul’s movements before they were made.

Honestly, it was more like watching a well-choreographed sword dance than a match.

Jo Gul’s sword cut the air only inches away from Chung Myung as if it was intentionally avoiding him with each step.

‘Just how far ahead is he able to predict Jo Gul’s movements?’

The only time Yoon Jong fought with Chung Myung was when he got beaten or when they were training together.

It has already been several months since Chung Myung came to Mount Hua, but it was his first time seeing Chung Myung spar in a match.

Yoon Jong was able to understand.

The difference between Chung Myung and them.

“Eik!”

Jo Gul clenched his teeth and shook his sword.

He couldn’t hit the opponent.

It was like fighting with a ghost. Even though the technique was executed perfectly, Chung Myung avoided it with casual movements.

Just one inch.

If Jo Gul aimed for Chung Myung’s head, he would tilt his head to avoid it. If he aimed for the shoulder, he would glide out of the way. Just one inch closer, and it could have been a hit or a strike or anything.

It was an uncomfortable feeling.

Jo Gul’s loss that first night that Chung Myung arrived in Mount Hua was one thing. But wasn’t it supposed to be different now? Even when he was doing his best, couldn’t he at least hit him once?

Jo Gul clenched his teeth and poured strength into the sword he held.

“Arghhhhh!”

Jo Gul’s sword brilliantly shone bright blue.

“Sword qi?”

“He can use sword qi?”

The voices coming from behind didn’t reach Jo Gul’s ears.

Jo Gul achieved this feat while in a desperate situation as he was determined to pummel Chung Myung.

But,

“This is the end.”

At that moment, Chung Myung suddenly stepped forward. He raised his sword above Jo Gul’s head with just one step.

Jo Gul saw it.

The sight of Chung Myung raising his sword.

The world seemed to come to a stop. Yet, within this frozen world, Chung Myung’s sword continued unimpeded. In a natural motion, like a gentle breeze or free-flowing water, the sword swung down.

‘This?’

The sword that pointed exactly at him stopped.

And

Swosh!

With a force that made his ears go momentarily deaf, it fell on Jo Gul’s head.

‘I’m going to die….’

Jo Gul couldn’t take his eyes off the sword in spite of all that was happening. In an instant, the life he lived till then flashed in front of his eyes.

Before he even realized it, the sword touched his head.

Paaah!

Then, with a sound reminiscent of eardrums exploding, the sword stopped right at Jo Gul’s forehead.

Thud!

Jo Gul fell backward to the ground, staring at Chung Myung as if his soul had left his body.

Then, Chung Myung smiled and opened his mouth.

“How does it feel to die?”

“…”

What do you mean? How does it feel…!? It feels exhausting.

Uh… um, well….

Chapter 70: Don’t worry! I’ll make you win! (5)

Sweat was pouring like a waterfall.

“Phew…”

When Jo Gul realized he wasn’t dead, his entire body began to pour out sweat as if to prove he was still alive. He was so drenched that it was difficult to open his eyes.

Soon, his body started to tremble.

‘What if it had cut just an inch deeper!?’

No, not even an inch more. Jo Gul might have died with his head split open if the sword had been stopped just a hair later.

“This… this…. Uh.”

He wanted to curse, but the shock he felt prevented him from speaking. His body was trembling, and despite his best efforts, there was no soothing that fear.

Chung Myung smiled and looked at Jo Gul.

“How was it?”

“… What?”

“I asked, how was it?”

“…”

‘What the hell do you mean ‘How was it?’ you son of a bitch!?’

Normally, he might have found the words to answer, but Jo Gul didn’t have the mind or body to spare right now.

“Do you feel like you’ve died?”

“That…”

Jo Gul squeezed out the last bit of his strength.

“I feel like I lost, you crazy bastard….”

“Hehehe.”

Despite being cursed, Chung Myung didn’t seem to mind.

It was natural. Jo Gul had experienced what it’s like to go to hell and back; he was bound to be upset. If Jo Gul had a bit more strength, he might have rushed and attacked Chung Myung for putting him through that.

“Okay, Sahyung will rest now.”

Chung Myung turned around cheerfully and shifted his gaze to the other sahyungs who were looking at him.

Flinch.

Those who made eye contact quickly lowered their gazes.

“Sahyungs. Sahyungs. Think very carefully.”

“…”

“Can you really avoid this?”

‘That devil!’

‘How did such a person even enter Mount Hua!’

‘Is a Taoist supposed to be like this?’

Looking at Chung Myung, they were sure that he was a perfect example of what a Taoist shouldn’t be like.

“Come on. Don’t waste time. If you want to get strong, you need to step forward. Great Sahyung?”

“…”

Yoon Jong glanced at Chung Myung with shaky eyes before turning his head and averting his gaze.

“J-Jonghak, how about you go next?”

“Uh? Sahyung. I think he called for you.”

“So, you’re not going out?”

When Yoon Jong turned and asked, Jonghak bowed his head.

‘Everyone here has turned into something strange because of him!’

Still, Yoon Jong had the dignity of a Sahyung, but after Chung Myung came, things changed. It wasn’t like Yoon Jong was the only one who changed, though.

“Aren’t you going to come?”

“…”

Chung Myung sighed, seeing the sahyungs push one another and try to avoid him.

“Such a shame. Sahyungs, who should be helping each other, are fighting with one another.”

‘Who do you think is the reason for this, you bastard!’

‘Did you sell your conscience somewhere?’

‘If only you weren’t here, this place would be at peace!’

Desperate cries echoed within the disciples’ minds but certainly didn’t come out of their mouths.

Seeing them like that, Chung Myung nodded.

“There is only one way to unite the quarreling sahyungs. Brotherhood blooms when you share in each others’ suffering. Only by overcoming tribulations together will love unite you; don’t worry, I’ll be sure to treat you all fairly!”

What?

Chung Myung raised his sword.

“If you won’t come to me, then I will come to you. Here I come!”

Don’t! Don’t come, you crazy son of a bitch!

Whether they wanted it or not, Chung Myung, who seemed to have gone mad, rushed at them. Frightened, the disciples tried to run, but Chung Myung pursued everyone like a wolf after sheep.

“You! Get over here.”

“Who would go to you! You insane freak!”

Yoon Jong, who was screaming, closed his eyes as the sword fell towards his head.

“Eu…”

“Ah…”

The third-class disciples, scattered around the training hall, all trembled with frightened eyes.

“No. Mother…”

“Father, I promise to live a good life….”

“The beef jerky… I hid it under the bed….”

“Are you seriously thinking about food right now?”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue at the Sahyungs spread out all over the place.

“Alright, you all did well.”

Normally, they would have been furious; but the current disciples didn’t even have the strength to yell or shout.

Having experienced a real sword fall on their head at frightening speed, they felt as if they had been pushed through the gates of the underworld. They didn’t want to do anything that would instigate Chung Myung to do it again.

Yoon Jong wiped the sweat running from his brows with trembling hands.

‘That fucking bastard….’

Yoon Jong had been beaten by Chung Myung countless times, but this was different. It felt like they had stepped one foot into the underworld this time.

Chung Myung looked at everyone and spoke.

“How was that?”

“… What?”

Fortunately, Jo Gul, who had rested, was able to speak.

“Why didn’t you stop my attack?”

“.. Huh?”

“It was an obvious strike. So, why didn’t you try to stop it?”

After doing all this, was he really asking that?

Jo Gul exclaimed, nearly in tears.

“It was fast! It was so fast that I couldn’t even think about stopping it! Even a three-year-old child would understand that it couldn’t be stopped!”

“Is that so?”

Chung Myung smiled.

“You understand well.”

“You…”

Jo Gul gritted his teeth.

“Then, why didn’t sahyungs stop it?”

“Huh?”

Jo Gul looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes. Just as he was about to say something to refute, Chung Myung slashed the sword down.

Paaah!

Dust scattered, and the sound of air being torn apart echoed around.

“Simple, isn’t it?”

“…”

It wasn’t just Jo Gul.

The other Sahyungs also stood up and watched Chun Myung’s sword.

“… this was the same as the strike you did to us?”

“Yes.”

“Wasn’t it several times faster, though? Was it this gentle?”

“It’s the same. A sword that’s falling on your head would naturally seem different than a sword strike you watch from a distance.

“…”

Jo Gul was an intelligent guy in his own way. He quickly understood what Chung Myung was hinting at.

“You mean I can do it too?”

“With training.”

Chung Myung raised his sword.

“Look.”

And he slashed.

Paaah!

Jo Gul firmly engraved that scene into his memory. It was undoubtedly not blinding speed or advanced skills. It was just a plain, simple slash straight to the ground.

Hold the sword and slash.

A simple movement performed so flawlessly that it seemed to paint a portrait in time.

Jo Gul opened his mouth unwittingly.

“This is a drop slash.”

“…”

Jo Gul tried to speak but could not.

“You’ve built your body; now you need to utilize it to handle the sword. First, the lower body.”

Chung Myung stomped for a firm footing.

“Firmly fix your lower body, raise the strength up till the waist, transfer power to the fingers, unite it with internal strength, and strike out all at once.”

Paaah!

Chung Myung smiled.

“Easy, right?”

“…”

After hearing the explanation, Yoon Jong spoke with a heavy voice.

“I understand what you are saying. You think that we should wield a simple sword based on a disciplined body rather than pursue flashy swordsmanship?”

“This is a One Hit Fatal Kill.”

Chung Myung supplemented Yoon Jong’s explanation.

“There is no thought of swinging the sword a second time. If you can’t deliver a killing blow in one strike, then be prepared to die.”

Yoon Jong sighed.

‘This is why he showed us this.’

It was said that one action could speak a thousand words.

There was a massive difference between hearing about a sword technique and directly facing it. It wouldn’t have been easy for people who never experienced the fear of that sword falling on their heads to understand what it meant to be on the verge of death.

“But Chung Myung.”

Yoon Jong exhaled and called him.

“I get what you mean, but we are disciples of Mount Hua. Would it be meaningful to win in such a way?”

“So what if we are disciples of Mount Hua?”

“If we’re disciples of Mount Hua, shouldn’t we defeat our opponents with Mount Hua’s sword arts?”

Chung Myung looked at Yoon Jong as if his words were absurd.

“What did I do just now?”

“A down slash.”

“What’s the first form of the Six Equilibrium Sword?”

“.. a downward slash.”

“Right. Isn’t the Six Equilibrium Sword one of Mount Hua’s techniques?”

When Chung Myung asked that, Yoon Jong coughed.

“I didn’t think it through.”

“Tsk, tsk, tsk.’

Chung Myung clicked his tongue and looked at everyone.

“The Sixfold technique used in the Six Equilibrium Sword is the foundation of all of Mount Hua’s techniques. Everything starts and ends with the Sixfold movement.”

Chung Myung looked at all those who were trying to avoid his gaze.

“You are chasing after more advanced techniques like the Falling Petal Swords and the Seven Star steps without fully mastering the basics!”

“Ugh.”

“Oh, the night air is quite refreshing.”

“The moon is bright too.”

The third-class disciples were flushed red in embarrassment and spoke strangely to avoid the topic.

“You need to clearly understand this.”

Chung Myung’s voice sank low. His usually playful tone had turned serious; noticing this, his sahyungs focused intensely on what he had to say.

“If you can’t master the Six Equilibrium Sword properly, there is no point learning any other swordsmanship. All the sword arts of Mount Hua are based on this. A building with an unstable foundation will collapse with even the slightest wind.”

Everyone nodded.

If they hadn’t seen it with their eyes, they wouldn’t have believed it. But haven’t they already experienced it now?

‘The sword seemed so strong that I didn’t think I could stop it.’

‘A simple strike seemed like the best technique in the world.’

‘What’s important isn’t the sword art being used, but the person who handles the sword.’

Jo Gul got up and looked at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes.”

“I will just ask one thing.”

“Sure.”

Jo Gul cleared his thoughts and opened his mouth.

“I understand that the Six Equilibrium Sword is important. But we aren’t you. It may sound silly, but we need the strength to break the nose of those Southern Edge bastards right now. More than the strength of a distant future.”

“Hmm.”

“To be honest, you are the only one who can use that technique so skillfully. That’s why I need to ask.”

Jo Gul’s eyes shone.

“If we do what you tell us, we won’t lose to the Southern Edge sect, right?”

Instead of answering, Chung Myung sighed.

Seeing his reaction, Jo Gul bit his lip.

‘I must seem pathetic to him.’

A person who learns martial arts should not dwell on the results of one fight for long. But losing to that sect was an experience that he never wanted to go through again. That shame and humiliation…

“What did Sahyung even take away from what I said?”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung blinked his eyes.

“You think you would lose to the Southern Edge Sect? Someone like that deserves to die! A disciple of Mount Hua losing to a scoundrel from the Southern Edge sect? I’ll smash that disciple’s head myself!”

Jo Gul trembled as he looked into the burning eyes of Chung Myung.

‘I can understand us behaving like that, but what kind of grudge does he have towards the Southern Edge sect?’

A guy who just entered Mount Hua.

“Didn’t I tell you? I will make you all win!”

Chung Myung raised his sword and pointed to the Sahyung.

“There is no such thing as a glorious defeat!”

“…”

“Winning is the only answer in a fight. Whether you need to hit their crotch or throw dust in their eyes! Once you win, it’s all over! Cowardice? Don’t even talk about it! Do you think a man who’s been decapitated on the battlefield can complain about cowardice? There is no such thing as companionship in a battle! Win by any means necessary!”

Chung Myung nonchalantly made a declaration that would shock the elders if they’d heard it.

Seeing such a scene, Jo Gul smiled.

‘Right. This guy is normally like this.’

It felt reassuring for some reason.

“So, what do we do now? How can we use a sword like you?”

“It’s simple.”

Chung Myung smiled and spoke.

“First, we will start by swinging the sword ten thousand times.”

“… that must be a joke, right?”

“No way.”

“Of course, I’m just joking.”

“Sigh.”

“It was a joke….”

Chung Myung had an ominously bright smile.

“Do you want to be defeated in the future? Or do you want me to kill you now?”

“…”

It seemed like there was a bigger villain inside Mount Hua than the Southern Edge Sect.

Chapter 71: Something seems to have changed in Mount Hua (1)

Swish!

Un Geom retrieved his sword.

Drops of sweat ran down his forehead.

‘A good sword art.’

There was definitely something different about the Seven Sages Sword that they had learned from Mount Hua and what he was following now. It cannot be called the best, but the sword was still amazing.

It would take a heavy investment of time to truly understand and master this sword art. However, even with his shallow achievements, Un Geom already understood that this Seven Sages Sword was a level higher than what they were currently taught.

‘If this sword can be taught properly, Mount Hua will become stronger.’

The present disciples will become stronger, and the future generations will be even more powerful.

“Ahem.”

Just thinking about it made Un Geom smile.

“Hmm.”

Un Geom quickly rubbed his smile away.

“This is quite difficult.”

He was still a teacher, which meant he had to be strict with his disciples. Lately, though, he can’t stop smiling.

Until now, the experiences the third-class disciples have shared could not simply be summed up as mere hardships. Ever since they entered Mount Hua until now, there has been nothing but struggle and suffering.

Still, they devoted their youth to Mount Hua. With the collapsing sect on their shoulders, they constantly overcame the hardships and persevered through suffering. After such a long period of darkness, they were only now seeing the light.

‘We aren’t fully out of trouble yet.’

Although Un Geom could finally see the light at the end of the long tunnel, he was all too aware that there was still a long way to go.

Even so, he couldn’t erase the smile on his face. It was all thanks to the third-class disciples, who started to grow strangely quick in recent times.

The elders and the sect leader seemed to find the greatest joy in the fact that Mount Hua was financially stable and had found its lost martial arts, but it was different for Un Geom.

As the head of the White Plum Blossom Boarding House, the growth of his disciples was what brought him the most satisfaction.

‘They’re different from us.’

The second-class disciples tried their best, but unfortunately, Mount Hua didn’t have an appropriate environment to train or improve. To be honest, they didn’t have much passion for martial arts either.

But the third-class disciples are more passionately devoted to their personal training than any of Mount Hua’s previous disciples.

“Hmm.”

Un Geom smiled, put the sword on his waist, and left the training hall with light steps. It was time to train the children.

His imagination was overflowing with pleasant thoughts.

Mount Hua’s desperate situation had been resolved. With their recovered martial arts and the third-class disciples showing a vigorous desire to grow their martial talents, it seemed that the hour of Mount Hua’s resurrection was growing near.

And the main characters of that revival will be the third-class disciples.

“I’ll have to work harder for that to happen!”

How could he call himself their mentor if he couldn’t even lead his students, who were working hard by themselves?

Un Geom turned and entered the disciples’ training hall before shouting with a flushed face.

“Okay, let’s do well today to—what is this!? Fuck!”

Un Geom stepped back in shock.

What was in front of his eyes could only be described as pure chaos.

“Ahhhh. Arm… my arm!”

“B-back… my back is down… broken!”

“S-save me… save me….”

Unknowingly, Un Geom rubbed his eyes.

What had happened in this training hall? Suddenly, Un Geom felt that his dreams of teaching Mount Hua’s future leaders had been set ablaze and were crashing down around him.

All the third-class disciples were lying on the floor, groaning while holding their wooden swords. Their shoulders trembling and mouths drooling.

“What the hell happened….”

At that moment, a sound erupted from somewhere nearby.

“Uhhhh!”

Un Geom turned his head and saw Jo Gul’s figure using his wooden sword with his shirt off.

“J—Jo Gul…”

“Uhhhh! Uhhhh! Hmmmmm!”

Sweat was pouring down his body like rain. Each time the sword was swung, sweat scattered, and a hot breath could be seen exhaling from his mouth.

Blazing red eyes, full of focus, and trembling shoulders told the story of a boy pushing himself past his limits. Even Un Geom felt his entire body tremble at the sight.

“Okay, one more.”

At those words, Un Geom’s eyes turned.

‘What is with him?’

Next to Jo Gul, Chung Myung was slowly holding his sword. Unlike Jo Gul, who was sweating profusely, Chung Myung seemed rather refreshing.

His hair was neat, not even a single strand out of place. He wielded his sword smoothly in a relaxed fashion, unlike the sahyungs scattered around on the verge of death.

“Just swinging your sword isn’t enough! If you are going to swing once, imagine squeezing out all your strength. From the tip of your toes to your head, and through your sword! Once more!

What was this situation?

Wasn’t Chung Myung the youngest of the third-class disciples? So why is he teaching Jo Gul?

However, everything Chung Myung said was correct.

“Okay, one more….”

“Kuaaak!”

In the end, Jo Gul, who couldn’t stand it, fell to the floor. Seeing that, Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

“Tch tch. You people are seriously weak.”

Chung Myung sighed deeply.

“You’re just overworking your body. You aren’t a cow! Use that head of yours! Use your brain! Think about how to swing the sword so that you can utilize all the strength in your body and then swing it!”

What?

Un Geom’s eyes trembled.

The other elders might be unaware, but Un Geom knew that Chung Myung could control the third-class disciples to some extent. It may be difficult to understand, but weren’t there always talented people whose skills transcended their age?

However, what Chung Myung was discussing now wasn’t something that could be waved off as simple talent or ability.

‘Does this mean that he has a higher understanding of the martial arts?’

The more he observed this kid, the more amazed he felt.

Un Geom, suddenly awoken from his thoughts, shook his head.

This wasn’t the time for such things.

“What is this!?”

Chung Myung shook his head when Un Geom asked.

“Oh my! Teacher!”

Chung Myung quickly ran up to Un Geom.

“How was last night?”

Seeing him act like a child, the third-class disciples gritted their teeth.

‘That sly son of a bitch!’

‘If he was in the Imperial palace, there would have been books written positively about him!’

‘He’s a demon with no spine, constantly changing sides!’

Why wouldn’t they be upset? Chung Myung was the youngest and should have shown respect to them as his sahyungs, but he only showed respect to Un Geom and the other elders.

In particular, Jo Gul and Yoon Jong, who were the biggest victims, dejectedly looked at Chung Myung with narrowed eyes.

“What happened here?”

“We were training.”

“Training? This is training?”

No, it certainly was training. Un Geom witnessed Jo Gul swinging the sword with his own two eyes. But the result was…

“Kuaak…”

“T-teacher…”

“Too… too difficult. I might die….”

The third-class disciples looked at Un Geom like puppies who found their master. Without realizing it, Un Geom ended up raising his voice upon seeing their expressions.

“Training is a part of the process to develop the body and mind. Don’t you know that too much training is poisonous? And you—”

“I know, teacher.”

“Uh?”

Un Geom’s eyes narrowed as Chung Myung’s words interrupted his lecture. Did this mean that he had a proper response to give in this situation?

“But this training wasn’t started by me. The Sahyungs, who didn’t want experience disgrace in the Mount Hua and Southern Edge Sect conference, have—”

“C-conference?”

Right. The conference was approaching soon. That was true…

“Sahyungs were upset with the humiliation they faced last time….”

Upset?

Un Geom slowly turned his head and looked at the third-class disciples.

The children were desperately waving their hands behind Chung Myung. Seeing their reaction, Un Geom said.

“Looking at the children, that doesn’t seem to be the case.”

“What? Is that possible? Sasuk! How could one be proud to declare themselves a disciple of Mount Hua if they’ve suffered defeat at the hands of those Southern Edge bastards!?

Huh?

He was right.

“We can lose once. But losing twice is unforgivable! A disciple of the Great Mount Hua should never accept such results.”

“… right.”

Confusion beset Un Geom as he began to nod his head.

There were only two things he valued most in the world. One was the pride of Mount Hua, and the other was to raise the disciples correctly.

Now, it seemed that both of his values had turned their blades towards one another and conflicted.

Chung Myung, who read the confusion in Un Geom’s eyes, approached and whispered.

“Sasuk, think about it. The best way to raise Mount Hua’s honor is to strengthen the Sahyungs and break apart those Southern Edge Sect bastards, right?”

“That…”

“The elders will also appreciate and praise Sasuk’s hard work.”

‘This sly bastard!’

Un Geom wasn’t oblivious; he could tell that Chung Myung was manipulating him, but such sweetly honeyed words were too enticing for Un Geom to ignore. He wasn’t interested in receiving praise for his efforts, but to beat down the Southern Edge Sect was….

“Do you think it’s possible?”

Unknowingly, Un Geom had asked for Chung Myung’s opinion.

Hearing that, Chung Myung smiled.

“I am Chung Myung.”

“…”

Un Geom looked at Chung Myung and coughed.

Looking back, it was none other than Chung Myung who had changed these children. Weren’t these children training because of Chung Myung?

Perhaps this process was more necessary than learning a new sword art. No matter how lucky he was, it was impossible to teach that new sword technique in a short period and overcome the Southern Edge Sect.

‘Just once more….’

Un Geom looked at everyone and opened his mouth to speak.

“Disciples! Listen to me!”

“Yes, Sasuk!”

The third-class disciples set their full attention on Un Geom, desperately pleading with their tired eyes. Their last hope…

“There’s a limit to how proud I can be that you are showing such enthusiasm in your training. After all, it is my responsibility to be the one who guides you all. However, it wouldn’t be right for me to disturb your ambitions when you’re voluntarily training so vigorously.”

… what is this?

Oh? Is that the sound of hope crashing into pieces?

“Until the conference, I will leave the training to you all. In the meantime, you don’t have to come to the training hall and are free to train anywhere. However, you must be careful not to hurt yourselves.”

Master?

… this isn’t right! Sasuk?

“Ahem. You may all continue now.”

Un Geom turned his body away.

Some third-class disciples unwittingly stretched out their hands to grab hold of their fading hope. But upon seeing the look in Chung Myung’s eyes, they quickly pulled back.

Eventually, Un Geom walked away, and Chung Myung turned his body and twisted his head toward the abandoned disciples.

“Who was the one that told Sasuk that you were having a hard time?”

“….”

“Say it quickly.”

“…”

The eyes of the third-class disciples were dyed with despair as they watched Chung Myung pull out the wooden sword on his waist.

Chapter 72: Something seems to have changed in Mount Hua (2)

“Tsk. This is too much work.”

Chung Myung climbed the mountain with an expression that clearly showed his annoyance.

“It’s so slow.”

Chung Myung sighed.

He had never raised a disciple in his previous life.

Even his sahyung, who always desperately searched for reasons to nag Chung Myung, never once dared to ask that he take in a disciple.

His sahyung held discussions with the other elders who were worried about whether Chung Myung’s unparalleled swordsmanship would be passed onto future generations.

What he told them was,

– I am worried about that as well. However, I am still a human. I feel sympathy and love just as anyone else does. I cannot ever request a disciple to be sent under him. Chung Myung is the sort of man that would beat a dog for not walking upright. Of what sin did the children partake to deserve such punishment? If we are Taoists who cultivate the Dao, we cannot commit such acts of cruelty.

Since then, no one ever asked Chung Myung to accept disciples.

‘Now that I think about it, it feels pretty bad. Those bastards just spoke about me however they wanted.’

What’s so bad about his methods? They are growing up so well!

Of course, it took a lot of work.

Chung Myung raising the third-class disciples was no different from an adult teaching an infant to walk.

If it was anyone else, they would coddle the child and hold them at every step. However, the toddler can only truly stand independently by being thrown off their feet and figuring it out for themselves.

“Ugh. I really would rather die than to suffer like this.”

As a result, it took more time than expected, and as the training dragged on, there wasn’t enough time left for Chung Myung’s own practice. He was almost at the point where he was ready to sacrifice his sleep in order to train.

Chung Myung took a deep breath and looked up at the sky.

“Sahyung. Do I have to go this far? It’s easier for me to just try and grow myself instead of waiting for them to catch up.”

– Well, do that then.

“Eh, seriously!”

Chung Myung sighed.

He was well aware that it would be impossible to recover Mount Hua’s former glory on his own.

Sure, Chung Myung could make Mount Hua famous alone, but he couldn’t live forever, right? Then, wouldn’t Mount Hua disappear once he dies?

What Chung Myung had to create was the spirit of Mount Hua, which would never disappear.

A flower with beautiful petals is nice, but it fades and rots quickly. The spirit of Mount Hua must be like the roots of a great tree, it may not be seen, but it keeps the being alive.

“I know…”

How can life be so easy?

Chung Myung felt dizzy at the task ahead of him.

He continued organizing his thoughts as he climbed the mountain. Upon arriving at his training ground, he quickly scanned the surroundings.

‘She won’t come here again, right?’

He was an hour early. It was time for everyone to be in bed. No matter how driven a disciple was, they wouldn’t come to train at this hour.

Of course, he would have to meet her later, but that would be when she officially comes back to Mount Hua.

“Uh?”

Chung Myung, who gazed around, raised the wooden sword wrapped around his waist.

His eyes, which looked at the sword, were serious as he stood tall. The playful eyes he had when teaching the children faded away; replacing them were the eyes of a swordsman who had been through countless battlefields with his sword.

‘Return to the old me?’

No, that won’t be enough.

Chung Myung broke his entire foundation. He denied the history he had built up in his previous life and started a new foundation.

To go further.

But that alone won’t be enough. Chung Myung changed the foundation of his strength, but he couldn’t change his swordsmanship. If the sword wasn’t changed, then he would have to make his sword stronger.

A little bit stronger, faster. No, it wasn’t enough.

‘Did I defeat the Heavenly Demon?’

No.

If the Heavenly Demon hadn’t exhausted his energy after the joint efforts of those who climbed the mountain, Chung Myung would have never been able to take him down.

Chung Myung had claimed that he was the greatest swordsman in the world, but he was just a loser that was unable to defeat the Heavenly Demon in frontal conflict.

‘What if I could have defeated the Heavenly Demon alone?’

If that was the case, no one else would have died.

Both the Sahyungs and Sajaes would have returned to Mount Hua safely. They would have lived their lives peacefully, and his Sahyung would be back to nagging Chung Myung while he secretly drank alcohol.

Then Mount Hua wouldn’t have collapsed, and no one would have died on that mountain with the Heavenly Demon.

Regret?

It’s not exactly like that.

Chung Myung wasn’t the kind to hold onto the past and weep. The problem was what lies ahead.

‘Where is the guarantee that someone like the Heavenly Demon wouldn’t appear again?’

Perhaps a more frightening character than the Heavenly Demon might aim for them.

To protect Mount Hua from all possible crises, he had to become strong. Greater than anyone in the world, more than Chung Myung of the past and the Heavenly Demon!

To do that…

Chung Myung’s sword, which was nearly perfect in the past, couldn’t hurt the Heavenly Demon.

‘Why?’

Because he hadn’t tried to sharpen the sword further?

No.

“No matter how sharp a tiger’s claw is, it cannot catch a flying bird.”

There is a limit that cannot be crossed.

The Heavenly Demon’s martial arts shattered everything Chung Myung believed was right. As if ridiculing Chung Myung, who thought that the end could be reached by following the path paved by the ancestors.

Just like a person with his feet on the ground looking at a bird flying freely in the sky, he had no choice but to stare at that unachievable dream.

If Chung Myung wanted to reach the Heavenly Demon’s level, then he would have to jump beyond his past self first.

But how?

Chung Myung’s eyes narrowed.

‘I’ll have to throw it away.’

But to discard everything?

Only when the vessel is empty can it be refilled with something new. However, Chung Myung already emptied everything when he was reborn anew. Now, he would have to refill it.

So, what should he fill it with?

Would it be Mount Hua’s teachings or Chung Myung’s own path? If not…?

“It doesn’t matter.”

Chung Myung’s sword begins to move slowly.

Protect the techniques and teaching of Mount Hua? Abandon Mount Hua’s guidance? Or create a new path as Chung Myung?

– It is all an obsession.

Right. Sahyung.

If filling it was natural, so was throwing things away. There was no need to decide right away what to fill and what to discard.

Look.

Isn’t the sword still moving as it did in the past?

Don’t set limits.

The moment you decide what to accept and what to abandon, the sword becomes bound by limits that have been created. Leave it alone. Let the sword travel as it pleases and as Chung Myung wills it.

The sword of Chung Myung drew soft arcs, cutting through the dark.

At the same time, it seemed like Plum Blossoms began to bloom in the sky.

Although it was the Plum Blossom of Mount Hua, it was different from what Chung Myung knew.

It was a little more lively and a bit gentler.

It stretched out and scattered and then descended.

From east to west and back to east.

The plum blossoms that began at the tip of Chung Myung’s sword bloomed. Soon after, white flowers encroached upon the night sky, bringing an early spring to the mountain peak where he was training.

Soft, fast, glamorous, and beautiful.

However, plum blossoms are bound to wither.

Atop the peak, the plum blossoms disappeared as if they had been a mere fantasy. Chung Myung stood alone amid the fading illusion with his sword stretched out and closed his eyes.

‘I feel like I learned something.’

He didn’t completely understand, but it felt like he took a solid step forward.

Although it was Mount Hua’s sword, it was a sword unique to Chung Myung that surpassed any of Mount Hua’s other techniques.

A sword that can go beyond his limits and the limits of Mount Hua too.

“Phew.”

Chung Myung let out a low sigh.

‘It won’t be easy.’

It wasn’t about inventing a new sword art. It was about opening a new frontier and creating new opportunities. Still, it was a long way off. Just as Chung Myung’s history grows with him, this sword will grow too.

Now it was just the bud of a plum blossom.

But someday…

“You…”

“Eik!”

Suddenly, a voice came from Chung Myung’s side, and he rushed away.

“Wow, Fuuuuuuuck! What!”

Before he could realize it, someone else had appeared. Chung Myung, frightened, repeatedly blinked as he scanned to see who it was.

‘… is she that girl from last time?’

Yu… Yu… Yu something.

Ah right! Yu Yiseol! That was her name.

Yu Yiseol was looking at Chung Myung with a blank gaze.

‘No, but how did she get so close to me? I didn’t even sense her.’

No matter how great her technique was, Chung Myung should be better than her! Even if he was deep in concentration, he could clearly feel the presence of those around him.

Last time too, this woman had done the same thing and suddenly popped up out of nowhere! What was with her?

‘Has she mastered the art of assassination? How can she keep doing this?’

Come to think of it, despite her being ahead of him right now, he could barely feel her presence.

It was one thing when you relied entirely on your eyes and ears, but it was unthinkable for this to happen to a Taoist who has mastered all five senses and utilizes their qi to sense their surroundings.

Seeing Yu Yiseol staring at him, Chung Myung was deeply concerned.

‘How do I fix this? How much did she see?’

For now, he needed to figure that out…

Yu Yiseol opened her mouth.

“Plum Blossom…”

Everything!

She clearly saw everything!

She tilted her head to the side as if she didn’t understand what she saw.

Right, yes! Do not understand it.

Chung Myung smiled brightly.

If it was anyone else, they would have been dumbfounded in this situation. But who was Chung Myung? The unprecedented accident of Mount Hua.

His Sahyung made sure to point out every time that there were more accidents after Chung Myung joined Mount Hua than in the entire sect’s history before his initiation.

For such an experienced Chung Myung, this situation was nothing.

First, he needed to act naturally.

He bowed his head to Yu Yiseol.

“How have you been?”

As Chung Myung took a step closer, Yu Yiseol flinched.

Why? Why flinch?

Yi Yiseol looked at Chung Myung with serious eyes.

“Are you going to kill me to silence the witness?”

“What the fuck, are you crazy?”

“…”

Ah…

The words naturally escaped him.

Chung Myung, who cursed without realizing, covered his mouth in shock.

Another day wasted; just why did this woman have to come and bother him so much?

Now, there was only one way out.

Chung Myung waved his hand and quickly fled the scene.

“Well then, goodbye for now!”

“Ah… wait!”

Yu Yiseol tried to stop Chung Myung, but he ignored her pleas and left at full speed.

‘When you can’t make any excuses, it’s best to just avoid the problem altogether.’

Yu Yiseol stretched out her hand towards his back but lowered it as he was already gone.

“Plum Blossoms….”

She looked at the running child’s back with blank eyes and clenched fists.

“I was caught!”

This was obviously Chung Myung’s mistake.

Thinking about it, though, it won’t make a difference if only one person caught him. Even if she told everyone what happened, no one would believe it.

But he had to be careful from now on. If there’s just one witness, they’ll be written off as crazy. But if three or more people saw it, then everyone would believe it.

‘When the Baek disciples return, I need to be careful with my training.’

Ah…

Not just the training, right?

Chung Myung nodded with a determined face.

“I have something I must do before the Baek disciples arrive!”

He quickly began to descend towards the sect.

Chapter 73: Something seems to have changed in Mount Hua (3)

“Here!”

“Oh. Young master, you’re here again. Come this way. We’ll guide you to a good seat.”

“I’m not asking too much of you, right?”

“Oh my. Why would it be like that? Thanks to your frequent visits, business is going well, and life is worth living. Hahaha!”

Chung Myung headed to a window seat at the guidance of the restaurant owner.

“Here is a cold wet towel. Wait just a moment more and I will bring the alcohol that you always have. What would you like to eat for today?”

“Just give me whatever you recommend.”

“Yes. I will talk to the chef and ask for the best food to be prepared.”

‘I don’t want the best, I want the most delicious, you bastard!’

Who was he trying to fool!?

However, the man ran to the kitchen and brought two bottles of chilled alcohol.

“Here you are.”

“Thank you.”

Chung Myung opened the lid without delay and poured it into his glass as soon as he received the bottles.

From the sound of pouring alcohol to the act of drinking alcohol, everything was delightful.

‘People live for this taste.’

No matter how much privilege Chung Myung had earned, and no matter how little he cared for the rules of Taoists, it was still unacceptable for a third-class disciple to drink alcohol in Mount Hua.

Alcohol wasn’t banned completely, but it was strictly prohibited within the sect grounds.

But who was Chung Myung?

He was the sort of man who must do exactly what he is told not to do; especially tempting are the acts that are forbidden.

‘Oddly, if you tell me not to eat, I end up eating more.’

The two bottles Chung Myung had stored in his cave were long gone, and now it had become a daily routine to change out of his uniform and stop by this place to have all that he wanted because of the permission the sect leader gave him.

How often did he frequent this restaurant? Well, only the owner of the place would know that.

“Kuah!”

Chung Myung gulped one glass down and looked at the other glass as if he had left the mortal plane and entered paradise.

“Taoists are supposed to go with the flow in life, so why do they have all these silly restrictions!?”

Aren’t Taoist rules stupid?

What?

Chung Myung is a Taoist, too?

No. He was a bit different.

Chung Myung poured another glass and brought it to his lips. Without holding back, he looked at the glass and then softly gulped with a smile.

“It isn’t the same as it used to be, sahyung.”

’Alcohol tasted the best when hiding from the watchful eyes of that nagging Sahyung. ’

“I am still here like this.”

There was no one there.

Chung Myung looked at the glass and smiled.

It felt strange.

He never missed anyone in his whole life, but now he was feeling sentimental while drinking.

“Tch.”

But it wasn’t like he was too deep in his thoughts.

The past is the past. If the sahyungs saw this side of him, they would laugh at him.

In this world, whether they were called Taoists, Saints, or Deities, his Sahyung was innately just a playful old bastard.

The same went for Chung Myung.

“Now, here is the leopard fish skin, and here is the pig feet fry.”

The leopard fish skin was made with oyster meat, pork, and jellyfish, and the other one was made with onion and pork feet. Both were Shaanxi foods.

“What about pork belly?”

“It’s coming soon.”

Chung Myung raised his chopsticks, smacking his lips.

Weren’t the things on his table the best delicacies? After drinking a glass of alcohol, having a delicious piece of meat feels no different from entering nirvana.

‘This is paradise.’

‘Sahyung, sorry, but I plan to live. So, I hope you live happily wherever you are.’

The door opened, and a group of men entered.

“Welcome!”

The owner ran and greeted them.

All those who entered were young men and women.

‘Wait, maybe they’re too old to be considered young men?’

The men seemed tall, strong, and well-developed, but the women were certainly a bit younger than the men. In any case, Chung Myung observed them from the side.

Those who came inside sat at the table next to Chung Myung. Chung Myung didn’t pay any more attention to them and went back to eating.

“We get to eat food after such a long time.”

“We don’t have to eat those fasting pills anymore, Sahyung.”

“Isn’t that why we’re here? Our priority is to go up the mountain as soon as possible and greet our elders, but I’m sure they will understand us stopping here first.”

Sahyung? Elders?

Chung Myung frowned and looked at the group seated next to him. All of them had black uniforms, and on the chest was a plum blossom pattern.

‘The Baek disciples?’

They had an embroidered plum blossom, so they all had to be from Mount Hua. Since Chung Myung had never seen them before, and their ages seemed to fit, they had to be the Baek disciples.

Chung Myung bowed his head.

He hadn’t committed any crimes, but he didn’t want to see them here. Nor did he want to get involved with them. Fortunately, he wasn’t in uniform, so as long as he didn’t get tangled up with them, there wouldn’t be any problems.

‘I can’t even eat properly. Ugh. I need to quickly leave after gulping the food down.’

Meeting these people here would be a pain in the ass right now. It was best to not get involved at all.

“But where is Samae Yu?”^1

“I think she went up Mount Hua first.”

“Didn’t we decide to meet in Hua-Um?”

“When did Samae Yu ever listen to us?”

“Hm. Then the masters might already know that we’re here.”

“It’s fine. Everyone knows that Samae Yu is unique.”

“Then we’re lucky.”

The young man sitting in the middle finished placing a simple order as he requested food and alcohol for everyone at his table.

‘Look at that. Tsk. Tsk.’

Chung Myung frowned.

‘These little second-class disciples are openly drinking in the middle of Hua-Um! Even if the sect is failing, this is too much!’

Children these days, seriously!

What?

What about Chung Myung?

Well, he is different. He’s close to a hundred years old, after all…

“Everyone worked hard and overcame the training really well.”

“Who among us could say they’ve suffered more than Sahyung? We just followed you.”

“Right. Sahyung had the most difficult time.”

A tall young man sitting in the middle with a smile.

‘Isn’t he handsome?’

Chung Myung was quite good-looking himself. But the black robe on this man and the presence he evoked,

How should it be put? Didn’t he seem to appear like the legendary heroes in fairy tales?

“We’ve all trained hard, together. I know better than anyone just how hard everyone has worked. So, I will treat you all to this alcohol today. Don’t feel burdened and drink as much as you want.”

“Thank you. Sahyung.”

“Just don’t get too drunk. We need to climb up to Mount Hua in the evening.”

“Yes.”

Laughter filled the table.

So, they finished their training and settled on having a drink in Hua-Um upon returning? Then, the one being called Sahyung must be the Great Sahyung of the Baek disciples, and the rest are the second-class Baek sahyungs.

Otherwise, they wouldn’t be able to enter this place without a second thought.

‘I can imagine how the sect will turn out.’

Chung Myung snorted at the scene.

When he was a second-class disciple, he wouldn’t have dared to even think about drinking with others. If anyone had been caught drinking, they would have been placed in the repentance room for an entire week!

That was why Chung Myung had to be stealthy when he drank!

Huh?

Yeah. He did drink. How could he not drink?

But it was fundamentally different! He drank in secret! Not openly like them!

Unaware of Chung Myung’s poisonous thoughts, the disciples clinked their glasses and began to drink. As soon as the snacks were served and the table was filled, the atmosphere heated up.

‘I should quickly eat and get out of here.’

Chung Myung moved quickly in a hustle. Yet, the moment he poured himself another glass, he heard some words that he couldn’t ignore.

“Baek Cheon Sahyung.”

“What is it, Sajae?”

“After all this hard work, we’ll be able to get good results in the conference, right?”

The one called Baek Cheon folded his arms and nodded.

“… Umm.”

“Right, Sahyung?”

“Sajae. To be honest, I don’t know. But there is one thing I do know.”

“What is that?”

“Effort never betrays a man.”

Baek Cheon’s eyes had a brilliant shine in them.

“We’ve done our best. We made it through that arduous training and constantly beat ourselves up. Even if we don’t win, isn’t it true that we’ve made commendable progress in this time?”

“Yes. Sahyung.”

“Don’t get too hung up on winning or losing. We’re in this for the long game. If we lose our eyes in the present, we’ll never be able to see the future.”

“Ah… I was short-sighted.”

“However, I do want to win.”

Baek Cheon smiled softly. When a smile appeared on that handsome face, the surroundings seemed to brighten in response. The disciples there looked at him with absolute trust.

But there was one person nearby who had a rotten mien in response to his speech.

‘Does he put oil on his lips?’

Chung Myung gulped down alcohol with a sour expression as he listened to those smoothly flowing disgustingly sweet words. He wasn’t the kind who would enjoy such cringe-inducing speeches.

‘I think there’s something hidden about this man.’

He was the same as the others, but something felt a bit off about him. Although, it didn’t feel like he was a bad person…

“Then, where do we stand? Can we fight against the Southern Edge Sect on equal footing now?”

“Well.”

Baek Cheon opened his mouth with a sullen face.

“The Southern Edge Sect is strong. Isn’t it one of the Ten Great Sects?”

“Yes.”

“In the past, Mount Hua was also one of the Ten Great Sects. However, to be honest, the difference between us and the Southern Edge Sect has grown beyond comparison.”

Everyone’s faces darkened at those words.

“But that’s just what others believe.”

Baek Cheon raised his voice as he spoke, refreshing the atmosphere.

“Skills aren’t necessarily proportional to fame. We lost to them in the last conference, but the difference wasn’t that large. During all this time, haven’t we focused on our training while even reducing our sleep? We’ll be able to contest against them well this time.”

“With the Southern Edge sect?”

“Was Southern Edge this great from its inception? Was Mount Hua always the Mount Hua that we know? Nothing is set in stone. If we work tirelessly, it’s not impossible for us to one day look beyond our current position.”

He spoke with a voice full of determination that attracted the hearts of those who listened.

As everyone gazed at Baek Cheon with admiration and respect, it happened.

“Puah!”

A low chuckle from beside.

The heads of the six people sitting at the table turned in unison.

“Uh…”

Realizing that their gaze was on him, Chung Myung covered his mouth.

‘Shit, I didn’t mean to react.’

Hearing such absurd words, he ended up laughing.

Receiving everyone’s attention, Chung Myung came up with a solution to the situation as usual.

‘Just act natural.’

And he started to cough.

“Puah! Ugh! Puah! Cough! Puaah!”

“…”

Chung Myung frowned when he saw that the disciples didn’t go back to talking with each other.

‘Why aren’t they deceived? My acting was perfect.’

Cough more violently!

“Young man.”

“What?”

Baek Cheon slowly rose from his seat and spoke to Chung Myung.

“Young man, who could you be? I don’t believe I’ve ever seen your face in Hua-Um before. If it isn’t too rude, may I ask your name and what family you belong to?

“…”

Why does it suddenly seem like Chung Myung was screwed?

Right?

Chapter 74: Something seems to have changed in Mount Hua (4)

Baek Cheon narrowed his eyes.

‘Who is this guy?’

He was nothing short of absurd.

From the moment they entered this place, he felt a sense of incongruity. Now that he looked closely, he understood why he felt that way.

Why was there a child, who might have just turned 15 this year, ordering all of this expensive food and alcohol?

Of course, it wasn’t impossible.

The sons of high-ranking officials or the children of wealthy elites could do this. The children of the merchant families also often enjoy such pleasures from a young age.

The problem was that this was Hua-Um.

As far as Baek Cheon knew, there were no high-ranking officials, no descendants of wealthy families, or children of wealthy merchants here. Even if they were here, Chung Myung’s age doesn’t match up.

So, who was this child that was drinking alcohol alone in Hua-Um?

“Cough.”

The child coughed and waved his hand.

“I’m just a passerby. Don’t worry about me and continue with your meal.”

“A passerby.”

Baek Cheon’s eyes softened.

“Right, that was also possible. Alright, then. Since we ended up meeting here, why don’t we introduce ourselves? I am Baek Cheon, second-class disciple of the Great Mount Hua.”

Chung Myung grunted a little as he covered his face with his long sleeves.

‘Ugh, this bastard! Why is he so persistent?’

He couldn’t back out or beat him up now.

If the fact that Chung Myung had beaten Baek Cheon so that he could run away spread around Mount Hua, then the sect leader would be enraged, and Un Geom, who began to nag him a lot these days, might run wild and try to cut Chung Myung down.

Then, everything Chung Myung had built up would come crumbling down.

‘I can’t let that happen.’

He can’t let himself get tangled up with this young man for no reason. Chung Myung coughed twice.

“I really don’t have a name worth offering….”

“Isn’t it a bit ungentlemanly to cover your face while having a conversation?”

‘Gentleman? What gentleman? You should just leave me alone, you bastard!’

Chung Myung’s emotions were slowly overwhelming him. For now, the first thing he needed to do was avoid further interaction.

Chung Myung quietly got up.

“Well, I need to leave.”

“Hold on.”

“Let’s have a talk the next time we meet.”

Chung Myung, who was turning around, smiled as he grabbed the alcohol bottle on the table and bowed with his face half-covered.

“Goodbye.”

“Young man. I would like to speak with you a bit longer.”

“I’m sorry, I have no interest in playing with men. Farewell.”

As Chung Myung rushed to the entrance, Baek Cheon’s expression went stiff, and he quickly stretched out his hand.

‘Where does he think he’s going!?’

The moment his hand went to grab the hem of Chung Myung’s clothes.

Swoosh.

Chung Myung smoothly side-stepped his grasp and avoided Baek Cheon’s hand, which merely cut through the air.

“Huh?”

“Take care!”

Chung Myung jumped out of the window next to the table and left.

Baek Cheon looked at the place Chung Myung had left with blank eyes.

‘He avoided it?’

He definitely used the Grasping Joint Lock at the last moment. Even if it didn’t reach the pinnacle, it was still enough to catch a child.

But it was avoided?

“Sahyung. Why didn’t you catch him?”

“… What?”

“Didn’t you let him go?”

A look of embarrassment appeared on Baek Cheon’s face.

How should he answer this?

“… holding a young child against their will isn’t something a Taoist should do.”

“As expected from Sahyung. Haha.”

Baek Cheon put on an awkward smile.

‘There must have been some mistake.’

He must have been tired from the long journey, or maybe he was too relieved by the fact that he came back to Mount Hua.

There was no way he could have lost that child if he had seriously used the technique.

“I thought there were more people in Hua-Um, and now there are many faces I’ve never seen before.”

“Hua-Um isn’t a small place, so there’s no way we could know everyone. If there is a chance, we might meet again.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

Baek Cheon smiled and went back to his seat. But his smile wasn’t as bright as before.

“Ugh! What rotten timing!”

Chung Myung kicked a stone lying on the road.

“Why did he have to come there and make a fuss! There were a lot of other people around! Anyway, have I run out of luck? Even the weakest bastards come to step on my toes!”

How unfortunate.

When he thought of the food he didn’t get to finish eating, his stomach hurt. How much money did he waste!?

“At least I saved the alcohol.”

As he climbed up to Mount Hua, Chung Myung continued to drink from the bottle.

“Ah, it lingers on the tongue.”

’If only there were snacks to go along with this. ’

Chung Myung smacked his lips and threw away the empty bottle.

“Ah. Climbing a mountain is so difficult.”

No matter how many times he climbed the mountain, it seemed like he could never get used to it.

‘But that Baek Cheon kid….’

Suddenly, a group of people outside of Chung Myung’s plans appeared. Of course, their presence didn’t bother him, but….

‘It might get a little annoying.’

Chung Myung’s life has been so comfortable on Mount Hua because of the preferential treatment he got for his achievements. But that wasn’t all.

The biggest reason was the age difference between the elders and the third-class disciples.

Compared to the elders, who were all over fifty years old, the third-class disciples were children below twenty. This gave them a bit of leeway to work and train.

The scariest person for a soldier in the army isn’t the general or the emperor. It is his immediate supervisor. Isn’t it common sense that a corrupt boss with a short temper is more frightening than a distant mastermind?

There wouldn’t be anyone that would think otherwise.

“Ugh. Baek Cheon huh.”

First of all, it seemed strange.

“Heh. I shouldn’t have laughed back there.”

But he couldn’t control it.

The words he heard from Baek Cheon were so absurd.

“Overtake the Southern Edge Sect?”

On what basis?

Chung Myung clicked his tongue over and over.

If only those idiots, who ran their mouths, could at least defeat the third-class disciples of the Southern Edge Sect.

“Oh my, Sahyung. In this era, just look at these fools that are considered disciples of Mount Hua. Seriously, kids these days! Phew!”

Chung Myung was more shocked than when he saw the state of the third-class disciples.

How much martial arts could the third-class disciples even learn? They wouldn’t have even gotten a clear taste of what martial arts is, so it wouldn’t matter.

But the second-class disciples are different.

The third-class disciples are taught the foundation, second-class disciples grow through training, first-class disciples reach the peak, and when they become an elder, it is natural for them to complete their own martial arts path.

Right… that is the standard.

“Oh, my God.”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

When he saw the second-class disciples, Chung Myung felt his stomach-turning. However, they were also disciples of Mount Hua, so Chung Myung should embrace them…

“I shouldn’t be wasting my precious time like this.”

Seeing the second-class disciples, an unknown sense of urgency grew in him.

“Ugh. How much longer will I have to wait for these disciples to grow into competent martial artists?”

It was still a very, very long way off.

“Jo Gul sahyung! All the third-class disciples have been asked to gather!”

“Why?”

“Our seniors are returning.”

“Well, okay. Did you tell Great Sahyung?”

“Yes! He said he’ll be there soon.”

“Okay.”

Jo Gul took off his training clothes and changed into new ones.

The sunset was approaching.

‘Come to think of it, I wonder if he’s back yet.’

Jo Gul opened the door, went out, and opened the door to Chung Myung’s room.

“Kuha… ugh…!”

“…”

When he saw Chung Myung on the bed, Jo Gul was left speechless. He was lying down in a weird way and mumbling in his sleep…

“Did he seriously get drunk!?”

Where was the smell of alcohol coming from?

Flustered, Jo Gul ran to Chung Myung, grabbed him by the shoulders, and shook him.

“Chung Myung! Sajae! Chung Myung! You crazy basta—”

“Huh?”

“—ah, nothing. Forget that last one.”

He kept shaking him.

“Everyone was asked to gather, the Sasuks are back. You should quickly wash up, you look terrible right now.”

“Ahhh.”

Chung Myung stretched himself out.

“I guess I dozed off for a bit when I took that break.”

‘That wasn’t a break!’

Chung Myung, no creature in the world would sleep the way you did. Just say you got drunk and fell asleep.

“You, wash up first….”

“Ugh!”

Chung Myung released a little qi and quickly scattered the scent of alcohol. Jo Gul, with his eyes wide open, was about to say something…

‘Huh?’

That overwhelming smell of alcohol disappeared in an instant. Jo Gul sniffed, just to be sure, but he couldn’t smell anything.

“Uh? Why don’t I smell the alcohol anymore?”

“Alcohol? What is wrong with you? We walk the path of purity, Sahyung, why would we have such things? We would get punished.”

“… No? I definitely…”

“Let’s go. We might be punished if we’re late.”

Jo Gul felt that the situation was a bit unfair, but Chung Myung was right about being late for now, so he hurriedly followed after him.

“But why do we need to go greet the seniors just because they’re returning?”

“We need to at least welcome them back. They are returning from a long and arduous training session.”

Arduous?

Do they think that staying in some closed space would promote growth?

They probably just went and locked themselves in some building or cave with no light for two or three months, ate fasting pills, and swung their swords a few times.

They probably thought to themselves…

‘Ah, I got so much training done.’

How pointless.

‘A bunch of young men and women, isolated in pairs, wielding swords or whatever. Such cheeky training. Yet, they arrogantly ran their mouths about how difficult it was and how they can overtake Southern Edge with just that.’

It wasn’t like that back in Chung Myung’s day!

It was inconceivable for such a thing to happen in Mount Hua a hundred years ago.

“They said they’d take down the Southern Edge sect bastards no matter what. This time, they really are coming back with great results. Even the sect leader wholeheartedly supported their training.”

“Is that so?”

“Yes. Baek Cheon Sasuk strongly requested it.”

Chung Myung snorted.

“Sure, sure.”

“You should also be careful of your attitude. Baek Cheon Sasuk is strict, so if you behave like you usually do, you’ll get in trouble.”

“Sure, sure.”

“I meant it.”

“Sure, sure.”

Leaving Jo Gul, who was nagging him, Chung Myung joined the third-class disciples. By the time Chung Myung arrived, quite a few people were already gathered.

The sect leader, elders, and the Un sasuks too. Everyone stood at the gate, waiting for the second-class disciples to return.

“They’re coming.”

“Open the gate!”

The newly built gate opened to the left and right. Soon, Mount Hua’s second-class disciples entered the scene, draped in black robes.

“Oh!”

“Look at the change in atmosphere.”

“It’s really amazing.”

The Un sasuks admired them and applauded. The elders also welcomed them with happy faces.

There was only one person with a dull face.

‘When will this end?’

Chung Myung wanted to go eat.

Baek Cheon, who led the disciples, responded to everyone with a dazzling smile.

‘Wow, look at this.’

Indeed, this disciple was unquestionably handsome.

Of course, even Chung Myung had people who called him handsome in the past. When he got dressed up and went down to Hua-Um, beautiful women would fall—

– Have some conscience.

‘Oh, come on Sahyung!’

Chung Myung shook his head and was just about to clap.

“Huh?”

Baek Cheon’s eyes, which accepted the others’ greetings, fell on Chung Myung. Baek Cheon, who paused for a moment, tilted his head.

After watching Chung Myung for a long time, he arrived in front of Chung Myung and smiled with confused eyes.

“By any chance….”

Baek Cheon smiled and stared straight at Chung Myung as he spoke.

“Haven’t we met before? Young man?”

“…”

Was he going to get caught this time?

‘Do I really need to beat the hell out of this guy?’

Chapter 75: Something seems to have changed in Mount Hua (5)

Baek Cheon smiled brightly with that handsome face.

It wasn’t a perfectly handsome face, but it had a unique magnetism that attracted others to him.

‘What a familiar feeling, it reminds me a bit of the past.’

Chung Myung experienced the same feeling from people of the Shaolin sect.

Of course, this idiot couldn’t be compared to them. But in Mount Hua, where there were many normal people, this feeling was weirdly out of place. It made him wonder why he was even here, in the ruined Mount Hua.

More problematic was that this man was trying to bite at Chung Myung’s ankles and hang off them.

“What are you talking about?”

For now, just act like you don’t know.

“You don’t know?”

“I have no idea.”

“Ah, is that so?”

Baek Cheon tilted his head slightly. Rather than acting confused, he tried to act in a way that would provoke Chung Myung into admitting the truth.

“That’s quite strange. I feel like I’ve seen your face before. When did you join us?”

The answer came from Yoon Jong and not Chung Myung.

“Sasuk, this child entered while you were all away from Mount Hua. So, you couldn’t have met him.”

“Is that so? I see.”

Baek Cheon smiled brightly.

“You seem like you are close to each other. As Great Sahyung, it’s good that you are taking care of the youngest. Don’t you think so?”

“Yes, sasuk.”

Yoon Jong answered with an awkward timbre. As if Baek Cheon discovered something from that answer, he nodded his head.

“It seems like this was a fateful meeting. It’s only our first meeting, but you seem so familiar to me. I think we’ll see each other in the future quite often. What is your name?”

“Chung Myung.”

“I am Baek Cheon. Be sure to remember my name.”

Then rang a firm voice.

“How can you leisurely have a chat over there when the sect leader is waiting for you!?”

“Ah, I’m sorry! I’m coming.”

Baek Cheon bowed towards Un Geom. He then turned and joined his other mates as they advanced ahead.

Jo Gul watched Chung Myung and whispered.

“Have you met Baek Cheon sasuk before?”

“No.”

Even if he did, the answer is no.

“Be careful. Baek Cheon Sasuk is a second-class disciple. He’s a great man.”

“Great?”

“Yes.”

Yoon Jong added to Jo Gul’s words.

“He’s known to be the savior of Mount Hua. A person said to have the potential to rebuild the crumbling Mount Hua.”

“Savior?”

Didn’t this phrase seem like something Chung Myung heard a lot in the past? When did he…? Ah, back when he first arrived on Mount Hua, people often used to say such things about him.

Although Chung Myung quickly turned from the savior into the most mischievous gossip topic of Mount Hua.

“Wasn’t Jo Gul the sect’s best genius?”

“What are you saying!? Someone might hear you!”

Jo Gul’s face turned bright red at those words.

“Baek Cheon sasuk isn’t someone I can compare to.”

“Yes. Yes. A loser mentality is good. Having a sense of defeat makes people look humble too.”

“Huh?”

“Nothing, Sahyung.”

Chung Myung looked at Baek Cheon, who was walking ahead.

‘Seems like a crane mixed in with a flock of hens.’

It sounds like a good thing. A very good thing.

But in reality, it isn’t a very nice thing to say.

A crane is a crane. It doesn’t make sense for a crane to be among the flock of hens.

And in most cases…

‘He has a flaw.’

While Chung Myung curiously looked at Baek Cheon, Yoon Jong continued to explain.

“Actually, it’s said that Baek Cheon sasuks’ sword techniques have reached the pinnacle. I heard that the elders have high expectations of him. Even though he’s young, he is a genius.”

“Hm.”

Perhaps, among the second-class disciples of Mount Hua, Baek Cheon was the most important.

‘And that’s very annoying.’

Chung Myung had also gone through this in the past.

Why were there so many things to learn? The other disciples would train moderately and then go to bed, but the elders would always latch onto Chung Myung and brush him up on other techniques too. Even Sahyung… no. There was nothing that his Sahyung didn’t involve him in.

But it was worth it.

It’s said the prestige of a sect is built over a long history, but the rise and fall of anything can often depend on a single person.

Even if it’s only a small or medium-sized sect, if they can produce a famous master, then people will flock to them in hopes of joining the same sect. On the other hand, no matter how long a sect has existed or how proud their history and traditions are, they are destined to stagnate and decline if they fail to produce any reputable masters.

The only way for the dying Mount Hua to rise again is to produce a powerful genius. If just one mighty warrior exists within the sect, the entire situation can be reversed.

‘Of course, that was the plan until I arrived.’

Now what, though?

There is a lot of money.

“Don’t the sasuks look strong?”

“Tell me about it. I don’t know if we can ever catch up to them.”

“So cool and strong.”

Chung Myung looked at the two, who were talking to each other with blank eyes.

‘Are these idiots’ eyes for decoration?’

Fine, let’s call them cool even without seeing anything. People’s tastes are diverse, and Chung Myung was a good person who didn’t impose his tastes on others.

But ‘looking strong’ and ‘being strong’ were not the same.

‘If these disciples are considered strong, then nobody would be considered weak!’

“Looking at Sasuk’s level, Sahyungs would be able to win.”

At Chung Myung’s words, Jo Gul dumbfoundedly smiled like it wasn’t a funny joke.

“What nonsense.”

“… uh, right.”

Sahyung.

My Sahyung.

I have to live here listening to such words on a daily basis. If you have any conscience, come down and say something! Am I meant to live here unfairly like this?

It was often said that people who ascend to the other world come to visit our world and give advice. Then Sahyung, who was known to be the icon of virtue, can come and advise something, right?

Right?

Won’t he listen to Chung Myung?

Come on!!

While Chung Myung was having a conversation with his Sahyung, the second-class disciples lined up.

“Huh?”

Just then, someone ran to join the lineup of second-class disciples from within the sect’s grounds.

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

‘Right, that one is also a Baek disciple.’

Yu… what was her name? Yu something.

He was entangled in a strange relationship with her, so he ended up paying a little attention to her. Surely, she couldn’t have told anyone about their meeting before, right?

When Chung Myung frowned while looking at Yu Yiseol, Jo Gul smiled insidiously.

“Come to think of it, this is your first time seeing senior Yu.”

“What?”

“Right. Yu Yiseol. Anyone who sees her for the first time can’t take their eyes off her. That’s how beautiful she is.”

“Great Sahyung.”

“Huh?”

“Do you have any cinnamon powder with you?”

“Why?”

“I want to spray some on my ears. I feel like my ears are bleeding from listening to Jo Gul sahyung.”

He couldn’t help but feel like this.

Yoon Jong nodded his head.

“It’s been a while since we both agreed on something. Well, I will give some to you later.”

“Thank you.”

Jo Gul’s expression grew distorted.

“Did I say anything wrong? It’s because there aren’t many who know about senior Yu. She’s probably the most beautiful woman in Shaanxi.”

Listening to Jo Gul repeat himself like a parrot, Chung Myung took a deep breath.

“You are known to be the best in Mount Hua, and she is the most beautiful around? If someone who doesn’t know our situation hears you, they’ll think that her and you are up to no good.”

“But that’s the truth.”

Jo Gul pointed to Yu Yiseol.

“Isn’t she pretty?”

“Sigh…”

Before Chung Myung could answer, Jo Gul continued.

“But don’t dream much. Senior Yu already has Baek Cheon in her heart.”

“… Sahyung.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung sighed deeply,

“Instead of wasting your time being interested in someone else’s love life, wouldn’t you have already made a name for yourself if you had just spent that time training?”

“You aren’t supposed to stab people with truth like that.”

“Just stop talking.”

Chung Myung looked at Jo Gul as if he was pathetic and turned away.

Looking back, she did say that she was his senior; apparently, that seemed to be correct.

Chung Myung looked back at Yu Yiseol.

When all the Baek disciples lined up, the sect leader, who was watching them, smiled warmly.

“You’ve all worked hard. The training must have been excruciating, right?”

Baek Cheon began to speak on behalf of the others.

“Sect leader. It wasn’t difficult at all. Our training was done with the support we got from the sect, so how can we call it difficult?”

“And the results?”

Baek Cheon smiled.

“We managed to realize that the path of the sword is endless in life. However, we have returned with achievements great enough that we would laugh in the face of our former selves.”

“That’s a good thing.”

Hyun Jong looked at Hyung Young.

“Finance head.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Now that the children of Mount Hua have returned from their hard training, shouldn’t we celebrate their return?”

“Tsk. What nonsen—ah, no, it’s nothing. Of course, we should.”

“…”

Hyun Jong stared at him with a subtle gaze.

‘This man is becoming more strange by the day.’

To be precise, the frequency of saying strange things had increased dramatically since the Eunha Guild arrived. It was hard to tell for sure, but it felt like the tight reins around him had finally gone loose.

“Well, we have it prepared in the meal room. It should be enough for everyone.”

“I see.”

Hyun Jong looked at the second-class disciples.

“There are many things I want to say, but it wouldn’t do to hold you here after your long journey back. Since I don’t want to keep you here, let’s head inside.”

“… sect leader. With all due respect, may I ask you one thing?”

Hyun Jong wanted to clear this crowd quickly, but Baek Cheon didn’t seem to notice.

“Feel free to ask.”

“The scenery here seems to have changed a lot since the last time we were here, I was wondering what happened.”

“Good things happened. Thanks to that, I was able to restore everything in the sect.”

It was a soft but firm answer. After hearing that, it was hard to ask what the ‘good’ thing was.

“You might have a lot of questions, but we also have a lot of time ahead of us. So, we can take this slowly.”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

“Un Am.”

“Yes.”

Un Am, who was on Hyun Jong’s side, came forward.

“Please look after these children who have suffered for so long.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Hyun Jong nodded and turned his head.

“Chung Myung!”

“…”

Chung Myung’s face contorted.

‘No, does that man really have to call me like this day after day?’

There shouldn’t be any work today.

“Yes! Sect leader!’

Chung Myung walked out,

“Come to my room for a while. I have something to discuss.”

“Again?”

Baek Cheon, who was watching this unfold, was shocked.

‘Again…?’

He spoke like that to the sect leader?

Baek Cheon doubted whether he had heard correctly or not. But it didn’t seem like he was mistaking the words because all the second-class disciples had the same expression on their faces.

However, he didn’t understand why the third-class disciples didn’t seem to discipline this child.

It wouldn’t be wrong even if this child was harshly hit for behaving like that to the sect leader!

But even the sect leader was smiling despite those words.

“How about if I prepare some snacks?”

“Okay. I get it. I will come.”

Hyun Jong led Chung Myung to his residence with a happy face.

Baek Cheon, who silently observed the scene, looked incredulously at Un Geom and asked.

“Sasuk. That child, just who is he?”

“Well.”

Un Geom smiled.

“I think it would be good for your mental health to not pay much attention to him.”

“What?”

“Especially if it’s you.”

Un Geom shrugged his shoulders and turned.

“Unpack your belongings and come to the meal room. Don’t be late.”

“… Yes.”

Baek Cheon felt a strange feeling again. Only this time, the sense of incompatibility felt much greater.

Perhaps, this awkward feeling was simply because he had returned after being away for a while.

But just one thing.

Baek Cheon’s eyes turned to follow Chung Myung, who was walking with the sect leader.

“Hmmm.”

He narrowed his eyes as he stared in disapproval at the one he didn’t like.

Chapter 76: Rolling Stone Gathers No Moss! (1)

“S-Sahyung!”

“…”

“What is all this? Despite all the hard work we did, no one is praising us….”

Baek Cheon couldn’t find the words to respond despite someone talking to him. It was because he, too, was surprised.

Unexpectedly, there was a huge feast in front of them.

From the perspective of the secular world, it may be somewhat lacking to be called a feast. However, for Mount Hua, this seemed no different from what would be eaten by an emperor.

What’s more, that.

That! There was that!

“… isn’t that meat?”

“Uh.”

Baek Cheon rubbed his eyes.

In front of his eyes was certainly food that had been acquired by killing a living animal and carving its flesh.

How could a pure sect commit such an act?

“Where did the money come from?”

‘I want to know the same!’

Just where did Mount Hua even get such money? Where did the meat come from?

“W-wait. Sahyung. Come to think of it, the inside of this place has also changed. I thought it might just feel awkward because we’ve been gone for so long, but doesn’t it look shiny and clean?”

“… now that you mention it, yes.”

Baek Cheon looked around. The entire building might not be newly built, but it looked like it had been recently renovated. All the holes in the walls were covered, and the whole place seemed to be fixed cleanly.

“There are new looking halls, and now this place? There’s even meat on the table!”

“…”

“I can’t imagine what happened to Mount Hua while we were away. Unless some God of Wealth descended onto this place.”

Baek Cheon smiled.

God of Wealth? Mount Hua is a sect that the God of Wealth had abandoned.

If any sect could compete with the Beggars Union, it would be Mount Hua.

No, even they might be richer than Mount Hua. Just because the Beggars Union was a group of beggars didn’t mean that the sect itself was poor.

But for Mount Hua to have such wealth?

Why did it seem so out of place?

Baek Cheon lifted his head and slightly looked at Un Geom.

“Sasuk. This food?”

“This is food the finance head prepared to raise your spirits. Eat a lot.”

No, why is he speaking so casually about this?

Sasuk used to say that he would survive solely on grass, like a rabbit, for the sake of Mount Hua. Where did that Sasuk go, and when did he switch sides like this!?

Even stranger was the reaction of the third-class disciples.

The third-class disciples, who were there to congratulate the second-class disciples, didn’t show any surprise at the quality of food placed in front of them.

They just stared at the table sternly.

Baek Cheon listened to their conversation from the side.

“I’m tired of meat, isn’t there anything different? Fish or something else.”

“Crazy bastard, where will we find fish on the mountains? Do you need to be beaten with a fish to restore your senses?”

What the hell are those idiots talking about?

What? They are tired of meat?

Unable to understand the situation, Baek Cheon, who was frustrated, opened his mouth.

“No…”

“Ahem.”

“Hahahahahaha.”

“…”

He was about to open his mouth.

Baek Cheon turned his head to the side to shut the mouths of his mates.

‘Let’s just eat first.’

‘We have money, so we get to eat meat. I was sick of having those pills for the past year.’

Baek Cheon, who felt suppressed by the laughs of the others, opened his mouth.

“Is it alright to start eating, even though the elders and sect leader haven’t arrived yet?”

“Huh? Ah, I didn’t notice. Hold a moment.”

“Yes. Thank you.”

Un Geom took his chopsticks and put a piece of meat in his mouth. That was the sign that the others could eat, and the Sahyungs frantically moved their chopsticks.

Papapak!

Food bounced into the air.

But there was nothing to worry about. The chopsticks caught everything in the air because it was precious meat that had to be treasured.

Baek Cheon closed his eyes upon seeing everyone’s behavior; he felt that he was staring deeply into the abyss.

It might look exaggerated to others, but this was a normal reaction. Mount Hua was the poorest sect in the world, and the disciples were the poorest people in the world.

They had only eaten food made with grains and a few nuts in all their time here. To say it politely, they served healthy meals. But truthfully, it was the cheapest diet that could be afforded.

Besides, thanks to their closed-door training, the second-class disciples only had fasting pills for the past year.

Some, like Baek Cheon, could purchase food with money when visiting family. However, most of the disciples hadn’t so much as smelled the scent of meat for years already.

Of course, they were losing control of themselves.

In the meantime, Baek Cheon looked at the third-class disciples leisurely eating their food.

Looking at their nonchalant attitude, he realized that this food was nothing special in the current Mount Hua.

“Sasuk.”

Un Geom, who was eating and drinking, turned his head and looked at Baek Cheon.

“What? Does the food suit your taste?”

“It isn’t like that… I just really don’t understand the situation. Just what happened to Mount Hua in the time we were all away?”

“Right. I didn’t think of this from your position.”

Un Geom laughed.

“It’s too long of a story to tell. You’ll find out eventually. All you need to know is that a lucky star rolled into Mount Hua.”

“Lucky star?”

It was then.

Kwang!

The door opened wide. The second-class disciples, who were gulping down meat, flinched and stopped at the sudden sound. If anyone could open the door so boldly, it had to be an elder…

‘Huh?’

‘Are there any elders who are that young?’

‘As if!’

Surprisingly, the one who opened the door was Chung Myung. The child, who followed the sect leader earlier, entered in anger.

“There’s a place to sit here.”

As Jo Gul slightly raised his hand, Chung Myung bowed to Un Geom and then stomped over to the seat. Those nearby the seat moved away slightly so that he could sit comfortably.

Baek Cheon narrowed his eyes at that sight.

‘They’re taking care of that child?’

Of course, it could happen. If they were polite and good kids.

But the third-class disciples Baek Cheon knew of were quick-witted and violent; the word ‘Good’ didn’t fit well with them.

There was only one reason they would be acting like this.

‘Has that child caught them all in his hand?’

It was unbelievable.

But there was too much visible evidence to deny it. The fact that the seat was left for him, and the seat was in the center, with Yoon Jong and Ju Gul on either side.

Yoon Jong is the Great Sahyung of the third-class disciples, and Jo Gul is the strongest of them.

‘So, he caught them both?’

But how could this child have turned them into his people? And…

‘Why hasn’t Un Geom sasuk said anything?’

It was quite rude to kick the door open. It would be troublesome considering that there were second-class disciples and Un Geom sasuk inside; it would have been appropriate to apologize right away.

Un Geom sasuk greatly values morals and manners, so he would definitely say something. Yet, he was casually eating like he didn’t care.

‘The more I think about it, the less I understand.’

Baek Cheon shook his head. In his eyes, he looked at Chung Myung talking to the others.

“Why are you so angry again?”

“He wants me to go to the Eunha Guild again.”

“… again?”

“Right! I’m not some messenger!”

Yoon Jong grinned at Chung Myung’s complaint.

“But you liked it at first.”

“That was only the first one or two times, ugh.”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

“Fortunately, I only need to visit the branch in Hua-Um. If I had to go to Xian city, I would have fallen dead.”

Seeing Yoon Jong smile and comfort him and Jo Gul chuckle at the side, Baek Cheon became convinced.

‘He has all the third-class disciples in his grasp.’

He wasn’t sure what method was used, but it was certain that Chung Myung had power over them.

‘In many ways.’

Baek Cheon smiled.

Yoon Jong, the Great Sahyung of the third-class disciples, always treated the seniors with respect.

Baek Cheon thought that Yoon Jong would have bowed to someone kind, but Chung Myung didn’t seem to have a kind inclination no matter how Baek Cheon looked at him.

‘I’ll have to find some time to have a conversation with him.’

While Baek Cheon was curious about the third-class disciples.

“Great Sahyung.”

‘Hmm?’

“Aren’t you going to eat?”

“Ah, I will.”

Baek Cheon picked up his chopsticks, but he looked around soon after picking them up.

“Where is Yu Samae?”

“Well? She was here a while ago.”

Two disciples looked around.

“She was there until we came into the dining hall.”

“It seems like she went off somewhere.”

Everyone answered indifferently like this happened a lot. But Baek Cheon didn’t like that response.

“Shouldn’t we look for her? This banquet is for all of us who went training. We should wait until we’re all together to have fun and celebrate.”

“But there is no one who can find Yu Samae. If she doesn’t want to be found, we can’t find her.”

“It’ll be a waste of energy, Great Sahyung.”

Baek Cheon’s forehead scrunched together.

“Umm.”

Those who saw it turned their heads away, feeling uncomfortable and sighing.

Yu Yiseol was a bizarre person; it wasn’t easy to find her unless she wanted to show herself. But since Baek Cheon had this stiff expression, they had to at least pretend to search for her.

‘Sahyung favors Yu Samae too much.’

He was normally a calm person that was fair to others, but he would always lose his composure over any issues involving Yu Yiseol.

‘Well.’

It wasn’t like they couldn’t understand, but it was annoying for them.

At the moment when one of them was about to get up, the shut door opened slowly.

Everyone’s eyes were upon the entrance.

Through the sunlight pouring in through the opened door, a woman walked in with small steps.

“Samae.”

Baek Cheon called.

Yu Yiseol, who came inside, scanned the surroundings as if trying to find someone.

Smiling, Baek Cheon raised his hand.

“Samae, over here….”

Yu Yiseol started to walk, but it was in a direction away from Baek Cheon.

Step! Step!

Yu Yiseol, who walked with a smooth gait, reached her destination and stared intently at the person sitting ahead of her.

Baek Cheon’s eyes twitched.

Yu Yiseol asked the man in front of her,

“Can I sit here?”

The second-class disciples, especially the men, were shocked enough for their eyes to pop out of their sockets.

‘Did Yu Samae talk to a man?’

‘No. When was the last time we even heard her talk?’

But the shock wasn’t over.

The man she spoke to was Chung Myung. He responded with annoyance written all over his face and waved his hand like shooing away a fly.

“No, you can’t.”

“… then let’s talk for a moment.”

Chung Myung firmly answered.

“No. I don’t want to talk to you. Go away.”

Is he crazy?

The color drained from the faces of the second-class disciples as they reeled in shock.

Chapter 77: Rolling Stone Gathers No Moss! (2)

‘What the hell is going on here?’

Jo Gul couldn’t come to his senses.

It was the first time Jo Gul saw her from such a close distance; he wondered if there could be any disciple in Mount Hua who didn’t know of Yu Yiseol.

It wasn’t because Jo Gul was a third-class disciple. He had never even heard of her having a friendly conversation with anyone. Despite being a disciple of Mount Hua, Yu Yiseol was known to keep her distance from others.

But now, she was talking to Chung Myung right in front of him. Soon, the piercing glares of the second-class disciples all stabbed into Chung Myung like razor-sharp daggers.

‘Wow, those eyes could really kill people.’

Well, it was all aimed towards Chung Myung, who was next to Jo Gul. But sitting next to him, it felt inevitable that he would be dragged into the crossfire.

‘Chung Myung, please!’

Be respectful, you bastard!

These are the second-class disciples; what is with that tone?

Despite all that, Chung Myung remained calm. In an atmosphere that felt like something was about to happen, Yu Yiseol whispered softly as if nothing was wrong.

“It’ll only be a minute.”

“I said I’m not interested.”

“But it really will just take a moment.”

“I said no! Don’t you get what I am saying!?”

Watch the way you talk! Speak politely, you bastard!

Jo Gul ended up pressing on Chung Myung’s thighs without realizing it, causing Chung Myung to turn his head toward him.

“What?”

“… Uh…”

You shouldn’t ask that!

Uh… he shouldn’t have asked that in front of his sasuks. He should understand what was happening.

Clicking his tongue, Chung Myung turned his head to Yu Yiseol.

“I have nothing to say or speak about with you.”

“But I have something to tell you.”

“I really don’t want to hear it.”

“It is fine, just one minute. Let’s go outside.”

“No need, can’t you see I’m eating?”

“Then, I’ll wait until you finish.”

The second-class disciples were on the verge of going crazy.

First, they had never seen Yu Yiseol speak so much at once to a younger disciple. No, to be precise, they didn’t remember her ever talking so much with any of the second-class disciples either.

But, didn’t it seem like Yu Yiseol was clinging onto this man?

Right. The second thing that made them agitated was the attitude of Chung Myung.

‘That crazy son of a bitch….!’

‘Nothing is going to happen now, right?’

‘Doesn’t that bastard have eyes?’

‘He has to be a true Taoist.’

Burning anger and subtle respect were poured onto Chung Myung.

As a Taoist who cultivates and walks the path of Dao, the first thing one must do is stay away from worldly desires. However, Yu Yiseol’s existence was one that destroyed that dedication. No matter how well-disciplined a person was, they had no choice but to listen and stray from their path if Yu Yiseol made a request.

Anyone would, seeing her beautiful face and expression.

However, Chung Myung was openly complaining that Yu Yiseol was annoying him. That was unimaginable for the second-class disciples.

“I said no! I have a lot of work to do. Find someone else.”

“I came here for you.”

“No, why would—”

It was then.

“Ahem.”

Although it was low, it was a sound that spread widely after being imbued with qi.

Everyone turned their heads to see Baek Cheon, who steadily got up from his seat and smiled at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung, was it?”

“Yes.”

A short answer.

But Baek Cheon wasn’t angry. In such a situation, showing anger meant that the opponent won.

“I understand that you’re tired from visiting the sect leader and taking on various tasks. You’re likely even doing work that I’m unaware of. However, since your senior is so kindly requesting your time, don’t you think you should hear what she has to say, regardless of how tired you may be?”

Baek Cheon spoke softly to Chung Myung. He thought that it would work out…

“Why?”

Baek Cheon’s hand trembled.

Did he hear wrong?

No? So why did he hear the word ‘why’?

Shocked, Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung’s expression. Seeing that pouty expression, it didn’t seem like he heard it wrong.

Forcing the anger down to calm himself,

‘Be calm.’

If he got angry at a third-class disciple, it would reflect negatively on his character.

“Did you say ‘why’?”

“Yes.”

“There are many reasons. First of all, a person should have manners. There is also a rule which says that you need to respect those above you.”

“Ah, manners?”

As if he understood, Chung Myung nodded and looked at Yu Yiseol.

“Senior.”

“Yes?”

“Apologize quickly. He’s saying that you aren’t behaving politely right now.”

“…”

Yu Yiseol raised a finger, pointing to herself.

“Yes. Apologize.”

“Me?”

“Ugh, you don’t seem to understand at all.”

Chung Myung explained it.

“This is a party to celebrate the return of the second-class disciples. It’s rude to make use of this gathering to sort out your personal affairs and act individually.”

“Ah…”

As if that made sense, Yu Yiseol nodded her head, stood from her seat, and bowed to Baek Cheon.

“I apologize, Sahyung. I didn’t think that far.”

“Ah, no, Samae. That’s not—”

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

Just why did it turn out like this?

And when he tried to open his mouth and manage the situation, Chung Myung spoke again.

“Not to him, you should apologize to Sasuk, since you made a mistake around your senior.”

“You’re right.”

Yu Yiseol bowed her head again towards Un Geom.

“This disciple was short-sighted.”

Un Geom smiled.

“It is fine now that you understand, so sit down.”

“Yes, Sasuk.”

It was Baek Cheon who ended up getting Yu Yiseol into trouble. He couldn’t figure out what to do.

He was flustered… and it was embarrassing to back down without seeing it through to the end. Aren’t the second and third-class disciples looking at Baek Cheon in anticipation of what he would say?

How could he sit back down when so many were watching him? It would turn him into a joke.

He let out a low, empty cough a couple times and looked at Chung Myung.

‘Oh no.’

‘I need to stop him.’

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong looked at each other.

It was hard to beat Chung Myung with a sword, but it was even harder to beat him with words. This guy had no sense of logic. He would resort to all sorts of sophistry and illogical things if it meant winning.

If the conversation continued, Baek Cheon might end up humiliated in front of them. So, Chung Myung had to be stopped.

“Kuahaha! Sasuk! Congratulations on your return!”

“Isn’t today really great? Since the sasuks have returned from training, it looks like we won’t have any problems in the future.”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong desperately tried to switch the topic.

They didn’t mean to defend Chung Myung. It was simply because they didn’t want to see Mount Hua turn into a mess, with Baek Cheon and Chung Myung fighting on their first meeting.

Baek Cheon glanced at the two of them.

Reflected in their desperate gaze, Baek Cheon opened his mouth with narrowed eyes.

“Chung Myung, was it?”

‘Ah what a persistent guy!’

‘I don’t know. I don’t know anything.’

Understanding that it was impossible to stop him, the two reached out and grabbed the hem of Chung Myung’s robe.

Please, just this once. Just this once in your life, behave politely…

Did he understand their earnestness? Chung Myung opened his mouth.

“You must have had a tough time traveling all the way here.”

Oh?

Yoon Jong and Jo Gul were shocked. How long had it been since such pleasantries came out of Chung Myung’s mouth…?

“You keep asking the same thing over and over. Do you need to go rest?”

… ehh, as if his character could change overnight.

Damn that consistent bastard!

Baek Cheon’s eyebrows twitched.

“I will ask once again. Are you certain that we haven’t met before?”

“Nope, I’ve never seen you before.”

“It will be better if you answer honestly.”

“Hey, I already told you that we’ve never met. Do you think I would deceive you?”

Looking at his glistening eyes, no one would think he was lying.

Except for the third-class disciples.

And Un Geom.

Uh… the second-class disciples might also doubt him. Uh… Hm.

“Really? I’ll know if I ask.”

Baek Cheon turned towards Un Geom. He didn’t want to do this, but this was the only way he could regain the upper hand.

“Sasuk. I saw that child in the morning, drinking alcohol at a restaurant in Hua-Um.”

Un Geom’s eyes twitched.

“Really?”

“Yes. As far as I know, it is forbidden for the third-class disciples to leave Mount Hua. However, it is definitely unforgivable for them to leave behind their uniform and travel in plain apparel down to—”

“It is fine.”

“Yes, I saw… huh?”

Baek Cheon, who bowed his head with clasped hands, lifted his head.

Did he hear it wrong again?

No, what was up with his ears? He keeps hearing the strangest answers…

“I said, it is fine.”

Baek Cheon looked at Un Geom with a shocked face.

Un Geom was a man who valued manners and discipline above all else. He wasn’t strict simply because he was head of the White Plum Blossom boarding house; his strict personality, which was sensitive to the rules, made him the head of the dorms.

And such a person said that it was fine for a third-class disciple to go down Mount Hua even if it was against the rules?

“S-sasuk?”

“That child is allowed to go down Mount Hua without asking for permission.”

“Uh, permission? Who would give a child such permission?”

“The sect leader granted it to him. Have you got an issue with that?”

“S-sect… leader? Really?”

He was so shocked that he had covered his mouth with both his hands. Hearing the tone of Sasuk’s voice, he knew that asking again would be crossing the line. Somehow, Baek Cheon seemed to be getting off on the wrong foot with everyone today.

“It doesn’t matter.”

Baek Cheon turned to Chung Myung with a shocked gaze.

Nom-nom-nom-nom.

“…”

Chung Myung was quickly moving his chopsticks and inhaling food as if he had no interest in what was happening. Baek Cheon would have been less angry if the child at least looked at him with a sneer, but this indifference was infuriating.

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

‘I’ll see this through to the end!’

He had no intention of backing down.

Baek Cheon opened his mouth again, but then a man came in through the entrance.

It was the finance head, Hyun Young, wearing his usual cold expression. He strode in and looked around.

“We greet the elder.”

“We greet the elder.”

When everyone stood and greeted him, he just waved his hand as if it was annoying.

“Right. Continue having a good time, I shouldn’t have come. I am only here to check it out. Everyone, eat as much as you want and rest in peace. I am leaving. Un Geom, be sure to keep an eye on them so they don’t play too much.”

“Yes. Sasuk.”

Baek Cheon, who was still standing, spoke.

“I have something to say to the elder.”

Hyun Young, who was about to walk out, turned and looked at him.

“What is it?”

“I apologize, but I saw a third-class disciple drinking alcohol down the Hua-Um today.”

“Alcohol?”

“Yes!”

Hyun Young’s face contorted.

“A third-class disciple drinking!? Are you sure you saw it with your own eyes?”

“Definitely. He denies that it was him, but I surely saw correctly.”

Baek Cheon slightly covered his face to hide the smile under his hands.

It might seem impolite, but that child was the one who provoked him first. So, he had to resort to something like this.

“Who is the disciple you saw?”

Baek Cheon turned to Chung Myung. He was pretending to be calm, but Baek Cheon was sure that Chung Myung was dying inside.

‘Don’t blame me for this.’

This is to set the rules straight in Mount Hua.

“The third-class disciple, Chung Myung.”

“… Who?”

“Chung Myung. That one over there.”

When it comes to the elders, they couldn’t know each of the third-class disciples by name, so Baek Cheon pointed to the child.

Hyun Young, who looked at Chung Myung, frowned. Then, opened his mouth in irritation with anger rising up.

“What about it?”

“Yes. That Chung Myung drank… huh?”

“What about it?”

“…”

What?

Chapter 78: Rolling Stone Gathers No Moss! (3)

“E-elder?”

Baek Cheon stared in stupefaction while Hyun Young looked at him with dissatisfaction.

‘Did I say something wrong?’

Baek Cheon rushed to clarify and repair this situation.

“It’s wrong for a third-class disciple to go down to Hua-Um village and drink alcohol. Although the child was given the authority, by the sect leader, to descend at will, was he given permission to drink alcohol too? I don’t think he understands what he did.”

Hyun Young’s face twisted again.

‘He seems to have understood it clearly this time.’

And immediately…

“You’re someone who doesn’t understand words.”

“…. What?”

Hyun Young spoke without even trying to hide his anger.

“Did you set the rules for Mount Hua?”

“H-How could I?”

“Then was there any rule in Mount Hua that prohibits one from drinking when they’re outside the sect?”

“…”

Baek Cheon couldn’t bring himself to answer that question.

No, there was no such rule.

After all, what kind of sect would create a rule that forbids drinking?

But a Taoist should have a sense of propriety!

“And.”

Hyun Young looked at Baek Cheon.

“What about it?”

“… Elder?”

“What’s wrong with having a couple drinks?”

“…”

Why did it seem like Hyun Young’s face kept growing redder and angrier?

That wasn’t all.

Eventually, Hyun Young’s face turned beet red as he pointed at Baek Cheon.

“There are so many bastards who can’t even pay for what they eat here! But the guy who feeds you, goes out and has some alcohol with his own money!? Huh? What do you think you are!? Do you think you can abuse your privilege as sasuk to torment him!?”

‘What? S-sasuk?’

“You’re eating meat with the money he earned! Now, he goes down and wants to have a drink with the money he saved up! But you can’t stand it, so you come to me to snitch on him!?”

Baek Cheon floundered with a stiff face.

It was difficult to understand; why was Hyun Young cursing at him? Was this really just for saying that he saw a third-class disciple drinking?

Is this really elder Hyun Young? Supposedly, he was meant to join the North Sea Ice Palace but ended up in Mount Hua, unable to fully demonstrate his skills. However, he was always known to be calm and cold; is this really the same man?

Seeing Hyung Young, wide-eyed and yelling, it was hard to tell if this was a dream or not.

“If you’re really so bothered by it, go down to Hua-Um and make some money… but no! You sit around gaining a reputation just for being a disciple and use your privilege as sasuk to bully him! Swinging swords and meditating all day isn’t going to bring any money or food to the table! Your mind! Use your mind and do something worthwhile! Should I open that head of yours and make something useful out of you!? What did you people even do to earn the meat on the tabl—”

Bang!

At that moment, someone violently slammed the door and entered.

“Hahaha! Here you are!”

A very strangely smiling face appeared as Hyun Sang covered the mouth of Hyun Young from behind.

“Eup! Eup! Eup!… let go of… eup!”

“Haha. Let’s go outside for a while. To a place away from the kids. Ah, stay still!”

Tah!

The sound of the door closing left the dining hall with a strange silence. No one could open their mouths.

Nom-nom-nom-nom.

In that awkward silence, there was only one sound they could hear, the sound of something being eaten.

“What…”

Baek Cheon mumbled.

“Just what happened here?”

It was a statement that represented the feelings of all the second-class disciples.

–

“Isn’t it too strange? Sahyung?”

Despite the question being directed at him, Baek Cheon just silently set down the teacup in his hand. It was an old teacup that he had been using for a long time. Before he went into closed-door training, he thought that this cup had its own charm. But looking at it now, it seemed more pathetic than elegant.

After all, this was the true state of Mount Hua.

Old furniture, old buildings, and old people.

The only hope of the worn-out sect were the disciples, and among them, their greatest hope was Baek Cheon.

However, Baek Cheon returned after a year away, and now his ‘hope’ seemed irrelevant to them.

“It’s strange that new buildings were suddenly built, and it’s strange that areas of the sect which were neglected for over a decade are repaired, no… I mean, that’s a good thing. We couldn’t do any of it before because the sect didn’t have the funds. But!”

Baek Sang spoke in a strong tone, unable to hold back his anger.

“Isn’t the behavior of the elders too strange? We came back from such a long and arduous training, but the sect leader didn’t say much.”

“Didn’t the sect leader praise you enough for your effort?”

“Still, it’s been a year since we’ve been away….”

“He is a man who is eager for change.”

Baek Sang bowed his head slightly. Thinking about it, the sect leader really didn’t say much. But it didn’t make sense to call him out like that.

“Sect leader could be fine, but wasn’t Elder Hyun Young or even Un Geom Sasuk acting the same?”

Baek Cheon didn’t respond. No matter what anyone said, it was truly bizarre. It wasn’t like they were dissatisfied with their elders, but their treatment was strange.

“Didn’t you feel it? The elders were all taking that child’s side.”

“Baek Sang.”

“Yes, Sahyung!”

“I am not that ignorant.”

“…”

How could he not understand when he was cursed and yelled at, right to his face?

“Sahyung. That kid, he is quite cocky, isn’t he?”

“Hmm?”

“Even if the elders take his side, shouldn’t he at least bow his head when we, his direct seniors, come back? But that one….”

Baek Sang went silent after that.

If only that child had sneered or laughed at them, they could have called him out properly, but they couldn’t do anything about his indifference.

“Phew.”

Baek Cheon narrowed his eyes.

“And I don’t understand why Yu Samae is so interested in him. Why, just why….”

A small ripple occurred in Baek Cheon’s teacup as his hand lightly trembled.

“It could be that Yu Samae had some reason.”

“But she barely speaks with us. I’ve never seen her talk so actively with anyone until now, and it isn’t like we’ve only spent one or two days with her, right?”

“…”

“Leaving us aside, at least Sahyung—”

“Baek Sang.”

“—Yes, Sahyung.”

“Don’t get too angry.”

Baek Sang bowed his head and glanced at Baek Cheon’s eyes.

Baek Cheon tried to manage his expression, but it was inevitable that he would show a bit of how uncomfortable he felt. His eyes kept twitching, and he struggled to hold back a frown.

‘I lost to that young boy.’

Not even a full saint or an elder?

The difference of level between disciples within sects like Mount Hua is akin to heaven and earth. Just like how the Baek disciples couldn’t speak against the Un disciples, Chung Myung also shouldn’t be able to speak against them.

‘Cheeky bastard.’

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

At that moment, Baek Sang, who bowed, continued.

“I apologize. It’s just unfair. We returned after such difficult training, but the elders didn’t recognize our efforts; and that snake-like bastard, who appeared out of nowhere, is taking over the sect by playing cute with the elders, right?”

“The time where we could play cute with the elders has already passed.”

“You know that’s not what I meant.”

He knew. He knew it too well.

Baek Cheon let out a low sigh.

‘It’s a feeling of subtly being taken over.’

Were they away for too long?

In the past, as soon as they returned, the adults would have greeted them warmly and then come to visit Baek Cheon later. Now, they barely showed interest in him.

Instead, they were all looking for Chung Myung.

Baek Cheon was unhappy over the sudden change in status.

He didn’t know what Chung Myung did to have such great expectations from the elders and receive their protection, but Mount Hua was his sect.

Baek Cheon was the only one who received the expectations of Mount Hua’s elders, and he had to be the guiding light that would return the sect to brilliance.

“Are you going to leave him like this?”

“What more can we do?”

“… shouldn’t we at least beat it into him or discipline him? If we leave it as it is, Mount Hua will be a mess. Sahyung should establish order and set him right.”

Baek Cheon smiled bitterly.

He didn’t like when his juniors talked back to him, but he wasn’t the kind to beat sense into others.

“Calm down for now.”

“Sahyung!”

Baek Sang raised his voice which made Baek Cheon frown. Seeing that, Baek Sang sighed and lowered his eyes.

Seeing that reaction, Baek Cheon nodded with a satisfied face.

“It’s not that I don’t want to.”

“Then why…”

“There are things we need to know first.”

“Huh?”

Baek Cheon shook his head and set the teacup down.

“There is a proper order we must follow. Don’t you think it’s necessary to know why the elders are all fawning over that child?”

“Ah, right. We should do that.”

“He’s coming.”

“Who?”

As soon as Baek Cheon finished, someone knocked on the door.

“Come in.”

Kik.

With the sound of the door opening, the person who entered bowed.

“Disciple Yoon Jong is here.”

“Welcome.”

Baek Cheon pointed ahead of him.

“Sit down.”

“Yes, Sasuk.”

Yoon Jong cautiously sat down. He couldn’t be sure if he should sit or not despite the offer.

Baek Cheon liked Yoon Jong’s attitude.

‘This is how things should be.’

Not behaving like that other bastard.

Baek Cheon, who was relaxed, spoke in a soft voice.

“Yoon Jong.”

“Yes, sasuk.”

“While I was away, you must have had a hard time trying to serve the elders and handle the disciples.”

“I just did what I was supposed to do as a disciple of Mount Hua.”

“Yes, you’re right. That is a natural action. But…”

Baek Cheon paused for a moment, which made Yoon Jong lift his head to examine his expression, and then the expected words followed.

“It seems like strange things are happening in Mount Hua right now.”

“… are you talking about Chung Myung?”

Baek Cheon didn’t respond, but Yoon Jong knew what he aimed for.

“It is my fault for not leading that sajae properly. If you are angry, please punish me, sasuk.”

“No, it’s not something you could handle. What I am saying is…”

Baek Cheon smiled.

“Tell me all of what happened while I was away. I’ll listen to your story and decide what to do next.”

Yoon Jong sighed deeply.

‘It’s natural for me to explain this to Sasuk, but it feels like I’m betraying Chung Myung.’

Before coming here, Yoon Jong had already told Chung Myung. He asked if he could tell everything to the sasuk who called him. And Chung Myung’s answer was simple.

- Go.

“…”

It would have been nice if he had given some instructions.

Yoon Jong glanced at Baek Cheon for a moment and then spoke.

“First, I think I should begin from the time Chung Myung entered Mount Hua.”

As Yoon Jong began to slowly unravel his story, the disciples listened to him with bated breath.

And as the story continued, Baek Cheon’s face gradually distorted more and more.

Chapter 79: Rolling Stone Gathers No Moss! (4)

Once the story was complete, no one spoke.

Everyone looked at Yoon Jong’s face with a serious expression, like they had fallen into trouble.

It was Baek Cheon that broke the long silence.

“So, that child….”

“Yes, Sasuk.”

“Discovered the treasure and lost martial arts books of the sect.”

“Yes.”

“And found a ledger which brought to light the affairs of the businesses under Mount Hua and helped confiscate back the businesses?”

“Right.”

“In addition, he even cured the illness of the Eunha Merchant Guild’s Elder Hwang?”

“Yes.”

“In return, Eunha offered to take care of Mount Hua’s finances… and Hua-Um.”

Yoon Jong nodded without saying a word.

Thinking back, it was strange. Hua-Um had a life that didn’t exist when they first left for their training.

Since they were away from Mount Hua for so long, he just assumed that Hua-Um had improved greatly during their time away, but that wasn’t it.

“… right.”

Baek Cheon opened his mouth but closed it again.

“I get it.”

“Yes, Sasuk. Then, I’ll take my leave.”

“Alright.”

As Yoon Jong left the room, Baek Cheon had a serious look on his face; and the others in the room also had sullen expressions.

“No, just what….”

Baek Sang opened his mouth, feeling frustrated and despondent.

“Then, doesn’t this mean that one child solved all of Mount Hua’s problems by himself?”

“…”

Shock and consternation could be heard in this disciple’s voice.

Baek Cheon couldn’t even respond.

The biggest problem with Mount Hua was neither their martial arts nor the small number of disciples. Mount Hua collapsed so quickly because they lacked the money to support themselves.

‘It wasn’t just that they didn’t have money.’

There was an enormous debt.

When he left for training, Baek Cheon’s greatest worry was returning after a year only to find the sect abandoned and destroyed.

But Chung Myung solved this issue.

“It’s understandable why the elders like him.”

Baek Sang laughed in self-derision at Baek Cheon’s words.

“Hearing elder Hyun Young yell at everyone about eating meat from that child’s money, I thought he was the child of a great merchant, and that he was giving Mount Hua a lot of money. but this…”

He was literally feeding Mount Hua.

Baek Cheon shook his head.

‘There’s no answer to solve this problem.’

If Baek Cheon was in Hyun Young’s position, he would have defended Chung Myung himself. That was how significant Chung Myung’s contribution was. He was a child that raised money like a god of fortune and solved all of Mount Hua’s financial woes, even the problems which persisted for decades with no resolution in sight.

It’s a good thing Hyun Young didn’t have children. If his child got into an argument with Chung Myung, his house would be a mess if he kept taking Chung Myung’s side.

He could always have another kid, but where in this world would he find another person like Chung Myung?

“… Sahyung, this…”

“Umm.”

Baek Cheon racked his mind, thinking heavily.

“If he had only solved one of the sect’s problems it would have ended with ‘he made a contribution’. But that child is intertwined with the Eunha Guild. As long as he has a connection with Eunha, which manages Mount Hua’s finances, and Mount Hua makes money from that relationship, Chung Myung’s position will continue to rise.”

At least for the foreseeable future.

“… but at some point, wouldn’t his importance settle as the sect grows?”

“Right. But will that moment come soon? As you know, this is all….”

Gold falling into a beggar’s lap.

It was good to see and good to touch. Even if it wasn’t used right away, wouldn’t you be happy just to possess it?

Chung Myung was the one who gave gold to the beggar known as Mount Hua. No matter how hard Baek Cheon tried, he couldn’t achieve anything like this.

‘I can see why the sect leader would meet with that child alone.’

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

When he returned from training, he thought that he would receive looks of adoration and approval from all the elders, but a guy who popped out of nowhere stole away the spotlight and received all of the elders’ expectations that should have belonged to Baek Cheon.

It was an issue that couldn’t be ignored.

“Is it really such a big deal?”

Baek Mun, who only listened to the conversation till then, spoke.

“The discovery of Mount Hua’s treasure was just a coincidence, and wasn’t it pure luck that he treated elder Hwang?”

“Sajae.”

“Sahyung, Mount Hua is a martial arts sect. It is unacceptable that the sect is giving preference to a child simply because he brought money into the sect. How can the others all encourage it and forget the values of Mount Hua?”

Baek Cheon slammed the table. And spoke.

“Sajae, you should choose your words very carefully. What you said is an insult to the elders and sasuks.”

“… that wasn’t my intention.”

“But you aren’t necessarily wrong.”

“Yes?”

Baek Chen calmly nodded his head.

“You are right. Mount Hua does seem unfamiliar now. No matter how much money is made, we must focus on our martial arts in order to truly restore the sect.”

“You’re right.”

“That’s true.”

Baek Cheon nodded at their responses.

“In the end, we have no choice but to get back to the basics. Now, the elders might be interested in him because of his contributions, but once they realize that the conference is approaching, there is no way that they’ll be able to pay attention to the third-class disciples.”

“Yes, sahyung. You’re right.”

“So, for now let’s focus on ourselves. We can fix that child’s attitude afterwards.”

Baek Sang glanced at Baek Cheon.

“But Sahyung.”

“What?”

“We aren’t going to be the only ones to participate in the conference. The third-class disciples will also be included in it.”

“Is there anyone here who doesn’t know that?”

“We can’t be the only ones working hard. Shouldn’t we also help prevent the third-class disciples from being humiliated?”

At that point, Baek Cheon looked with interest at Baek Sang.

“What do you think, Sajae?”

“If we’re only thinking about ourselves, then it would be fine for us to focus on our own training. However, as seniors to the third-class disciples, how can we forget to assist them? Even if it’s a bit troublesome, we should take care of our juniors. It might even help us out in the conference as well.”

Baek Cheon grinned.

“As expected, Sajae cares about everyone in Mount Hua more than anyone else.”

“I am embarrassed, Sahyung.”

“I think it’s a good idea. We must have gotten alienated from them since we were away for a year, so it wouldn’t be a bad idea to sweat together for a while.”

“Yes, Sahyung. That sounds like a good plan.”

Baek Cheon and Baek Sang smiled at each other.

In the end, dignity comes from strength. A gentle person is respected, but respect only goes so far.

Even in a family, authority is necessary. If left as it is, a day will come when the third-class disciples run amok without regard for their seniors.

Before that, they had to be put in place.

Teach them why the sasuks were adults and why the third-class disciples must bow their heads.

“I hope that child, Chung Myung, has a talent for martial arts. Then, wouldn’t Mount Hua have one more capable person to lead the future generation?”

“The person who will lead the future generation is you, Sahyung.”

“I cannot lead forever. It would be for the best if there was a smart child who followed my commands.”

Baek Cheon smiled.

“It looked like he couldn’t even walk properly, is there any hope for that child to have talent in martial arts?”

Baek Mun said while shrugging his shoulders.

“Shouldn’t that be why we teach and lead the juniors? Though it might be a little daunting for Chung Myung.”

“I understand.”

The three of them smiled happily at one another.

‘I need to teach you to properly appreciate the dignity of your superiors.’

Baek Cheon’s cold eyes smirked as well.

“Are you sleeping?”

“Uh.”

“Ugh, I was dragged to Sasuk’s room because of you, and you’re lying down so comfortably?”

Yoon Jong’s face tensed up.

‘I shouldn’t bother….’

He had no intention of asking Chung Myung to be polite to him; he threw away such notions on the evening that Chung Myung joined the sect.

Nevertheless, he felt emotional after seeing the Baek disciples treat Baek Cheon with such respect.

‘That’s how sects are supposed to be.’

Seeing how Baek Cheon was revered, Yoon Jong felt like crying.

‘There was a time when I was treated like that.’

After a certain person arrived, everything changed. Bad habits are easy to learn but hard to correct…

“What are you thinking about, Sahyung?”

“… nothing.”

This one is the problem! This guy!

There was some respect shown for Yoon Jong in the past, but now Jo Gul treats him like some neighborhood brother!

Yoon Jong took a deep breath and looked at Jo Gul.

“Gul.”

“Yes.”

“Is it really a good thing that Chung Myung came to Mount Hua?”

“Don’t talk about strange things. Did something happen?”

‘Is that any way for a junior to speak to their senior?’

Ugh…

In the end, Yoon Jong decided to let go of everything and glanced at Chung Myung, who was lying on the bed, before opening his mouth.

“Senior asked me to tell him what he has been up to so far.”

“And so, did you decide to snitch?”

“… what’s the point of hiding it?”

“That’s true.”

They were going to find out eventually anyway.

“And the reaction?”

“Are you asking because you really don’t know?”

“… I guess it’s obvious.”

Yoon Jong and Jo Gul sighed. Seeing Chung Myung still lying on the bed tapping his stomach, they couldn’t help it.

‘Crazy bastard.’

‘Good for nothing bastard.’

Anyway, Baek Cheon wasn’t their sahyung; he was their sasuk. How could Chung Myung even think about provoking someone so senior to them on their first meeting?

Baek Cheon wasn’t strict with the third-class disciples. However, if the relationship goes sour, there is no way to know what the future will hold.

“Well, it won’t be good.”

No one in the world can crush Chung Myung. Didn’t Yoon Jong and Jo Gul also get defeated by him?

Fortunately, they were able to make the most of their situation. However, if Baek Cheon tries his luck and decides to trample on Chung Myung, then the situation could erupt into an even bigger mess.

“Well, arrows are going to fall on us.”

“I know.”

Once again, Yoon Jong sighed and looked at Jo Gul.

“We should have assumed this would happen when we learned that the sasuks were returning.”

“Right.”

“Call the others and tell them to be careful of their behavior from tomorrow on. Even if it’s nothing special, if they find something to nitpick, I’m sure they won’t let us off easily.”

“Yes, I get it.”

Jo Gul readied himself to leave with that response, but then he stopped and glanced at Yoon Jong.

“But Sahyung.”

“Yes?”

“I am curious about something….”

“About what?”

“If Baek Cheon sasuk and Chung Myung fought, who would win?”

“… don’t think about such ridiculous things and do what you are told.”

“Tch.”

Jo Gul clicked his tongue and went out.

Left in Chung Myung’s room, Yoon Jong glanced at the owner of the room, who was still dreaming soundly.

‘Who would win?’

Was he asking because he really didn’t know?

“… sleep well. Troublemaker.”

Now, the peace in Mount Hua was finally shattered. In the future, there will be a lot of commotion.

Chung Myung continued to sleep peacefully; his face seemed absent of any care or concerns in the world. Looking down at him, Yoon Jong sighed before walking out of the room with a subtle smile.

Chapter 80: Rolling Stone Gathers No Moss! (5)

“Listen.”

“Yes. Sect leader.”

Un Geom reached out and took a teacup.

Plum tea, made by drying plum petals, is one of the things that Hyun Jong is most proud of. Bringing that tea out meant there was quite a lot to talk about today.

“How is it?”

Before Un Geom answered, he glanced at Un Am. He was checking whether it was fine to speak in the presence of others. Hyun Jong, who took the tea, recognized this and said.

“It is fine.”

“Yes, then.”

Un Geom opened his mouth.

“As the sect leader said, I didn’t intervene. And…”

“And?”

“There seems to be a bit of a problem.”

“Hmm.”

Hyun Jong nodded at it.

“The atmosphere would have turned sour if Hyun Young sasuk hadn’t arrived when he did. As the sect leader said, there are subtle sparks flowing between the second and third-class disciples.”

“I see.”

Hyun Jong sighed.

This happened because of their decision.

‘I was in a hurry.’

The difference between the Un disciples and the Baek disciples was too great, and the difference between the Baek and the Chung disciples was too close. As a result, the youngest of the Baek disciples, Yu Yiseol, was almost the same age as Yoon Jong, the oldest of the Chung disciples.

Given that it was customary to have a few years difference between any group of disciples, it was apparent that this problem would explode at some point.

‘It was inevitable.’

When they received the third-class disciples, Mount Hua couldn’t actually afford to accept any new disciples. At that time, the sect’s finances were dwindling to a dangerous low. It had grown so severe that new students were barred from joining.

Then, someone suggested the idea of getting support from the disciples’ families in return for allowing their children to join the sect. That was the beginning of the problem.

With Mount Hua desperately struggling to hold together their crumbling foundations, it was necessary to gather funds by any means available to them.

However, even if they had fallen from grace, Mount Hua was still a prestigious sect. They tried to be selective of who they accepted, but for the sake of the disciples who would grow up within the sect, they took the disciples of families who offered support without question.

As a result, Chung disciples are somewhat lacking in martial arts talent.

“In the past, the Chung disciples wouldn’t have dared to act against the Baek disciples. But aren’t the Chung disciples now different from what they were?”

“Yes.”

Did they have a central figure? Didn’t that figure change?

A seemingly meaningless change began to ripple out and influence much more than expected. A single individual’s existence was affecting not only their group but also the relations between other groups.

With Yoon Jong and Jo Gul as the center of the Chung disciples, they barely passed as third-class disciples of Mount Hua. However, now the third-class disciples were gathered around Chung Myung, who isn’t satisfied with merely passing but wants excellent results.

People who are twenty years apart don’t see each other as competition, but those who are ten years apart, or even less, have no choice but to be conscious of each other.

“It’s my fault.”

As Un Geom bowed his head, Hyun Jong firmly shook his head.

“It isn’t your fault.”

“Sect leader…”

“I was the one who insisted that you be the head of the White Plum Blossom Boarding Hall. Didn’t everyone agree at the time? In the first place, this is something we all predicted when we started receiving the third-class disciples ahead of schedule.”

These words weren’t just meant to comfort Un Geom.

Mount Hua benefited a lot after creating the White Plum Blossom Dorms. But where there is something to gain, there is something to lose.

In the past, no junior would dare to skip the formalities with their seniors, regardless of the age difference.

However, the third-class disciples never received anything from the second-class disciples. They were taught by Un Geom and trained together with their comrades. Naturally, the distance between the two groups was bound to widen.

That was the biggest weakness of the White Plum Blossom Boarding Hall.

Un Geom glanced at Hyun Jong and asked.

“Sect leader. What do you believe we should do?”

Hyun Jong savored the plum tea without saying a word. It felt calming to him, smelling the subtle scent wafting through the air.

“What can we do?”

“But leaving it like this….”

“People are always like that. Would their hearts be satisfied if we intervene and forcefully lead the situation? Sometimes, it isn’t wrong to let the disciples clash with each other and learn from their disagreements.”

“Sect leader, this is about our disciples.”

“If you put your mind to it, you could even change the direction of a river. But if you force the stream to turn, even if it seems plausible at first, there will be problems that arise farther down the flow.”

Hyun Jong said with a smile.

“Un Geom.”

“Yes, Sect Leader.”

“Let’s trust our children.”

“…”

Un Geom looked at Hyun Jong with a complicated expression. The expression said he had doubts about this.

At that time, Hyun Jong spoke about a different topic than Un Geom expected.

“Baek Cheon isn’t that kind of problem child.”

“Huh?”

“Don’t you think so too?”

Un Geom’s face went stiff.

‘No, it isn’t him, sect leader!’

Baek Cheon isn’t the problem. Sect leader! The problem is Chung Myung!

Only then did Un Geom realize that there was a huge gap in the way that the other elders saw Chung Myung compared to him.

The head of the White Plum Blossom dorms, Un Geom, saw Chung Myung up close as he controlled the third-class disciples. However, Hyun Jong and other elders only saw him as an adorable little puppy that brought blessings to Mount Hua!

“Isn’t Baek Cheon a careful and upright child? Even if his pride gets damaged and he loses himself to a moment of anger, he isn’t the sort of person to harm a child because of it.”

Pardon?

Who will hurt whom?

Baek Cheon will hurt Chung Myung?

‘This is crazy.’

Somehow, the sect leader was too naïve!

However, explaining it seemed impossible. No, even if he could explain, the sect leader wouldn’t believe it.

In fact, Un Geom doesn’t fully understand Chung Myung himself. The way that the sect leader saw Chung Myung was miles apart from how Un Geom viewed him; how could he possibly convince Hyun Jong?

“… yes, I understand. Sect leader.”

In the end, Un Geom had no choice but to silently leave.

“Un Geom.”

“Yes, Sect Leader.”

“There isn’t much time left before the conference.”

As soon as the word ‘conference’ came out, Un Geom’s face darkened.

To be honest, the disciples of Mount Hua didn’t have any negative feelings towards the Southern Edge Sect in the past. In the first place, Mount Hua’s feelings for the Southern Edge sect had stemmed from a competitive spirit.

But isn’t competition inherently between people who are similar and not too different? The gap between Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect was like Heaven and Earth. No one had the burning spirit necessary to take down the Southern Edge Sect.

But, even if there was no motivation in this competition, who would want to see their disciples get beat up by the other side?

For the youngest children, the difference between them isn’t too great, and the loss is not too humiliating. However, the difference more than doubles when the older disciples take center stage, and it only grows farther when those who trained directly under an elder appear.

“We’ve solved many problems. But the most important problem hasn’t been solved yet. We are only at the beginning, and we need to recreate the splendid glory of Mount Hua.”

“I’ll keep that in mind, Sect Leader.”

“Right. Both of you can leave.”

“Yes.”

“Yes.”

As Un Geom and Un Am left, Hyun Jong got up from his seat and opened the window at the back of his room, so he could see the peaks with melted snow.

There were small flower buds on the plum tree that had grown fast. By the time the conference begins, spring plum blossoms would likely bloom all over the mountain.

‘Plum Blossom… Plum Blossoms.’

The Seven Sages Sword is back.

However, Hyun Jong was keenly aware of the fact that it was impossible to reproduce their past glory with just one sword art.

‘Perhaps if we still had the Plum Blossom Sword technique.’

Hyun Jong tightly shut his eyes.

He knew that dwelling on what was lost in the past wouldn’t bring about a change. This wasn’t the time to search for what they lacked; it was time to reinforce what they had.

Even so, regret lingered in the corner of his heart.

“Oh ancestors. Look down on Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong was still unaware that an ancestor had already descended on Mount Hua.

Unfortunately, Hyun Jong made two mistakes.

One was that he thought Chung Myung was a good child.

But from Mount Hua’s point of view, it wasn’t a large issue. Chung Myung’s ultimate goal was to help grow Mount Hua. The more Hyun Jong favored Chung Myung, the wider his activities could be.

It wasn’t intentional, but thanks to Hyun Jong giving preferential treatment to Chung Myung, Mount Hua was developing faster.

But the other mistake was more fatal…

Baek Cheon was not as mild-mannered or gentle as Hyun Jong thought.

“Anything…”

“…”

“… Need food.”

“…”

The third-class disciples huddled together in their boarding hall had shocking faces.

Chung Myung’s practice left the disciples completely drained. He could somehow gauge the strength remaining in each and every disciple and would cruelly use that information to push them to their absolute limits, squeezing out every last drop of sweat from their bodies.

Therefore, after everyone was done training, they would come back with stiff faces and sunken cheeks.

Surprisingly, however, no third-class disciples expressed dissatisfaction from the harsh training.

Of course, they felt like they would die each time they practiced under him, but weren’t humans known to be adaptable?

After this terrible training was repeated for over a week, it somehow became more bearable. They’ve developed so much that even when they stumble into the underworld and lock eyes with that villainous Death, they turn their backs on the Grim Reaper and return on their own.

- The more that iron is beaten, the stronger it becomes, and the more a man gets beaten, the stronger he returns! Moss doesn’t gather on a man that’s been beaten.

‘Moss doesn’t normally grow on people anyway! You madman!’

Even worse was that the third-class disciples could see that Chung Myung was right. They could feel their bodies changing day by day.

Now they understood what it meant to have a ‘fit body.’

But

The problem was that a new calamity struck the third-class disciples, who believed that they could overcome anything if they just followed Chung Myung’s training routine.

“…I think I’m going to die.”

“Uh… the sasuks are seriously….”

“Isn’t it getting worse each time?”

The Baek disciples were tormenting them.

That day,

After Chung Myung and Baek Cheon confronted each other, they began skillfully bullying the third-class disciples. It was clear that they were deliberately harassing them on each occasion.

“Why are they doing that?”

“Do you even need to ask?”

“Ugh.”

All eyes turned to the same location, and the one at the end of the gaze was,

“Huh?”

Chung Myung, who received their gazes, just tilted his head.

“Why are you looking at me?”

“…”

“…”

This bastard was definitely born without a conscience.

Chapter 81: Fight? You are so done now (1)

“They told me that when I walk on the mountain, I need to keep my knees straight.”

“I was told that if I wanted to get some water to drink, I needed to ask them for permission first.”

“Ah fuck. They’re acting so cheap and dirty.”

The second-class disciples tormented the third-class disciples in any way they could imagine.

Every time they trained, they would nitpick the tiniest details and make all sorts of new rules to torment them.

Today, even though their boarding house was clean, the second-class disciples demanded they clean it until not a speck of dust could be found.

“I’d rather take a beating.”

Jo Gul grunted.

He was someone accustomed to bullying others with his fists, so he couldn’t get used to this kind of abuse.

“I never imagined that the second-class disciples were such people.”

“I respected them!”

“We aren’t in some neighborhood brawl, are their actions even acceptable?”

Yoon Jong sighed.

‘There’s nothing that says they can’t do this.’

There was no doubt that the second-class disciples were harassing them. The malice and ridicule being directed at the third-class disciple were evident.

Despite that, their actions couldn’t be criticized. In the first place, everything that the second-class disciples demanded of the third-class disciples was rules and norms set forth by Mount Hua.

Then what was the problem?

‘Because such rules were established at least two hundred years ago.’

Inherently, old rules are modified and changed according to the current times.

But Mount Hua never did that.

Therefore, it was decided that the sect would pick and choose which rules to follow according to the times while ignoring the ones that were out of date.

However, the second-class disciples used such archaic rules to attack and control the third-class disciples.

Leaving everything else aside, the biggest problem was that there were common rules which gave the older ones the power to rule.

“No, they said Mount Hua’s disciples should never let go of their sword. Do they want us to hold our swords even when we’re bathing or doing laundry? What about when we use the bathroom!?”

“… I was told to hold it in hand even when I eat.”

“And hold it while sleeping!”

“What nonsense is that? Are we supposed to memorize every rule our ancestors came up with throughout all of Mount Hua’s history!?”

“… they don’t even know all of them.”

“That’s what I am saying!”

The third-class disciples gnashed their teeth.

It felt as if their nerves were going to split in anger because of this absurd abuse of power like their lives were shortening each time the second-class disciples approached them.

“I can’t even eat or sleep properly!”

“They gather us just because they’re bored, and they blame everyone and swear at us even if only one person made a mistake.”

“What the hell are they trying to achieve?”

“Ugh! Can’t we do something about this?”

Yoon Jong sighed.

“What can we do?”

“Isn’t this a bit harsh? To be honest, they aren’t even hiding that they’re bullying us, they are clearly crossing the line.”

“Right! I can tolerate anything else, but I can’t stand them disturbing our training time! Anyway, this is a martial sect, how can they dare to interfere with our practice!?”

The third-class disciples had bloodshot eyes.

Actually, until now, the second and third-class disciples had no reason to fight. The second-class disciples were too busy with their own training, and the third-class disciples would learn from Un Geom in the White Plum Blossom dorms. They had very little interaction with each other.

Still, before all of this happened. The third-class disciples felt a sense of admiration and longing towards the second-class disciples. But now that the seniors turned against their juniors like this, they were feeling an indescribable sense of betrayal.

Yoon Jong turned his head to the culprit behind this.

He looked at Chung Myung, who was leaning on a chair and said

“Chung Myung.”

“Huh?”

“… shouldn’t we do something?”

“About?”

“Sasuk, sasuks!”

Yoon Jong deeply sighed.

Everyone was yelling and cursing until now, but Chung Myung didn’t register a word of what was happening?

Right now, the second-class disciples wanted the third-class disciples to bow before them, especially Chung Myung.

‘Despite this being a boring way to get that done.’

But Yoon Jong could understand the second-class disciples in his own way.

In fact, it wasn’t the second-class disciples that were wrong for feeling disrespected by Chung Myung, but the path they chose to get them to submit was wrong. To be precise, the path wasn’t entirely wrong, but the way they were acting was.

Even if Yoon Jong was a second-class disciple, he would have a hard time tolerating a person like Chung Myung.

So far, there have been no problems with elders and the first-class disciples^1. This was because Chung Myung never crossed the line when dealing with them. It was unknown what was going on in Chung Myung’s mind, but he would always show respect to the adults within the sect.

But the Baek disciples were different.

Didn’t Yoon Jong already see for himself how Chung Myung spoke with the Baek disciples?

“… isn’t it obvious what they want?”

“Obvious?”

Yoon Jong sighed.

“I won’t tell you to change your personality or bow to them. Just try backing down and comply for a bit….”

“Comply?”

Yoon Jong’s eyes trembled at the way Chung Myung said it.

Shit, he chose the wrong word…

However, contrary to Yoon Jong’s expectations, Chung Myung didn’t throw a fit. Rather, he looked at Yoon Jong with bright eyes and spoke with creepy cheerfulness.

“Sahyung, Sahyung!”

“Huh!?”

“I think I know of a better way to solve this! With this method, I can really solve everything!”

Seeing Chung Myung’s face bright with excitement, Yoon Jong felt anxiousness sink into him, but he couldn’t avoid asking.

“… what method is that?”

“Do you need to ask? I am going to destroy those sasuk bastards!”

As soon as Chung Myung answered, he got up from his seat, and Yoon Jong desperately yelled.

“Catch him! Catch that madman! If we don’t catch him, we all die! Get him!”

Perhaps the others felt the same anxiousness, but all the Sahyungs ran and prepared to catch him at once. While they all held onto Chung Myung’s limbs and pulled him back, Jo Gul jumped up and crushed Chung Myung’s body to the floor.

“Ahhhh!”

“Don’t let him go! Never let go!”

“Let go! Aren’t you going to let go!”

The third-class disciples clung to him like dogs holding onto food. In their desperate eyes, there was only one thing going on ‘Don’t let this mad dog loose outside of the boarding house!’

“Chung Myung! Calm down! Chung Myung!”

“I will smash them all!”

“There are rules to seniority in the sect! if you ignore that, you will be excommunicated if you beat the seniors!”

Chung Myung’s eyes lit up.

“Fine! I won’t smash them completely! I won’t! I will just hit one person! Just one I am telling you!”

“That’s still fighting someone from a level higher than us, you idiot! Ugh! Just hold him tight!”

“Ah, how can this bastard be this strong!?”

“Ughhh!”

Chung Myung grunted through his teeth.

“Those bastards are doing things that we didn’t even do a hundred years ago! I’ll just teach them a short lesson!”

A Taoist home needs to be pure and natural. In other words, it is a place unbound from norms and classes created by society.

Wasn’t there a famous story of how Confucius came to greet Lao-tzu and he said to not do such things?

However, the disciples of such a sect were doing such things?

“Calm down, Chung Myung! We will be in huge trouble if you beat the sasuks!”

“All the things you did till now won’t matter anymore!”

“Stay still will you!”

“Let go! Let go of me!”

The third-class disciples all built a giant human tower and pressed Chung Myung to the ground. Yet each time he wriggled, the massive tower reeled.

Seeing that, Yoon Jong broke out in a cold sweat.

‘No, does this even make any sense?’

Baek Cheon is the strongest of the second-class disciples.

Until Chung Myung arrived, Baek Cheon naturally stood first among the disciples. Everyone had no doubts that he would continue to be first for a long time and eventually become the greatest master within the sect.

Jo Gul wasn’t inferior to him, but learning martial arts like the second-class disciples would take time. It was virtually impossible for Jo Gul to catch up with Baek Cheon, who had already trained in martial arts for nearly a decade.

Even if it was possible, it would take decades for it to happen.

That was why the disciples were accepted with large age gaps. No matter how talented they were, it would take enough time to accumulate their skills. Therefore, the different disciples’ groups couldn’t overcome one another easily.

But what was happening in front of Yoon Jong now?

The youngest of the third-class disciples, who only recently entered Mount Hua, was talking about destroying all the second-class disciples.

‘The real problem is that no one here thinks it’s impossible.’

What if it was thought about rationally?

He couldn’t understand.

No matter how strong Chung Myung was, it was unlikely that he could win against Baek Cheon. Even if Chung Myung had learned martial arts since birth, Baek Cheon would still have more years of training under his belt.

Moreover, Baek Cheon was not a man that lacked talent.

It would be impossible to overcome such a difference. A person who could do such a thing would be a genius. However, even if Chung Myung was a genius, he couldn’t overcome a ten-year age gap.

If Yoon Jong thought about it rationally, it was impossible for Chung Myung to defeat Baek Cheon.

‘But the problem is that it still feels like Baek Cheon sasuk will get beaten quite a lot.’

In the first place, common sense and rationality didn’t apply to Chung Myung. Has anything that this guy did till now made sense?

“Chung Myung.”

Yoon Jong sighed and said,

“I understand how you feel, but not now.”

“Why?”

“The conference is coming soon.”

“What about it?”

“… Baek Cheon sahyung is the person who will represent the second-class disciples. What will happen if you beat him so badly that he can’t participate?”

“Come on. You don’t think I will beat him like that, do you? I just need to beat him so that it hurts without leaving any visible signs, that’s my specialty! Don’t you know?”

“I know.”

Yoon Jong knew very well because he had been hit like that countless times.

“But you can’t do that. Baek Cheon Sahyung is our sasuk. Will he be able to perform properly after having his confidence shattered like that?”

“…”

“Let’s hold on a little longer. It’s better for us to be harassed by the Baek disciples than to be humiliated by the Southern Edge sect.”

Chung Myung frowned.

“I think it would be better to just hit him.”

“Just this once, I am asking you to let this go. Please. The conference is a huge deal for us. Please.”

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung turned his head and spoke in a dull voice.

“Move now.”

The sahyungs looked at Yoon Jong, and when he nodded, they very slowly let go of Chung Myung and moved to the side. Still, they stayed close enough to be able to catch him if he suddenly ran.

“Then we need to just wait until the conference is over, right?”

“… don’t have to wait till then, but….”

“What is with you!? Say it clearly!”

Yoon Jong tightly closed his eyes and spoke as if he was quelling a raging fire.

“Yes! Only till the conference!”

“Okay!”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“This is something the great Sahyung requested, so I have to listen.”

“… thank you, so much.”

“Why are you crying?”

“No. Nothing.”

‘These aren’t tears. It’s the sweat from my heart, you bastard!’

“But what should I do if they come to me for a fight?”

“… would that even happen?”

“Just, what if?”

Yoon Jong sighed.

“Then you can handle it however you want. I wouldn’t know what to do if that happened anyway.”

“Really?”

The corners of Chung Myung’s mouth curled into a devilish grin, and seeing that smile, Yoon Jong’s heart suddenly felt a hundred times more uncomfortable.

Chapter 83: Fight? You are so done now (3)

“You should call me Sago^1, I am your Sago”

“So what?”

“You need to respect your seniors.”

‘Forget that. You are more like a ghost!’

Chung Myung sighed in frustration.

It was ridiculous that she had such a faint and hazy presence. Certainly, the world is a large place, it’s not strange that such a unique constitution exists, but her mind was also weird.

In fact, Chung Myung highly specialized in detecting the presence of others with his qi. If you simply used your five senses instead, then it wasn’t impossible to keep track of her.

The real problem was something else.

“Just why are you following me like this!?”

“Is that how you should ask?”

“… senior.”

Chung Myung felt a deep sadness in his chest.

‘If the Sahyungs saw me now, they’d fall over gasping for air at the hilarity of this situation… no, they might even cry while laughing.’

Maybe they’d even clap their hands until they break. That was how great this sight was.

Chung Myung had to respectfully address a girl who is even younger than the granddaughters of his peers. He felt as though he had attained enlightenment, as he saw the world openly mocking him and showing him the futility of his actions.

Would the world be fine if he decided to stray from the path and abandon these rules?

-No, it wouldn’t, you bastard!

Ah, seriously, come on!

Chung Myung took a deep breath and looked at Yu Yiseol.

“So, why? Why do you keep following me!?”

“Hmm?”

“… senior.”

Yu Yiseol raised her eyebrow in discontent.

Honestly, it looked like she was trying to slightly intimidate him, but it looked cute on her.

‘She isn’t cute just because I’m old.’

As Jo Gul and the rest of the third-class disciples said before, she was a beauty. If she had a more colorful expression and didn’t give such a cold impression, then she would attract several times more attention than she does now.

What an unfair world for people to care so much about appearances. Well, Chung Myung was also famous for his great looks in the past…

Ah, fine! Fine!

“That sword.”

Yu Yiseol said while looking at Chung Myung.

“The sword which creates Plum Blossoms.”

“I have no idea what you’re talking about.”

Chung Myung acted dumb.

It wasn’t something that could be understood if explained, and he didn’t have a reason to speak either. It was annoying how she’d constantly pester and follow him, so it was better to simply escape.

“I don’t know what I did, and I don’t know what you are talking about so don’t waste your ti—”

“Teach me.”

“—me and go…?”

Chung Myung was shocked.

“What was that?”

“Teach me.”

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

‘Is this the reason she followed me?’

He thought that she would create trouble by telling others that he secretly learned some sword techniques outside of Mount Hua or blackmail him, but he didn’t expect such words to emerge.

Now he was curious.

“You know what it—…no. I don’t know what you’re talking about.”

Yu Yiseol slightly bit her lip.

“I’ll tell the sasuks.”

“Go ahead. It’ll be good if they believe you.”

“I’ll tell the sect leader too.”

“Sure, sure. Do whatever you want.”

Chung Myung clenched his nose with one hand and waved with the other.

‘Let’s see if they believe you or not.’

Who would believe that Chung Myung, who entered Mount Hua less than a year ago, could perform the Plum Blossom Sword?

What would the sect leader say?

‘Haha. It seems like our Yu Yiseol has had a difficult time during her closed room training. I’ll find a good physician for you.’

That would probably be what he says; she would be lucky if they didn’t toss her out of the room.

“Teach me, and I won’t tell anyone.”

“I’m telling you. I don’t care who you tell.”

Chung Myung smiled.

“So, don’t interfere with other people’s training and go away. Because of you, I can never get any practice done.”

Go away, okay?

Just go! You are like a leech!

Chung Myung, who was about to retort again, went dumb at Yu Yiseol, who stared and said.

“You aren’t going to teach me?”

“Excuse me. Sago (female senior of a higher level).”

“Huh?”

“You are the sago, and I am the sajae. What could I even teach a Sago? Rather, I should be learning from you.”

“…”

Yu Yiseol flinched at Chung Myung’s words.

‘Oh, that seemed to work.’

Since she kept emphasizing her seniority from the moment they met until now, this might work…

“There are no hierarchies when it comes to learning.”

“…”

No, where the hell did she learn to think like this? Did the Baek disciples have some Confucian teachings within them? How dare Confucianism enter into our precious sect!

“So, teach me.”

“No, because I have nothing to teach you!”

Chung Myung bluntly cut her off.

“I don’t know what Sago could have seen, but it must have been a dream. Or maybe it was a fantasy? Otherwise, you must have been overworked and hallucinated. I have no idea what Sago is even talking about! So stop with this and leave me alone.”

Chung Myung cut off her words which made her narrow her eyes.

“I couldn’t have been wrong.”

“No, that is just nonsen—”

“Because I have seen it before.”

“Before…”

Chung Myung’s eyes lit up.

“What?”

The atmosphere around Chung Myung changed as he glared at Yu Yiseol with sharp eyes.

A sword that makes plum blossoms bloom.

The Plum Blossom Sword technique.

There are numerous sword arts in Mount Hua which were modeled after plum blossoms.

However, this technique does not merely mimic the shape of plum blossoms; there were only a few techniques that could truly make plum blossoms bloom.

And there was no way that it could be passed on to normal disciples. At the very least, one had to be an elder, and it was only transferred from a master to his disciple when the master felt that their disciple was worthy.

However, on that fateful day in the past, all the elders of Mount Hua died. Nobody could have predicted that they would be annihilated, so none of the elders had passed their techniques onto their disciples.

That is to say.

If someone could make plum blossoms, it must mean that they learned the Twenty-Four Plum Blossom Sword technique.

And the only place where the sword technique was currently being taught…

“What is your relationship with the Southern Edge Sect?”

As Chung Myung spoke in a sneer, Yu Yiseol tilted her head.

“Southern Edge?”

“…”

“Why Southern Edge?”

Is she not related to them?

Chung Myung stared at her face. No matter how he looked for signs of deceit, he could only see confusion in its place. If she was just acting, then she would do better by giving up the sword and becoming an actor in a drama group. She could even perform in front of the emperor.

However, Chung Myung didn’t think that Yu Yiseol had the brain to control her expression so perfectly.

Chung Myung was losing it.

‘But.’

Even if she was a spy of the Southern Edge Sect, there was no way that she could have seen anyone perform the Plum Blossom Sword technique. The Plum Blossom Sword technique has a deeper meaning only when combined with Mount Hua’s cultivation method.

… they couldn’t have stolen that too, right?

No!

Chung Myung, who returned to his casual smile, shrugged his shoulders and asked.

“You saw it before, what do you mean?”

Now Yu Yiseol’s face darkened.

“A very long time ago.”

Yu Yiseol looked up at the dark sky as if recalling old memories and spoke again with a stern face.

“Teach me.”

“I’m telling you that I don’t know what you’re talking about.”

“Is that so?”

Yu Yiseol nodded her head.

‘Has she finally given up?’

Thank Go—

“Then there is nothing I can do.”

Srrng!

Yu Yiseol unsheathed the sword from her waist as Chung Myung looked back in horror.

“Ah! W-What is up with you so suddenly!?”

“You’re not going to teach me, right?”

‘What’s wrong with this crazy bitch!?’

Who draws their sword just because somebody won’t teach them swordsmanship? What the hell were these Baek disciples being taught?

“You’re drawing your sword just because I won’t teach you?”

“It’s because you are right.”

“What?”

“I am the senior, and you’re the junior.”

“…”

“So, I need to educate you properly.”

Yu Yiseol raised her sword and aimed it at Chung Myung. Seeing that, he smiled.

‘No wonder the Baek disciples aren’t close to her.’

Of course, they weren’t. Because she was absolutely insane!

‘Isn’t her obsession with the Plum Blossom Sword technique weird too?’

“I’m coming!”

“What coming!? Don’t come!”

But there was no way this mad woman would listen to Chung Myung. Yu Yiseol quickly ran towards Chung Myung with her sword pointed straight.

“Ah!”

Chung Myung quickly retreated with the wooden sword in his hand as the sword of Yu Yiseol arrived before him.

“No! what kind of Sago would attack their Sajae with a real sword!”

“Because you are stronger than me.”

Huh? That is true, isn’t it?

No, but what makes her believe that?

She couldn’t possibly have known that. How strange. She clearly had the wrong impression, but Chung Myung couldn’t even correct her because she ended up with the correct answer.

Phat! Phat!

Just like Chung Myung had seen before, Yu Yiseol’s sword was light and had a brilliant elegance to it.

It pierces sharply and bends gently. The sword shakes like an illusion before lightly stabbing in again.

Mount Hua’s Sword.

Since returning to Mount Hua, Chung Myung had seen many swords. He had seen the Baek disciples’, Un Geom’s, and sometimes he had the opportunity to see the elders’ swords as well.

However, the sword unfolding before him now was closer to the true source of Mount Hua than any of the others he’d seen.

Just seeing this swordsmanship made him feel strangely sentimental.

Why?

‘Because her movement resembles the past Mount Hua? If not—’

“Move!”

At that moment, Yu Yiseol’s sword came to pierce Chung Myung at the speed of light. Chung Myung turned his head and narrowly avoided it.

Swosh!

Several strands of his hair lightly drifted to the ground.

“EEEikkk!”

Was this crazy bitch really going to stab him?

“Have you gone insane!? If I didn’t avoid that, I would have died!”

“There’s no way that you wouldn’t have avoided it.”

“Why are you so confident in me!?”

What is wrong with her head? Why doesn’t she think like normal people?

No wonder she has such a pretty face but no friends!

But there was no time for conversation.

Yu Yiseol’s sword began to sharpen as she closed in on Chung Myung. Still, it would be easy enough for him to deal with it.

Ugh… if he could attack, that is.

If Chung Myung turned Yu Yiseol’s attack against herself, then she would go from being confident in his skills to a hardcore fan of his. He needed to find some way to subdue her without getting hurt and without showing his ability.

Swish!

“I said don’t do that, woman!”

“It’s Sago!”

“What kind of Sago tries to kill her junior! Just what is wrong with your brain?”

‘Oh my! My ancestors. This is how far our Mount Hua has fallen!’

Chung Myung, who was lamenting his fate, frowned for a moment.

Perhaps it was because he was able to leisurely observe the incoming attacks despite their conversation, but he could see Yu Yiseol’s movements slowly changing. As if her eyes were drunk and losing focus, her sword began to deviate from the set path.

‘Oh?’

Enlightenment in the middle of a spar?

‘Even Jo Gul couldn’t achieve that.’

Jo Gul could be considered the best in Mount Hua in terms of swordsmanship talent.

‘No.’

Chung Myung stretched out his wooden sword and helped the deviating sword return to the proper path.

Achieving enlightenment meant entering a trance-like state and finding their one true sword. If you intervened without the confidence or ability to handle it, then it was possible that the enlightened state could be shattered immediately; in the worst case, they may even receive a backlash and die.

Ordinary people would have rushed to retreat without daring to get involved.

But Chung Myung could anticipate and understand the sword’s path at each moment and lead the sword in the best direction.

‘Not there. Right, this side. No no, I said here.’

Tuk! Tuk!

Chung Myung would stretch out his sword and tap Yu Yiseol’s sword, leading it to the correct path. The only thing that could be done in such a situation was to let it flow…

“What are you doing!? You bastard!”

Chung Myung turned his head to see who suddenly intervened.

Baek Cheon, who seemed to have lost his mind in anger, rushed to him at a frantic speed.

Ah… why the hell are you here!? You damn brat!

Chapter 84: Fight? You are so done now (4)

“You bastard! What are you doing!?”

Seeing Baek Cheon running at an insane speed, Chung Myung looked up at the sky with a soulless face.

Haa.

Oh dear, my poor fate.

Baek Cheon lunged at Chung Myung and swung his sword without hesitation.

Wait, why did he also have a real sword?

‘What is with these disciples constantly taking out real swords? Who will take responsibility if they unsheathe their sword and something crazy happens?’

While Chung Myung was lost in thought, Baek Cheon’s sword threateningly sped towards him. A deep blue and black qi formed around it, aiming for Chung Myung’s shoulder.

Baek Cheon did well to aim at a non-vital area despite his hysteria.

But,

“The after-effects of that sword qi will kill me anyway, you crazy bastard!”

Chung Myung kicked the flying sword with his foot.

Kang!

A loud sound rang throughout the area as the sword, layered in qi, and the foot collided with one another. Unable to withstand the impact, Baek Cheon was thrown back.

“Uh?”

Baek Cheon swiftly rose to his feet, alternating between Chung Myung and his sword. His eyes shook in bewilderment. Everything happened so quickly for him that he didn’t understand what had happened.

“Tch.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue and examined Yu Yiseol’s condition. Such a huge sound broke out next to her while she was in a trance, so her enlightenment…

“She’s fine?”

Normally, this much commotion would rouse a person from their enlightenment, but Yu Yiseol was still entranced.

Slow.

She’s too slow.

But she was benefiting from her dull wittedness. It wasn’t common for a person to fall into a trance while swinging their sword.

In Buddhism, it was referred to as ‘exaltation’ in the sense that one forgets themselves. Casting off their shell and entering a new realm. For warriors, this was the absolute most crucial moment.

If she had been woken out of it, she would have regretted it all her life.

“Bastard! What are you doing!? Don’t you know how important enlightenment is for a warrior?”

‘And you attacked me despite knowing that?’

Chung Myung gazed at Baek Cheon with wide eyes.

“Touching someone in a trance! No matter how little common sense you have, there are some things you can’t do! You ruthless brat!”

Baek Cheon stared at Chung Myung.

“It’s true that I didn’t like you, but I had no idea that you were such a rotten bastard you’d even mess with someone in a trance! I should correct that habit of yours right now!”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

‘No, you idiot. I didn’t mess with her, I helped guide her.’

’Haha, but how would you know that? It’s my fault. I’m the sinner here.’

“If you knew how important a trance was, then why did you draw your sword and attack?”

“What?”

“What if your sword had gone towards Sago and hurt her?”

“If you hadn’t counterattac—!”

“Then I should just die?”

“…”

Chung Myung responded to Baek Cheon, who seemed flustered.

‘Are all the Baek disciples crazy?’

The world is usually dominated by ordinary people with a few madmen mixed in. However, it seemed like the Baek disciples took that rule in reverse and flooded themselves with insane kids.

Out of all the Baek disciples Chung Myung talked to, there wasn’t a single normal person yet.

If Yoon Jong had heard, he would have said that one dog was barking at another, but he wasn’t here to complain.

“Are you saying that I was trying to kill you?”

“It didn’t look like you wanted me alive.”

“… it was an urgent situation.”

“And you even drew a sword.”

“.. t-that.”

Baek Cheon’s face, which heard Chung Myung’s argument, flinched.

Wait a moment.

As Chung Myung said, Baek Cheon utilized sword qi on a real sword. So, how was he able to escape without a single wound?

Does that mean this kid could casually handle Baek Cheon’s attack?

“Get away from Samae!”

Baek Cheon’s face hardened as he spoke in a determined voice.

“I won’t ask what you were doing. But put your sword down and step away from her. Otherwise, you will have to deal with me as a warrior and not your sasuk.”

Oh, doesn’t that sound good?

Chung Myung was delighted.

“Really?”

“…”

Great, this was what Chung Myung was hoping for.

“You bastard, until the end….”

Baek Cheon gnashed his teeth.

Humans were the sort that needed to adjust their thinking based on their individual situations.

If your perspective changed, then Baek Cheon’s anger was reasonable. From his point of view, an irredeemable taboo had been transgressed by his junior.

Normally, it was right to put a stop to those actions.

The problem was…

Chung Myung licked his lips and turned his head.

‘If I help a little more, it seems like something amazing will happen.’

Yu Yiseol was currently in a state of enlightenment. Although it usually didn’t occur in such a random fashion, enlightenment always comes on suddenly. Who knew when or even if she would ever have another opportunity like this!

Some people fight and struggle their entire lives without ever experiencing enlightenment, while others reach that state from ordinary tasks like eating. This wasn’t something that could be sought after with effort or because one desires it to happen.

It depends on the will of heaven.

And the greatest miracle that occurred to Yu Yiseol was not simply enlightenment. It was that Chung Myung was by her side at the time she entered her trance.

Basically, those who fall into a trance forget themselves and their surroundings, focusing solely on using their sword. During this, they develop their own sword or the next level of their sword, and sometimes they achieve a higher realm.

That was why nobody should tamper or touch them. A serious accident could happen if the opponent didn’t understand how to properly handle the sword.

But who is Chung Myung?

He is an amazing martial artist who understands all of Mount Hua’s sword techniques and set foot on a plateau no one had ever climbed before. With his current body, attaining enlightenment might not be possible, but it will be difficult to find anyone in Mount Hua who has a better understanding of sword techniques.

Even if one considers the entire history of Mount Hua, one might not find a greater master.

So, he could intervene in Yu Yiseol’s trance and guide her to a higher realm…

‘Why did that bastard have to show up!’

It is even more difficult to lead one in front of others. If something went wrong, it would turn into a bigger problem.

Chung Myung glanced at Yu Yiseol.

‘What can I do? This is your luck.’

Although it was a pity that he couldn’t help someone who might lead Mount Hua, Chung Myung didn’t feel much regret since that ship had already sailed.

‘But it’s another thing altogether to beat the guy who made you miss the ship.’

Chung Myung took a couple steps away from Yu Yiseol and glared at Baek Cheon.

“Is this enough?”

“More.”

“Tch.”

He once again took a couple steps away from Yu Yiseol.

“Good?”

“… are you messing with me? Get out of here. I have no intention of letting you harm Samae.”

“Who’s the one causing harm here? You’re the one causing harm.”

“Is that any way to speak to your senior!?”

Chung Myung speechlessly stared at the sky after hearing Baek Cheon’s response.

‘Why are these kids so obsessed with formalities?’

Yu Yiseol was the same, and now Baek Cheon too.

“Yes, Sasuk. The problem here is Sasuk.”

Baek Cheon stared at Chung Myung with cold eyes.

“I tried to understand the reason for your arrogance.”

What was the result?

The moment Chung Myung arrives, he talks shit and escalates a problem and makes it all about himself, and now he acts like a master… ah, the problem here is also because of him, right?

“But my patience has its limit, and there are people in this world who don’t understand words.”

“Wow…”

Baek Cheon frowned at Chung Myung’s exclamation.

“What are you trying to say?”

“Nothing, nothing at all. It’s just a bit funny.”

“What is?”

“You wouldn’t understand even if I told you.”

It’s been a hundred years, and he was saying the same thing Chung Myung used to say when he was a Sahyung.

- There is no use talking to you.

- Rather than discussing the path of Dao to Sahyung, it would be faster to recite it to a cow or a hen.

- Don’t bother speaking if you can’t fight.

Humans are so similar.

Otherwise, Chung Myung hasn’t changed much in a hundred years.

Baek Cheon sharply called out to Chung Myung, who was chuckled in reminiscence.

“Raise your sword. Today, I will teach you what manners are.”

“Will you be fine?”

“Bastard!”

“No. No. not that… but, if you are in a hurry.”

As Chung Myung spoke, Baek Cheon narrowed his eyes.

“What do you want to say?”

“No, I’m just worried. If news got out that Sasuk fought with his sajae then your name might be tarnished.”

Baek Cheon laughed bitterly.

“After coming this far, now you want to play that card? You’re wrong if you think that your peers or the elders will protect you. Perhaps in the future, but at this moment there is no one that can save you. As for my punishment, I will accept it later.”

“Ohh, I haven’t heard such a manly speech in a while.”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“But I have a better idea, would you like to hear it?”

“… what are you planning?”

“No. Nothing, let’s each just swear an oath. We won’t tell another soul about what happens here tonight.”

“What?”

Chung Myung smiled.

“I’m saying that even if I get beaten, I won’t tell any of the elders or anyone else. Likewise, you can’t run and tell anyone if you lose this battle. Do you understand what I’m saying?”

Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung.

‘What is he thinking?’

Baek Cheon examined Chung Myung’s expression then smiled.

“It looks like you are trying to get out of this situation, but do you think I’ll care if you try these tricks? You—”

“No, that’s not the case.”

Chung Myung sighed, unable to overcome his frustration.

“I am saying that we should throw away the titles of Sasuk, Sajae and Sahyung and have a clean fight.”

“…”

“If we make a promise to each other, that no matter what happens, I will not reach out to my seniors. I will stand here and fight my best. Of course, the same goes for Sasuk too, what do you think?”

Baek Cheon had a subtle smile.

“Alright, it seems you have quite a manly side to you. If you want, then I swear. I won’t tell anyone what happens here.”

From Baek Cheon’s point of view, there was no reason not to accept that offer.

The most difficult part of beating Chung Myung would be dealing with the Un disciples or the elders. Wasn’t it obvious that they were all protective of Chung Myung? So, if news got out that Baek Cheon attacked him, wouldn’t it cause an endless amount of trouble for him?

Yet now Chung Myung himself wanted to keep this matter hidden? There was no reason for Baek Cheon to refuse.

But… he couldn’t erase this weird feeling inside him.

“Then I swear.”

“You seriously have a manly side as well.”

“Yes. I swear too.”

“Then our grudges will vanish the moment we finish.”

Baek Cheon lifted his shining sword and pointed toward Chung Myung.

“I’ll admit that you’re quite bold. In this fight, I am not your sasuk, nor are you my sajae. I will use this fight to settle all the bad feelings that I have towards you. And you too….”

“Fight?”

At that moment, he heard an eerie voice from Chung Myung.

Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung with curiosity in his eyes.

‘Huh?’

Then he noticed.

Chung Myung was smiling, but unlike before, this was an evil grin that distorted his wicked features.

“Fight? You’re going to die now, you bastard.”

Chung Myung said and walked towards Baek Cheon.

Chapter 85: Fight? You are so done now (5)

‘Has he lost his mind?’

Baek Cheon couldn’t help but feel flustered.

Chung Myung was walking with his head tilted to the side. It looked like some back-alley gangster walking in to threaten innocent civilians.

There were two reasons why Baek Cheon was flustered.

First, was that Chung Myung acting like a gangster seemed to suit him too well. Second, the person Chung Myung was currently intimidating was none other than Baek Cheon himself.

‘Did he really lose his senses?’

Baek Cheon was Chung Myung’s sasuk.

Of course, that wasn’t important because they both agreed beforehand that they would leave their titles behind for this battle.

What truly mattered was that Baek Cheon was different from Chung Myung, who had just entered the sect.

Baek Cheon entered Mount Hua when he was even younger than Chung Myung. In other words, he had already spent over 15 years learning martial arts.

But what about Chung Myung?

‘It’s only been half a year since he started.’

Even if Chung Myung began training within his mother’s womb, he would still have spent less time practicing than Baek Cheon. Even if Chung Myung was talented enough to become the world’s greatest master, right now, it was impossible for him to defeat Baek Cheon.

Even those with talent need time to properly develop.

If talent alone could surpass the walls of time, then would anyone even try to master martial arts?

‘But…what is with his reaction?’

However, Chung Myung acted as if he truly believed he could defeat Baek Cheon.

Baek Cheon was so confused that he couldn’t even speak.

“… you’re really crazy.”

“No. Not at all. The crazy one here is you.”

“What?”

“If you weren’t crazy, then why would you try and challenge me?”

If those who were entangled with Chung Myung in the past were present, they would all vigorously be nodding their heads.

The Southern Edge Sect called him the devil that descended from Mount Hua, and the Wudang sect used to say that Chung Myung’s name reached the sky, but his evil deeds covered the earth.

‘Fuck you.’

Chung Myung raised his hand.

Surprisingly, Chung Myung wasn’t someone that liked resorting to violence.

…What?

What about all the things he’d done so far?

That was all because the others wouldn’t listen otherwise.

For Chung Myung, violence was just a means to an end. He ultimately wanted everyone to do well on their own, without Chung Myung having to force them again.

Why would anyone use violence if everything could be settled peacefully? People only got beatings because they refused to listen.

But now, Chung Myung started to think it might be better to use violence as an end rather than means.

“Your self-indulgence knows no bounds. My hands are heavy and full of resen—”

“Come on.”

“—what did you say?”

Chung Myung just shrugged his shoulders,

“I usually don’t like talking before a fight but listen well. In a little while, you won’t be able to speak even if you want to, so just come at me.”

“Arrogant until the end, you bastard!”

Baek Cheon grabbed his sword.

He also didn’t want to waste any more time.

‘I was going to go easy on him.’

Baek Cheon ground his teeth.

No matter how angry he was, he couldn’t actually cut down his own junior. But Chung Myung could be overwhelmed with swordsmanship. Baek Cheon intended to beat Chung Myung so thoroughly that he would piss himself in fear whenever they crossed paths.

Baek Cheon grasped his sword and rushed towards Chung Myung.

The sword quickly cut through the air towards Chung Myung. It was a sword that seemed different from Yu Yiseol’s. At first glance, they may look similar; however, Baek Cheon’s was heavier and fiercer.

In a way, it was the same as the Southern Edge Sect.

A sword that minimizes the colorful changes that were the basis of Mount Hua’s art to take advantage in a sword fight. With only a moment of inspection, Chung Myung had firmly understood the essence of Baek Cheon’s style.

‘Strange.’

The Southern Edge Sect abandoned their swords and tried to emulate the splendor of Mount Hua. However, Baek Cheon reduced the splendor of Mount Hua’s sword to achieve the simplicity of the Southern Edge Sect.

‘Well.’

Thinking about it, it is normal.

All sword arts undergo constant changes, and those changes are always seeking to advance the style. Naturally, one would seek inspiration for their swordsmanship from those who are in a better condition than themselves.

In Mount Hua’s heyday, the Southern Edge Sect was crushed by Chung Myung and would have thought that a flashier sword was the answer.

On the other hand, the second-class disciples of the current Mount Hua were crushed by the Southern Edge Sect through the conference and desperately recognized the gap between their skills. They must have considered the sword of the Southern Edge Sect to be the right answer.

It was understandable that both sects would resemble one another.

But!

‘Pathetic fools.’

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

Does that mean Baek Cheon learned the style of the Southern Edge Sect because there was nothing more for him to learn here? Well, Chung Myung didn’t like this bastard from the start.

‘An idiot who doesn’t even understand what he has now covets someone else’s art?’

Chung Myung must let him know. What Mount Hua has.

Baek Cheon rushed in.

“I am going to change your attitude today.”

Chung Myung clenched his fist as he watched Baek Cheon rushing towards him.

“I’ll change!”

He put the right foot back.

“That habit of yours!”

And tilted his back a little.

“Which!”

The fist pulled back and then extended forward.

“No one fixed till now, you son of a bitch!”

Pride.

Chung Myung’s fist penetrated through the changes made in Baek Cheon’s sword. A fist that stretched out at an accurate angle and appropriate speed, aiming between the changes and transitions.

Baek Cheon was shocked as he saw the fist of Chung Myung piercing through the sword technique.

It was easy to say that it could be done. However, it was absurd that Chung Myung could accurately shove his fist through a sword art that could easily slice his arm off.

From Baek Cheon’s point of view, it felt as if the arm of a ghost had emerged from the abyss.

But there was no time to be surprised.

Tuk!

Baek Cheon’s jaw was hit.

Drrrrk!

And he heard a squeaking sound behind his neck. In an instant, his consciousness flew away, then swiftly returned.

When he came to his senses, his body had been knocked back repeatedly, bouncing off the ground.

‘What?’

What just happened?

His senses had dulled for a moment. Baek Cheon didn’t realize what had happened to his body when he bounced back. He was overtaken with a distant understanding of reality.

Kuk!

“Kuak!”

The moment his body settled on the ground, an indescribable pain shook him to the core.

“Ackk!”

His back was fine. But searing pain radiated from his jaw, where Chung Myung had struck.

Grabbing his chin, Baek Cheon groaned.

Learning martial arts meant that one had to get used to suffering. It wasn’t simply pain from pushing the body to its limit but also frequent injuries from training and sparring.

But this was unlike any pain Baek Cheon had suffered before. It really felt like a new world of pain had opened up for him.

“Wake up, you bastard.”

Chung Myung said while tilting his head and approaching Baek Cheon.

Seeing that, Baek Cheon got up.

Chung Myung seemed a bit surprised.

“Oh? You actually got up?”

Obviously, he got up!

While he was enduring the pain in his jaw, Baek Cheon felt like his heart was being rent as Chung Myung mocked him. Baek Cheon struggled to comprehend the current situation.

He desperately tried to calm his trembling legs and raised the sword again. The bitter taste of blood in his mouth clearly reminded him of reality.

“H-How?”

Baek Cheon was not stupid.

The earlier exchange was no accident. No one in this world would risk losing their arm to a sword technique for a chance at a lucky strike.

In other words, Baek Cheon’s sword was clearly visible to Chung Myung’s eyes.

“How did you do that?”

Chung Myung looked at Baek Cheon as if he were pathetic.

“Your technique reduces the myriad changes and flows between changes depending on how you choose, but so what? Did you think that your technique was flawless? Really, for every one thing that you know there are two things you don’t. Of course, there are gaps in your sword art!”

Baek Cheon stood there wide-eyed.

“N-No one managed to find them till now.”

“Obviously, because the people you were dealing with were stupid. Any elder could have figured it out immediately.”

Wait, maybe not?

Uh… what was the level of the current elders? Huh?

Leave that aside.

“You mean my sword is wrong?”

“Yeah.”

Chung Myung spoke as if he didn’t even need to think about it.

“For now, you must be able to stand ahead of your peers by a little bit. But as time passes, your sajaes will start to outpace and overtake you.”

“How can you know that!? You only recently joined the sect! I can’t believe your words! I won’t!”

“Ah. Do whatever you want.”

Chung Myung smiled bitterly.

The disciples of Mount Hua were committing the same mistake the Southern Edge Sect did, and Chung Myung could even understand their reasons.

‘It isn’t that strange.’

Perhaps, even in Chung Myung’s time, something like this happened countless times. At the time, however, Chung Myung simply didn’t know what consequences such a change could bring.

Due to Chung Myung’s vast experience, his eyes could see how someone’s sword would develop. Seeing young disciples who were only beginning to develop their style, things that had never been noticed before began to appear.

“Be grateful that I am a disciple of Mount Hua.”

“What?”

Chung Myung raised his wooden sword.

Honestly, Chung Myung still wanted to crush Baek Cheon, but wasn’t he also one of Mount Hua’s cute disciples? Even if he was going to be crushed, it would be nice to beat him in a way that would help his development.

“Don’t worry. I’ll take you down with a sword instead of a fist. Ah, I’m so kind.”

“…”

Is Chung Myung crazy?

No, he really is crazy, right?

Seeing the bewildered expression on Baek Cheon, Chung Myung took a deep breath.

“Some say that the purpose of Mount Hua’s sword was to resemble plum blossoms. But that is only what those who are unfamiliar with Mount Hua’s sword say. Mount Hua’s sword doesn’t imitate plum blossoms. The sword of Mount Hua aims for….”

Chung Myung, who had been speaking seriously, suddenly frowned.

“Ah, never mind. Do you understand what I am saying? Sometimes it’s easier to understand when your body gets beaten rather than with your brain. I’m coming!”

“Uh, Huh?”

Without realizing it, Baek Cheon took a step back.

However, the speed at which Chung Myung rushed toward him was twice as fast.

Baek Cheon swung his sword and tried to stall Chung Myung. Even if he was injured, his instincts as a swordsman still allowed his body to react before he had time to process what was happening.

At that moment, Baek Cheon noticed.

The image of Chung Myung’s fingers slightly trembled, then the wooden sword multiplied into dozens or more and filled his vision.

‘W-what is that…?’

“Thighs!”

Twack!

The wooden sword hit Baek Cheon’s thigh, and he opened his mouth with tears brimming in his eyes.

But it didn’t end there,

“Wrist!”

Thwack!

Chung Myung’s sword precisely struck Baek Cheon’s wrist, which was holding the sword. From wrist to hand, it felt like his arm went numb for a moment, and he lost grip on his sword.

‘H-Hold on…’

At that moment, Baek Cheon’s ears were filled with a sound he dreaded hearing.

“Head! Head! Head! Head! Head!”

Why not just once, you bastard?

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

Baek Cheon was hit by a series of blows, feeling like his head was going to explode; his mouth fell open as his eyes rolled back.

Even as he collapsed, his mind was obsessed over a single thought

‘Why did you say head five times but hit me six times?’

It was a question that was left unsolved as his consciousness flew away.

Chapter 86: What bullshit. I am the strongest! (1)

“Uh…”

As soon as Baek Cheon regained his senses, terrible pain came over him. He could barely get up as he groaned in pain from his head which felt like it was splitting open.

‘How long have I been out?’

It felt like a long time had passed as Baek Cheon awoke. As soon as he opened his eyes, he saw the dark sky. Fortunately, it seemed like it had been less than half a day at the most.

“Ack.”

When he turned his head to the side, he saw Yu Yiseol slowly wielding her sword in the distance.

‘It doesn’t seem like much time has passed.’

Of course, it wasn’t possible to infer the time from her form alone. A person experiencing enlightenment sometimes doesn’t return to reality for several days or more.

Suddenly, Baek Cheon’s ears were greeted with the sound of an eerie voice which was both familiar and unfamiliar.

“Up already?”

“…”

Baek Cheon’s head reeled around.

The figure of Chung Myung squatting, with a wooden sword draped over his shoulder, came into his view.

Flinch.

Baek Cheon’s body tensed and screamed to retreat before he could calm down and hurriedly move back.

“I guess you are a bit surprised.”

Chung Myung smiled.

Baek Cheon stared at Chung Myung with shocked eyes.

‘I lost.’

No, it wasn’t that he lost.

The fight from before was so embarrassing that it bordered on laughable to discuss victory and defeat. He still didn’t understand how it happened; there was only one conclusion he could arrive at.

He was completely outclassed.

Baek Cheon raised his hand and touched his head. His head, which was beaten by Chung Myung, was still ringing like a bell.

But it wasn’t something to be embarrassed about. The scoundrel who knocked him out cold was watching him with eyes wide open.

“Can I ask you one thing?”

“Sure.”

“… how are you so strong?”

“What?”

Chung Myung looked at Baek Cheon.

‘Interesting.’

Usually, people who experience such nonsensical things are unable to accept reality. Even when the result was clear and obvious, they would kick and scream in denial and lash out like a wild boar.

In particular, those overly boastful types that are full of pride never seem to admit defeat until they’ve been beaten again and again.

However, Baek Cheon managed to acknowledge reality rather quickly, despite his prideful nature.

That’s at least one thing that deserves to be praised, but…

“It’s not that I’m strong, it was sasuk that was weak.”

“Me?”

“Yes.”

Baek Cheon’s eyes trembled a little.

“I’m…weak?”

“Yes.”

Baek Cheon staggered and rose to his feet, glaring at Chung Myung with eyes that could kill.

“Don’t ignore me. I am Baek Cheon. The great sahyung of the Baek disciples and the person who will one day lead the Mount Hua sect.”

“Uh, right.”

Chung Myung politely nodded his head. There didn’t seem to be anything wrong with Baek Cheon’s words.

There was just one thing.

“But that doesn’t mean that you aren’t weak.”

“…”

As Baek Cheon couldn’t refute, Chung Myung raised his finger and pointed to his senior.

“A frog in the well.”

“…”

“That’s the right phrase for sasuk right now. A well so narrow that even passing frogs wouldn’t think of entering it, and a frog with its inflated ego trapped at the bottom.”

Baek Cheon’s face was distorted.

“And I’m the frog?”

“Yes.”

“Me?”

Chung Myung grinned at Baek Cheon, who couldn’t admit the truth and continued to ask the same question.

“You are the frog, Sasuk.”

“…”

“Sasuk should already know that Mount Hua is on the verge of ruin.”

“… of course.”

It was harsh to say that it was on the verge of ruin, but there was no denying that it had fallen.

And it was Baek Cheon’s role to resurrect Mount Hua. At least, that was what he had believed until now.

“That’s why I’ve been trying so hard till now. To somehow make Mount Hua….”

“Sasuk?’

Chung Mung looked at Baek Cheon with absurd eyes.

“When did you try hard?”

“…”

Baek Cheon was at a loss for words at Chung Myung’s question.

“It doesn’t seem like that to me at all. It looks like a bunch of kids left to go play house and close up together, before returning and partying at a restaurant. Drinking and congratulating one another on a job well done. Even now, when the conference is fast approaching, aren’t you and the other sasuks wasting time bullying the third-grade disciples? What effort? What ‘trying hard’ are you doing?”

Baek Cheon went silent.

Until now, he never thought that he lacked effort. However, he couldn’t say anything when Chung Myung pointed out his inadequacies.

“It seems like sasuks don’t know what hard work truly is. Doing everything you want to do and investing the remaining time to train isn’t working hard nor is it effort.”

“…”

“Sasuk didn’t really try till now, you just wanted to rule over a small kingdom called Mount Hua. There was no competition for you around and no one who could nag you. It was a comfortable setting for you, right?”

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

“No, No. Don’t make such a face. I am not criticizing Sasuk. But if you refuse to be compared to others and want to live like a king here, you shouldn’t be talking about how hard you’ve tried.”

Chung Myung said sullenly.

“Have you ever had a proper fight with anyone?”

“…”

“At best, you would have confronted the Southern Edge Sect. Sasuk, the Southern Edge sect may be treated like the grim reaper here, but the Southern Edge sect is likely near the bottom of the Ten Great Sects. The disciples of the other Nine Great Sects are soaring through the sky, are you strong enough to fly with them? You think you’re strong? Sasuk?”

Chung Myung had a smirk on his face.

“Don’t get me wrong, you frog. It isn’t that I’m strong, you are weak.”

An alarm rang loudly in Baek Cheon’s head.

‘Am I weak?’

He didn’t want to admit it.

However, there wasn’t a single mistake in Chung Myung’s words.

Mount Hua was struggling to contend with the Southern Edge Sect. Actually, even if he took part in the conference and managed to defeat them, there were other sects stronger than them.

“…then does that mean there are people stronger than you in the other great sects too?”

“What bullshit. I am the strongest!”

“…”

‘You aren’t making any sense, you bastard!’

“But it’s not because I am stronger than Sasuk. Right now, Sasuk wouldn’t even be able to beat over the Southern Edge sect. Of course, it’s not even worth comparing you to the Shaolin and Wudang sects.”

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

However, Chung Myung threw another sharp word at Baek Cheon without mercy.

“So, even if it wasn’t me, there are plenty of people that could defeat Sasuk. Do you understand?”

‘I understand…. but I don’t want to understand.’

Who would ever want to acknowledge that they were just another grain of sand in this world?

But Baek Cheon clenched his teeth without protesting.

“I know.”

“…”

“You think that a disciple of Mount Hua doesn’t understand that? I know. I certainly know. But it doesn’t matter. I am not a disciple of the Wudang sect, so I have no choice but to work hard with what I have!”

“But you didn’t work hard, Sasuk.”

Chung Myung said with a sullen face.

“You didn’t try enough, and the direction of your effort was wrong anyway. Do you think someone can become a master just by working hard? Then you should give this up and try to do that. After five hundred years of beating up scarecrows, maybe you’ll finally be able to properly use your sword.”

Chung Myung had refined pissing people off with his words to an art form.

While frowning deeply, Baek Cheon asked.

“So, you know how I should train?”

“I think I at least know better than Sasuk.”

Chung Myung smiled.

At that, Baek Cheon sighed.

‘Goblin-like bastard.’

Baek Cheon couldn’t understand this child. How could he be strong and bold? How did he still have that relaxed expression on his face? He couldn’t understand.

‘That’s why he can confidently act so cocky.’

In Chung Myung’s eyes, the Baek disciples are nothing more than fools with no skills that argue and harass others with their authority.

Even if their situations were reversed, he would have only acted worse than Chung Myung.

Just one thing was certain now.

Chung Myung was stronger than Baek Cheon could imagine. He didn’t know how, but he was stronger than the Baek disciples.

Even if Baek Cheon sparred with Un Am or Un Geom, he wouldn’t be defeated as disastrously as this.

After a moment of hesitation, Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung with determined eyes.

“Then, can you make me strong?”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

‘I knew it! This guy is definitely strange.’

Baek Cheon had great pride yet remained aware of reality. Usually, when one thing goes wrong, everything goes wrong.

Putting that bluntly, this bastard was a prideful person who knew his situation very clearly.

Wasn’t this the most terrifying aspect of a human?

But it wasn’t bad, especially not for a martial artist. In the end, such a person will become strong. Or perhaps his pride could drive him to become the strongest.

“Of course, that’s possible.”

Baek Cheon quietly nodded his head.

“Then…”

Bowing, with both hands outstretched to beg,

“Uh?”

Baek Cheon spoke in a serious tone.

“Please, make me strong. I will do anything you ask of me.”

“…”

Baek Cheon lifted his head and continued.

“If I can become strong, I wouldn’t hesitate to learn from Sajae. If our relationship as Sasuk and Sajae is a burden to you. I will not treat you as one—”

“Don’t want to.”

“—As a teacher… Huh?”

Chung Myung answered again.

“No, I don’t want to.”

“… Why?”

Baek Cheon asked.

Wait, wasn’t he saying all that nonsense to Baek Cheon because he wanted this to happen?

“Why should I? It’s bothersome.”

“…”

“And you seem to be mistaken, Sasuk.”

“What?”

“It isn’t over yet.”

Chung Myung stood up, raised the wooden sword, and spun it around.

“There is something very strange about humans. They don’t think about what they’ve done and come to compromises in their own minds. They always think they’ve done enough to repent for their crimes.”

“…”

“Yep, right, that’s right. You must pay for your sinful actions. Have you paid? Bullshit! Maybe you paid enough for how much you harassed the third-class disciples, but!”

Chung Myung’s eyes were blazing.

“My anger will not subside with just that!”

‘No, you idiot!’

Baek Cheon stepped back, terrified.

However, Chung Myung slowly approached Baek Cheon with a reaper-like smile.

“You still don’t get it, right?”

“No! I get it. I’m already convinced too!”

“No, No. Sasuk doesn’t understand yet. It’s clear from what happened just now.”

‘Why do you get to decide whether I understand or not!?’

He said he gets it!

“Don’t worry. The night is long. I’ll make sure to convince you tonight. Why, just why my Sasuk is so weak and why my Sasuk’s sword is wrong. And…”

Chung Myung’s eyes shone again.

“Why you shouldn’t touch me.”

“…”

“Ehehehehe! I am coming!”

“Eikk!”

Sadly, Baek Cheon’s screams couldn’t reach Mount Hua.

Unfortunately for him.

Chapter 87: What bullshit. I am the strongest! (2)

Thud!

Chung Myung refreshingly stretched his body as he watched Baek Cheon collapse once more to the ground.

“Ah, it feels like I’ve been relieved of a ten-year-indigestion.”

Chung Myung smiled as he looked at Baek Cheon, who was completely out cold and unable to move.

“I did my best.”

Although a bit heavy-handed, Chung Myung beat Baek Cheon without leaving any lasting injuries on his body. Even though he fainted, he would be fine once he woke up. Though, the pain would linger for around a day.

“Right, it feels comfortable to just beat up your problems like this!”

Chung Myung turned around. Whether Baek Cheon and the others could compete in the conference wasn’t Chung Myung’s problem.

“… no.”

Come to think of it, he didn’t want to see the Southern Edge bastards act triumphantly in front of him.

“Hmm. So how—ackk! Shit! You shocked me!”

As Chung Myung was squatting and contemplating, he was suddenly startled and quickly escaped to the side. Yu Yiseol had appeared in front of him, squatting and staring without warning.

“A-ah seriously! Are you a ghost!?”

He had to do something about her. If this kept happening, again and again, he was bound to die from a heart attack before Mount Hua could even revive.

“Announce yourself when you appear! Say something!”

“I did!”

“When!”

“Before, when you were beating him.”

“…”

Chung Myung glanced at Baek Cheon, who was laid out like a corpse and turned to Yu Yiseol.

A soft smile on her lips.

“You saw that?”

“Yes.”

“You saw everything?”

“Only from a little while ago.”

“Hmm.”

“Are you going to kill me?”

“No, that’s a bit too far.”

She always goes for killing and murder.

Chung Myung closely examined Yu Yiseol’s head.

And tilted his head.

“What?”

“No, I just thought that if I slapped the back of your head a little, you might forget what you saw. Amnesia or something.”

“… I forgot.”

“Really?”

“Yes. I forgot everything.”

She’s dull but has great survival instincts.

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes as Yu Yiseol spoke.

“Instead, teach me that sword.”

This woman never gives up! What is going on in her head?

He had barely escaped before, but it wasn’t possible anymore. Hadn’t she even seen Chung Myung happily beating Baek Cheon? He couldn’t hide his skills anymore.

Then, he should change his strategy.

Chung Myung took a deep breath and began to speak.

“Why do you want to learn it?”

“…”

Maybe it was an unexpected counterattack because Yu Yiseol slightly flinched. She looked at Chung Myung with a somewhat shocked expression. To show such an expression on her face…

‘She’s the kind that can’t lie.’

Yu Yiseol hesitated for a moment and then opened her lips.

“I cannot tell you the reason but….”

Yet, there was sincerity in her hesitancy.

“I need to master that sword art.”

Chung Myung looked at Yu Yiseol.

‘I don’t think she’s interested merely because she thinks it’s pretty.’

There was a certain eagerness in her eyes. She was safeguarding a story that gave birth to her stubbornness. A tale that Chung Myung hadn’t the faintest idea about.

“So, you want to learn that technique?”

Yu Yiseol decisively nodded.

“You don’t need to.”

“Huh?”

“It was originally Mount Hua’s sword art. If you wait, you will naturally be able to learn it.”

“… Mount Hua no longer teaches it.”

“Oh?”

She knows that it no longer exists in Mount Hua?

Then, she recognized that the sword Chung Myung unfolded was the Plum Blossom Sword technique. To be precise, though, it was Chung Myung’s variation of the Plum Blossom Sword technique.

Chung Myung nodded.

“Yes. It’s not in Mount Hua right now.”

“…”

“But it’ll be back soon. Once the time is right.”

“Time?”

Chung Myung looked at Yu Yiseol. Instead of answering her question, he stretched his hand out and pointed at the sky.

Soon, Chung Myung’s finger smoothly cut through the air.

At first, Yu Yiseol tilted her head as if she couldn’t understand the gestures. Soon, however, she realized that his hand was drawing a sword path and observed it seriously.

“Yue Maiden Sword?”

“That’s right.”

Yu Yiseol gasped upon seeing Chung Myung’s gestures.

It was definitely the Yue Maiden’s Sword.

The technique that she had polished and honed for the longest time.

However, Chung Myung’s Yue Maiden Sword differed from Yu Yiseol’s. Rather than a difference in the movements, there seemed to be a more fundamental difference.

When the variable short and long hand gestures ended, Yu Yiseol sighed quietly.

“Did you understand?”

Yu Yiseol shook her head.

“No. I don’t understand a thing.”

The moment Chung Myung was about to say something, Yu Yiseol spoke up first.

“But it’ll be my task to figure it out. I think I know what you are talking about. You mean that I can’t begin learning it unless I reach a certain level, right?”

“Yes.”

“I must lay the foundation by refining what I have now.”

“You are good.”

Yu Yiseol nodded.

“I know.”

Chung Myung looked at Yu Yiseol.

‘I thought she was dumb, but I guess she has a good head.’

After all, the mind and the personality are separate things.

“Right. But, if you tell anyone about what happened here today, I will never teach you.”

“I won’t speak a word about it.”

“Very nice. That’s a good girl.”

As Chung Myung nodded, Yu Yiseol narrowed her eyes.

“I am your senior, and you are my junior.”

“I know, I know. Right, good girl.”

“…”

Chung Myung could see Yu Yiseol’s hand tightly clenching her sword.

Chung Myung quickly turned around.

“Then, until we meet again, Sago. Don’t come to me before then. It’s annoying.”

“Excuse me…”

Yu Yiseol reached out and tried to catch Chung Myung, but he didn’t wait around and immediately headed down the mountain.

“Ah! And throw that idiot inside his room. If you leave him there, he will just die of shock when he gets up.”

Yu Yiseol sighed at Chung Myung’s words which echoed from afar.

‘Plum Blossoms.’

The tip of Chung Myung’s sword released the Plum Blossoms.

A sight she had been unable to see despite all her time spent in Mount Hua.

Just…

Yu Yiseol closed her eyes.

The sword moved inside her mind. The tip of the sword smoothly sliced through the air before shaking; then, it began to release brilliantly bright and clear plum blossoms.

Plum Blossoms.

At the end of the sword

The man holding that sword.

‘Father.’

-I will certainly restore this technique. One day, I’d like to return to Mount Hua and repent for my sins with this. Yiseol. Come with me. There’s no place better than Mount Hua.

Yet, he didn’t manage to make the plum blossoms bloom fully in the end.

But now, right in front of her, was a person who could make it happen.

“I must learn it.”

At all costs

Bang!

Chung Myung sprinted through the door of the White Plum Blossom Boarding Hall.

“Eik!”

“He’s here!”

And was met with a strange reaction.

“What?”

Although it was early morning, it seemed like Yoon Jong and Jo Gul were waiting for him on the first floor.

“It seems like your training has gotten a bit too comfortable. Are you here to check up on me?”

“No, this place was a mess!”

“Huh?”

“Baek Cheon Sahyung was missing, so the Sasuks all came and checked this place out.”

Those disgusting bastards.

Why would they come to this dorm if Baek Cheon went missing? Did they think Chung Myung kidnapped him?

Ah.

‘I didn’t think about that. I could have kidnapped him and beat him up in secret.’

It seemed like some intelligent kids were mixed in with the second-class disciples.

“They’re tossing accusations out without any proof. It pisses me off.”

Hearing those words, Yoon Jong smiled.

“I guess it wasn’t you! Thank god—”

“They were right, though”

“…”

‘If they were right then why are you getting offended!? Why!?’

No, that wasn’t important.

“You were with Baek Cheon Sahyung?”

“Yes.”

“Wait, I guess… this isn’t what I think it was right?”

“What do you think it was?”

Yoon Jong smiled a bit awkwardly.

“It’s unlikely. I know you’re a very thoughtful person, so what I am thinking about probably didn’t happen, but I hope that you didn’t decide to hit Sahyung’s face or punch him in the stomach like you said before….”

“What’s the difference between the two?”

“Attacks to the face add bonus damage.”

Jo Gul nodded in agreement as if acknowledging the truth of that statement. Chung Myung waved his hands in the air.

“Eh. It isn’t like I am some kid.”

“N-No. Right. Chung Myung! This Sahyung always believed in you. No matter how crazy you are, you wouldn’t hit our Sasuk.’

“I didn’t hit him.”

“Right!”

“I beat the shit out of him.”

“Right. Shit out of him. Baek Cheon is already a shitty person—what?”

Yoon Jong’s face trembled.

“Beat?”

“Yes.”

“Who? Our Sasuk?”

“It’s a j–joke, right?”

“No way. Am I a person that jokes about a beating?”

At that moment, Yoon Jong rushed to Chung Myung at the speed of light and shook him by the collar.

“Hey, you crazy dog! Do you always have to do your best, even when you’re causing trouble!? What do we do if he tells someone what happened!? This is all because you don’t understand how serious the crime of assaulting a senior within the same sect is.

“Oh, my god!”

Chung Myung kicked Yoon Jong.

After lightly disposing of Yoon Jong, Chung Myung caressed his neck.

“I already know all that. There won’t be any problems, so quit worrying. Don’t you know how I handle things?”

“… I know. I know.”

Yoon Jong said slowly.

“Oh, my God. Even if you’ve lost your mind, this is too much. How can you hit our Sasuk? There are some sins that should never be committed.”

“When did he ever follow rules?”

“Ugh…”

Yoon Jong groaned at the cruel truth which emerged from Jo Gul’s lips. Tears stung his eyes when he thought of what would happen in the morning.

“What is with this atmosphere? Do you think I would handle this situation poorly?”

“… so, what did Sasuk say?”

“He asked me to make him stronger.”

“What?”

Both Yoon Jong and Jo Gul looked at Chung Myung in shock at that unexpected answer.

Chung Myung slowly asked them.

“How is that?”

“…”

“…”

The two looked at each other.

‘Does this make sense?’

‘No, thinking about it, not a single thing makes sense here anymore.’

‘But…even Sasuk?’

‘We are Sahyungs…’

A widow knows how another widow feels. Since they suffered similarly, they could understand how Baek Cheon felt when he said that.

“S-so what did you say? Did you agree?”

“No. I just beat him up.”

“You beat him?”

“Yes.”

“Why?”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders.

“Does there need to be a reason? To feel relieved. I just beat him until I felt better.”

“…”

At that moment, Yoon Jong regretted not training hard before Chung Myung arrived. If he had the chance to return to his past, he was confident that he would train without a moment’s rest until the moment Chung Myung appeared.

Only then would Yoon Jong be capable of smashing Chung Myung in the face, at least one time.

It was then that Yoon Jong realized there was no way to stop a madman from running amok if that man was powerful.

“Don’t worry about anything and just go to sleep. You’ll find out the results once you wake up.”

“…”

“Sleep tight.”

Chung Myung moved upstairs, while Jo Gul and Yoon Jong sighed deeply.

“… do you think it’s true?”

“There’s one thing I realized about Chung Myung.”

“What is it?”

“Even if he speaks bullshit, he never lies.”

“… what a great thing to realize.”

A very great thing. You bastard.

“But Sahyung.”

“Yes?”

“Doesn’t this mean that Baek Cheon Sasuk attacked Chung Myung first?”

“…”

“Isn’t that how it is?”

“He’ll speak bullshit, but he doesn’t lie.”

“It sounds unbelievable. But even Baek Cheon Sasuk got beaten.”

“The one that did it was Chung Myung.”

“… that sounds convincing.”

Yoon Jong shook his head and looked up at the stairs Chung Myung had used.

There was a monster dwelling in the White Plum Blossom Boarding house.

Where was Mount Hua heading? Mount Hua…

Yoon Jong wanted to cry.

Chapter 88: What bullshit. I am the strongest! (3)

Yoon Jong’s eyes narrowed as he looked around.

There were none.

He couldn’t see a single one.

Unlike yesterday, he couldn’t see any of the second-class disciples that had frequently been tormenting them recently.

‘Was it true?’

It’s not that Yoon Jong didn’t trust Chung Myung’s words.

As Jo Gul said, Chung Myung was a person who spoke nonsense but didn’t lie.

The problem was that Chung Myung’s ‘solution’ was far from the solutions that ordinary people would think of.

So, he thought that this would cause more trouble…

‘He seems to have solved everything well?’

He had doubts about how it was solved, but he surely settled the matter.

“Sahyung. It seems like Chung Myung’s words were true, right?”

“…”

Yoon Jong nodded at Jo Gul’s words.

But was it really plausible for things to be this simple?

‘If we encounter problems with Sasuk, are we supposed to spar and defeat them to solve the problem?’

Even ignoring common sense, wasn’t this abandoning the rules of the sect and coming up with their own way to solve the issue?

The problem was that this madman’s method actually worked.

‘Just what is going to happen to Mount Hua in the future?’

Yoon Jong never thought of himself as a grumpy figure, but when he saw how Chung Myung behaved, he began to feel like being a grumpy old man wasn’t such a bad thing.

Wouldn’t it be a beautiful world if that grumpy bastard could keep things in order?

“What are you thinking?”

“… I was thinking about the future of Mount Hua and what it feels like to be an old man.”

“…”

Jo Gul.

‘Did he finally realize how he acts?’

Yoon Jong sighed, noticing how Jo Gul was looking at him with pitiful eyes.

The third-class disciples who were watching from the side slowly approached Yoon Jong and spoke.

“The dorms seem a little strange today, Sahyung.”

“… I guess so.”

“Why are they doing this? I’m worried that they’re going to do something worse.”

“Right.”

Yoon Jong looked up at the distant sky.

‘These kids also aren’t in their right minds anymore.’

To say that their Sasuk was beaten.

Such a thing would be unimaginable in Mount Hua before Chung Myung arrived. However, like Yoon Jong and Jo Gul, the third-class disciples also seemed to be getting influenced by Chung Myung’s unreasonable teachings.

If things continued like this, Mount Hua might be filled with people who behave like Chung Myung…

Yoon Jong shuddered; he didn’t want to imagine such a future.

‘Just thinking about it is terrifying.’

The problem was that it seemed like this thought could very well become a reality.

“I’m more anxious because it’s quiet. Should we sneak a peek?”

“I don’t think those idiots have come to their senses already. Doesn’t it seem like they’re up to something? Sahyung?”

‘Oh my God.’

Just where did the trust between fellow sect disciples go?

“It’s noisy. Come and get ready for training!”

“… Yes.”

‘Sajae.’

‘What is with his temper?’

Yoon Jong sighed deeply as he lamented how his juniors looked at him with that question burning in their eyes.

Day by day, Mount Hua was turning away from the Mount Hua Yoon Jong knew. Of course, this change wasn’t necessarily bad, but… he honestly felt that he didn’t want to open his eyes and see the future that Chung Myung would create.

“Sahyung. Then, did Chung Myung really beat Baek Cheon sasuk?”

Jo Gul asked softly so that the others wouldn’t overhear, and Yoon Jong frowned.

“What are you even asking for? There’s no way he would lie, and if it weren’t for that, the seniors would still be harassing us today.”

“… No. That…”

Jo Gul scratched his head.

“I just can’t understand it. No matter how strong Chung Myung was from the beginning, there’s still a difference in the amount of time he and Baek Cheon sasuk studied martial arts.”

Yoon Jong couldn’t understand either.

‘Does this make any sense at all?’

It made no sense. But wasn’t Chung Myung always doing things that made no sense?

“Then Sahyung, Chung Myung is stronger than Baek Cheon, right?”

“Why do you keep asking such obvious—”

“Then, what about compared to the Southern Edge Sect?”

Yoon Jong went silent.

Compared to them?

This was something Yoon Jong never thought about.

“Chung Myung shouldn’t be inferior to the Southern Edge Sect either, right? He even defeated senior Baek Cheon.”

“Hmm.”

Yoon Jong, with a stiff face, fell into thought.

“Then, in the conference this time….”

“Gul.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

“If Chung Myung wins, will it make a difference?”

“… wouldn’t things change?”

Yoon Jong shook his head.

“When a master expert is born in a sect, it’s something to celebrate. However, a single master’s reputation belongs solely to themselves. They can’t do anything alone. The moment that Chung Myung disappears, Mount Hua will fall again like before.”

“…”

“If we truly want to revive Mount Hua, we also need to become strong. We can’t simply rely on Chung Myung. We won’t be able to declare Mount Hua’s revival until the day arrives when the world becomes unable to ignore any random disciple within the sect.”

“Right.”

“But as you said, I am also curious about the conference. This time will be different.”

“What do you mean?”

“Chung Myung…”

Yoon Jong took a deep breath and said,

“Will he truly become a hero that brings change to Mount Hua? Or will he be a tyrant who reigns over this small Mount Hua?”

Yoon Jong and Jo Gul faced each other with serious eyes.

Chung Myung…

“Ah, seriously! Get out of here!”

The two slowly turned their heads towards the sudden interruption.

Chung Myung was swearing as he came down.

“…”

“Isn’t that Senior Yu?”

Yu Yiseol was chasing after Chung Myung, who was fleeing with his full might.

“Teach me.”

“I already told you that I had nothing to teach! I told you to not come! You horrible leech!”

“The Yue Maiden Sword!”

“Go to Un Geom Sasuk and ask him! He’ll teach you!”

“Un Geom Sasuk is a man. The Yue Maiden Sword is a technique for women. It is a skill that Un Geom sasuk cannot handle.”

“Then am I a woman? Well? Am I a woman?”

“Teach me.”

“Ahhhhhh! How do I get through to your mind?”

Chung Myung and Yu Yiseol quickly passed between Yoon Jong and Jo Gul. The two who were left behind stared in bewilderment at the absurd sight.

‘When did those two become friends?’

‘Did Senior Yu always talk this much? It seems like Yu Sago has spoken more in the past few days than she has in the entire time I’ve been in the sect.’

‘Actually, is it fine for that idiot to talk to Yu Sago like that?’

Well, he has always been arrogant.

“… what you said earlier. Whether he’s a hero or a tyrant.”

“Gul.”

“Yes. Sahyung.”

“Let’s go train.”

“… Yes.”

Baek Sang’s face crumpled.

“Sahyung, are you really going to leave it like that?”

Hearing the dissatisfaction in Baek Sang’s voice, Baek Cheon smiled.

“Why are you so angry?”

“Aren’t they acting too arrogantly! Especially that one, Chung Myung! He doesn’t even show a shred of remorse. Isn’t it alright to punish them now?”

Punish?

You?

Him?

“Someone like you?”

“Huh?”

“Nothing.”

Baek Cheon forced himself to smile.

Although it had died down a little, his entire body throbbed in pain.

Baek Cheon turned his eyes towards Chung Myung, who was fleeing from Yu Yiseol.

‘Sneaky son of a bitch.’

How could he beat a person so well without leaving any scars on the outside? The more he thought about it, the more absurd this guy seemed.

Thankfully, he avoided being embarrassed in front of others, but he couldn’t even complain about this injustice to anyone. He’d be treated like a madman if he tried to complain about his junior abusing him without even having any visible injuries.

Or maybe he’d be treated as trash with no future prospects.

Of course, even if there were wounds on his body, Baek Cheon would never tell anyone about how he was beaten like a dog. Still, he couldn’t help but feel disappointed.

“Why did you suddenly tell us not to touch the third-class disciples?”

“Baek Sang.”

“Yes. Sahyung. I just don’t understand the reasoning behind it.”

The reasoning was to have a happy life.

Baek Cheon was doing it to avoid getting hit again.

But Baek Cheon could never speak his reasons out loud. He had a dignified image to maintain.

“Isn’t the conference approaching?”

“… That’s right.”

Baek Cheon spoke with a stern expression.

“I was thoughtless. Ruling over the third-class disciples is something we can do at any time. But not the conference. Doesn’t this event only occur once a year?”

Baek Sang silently nodded.

Seeing that Baek Sang still wasn’t fully satisfied, Baek Cheon narrowed his eyes.

“Governing the third-class disciples is an internal task, and the conference is external work which affects the honor of the Mount Hua sect. The inside is important, but the outside is more urgent. Moreover, considering what happened in the conference last time, let’s put aside everything else for now and concentrate on producing positive results. Everything is at stake this time; don’t you think so?”

“… yes.”

“Right now, our enemy isn’t the third-class disciples, it’s the Southern Edge sect. We shouldn’t forget the reason we spent this last year in closed-door training.”

Baek Sang took a deep breath and lowered his head.

“Sahyung is right. I must have lost focus.”

‘I must have been out of my mind.’

And he was still out of his mind.

Regardless, Baek Cheon was glad that Baek Sang didn’t press the issue any further.

‘Weren’t you the one that started this in the first place? Why are you pretending to be some nice guy now?’

If Baek Sang had decided to ask that question, Baek Cheon would have been at a loss for an answer.

“Thanks for understanding. Let’s not worry about the third-class disciples for now. Our first priority is to focus everything we have on the upcoming conference. Ask our sajaes to reflect on their martial arts and reflect on what they’ve refined during our closed-door training.”

“Yes, Sahyung!”

Baek Sang bravely gave a loud response.

With that, Baek Cheon lowered his head with an expressionless face.

‘Even after the end of the conference, I don’t plan on touching those third-class disciples.’

Baek Cheon didn’t want to see what would happen to him and his peers.

Baek Cheon turned to look at Chung Myung off in the distance.

‘We aren’t the only ones who will be surprised.’

Perhaps even more than Mount Hua, the Southern Edge sect would be surprised. When he thought of the future, the pain of being beaten by Chung Myung slowly vanished… ah, never-mind… it didn’t vanish.

It hurt more.

It hurt down to the bone.

‘Damned bastard, why did you have to hit so well!?’

Baek Cheon sighed and turned away.

‘I just need to do what I can do.’

Although he felt that life became twisted because of Chung Myung. Baek Cheon’s purpose, to prove himself in the conference, hadn’t changed.

Considering that the Southern Edge Sect would soon be coming to Mount Hua, he didn’t have the time to behave selfishly now.

This time, he must prove his worth.

But…

Baek Cheon looked back.

“Why does he keep hanging out with Yu Samae?”

He didn’t like it.

Baek Cheon glanced at them and headed to training while suppressing an uneasy feeling.

The conference between Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect was fast approaching.

Chapter 89: What bullshit. I am the strongest! (4)

“Sect leader.”

Hyun Jong silently poured tea into a cup without responding. The fragrant aroma of tea permeated throughout the room.

Whenever he felt angry, Hyun Jong made tea like this. There was nothing like this tea to stabilize his body and calm his mind.

“They will arrive today, Sect Leader.”

“Are the preparations complete?”

“Yes. Sect leader. Nothing will go wrong while welcoming the Southern Edge Sect.”

“That’s good to hear.”

Hyun Jong let out a low sigh.

‘At least this time, I don’t have to feel embarrassed.’

It was shameful to be left behind in martial arts, but what was even more embarrassing was Hyun Jong’s inability to properly treat the Southern Edge Sect disciples last time.

How would Hyun Jong feel if they had no choice but to show the ruined buildings, poor meals, and devastated training halls to Mount Hua’s most bitter rival?

It was a sensitive issue, especially for Hyun Jong, the sect leader of Mount Hua.

It wasn’t easy to tolerate the piercing gazes of the Southern Edge Sect disciples, who looked at him in mockery and disdain. He had no choice but to bite his lip and endure the ridicule in the past.

“The more I think about it, the more I believe Chung Myung has done a great job.”

Un Am said.

It was well known that Hyun Jong cared deeply for Chung Myung, but Un Am truly understood the heart behind those actions. From Hyun Jong and Un Am’s perspective, Chung Myung was nothing less than a benefactor who helped seal the leaks on their sinking ship and pulled it up from the depths.

This wasn’t just about being able to feed people.

It was a sect with a long history. At the very least, it should have a dignified appearance which makes its history seem plausible to outsiders. Although appearance is nothing more than empty courtesy, the world still evaluates others based on what could be seen.

People would listen to a scholar before they listened to a beggar.

Chung Myung not only solved Mount Hua’s financial woes but also restored the sect’s face.

How could Hyun Jong not favor the child?

Un Am’s smiling gaze made Hyun Jong feel slightly embarrassed. He lightly coughed before recommending that Un Am have some tea.

“Drink.”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

Un Am took a light sip from his cup and nodded quietly.

“How is it?”

“It seems to have gotten stronger. It’s been dried for a long time, and the taste seems to have faded a bit.”

“Yes.”

Hyun Jong nodded, pleased with Un Am’s analysis.

“Well-dried plum blossom leaves actually become more fragrant. This is something I only realized after decades of drying plum blossoms.”

Hyun Jong looked at the teacup and spoke.

“It is the same with Mount Hua. We merely endured. We vowed to recreate the glory of the past, but the reality is that it was difficult to even survive each day.”

“… Sect Leader.”

Hyun Jong smiled as if to soothe Un Am’s worried tone.

“But we persevered and held on. Finally, this day has come to us. Sometimes, the correct answer is to wait rather than move in haste.”

It was spoken with a strange feeling inside.

Un Am looked at Hyun Jong with renewed vigor.

‘We aren’t the only ones moving forward.’

Occasionally, sect leaders fall under the illusion that their sect has already gone as far as it can. But a man can evolve until the day they die. Hyun Jong, who was walking on the path of a Taoist, would not stop refining himself till the day he stopped breathing.

How could one not trust him?

“Mount Hua’s sect leader will bring back the glory of the past.”

“I would like that, but the credit won’t go to me even if that happens. It will be a result of the disciples’ efforts.”

“How can you say that it’s not your credit, Sect leader?”

“Un Am.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“I am a man who understands his own shortcomings. If Mount Hua hadn’t collapsed, would I have ever been asked to be the sect leader? If my Sahyungs hadn’t left Mount Hua, I would have spent my time studying scriptures.”

Un Am answered in a serious tone.

“By leaving Mount Hua, they proved that they were unworthy of being the sect leader. The sect leader is the most decent and honorable person in Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong smiled without answering.

It’s a sad story. So, the conversation needed to be changed.

“So, what do you think about the second-class disciples?”

“Now that they’ve finished with their training. They are trying to stabilize their minds and bodies.”

Un Am’s face slightly darkened when the topic shifted to the second-class disciples.

“Sect leader.”

“Say it.”

“Honestly, I feel a bit worried.”

“Worried… why?”

With a low sigh, Un Am continued.

“As I said before, Mount Hua’s momentum right now is excellent. But, whether or not we lose momentum, doesn’t it all come down to the conference’s outcome?”

“Do you believe that the second-class disciples will be unable to handle Southern Edge’s disciples?”

“I want to believe in the children. But… as you know….”

Un Am didn’t try to say more.

He knew that Hyun Jong understood the difference between Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect.

Mount Hua was barely surviving through the dark history which haunted them for years, while the Southern Edge Sect had been shining and advancing in recent times. It was natural for a significant difference to exist between them.

No matter how hard the second-class disciples tried, it would be difficult to overcome that gap.

Un Am was worried that the disciples, who had only just found new hope, would once again be captivated by a sense of defeat.

“How about the third-class disciples?”

“… Sorry?”

“Aren’t the third-class disciples also going to participate? Are they all well prepared?”

Un Am was a bit puzzled when Hyun Jong suddenly asked about them, but he had no choice except to answer the sect leader.

“The preparations… seem to be going well.”

Not overdone.

Not too much.

Un Am only briefly saw the third-class disciples training when he would pass by the training grounds on occasion, so he had no choice but to express his opinion so hazily.

Since the children’s training was entirely left to Un Geom, Un Am didn’t feel the need to know or interfere with them and simply thought that they were training normally.

“They’ve only recently begun training….”

Hyun Jong nodded quietly.

He fully understood Un Am’s concerns.

“Un Am.”

“Yes.”

“What would you do if there was a mountain in front of you?”

“That…”

Un Am couldn’t easily speak.

“Suppose that there is a mountain in front of you that you must cross. If there is a path around it, then you could travel that road. If you have time, then you can rest and climb at your own pace. However, what if neither option is available and you need to cross it despite that?”

“I am afraid that I wouldn’t be able to overcome that mountain.”

“Even so, you would still gain experience. Next time, wouldn’t we be able to cross the mountain more easily?”

Un Am let out a deep sigh.

He didn’t feel like everything the sect leader said was convincing, but he couldn’t ask anymore because the sect leader said it.

Hyun Jong smiled and spoke when Un Am’s worried expression didn’t fade.

“The Mount Hua and Southern Edge Conference is a venue for such exchanges.”

“… Yes.”

“It doesn’t matter whether we win or lose. What’s most important is who can develop further by using it as a stepping stone.”

“What the Sect Leader said is correct.”

“These guests are coming from far away. Make every effort not to neglect them.”

“I will keep that in mind.”

Un Am nodded.

“There will be no problems with Elder Hwang of the Eunha Guild either.”

“Elder Hwang… right. I need to meet with Elder Hwang once.”

“Isn’t the sect leader quite busy? I’m sure he will understand.”

“Right. Thank you.”

Since the day Elder Hwang and Eunha came to Mount Hua, they have been pouring funds into the sect. Looking at the scale of investment, it seemed as if they intended to make Hua-Um stand on par with the capital.

“Won’t this cause problems with the Southern Edge Sect?”

“Everything will go smoothly.”

As usual, it will be calm.

Un Am bowed his head and stood up.

“Then, I will go for a final check.”

“You’ve been through a lot.”

“Please, don’t mention it.”

Un Am took a step back.

As he quietly closed the door and went outside, Hyun Jong looked down at the teacup in front of where Un Am sat.

The half-empty teacup had light steam drifting from the surface, seemingly conveying how Un Am felt.

“Winning isn’t important….”

Hyun Jong frowned.

“Despite being a Taoist, I can lie so casually.”

Hyun Jong was well aware that winning wasn’t important. But this conference was a battle that couldn’t be won, and he was forced to push his disciples into these unwinnable matches.

They couldn’t win without a miracle.

Unless a miracle happens…

Hyun Jong suppressed his heavy heart and closed his eyes.

“It’s still such a small place.”

The disciples of the Southern Edge Sect glanced around at Hua-Um and spoke with a smirk.

Although they had been to this place in the past, this Hua-Um village was very small. Compared to Xi’an, where they usually went, this was no better than the empty countryside.

“Sahyung. Did Mount Hua really used to be in the Ten Great Sects?”

“Of course.”

“But isn’t this village too small and shabby for a sect that used to be great?”

Jin Geum-Ryong said with a smile.

“You’ve got it backward. This village was only able to form because Mount Hua was here. In the past, Mount Hua was strong enough that this village developed so that the people coming to visit the sect would have somewhere to live.”

“I see.”

Jong Seo-Han nodded as if he finally understood.

“But aren’t they utterly ruined now?”

“That’s true too.”

Jin Geum-Ryong nodded.

Jong Seo-Han looked around and opened his mouth.

“I honestly don’t know why this pointless event is being held. What’s the point in clashing swords with Mount Hua when the results are obvious? Wouldn’t it be better for us to simply swing our swords on our own?”

“This has been decided by the elders; they have their own plans. Be mindful of what you say.”

“Yes, but…”

Jong Seo-Han slowly turned his head back.

Looking at the person following behind him, he smiled.

“But this time, the conference is quite meaningful. It’s worthwhile to take revenge for those who have been disgraced.”

It was a provocative remark.

However, the one receiving the provocation, Lee Song-Baek, continued walking in silence.

‘That’s no fun.’

Jong Seo-Han narrowed his eyes.

Thanks to Chung Myung’s actions at Elder Hwang’s residence, it became common knowledge within the Southern Edge Sect that the Eunha Guild had chosen to support Mount Hua over themselves.

Of course, despite his actions to repent, Lee Song-Baek drew unfavorable gazes for his role in beating Chung Myung and damaging the sect’s reputation.

‘There’s no reaction, no use teasing him.’

Since that day, Lee Song-Baek has changed as a person. He used to be quite serious, but now he is more reticent and stoic.

“We were disgraced by Mount Hua for the first time in 100 years, so we need to repay this debt, Great Sahyung.”

“That’s right.”

While Jin Geum-Ryong and Jong Seo-Han were walking, Lee Song-Baek walked along without wanting to get involved in their conversation.

His gaze turned toward the towering Mount Hua.

‘Mount Hua?’

When he visited this place in the past, he felt light-hearted. But now, the shadow of one person overlapping Mount Hua could be seen.

‘We may be walking straight into the tiger’s den.’

Lee Song-Baek seemed to see the smiling face of Chung Myung.

Chapter 90: What bullshit. I am the strongest! (5)

“What the hell!?”

Jong Seo-Han was annoyed as he spoke with a voice full of anger.

Climbing a mountain wasn’t an easy task, even for those who learned martial arts. This steep mountain looked like it would even be difficult for a bird to ascend.

“I don’t understand what the hell these people thought when they built their sect in a place like this. No wonder their sect is doomed.”

Chung Myung would applaud if he could have heard that statement.

But Jin Geum-Ryong didn’t seem to agree.

“The sect’s location is meaningful; it represents a disciple’s desire to sacrifice and leave behind their mundane and materialistic lives while returning to nature. Naturally, they would choose a difficult location for outsiders to enter.”

“What sort of place is Mount Hua? It’s only half a sect now. At least if it was the Wudang sect that built this place, it would be understandable.”

“Well, you are right.”

Those who climbed Mount Hua before must have had a hard time, so they built a place to rest. The disciples of the Southern Edge sect were resting there now.

One of the second-class disciples opened his mouth with a sullen expression.

“After going through all this trouble, we should be treated to something amazing. Instead, they’re going to feed us grass and make us sleep in ruined rooms.”

“I don’t care about the food; I just want to sleep comfortably. Last time, I couldn’t even sleep without worrying that the building would collapse on me.”

“Even beggars wouldn’t sleep in such a place. What kind of sect is this? This is worse than the Beggars Union.”

Dissatisfaction and scorn mixed into the conversation.

“I think we should stop this useless conference already. We gain nothing from it. We travel so far away to come to Mount Hua and suffer this poor treatment, yet Mount Hua is the only one getting anything good from it.”

Jin Geum-Ryong just shrugged it off.

“I know that everyone is dissatisfied with this, but it would be better for you all to calm down. Don’t you know how the elders feel about Mount Hua?”

“We don’t get it. Why are they so obsessed with a ruined sect?”

“I know.”

“Maybe it’s because of their potential.”

“Potential?”

Someone snorted.

“If they had potential, they would have already changed. Why would they allow themselves to decline for a hundred years if they had some way to reverse the situation?”

“Every sect has its history; what matters is now.”

While everyone was disparaging Mount Hua, one person spoke up.

“You had better not underestimate Mount Hua too much.”

Everyone’s eyes turned together.

Lee Song-Baek.

With an expressionless face, he said.

“If you do, you may end up disgraced.”

Jong Seo-Han frowned.

“Like Sahyung?”

“…”

Despite the obvious provocation, Lee Song-Baek didn’t respond.

“Don’t worry, Sahyung. We won’t afford Mount Hua any chances. We’ll even break the one that trampled on Sahyung’s dignity for you.”

“I am just saying that you should remain alert.”

“What could staying alert around Mount Hua even do for us?”

“I…”

Lee Song-Baek was about to say something but then sighed slowly. Whatever he said wouldn’t work.

Elder Ki Mok-Seung and Lee Song-Baek had the most horrible experience because of what Chung Myung had done at the Eunha Guild.

In particular, all criticism for the incident had fallen onto Lee Song-Baek. It wasn’t surprising; how could people blame an elder?

“Do as you please. But if you let your guard down, there will be a price to pay.”

As Jong Seo-Han frowned and was about to say something, a soft voice came.

“You aren’t wrong.”

Everyone’s heads turned again.

Everyone stood up when they saw the man slowly ascending the mountain.

“Sit.”

“Yes.”

The elder of the Southern Edge Sect, Sama Seung^1, looked at everyone once and spoke.

“Did you all forget what happened with Eunha?”

When the word Eunha was spoken, Lee Song-Baek flinched. But the other disciples answered without delay.

“I haven’t forgotten.”

Sama Seung’s eyes shone.

“Everything was ruined, and we were put to shame because of that collapsing sect. Do you understand how angry the sect leader was?”

Everyone bowed their heads at his words.

Not because they did something wrong, but because of the qi releasing from his body.

“It is enough to be disgraced by Mount Hua once. We must not suffer such a disgrace again. Our Southern Edge Sect should rise above the world and stand over others. How long do you believe we should waste our time fighting with third-class disciples from Mount Hua? You need to put an end to this atrocious relationship! I will not forgive anyone who suffers disgrace at the hands of Mount Hua, even if it’s only due to a moment of carelessness!”

The Southern Edge Sect’s disciples held their breath while listening to the cold voice of their elder.

“A general on the battlefield should never have remorse, and a lion should do its best to catch a rabbit. It’s not enough to simply defeat Mount Hua; the Southern Edge Sect must be strong enough to trample Mount Hua without even giving them a chance to stand against us. Do you understand?”

“Yes, Elder!”

The sharp eyes of Sama Seung looked around at the disciples and nodded.

“However, there’s a difference between vigilance and fear, right?”

“Yes.”

“Hmm.”

Sama Seung turned and looked at Mount Hua.

“Get up. Now that you’ve had a good rest, we should arrive before those waiting for us get tired.”

“Yes.”

The Southern Edge Sect’s disciples resumed climbing again.

After climbing the mountain for a long time, the disciples, who had almost arrived at Mount Hua, began to say.

“This is hell.”

“We really shouldn’t come next time.”

“If it’s the same as last time, shouldn’t we reach the gate soon?”

Climbing the steep mountain, they would soon find the ruined sect’s gate.

Seeing the end of their long journey, the disciples rushed to the top.

And they arrived.

“Huh?”

“What is that?”

And were taken aback by the sight in front of them.

Surely, when they came here two years ago, Mount Hua’s gate was old and looked like it would fall apart at any moment. The gate didn’t even function as a gate.

But now, that old gate wasn’t there. They were greeted by a massive door that seemed brand new.

‘Am I seeing things?’

‘No way.’

‘This makes no sense. Did someone else come up to Mount Hua and establish their sect here?’

They slowly looked up.

The gate may have changed, but the signboard hanging from the entrance showed that the sect’s name remained unchanged. However, the old signboard that was previously crumbling had been replaced with a new one that proudly bore the sect’s name.

When they saw the name ‘Mount Hua’ in the dragon and snake calligraphy, they felt an unfamiliar pressure fall onto them.

“W-what is this….”

It was well-known that the Eunha Guild had joined hands with Mount Hua.

However, the partnership with Eunha was very recent. It was impossible for the sect to rebuild their front gate in such a short amount of time. Not even the Eunha Guild could accelerate development so much.

“This shouldn’t be possible.”

JIn Geum-Ryong mumbled.

Wasn’t this sect supposed to be even worse than the Beggars’ Union? Was this the same Mount Hua that was ridiculed for being unable to accept disciples, even when the sect opened its gates to search?

What kind of money did Mount Hua possess to build this gate?

“Silence.”

Sama Seung spoke slowly.

“It seems like they begged for money somewhere. But even if they can change the gate, the roots of the sect won’t change. There’s no need to make a fuss out of this.”

“Yes!”

“Don’t act like this changes anything.”

Sama Seung walked towards the gate with a slightly offended expression.

It was then.

Kik!

The huge gates began to open, and a man slowly walked out from inside.

Martial arts head, Hyun Sang.

When he saw the disciples of the Southern Edge Sect approaching, he looked at them.

“You must have been through a lot coming all this way. Elder Sama. I met you once before. I am Hyun Sang, elder of Mount Hua.”

“It’s Sama Seung.”

The elder’s response was very short.

However, Hyun Sang didn’t show any offense and smiled.

“Nice to see you again, Elder Sama.”

“The sect leader hasn’t come out?”

Hyun Sang’s eyes twitched.

“The sect leader is inside.”

“But your guests have traveled from so far away, and he doesn’t even show his face?”

Hyun Sang bit his lip.

Sama Seung is an elder of the Southern Edge Sect.

Although he was a well-known elder with high status, he wasn’t someone esteemed enough for the sect leader to personally greet.

Sama Seung clearly knows that, but asking for the sect leader meant that he was being openly disrespectful of Mount Hua.

Hyun Sang opened his mouth while holding back the anger which was rising in his chest.

“Let’s head in. A banquet has been prepared to welcome the disciples. It might not be enough, but I hope you will forget the long journey you overcame to come here and enjoy it.”

“Banquet? The Mount Hua and Southern Edge conference isn’t about eating and playing.”

“… We understand that.”

“Still, it is fine. Take the lead. I need to meet the sect leader.”

Hyun Sang let out a low sigh.

‘My words don’t seem to be getting through.’

The Southern Edge Sect acted the same in the past, but it wasn’t this extreme. Perhaps, this was being done with some purpose in mind.

But didn’t Hyun Jong already warn the elders not to behave recklessly? Remembering these words, Hyun Sang choked back his anger and smiled.

“Come with me.”

“Hmm.”

Sama Seung entered with small steps. In the meantime, the newly built gates caught his eye.

‘Looks like they got some support.’

It seemed like some blind fool threw quite a bit of money into Mount Hua. So, the sect used the money to deal with the most urgent issues. The first thing they worked on were things that people could see, like the gates.

But the internal buildings couldn’t be…

“What?”

Those who entered the gate let out a gasp.

“T-training hall?”

“When?”

They could clearly see that the training halls were all newly rebuilt with blue tiles laid out over the spacious area as they entered the gate.

‘T-they repaired all of this?’

No, was it all new?

Did the God of Wealth descend on Mount Hua?

“It’s better than the Southern Edge Sect.”

The slight murmur that someone from behind whispered represented the feelings of everyone present. Compared to this, even the Southern Edge Sect looked shabby.

Just two years ago, Mount Hua and everything within were crumbling and in ruins. When did such a dramatic change occur?

Sama Seung’s face contorted as he came to a halt.

As the elder stopped walking, Hyun Sang looked back and asked.

“Is something wrong?”

“Doesn’t it seem like a lot has changed?”

Hyun Sang smiled and answered.

“Good things have happened.”

“Does Mount Hua still have someone that supports you? I hope that such a prestigious sect wouldn’t resort to fraud or thievery.”

Instantly, Hyun Sang’s face burned red with fury.

Even if the sect leader had ordered them to maintain peace, this was an intolerable remark.

“Be careful of what you say—”

It was then.

“Fuck you! Do you have a death wish!?”

Everyone’s eyes turned to the voice that came from the side.

Sama Seung’s face went stiff, seeing the scene unfolding in front of him.

‘W-what is he doing?’

His eyes caught sight of a series of disciples running like horses. It appears they had been training for a long time. Their robes were drenched in sweat, and their expressions seemed like they would faint any moment; despite that, they continued to press forward with staggering legs.

It was a bizarre sight.

However, that wasn’t where Sama Seung was looking.

He stared at the one that interrupted their conversation.

Next to the running group stood a person in clean clothes with a calm expression. Unlike the others, he ran with the group as if he was taking a brisk walk.

A small child.

Sama Seung, who looked at the child, asked in a hoarse voice.

“What did you just say?”

Read the manhwa on Asura Scans!

Chapter 91: If you lose to those bastards, you lose everything! (1)

The disciples of Mount Hua, who were exhausted and on the verge of collapse from running, came to a hurried stop. Unfortunately for them, they happened to stop right as the Southern Edge Sect arrived at the same location.

Standing next to the third-class disciples, who were gasping and panting for air, Chung Myung awkwardly tilted his head and looked at Sama Seung.

“Me?”

A face that didn’t seem to understand anything. Seeing the child’s attempt to act innocent, Sama Seung asked again.

“I asked you, what did you just say?”

“Oh, that.’

Instead of answering, Chung Myung kicked the already staggering Jo Gul’s shin.

“Ack!”

“Fuck you! Do you have a death wish!? Can’t you run straight!?”

“I am your Sahyung, you jerk!”

“Ah, I forgot for a second there.”

Chung Myung scratched his head and grinned as he looked at Sama Seung.

“That must be what you heard. So embarrassing.”

“…”

Sama Seung glared at Chung Myung with venom dripping from his gaze.

Sama Seung was not stupid enough to misunderstand who those words were directed at. There was no way he would be deceived by a child and his antics.

“This…”

At that moment, someone gently tugged on Sama Seung’s sleeve. At this, he stopped himself from speaking and glanced back.

It was Jin Geum-Ryong.

“Elder, nothing good can come from arguing with a child.”

“Hmm.”

Sama Seung sighed and nodded.

No matter how angry he was, he was an elder of the Southern Edge Sect. The difference in status was too great for him to speak to a child. If rumors spread that a third-class disciple from Mount Hua and an elder from the Southern Edge Sect engaged in an argument, it would disgrace his name.

Jin Geum-Ryong stepped forward.

“Who is this young disciple?”

“Who am I? Would you even know if I told you?”

“…”

Jin Geum-Ryong looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes.

He had never before met anyone who answered him with a question like this. Feeling beyond upset, he calmed himself and smiled.

“Perhaps I might know you? So, why don’t you tell me?”

“Well, it isn’t difficult. I am Chung Myung.”

“Chung Myung?”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s smiling face immediately went stiff.

It was a familiar name.

Wasn’t Chung Myung the name of the Mount Hua disciple that humiliated the Southern Edge Sect?

Jin Geum-Ryong narrowed his eyes and looked at Chung Myung.

‘He’s younger than I thought.’

He thought it was absurd.

Thanks to Chung Myung curing Elder Hwang, the Eunha Guild severed their relationship with the Southern Edge Sect and began supporting Mount Hua.

It was such an embarrassment that the Southern Edge Sect refused to discuss the matter, even more so because Mount Hua was at its center.

Thanks to that, the elders and the sect leader were furious. But the one that caused such shame to fall upon the sect was this young child?

“I see. Disciple Chung Myung. But it seems like disciple Chung Myung never learned proper manners.”

Although it was an outright rebuke at his attitude, Chung Myung picked his ears and whistled.

“I’m sorry, but I can’t hear you very well. Could you come closer and speak up a bit?”

“… what did you say?”

“Are you deaf? Come closer and talk to me. Can’t you hear?”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s face hardened.

‘Just what the hell does this kid believe in?’

If what Lee Song-Baek said was true, this child was knocked back after one strike. This child had little training in martial arts. What did he believe in that gave him the confidence to speak such nonsense?

Unless he was someone with no sense.

It made Jim Geum-Ryong want to pull out his sword and cut down the arrogant child right in front of him.

However, this was Mount Hua and not the Southern Edge sect. He couldn’t act carelessly here. This wasn’t Jin Geum-Ryong’s role to play.

Gnashing his teeth, he tried to speak softly.

“Aren’t you a third-class disciple of Mount Hua?”

“That’s right.”

“Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect have shared weal and woe in the past. Since that’s the case, and since I am the senior, shouldn’t you be the one to come closer to speak? Of course, as long as you have the slightest sense of manners.”

“Ah, really?”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“Then, why didn’t you say that to your elder earlier? If you think that it’s more polite for me to come closer to sasuk, then shouldn’t the elder of the Southern Edge Sect be the one going to visit our sect leader?”

‘Ah, shit.’

Aghast, Jin Geum-Ryong hastily fell silent.

He was trying to scold Chung Myung, but this child used it as an opening to point out Sama Seung’s rudeness.

‘I ended up making a mistake.’

No, it wasn’t a mistake.

This small child led the flow of conversation like that. Letting Jin Geum-Ryong stumble onto his mistake and admit his elder’s fault.

“This…”

At that time, Sama Seung, who was watching the situation, opened his mouth.

“This young man’s mouth doesn’t seem ordinary.”

“Elder.”

“Move.”

Jin Geum-Ryong, who bit his lip, stared at Chung Myung and then moved back without another word.

Sama Seung smiled.

“Since your actions came from your pure-hearted desire to protect your sect leader’s dignity, I won’t hold you accountable this time.”

“Yes, thank you.”

“But you had best remember one thing. Your rudeness and mine aren’t the same. Do you know why?”

“… Well?”

“Because of power.”

Sama Seung spoke in a low voice.

“It is only when one’s actions are pointed out that impoliteness is considered rude. If no one is willing to point it out, it is simply a passing remark. The right to point out such impoliteness comes from power. Your actions are rude because of your weakness, but my impoliteness cannot be considered rude because of my power.”

Chung Myung frowned.

“I think you should learn to speak more kindly before worrying about being polite.”

“… what a crazy one.”

Sama Seung turned away from Chung Myung and looked at Hyun Sang.

“I apologize for the disrespect earlier.”

“Ah, no. Elder, why are you like this?”

“Now that the child pointed out what I did, wasn’t I being rude? I need to apologize.”

Hyun Sang wasn’t sure what to do.

It was a strange situation where the person who committed the mistake apologized, yet the person receiving the apology was the one that felt more uncomfortable.

Sama Seung smiled and looked back at Chung Myung before speaking.

“Courage is easy to forgive when you’re young. However, one day, your actions may cause you to lose your head. Remember my words.”

With that, Sama Seung turned around.

“Let’s go.”

“Yes, elder.”

Guided by Hyun Sang, he led the disciples and began walking again.

Meanwhile, Lee Seong-Baek bowed his head to Chung Myung.

When Chung Myung returned his greeting with a slight nod, he smiled faintly and walked ahead.

As the Southern Edge Sect disciples moved away, Jo Gul spoke with a pale face.

“Have you lost it? What the hell are you trying to do?”

“What?”

“That person is an elder of the Southern Edge Sect! Elder! Southern Edge Sect!”

“Yah!”

Chung Myung kicked Jo Gul in the shin again. He struck the same place as before, and Jo Gul agonizingly clutched his leg as he rolled along the floor.

“Ack!”

“Are you a disciple of Mount Hua? Didn’t you hear the bullshit he was spouting towards the sect leader? You think we should hold back?”

“Do you think we’re enduring because we want to?”

Yoon Jong stepped forward with a stiff face.

“Of course, we’re angry, but his words are right. A man without power has no right to point out the flaws of someone who does have strength.”

“Who said we lacked power?”

“…. Huh?”

Chung Myung turned his head and looked at the disciples of the Southern Edge Sect, who were walking away.

‘Those bastards, how dare they.’

It was annoying that those thieves were brazen enough to walk into Mount Hua on their own feet, but they even dared to insult the sect leader.

Even though Chung Myung believes that the current sect leader of Mount Hua lacks the qualifications of a real sect leader, Hyun Jong is still Mount Hua’s representative. So, Chung Myung must protect his dignity from others.

For those idiots to insult the sect leader of Mount Hua…

Chung Myung’s eyes began to blaze in a fury.

“I tried to be good to them. But those bastards, even in a new life, want to start fights with me.”

“… No, let’s calm down….”

“Chung Myung. Please, I beg of you. Let’s think first and then act. Huh?”

The third-class disciples panicked when they saw the look in Chung Myung’s eyes. They all knew they would be unable to do anything if Chung Myung got angry.

At that moment, Chung Myung shook his head.

“Did all the Sahyungs get a good look?”

“… what?”

“What those bastards are doing. Even if they ignore Mount Hua, there Is a limit to it. Are Sahyungs going to endure everything they say?”

“… no, we don’t want to tolerate it either. But how do you….”

“Listen well, Sahyungs.”

Chung Myung spoke with eyes that didn’t stop blazing.

“If you lose to those bastards, you will lose everything.”

“…”

The faces of Yoon Jong and all the third-class disciples went pale.

Chung Myung’s eyes were spitting flames.

“You can lose to anyone else. It doesn’t matter where you go or who beats you up. Only those Southern Edge Sect bastards, they are the only ones that you can never lose to. Even if you have to die. Anyone who makes me see such a shameful sight had better be prepared. There will come a day where the one who makes others shed tears of blood will shed tears of blood themselves!”

‘What you’re saying doesn’t fit the situation, you brat!’

‘It is the other way around for us!’

‘You’re the one making us cry bloody tears!’

“Why aren’t you answering?”

Chung Myung asked with eyes sparkling in madness. Just the sight made a chill run down their spine.

“N-No. We want to do that too. But we…”

“What? We what?”

Chung Myung approached the third-class disciples with a frightful glare.

“Are you not confident that you can win?”

“R-rather than that….”

“Are you confident enough to die?”

“…”

“Let me see a single loss. Just one. That’s fine, right. Let’s all die together. You die, and I die too.”

“…”

The Mount Hua and Southern Edge Sect conference.

An event that was held to deepen the friendship between Mount Hua and Southern Edge.

However, now it seems like blood would be spilled because of one person’s anger.

“That little boy….”

Jong Seo-Han glanced back. Jin Geum-Ryong approached him and quietly asked.

“Are you concerned about him?”

Jong Seo-Han whispered, making sure that no one else heard him.

“Rather than being concerned, it feels ridiculous. I don’t know where such a kid came from.”

“Leave it alone.”

Jin Geum-Ryong spoke in a stiff voice.

“It is the privilege of the weak to go wild and crazy without knowing the truth. Only a foal who doesn’t know how high the sky is would act so recklessly.”

“That is true, but….”

“I have no remorse; he acted arrogantly on his own will. Since we’ve come here for the conference, there will be plenty of opportunities for us to punish him in the future.”

“I’d love to see if he can still talk like that once I tear off his mouth.”

Jin Geum-Ryong smiled brightly.

“That isn’t something a virtuous disciple should say.”

“He was the one who started this fight.”

“True.”

To be precise, the Southern Edge sect started this fight, but Jin Geum-Ryong didn’t bother pointing that out.

“Don’t worry about useless things.”

Sama Seung, who was ahead, spoke in a low voice at that time.

“In the end, a warrior will always speak with his sword. No matter how sharp his tongue may be, nothing will change.”

“Yes, elder.”

“Strength isn’t everything. But this is a place where nothing can be done without power. You all shouldn’t forget that fact.”

“I’ll keep that in mind.”

Sama Seung narrowed his eyes.

“This time the conference will be interesting. Seeing them behave so arrogantly, they must have something to believe in. We must be sure to thoroughly trample their beliefs and quash their hope. Do you understand?”

“Yes! Elder!”

Sama Seung nodded his head with a smile.

‘A very interesting one.’

Still, it was somewhat commendable. Even the elders of Mount Hua were fearful about speaking against the Southern Edge Sect, but that young man stepped forward fearlessly…

Sama Seung stopped and looked back.

The disciples who were following him were startled and halted in place.

“Elder?”

“What’s wrong?”

Sama Seung, who was staring back with a fear-inducing gaze, soon calmed his expression.

“No, nothing. It was nothing.”

The elder then turned around while gently waving his hand.

Yet, his face hardened again.

Chung Myung clearly pointed out Sama Seung’s fault. That meant… he’d heard how rude he was to Mount Hua’s sect leader?

‘Then…he heard what I said at the gate from that distance?’

It was such a great distance that Sama Seung hadn’t even known about Chung Myung’s existence.

‘No, that can’t be right.’

He must be mistaken.

‘I must have been nervous. To think such absurd thoughts.’

With a low smile, Sama Seung hurried along.

However, his steps were a little heavier than before.

Chapter 92: If you lose to those bastards, you lose everything! (2)

Sama Seung sat across from Mount Hua’s sect leader, Hyun Jong, and carefully observed him.

‘Hyun Jong.’

Hyun Jong was the one who somehow managed to hold together the crumbling fragments of Mount Hua and prevent a total collapse of the sect. The sect leader of the Southern Edge Sect had evaluated Hyun Jong as a man who would have excelled in his position if only the circumstances hadn’t been so disastrous.

‘It’s an over-evaluation.’

Hyun Jong had never once shown excellence befitting his title. Anyone willing to sacrifice themselves for their responsibilities would receive a good evaluation.

‘However, a person’s greatness isn’t judged by their character, but by their achievements.’

Sama Seung turned his head and looked around.

To the left and right of Hyun Jong, there were the martial arts head and the finance heads. The Un disciples, including Un Am and Un Geom, were also seated here.

All of Mount Hua’s major figures gathered to welcome him. This wasn’t the first time he had seen this…

‘Definitely.’

It felt a little different than before.

At the previous conference, everyone he had seen looked tired of their lives and depressed.

But now, it felt like there was no pressure binding them, and a subtle relaxation was felt around them.

‘I don’t like this.’

Sama Seung narrowed his eyes.

It didn’t matter what the source of their confidence was. Whether it was money or martial arts, it would just be groundless bravado. There was no way for Mount Hua to do anything except fall.

Sama Seung was dissatisfied with the confident atmosphere the elders of Mount Hua exuded.

“I’m not sure if you’ll enjoy the tea.”

When Hyun Jong spoke, Sama Seung lightly nodded his head.

“It has a deep fragrance.”

“I am glad you like it.”

Sama Seung smiled.

“It indeed has a deep fragrance, but I don’t enjoy the scent of plum blossoms.”

Hyun Jong’s eyes widened a little. However, he soon regained his composure and spoke in a soft tone.

“Is there a reason?”

“There are many scents in the forest. The scent of soil, trees, and even the dew on the leaves. But when the plum blossoms are in full bloom, their scent is the only one around. It is so thick that it obscures everything around them.”

Just like Mount Hua in the past.

“The world is a place where we exist together to live in harmony. That is why I prefer the subtle scent of green tea over the plum blossom, which breaks down that harmony.”

Sama Seung spoke calmly, but the Un disciples couldn’t hide their flushed faces. This was no different from openly talking back to the sect leader and criticizing the difference in authority.

However, the Hyun elders took Sama Seung’s words differently.

‘Does he mean that back when Mount Hua had dominance, we refused to live harmoniously with others?’

Bringing this subject up at such a moment must mean that the Southern Edge Sect still hasn’t forgotten their past grudges.

This wasn’t something the elder would dare to say in front of any other sect’s elders. However, no one pointed out Sama Seung’s actions.

As Sama Seung said, respect depends on the one who has power. The moment one becomes unable to punish disrespect and rudeness, their authority slips into an illusion.

With only a few words, Sama Seung managed to create the atmosphere he wanted and spoke with a smile.

“Sect leader.”

“Speak.”

“We in the Southern Edge Sect have no intention of continuing this tradition and holding any more conferences after this one.”

Hyun Jong frowned.

“Can I know the reason?”

“Simple.”

Sama Seung smiled and spoke.

“It is because the exchange with Mount Hua doesn’t help the Southern Edge Sect develop in any way. Isn’t the gap between us already too wide to bridge?”

Hyun Jong closed his eyes.

It was such a disgrace to hear this and to see that smug look on his face. Even elders sitting beside him struggled to contain their anger.

‘This bastard…’

Hyun Young’s beard trembled.

This was intentional. How could someone say such a thing in front of their Sect Leader?

Hyun Jong slowly opened his eyes.

“The conference isn’t just a ceremony to help with development. In the first place, this was done to help foster friendship between our two sects and grow closer—”

“Isn’t that just a façade?”

Sama Seung cut off Hyun Jong’s words.

“This…”

Hyun Young was boiling past the point of no return when Hyun Sang pressed his knee down, begging him not to act out of line.

Hyun Young looked at Hyun Sang and then at Hyun Jong as he bit his lower lip.

‘Isn’t he overdoing this?’

Who didn’t know that the two sects were as incompatible as oil and water? Even Mount Hua was keenly aware of that fact.

Mount Hua is a sect that boasts its history and tradition. Although it’s no longer there, Mount Hua’s name proudly stood alongside the Nine Great Sects and had aimed to be the greatest of them all.

Even if it wasn’t Mount Hua, but some lesser sect instead, it was impolite to behave like this to their face. Sama Seung couldn’t be ignorant of what a wicked deed he was committing.

Sama Seung glanced at Hyun Young and smiled.

Despite understanding the deeper meaning behind that smirk, Hyun Young couldn’t do anything but tighten his grip and endure.

Martial arts sects are ruthless.

Those who lack strength have no choice but to endure humiliation from the powerful.

After glancing at each of the people gathered in the room, Sama Seung continued.

“The Southern Edge Sect and Mount Hua have never had a good relationship. To be honest, wouldn’t it be more accurate to say that we are closer to being enemies? I’m sure that those in this room likely want to eat me alive and chew me down to the bone.”

“… It’s not that bad.”

“Then, is there anyone here who has good feelings towards me? No, does anyone have any good feelings towards the Southern Edge Sect itself?”

No one answered.

It wasn’t difficult to answer ‘yes,’ but why should they lie? They knew the truth, and so did Sama Seung.

“There is nothing more futile than trying to reconnect a thread which is already severed.”

Sama Seung’s voice was firm.

As if everything had been decided, and this was just a notice.

When an elder speaks with such confidence, it usually means that the decision has already been settled, and they’re simply relaying the message. So, this wasn’t just Sama Seung’s will, but that of the entire Southern Edge Sect.

Furthermore, the Southern Edge Sect was officially saying that they would stand atop Mount Hua and put them under their feet.

A declaration that they would no longer regard Mount Hua as competition in the future.

It was disgraceful.

Completely humiliating.

And when no one dared to speak, Un Am spoke up.

“Isn’t this a bit too sudden?”

“It should have been done already.”

“Elder.”

Seeing that Un Am didn’t back down, Sama Seung glanced at him as if looking down on him.

“Then, do you think Mount Hua has the qualifications to compete with the Southern Edge Sect?”

Un Am went silent. He couldn’t answer that.

With a smile, Sama Seung continued.

“I think the Southern Edge Sect has done everything we could to treat Mount Hua with utmost kindness until now.”

“Utmost kindness? You are acting too much!”

As Un Am raised his voice, Sama Seung laughed.

“What is too much?”

“…”

“The Southern Edge Sect has forgotten the grudges of the past and helped Mount Hua till now. In fact, isn’t it unfair for us to continue like this with Mount Hua? The conference has always been held in Mount Hua, and we’ve even provided a certain degree of wealth whenever we travel here for the event. Yet, despite our kindness, you still choose to blame us?”

This wasn’t right.

Un Am ground his teeth.

The reason why the conference was held in Mount Hua was obvious.

Southern Edge did it to come and ridicule the crumbling Mount Hua and to show off their own martial arts.

The wealth they provided as ‘support’ to Mount Hua was just a pretense of keeping the sect from refusing to hold the conference.

“Sect leader.”

Sama Seung spoke resolutely.

“It might be hard to understand but allow me to simplify it. Once you see the results of this conference, you will be the first to ask that this never happens to Mount Hua again. Think carefully about this if you don’t want to ruin the children.”

Sama Seung got up from his seat. Then left the room without letting his mood be affected by the change of atmosphere.

While everyone else was too shocked and didn’t know what to do, Hyun Jong asked a question.

“Is this path the final one which the Southern Edge Sect has chosen?”

Sama Seung stopped walking and slowly turned his head to look back. Hyun Jong’s expressionless face left Sama Seung unable to discern the intentions behind his question.

“That isn’t up to me to decide.”

With that, the foreign elder opened the door and left the room.

Anguish filled the faces of those who were left behind.

“How can they say such a thing!?”

Hyun Young couldn’t hold back his anger and slammed the table. Cracks appeared on the table.

But no one thought of blaming him.

Un Geom opened his mouth with a heavy feeling.

“Every time the conference is held, they’ve always been aggressive, but this is the first time they’ve acted so viciously.”

“That’s right. This is over the line!”

“How can a mere elder speak like that to the sect leader!?”

“Isn’t the Southern Edge Sect supposed to come and relay this directly?”

No one could hold back their anger and continued adding to each other’s grievances.

Among them, only Hyun Jong quietly shook his head with a sad face.

“… leave it alone.”

“But sect leader!”

“Words are sometimes spoken in vain. Would our words have any meaning now?”

Un Am bowed his head. The others also bowed, their faces shifting between expressions of anguish and fury.

Hyun Jong said.

“I can tolerate any amount of disgrace. Even if they spit in my face, I can smile back at them. That isn’t what I’m worried about right now.”

“… then?”

“I’m worried about the children.”

“Ah…”

Un Am’s eyes trembled.

“Looking at how he said it directly, surely, the conference will be extremely daunting this time. I can endure the insults they cast on me, but what should I do if our children are going to suffer too?”

Hyun Jong’s face turned bitter. As a sect leader of a weak sect, the burden he had to endure was too heavy.

“Then, even now….”

Un Am kept his mouth shut.

He wanted to say ‘Then we should stop the conference now!’, but before he could even finish speaking, he realized what situation they were in.

It was a disgrace worse than death for those learning martial arts to give up in fear of an opponent.

Moreover, the children can understand the situation well enough. If they are asked to surrender without a proper match, this will haunt them for the rest of their lives.

“My sins are too great.”

Hyun Jong sighed deeply. Nobody could find any words to comfort him, and so everyone decided to remain silent.

Un Geom, who was quietly listening to the conversation, spoke up at that moment.

“Sect leader. There is no need to think like that.”

Hyun Jong’s eyes turned to Un Geom.

“They want to show a clear gap between Mount Hua and themselves in order to spread the news that we’re no longer worthy of being a prestigious sect within Shaanxi. It would be a decisive blow for our sect, which has already fallen so far from our peak. Isn’t that what they’re aiming for?

“True, but we’ve run out of tricks up our sleeve.”

“We don’t need any tricks. Wouldn’t it be enough as long as we don’t let them win so easily?”

“…”

“Sect leader.”

Seeing Hyun Jong at a loss of words, Un Geom slightly smiled as he spoke.

“Trust the children. Maybe we’ll receive some good news.”

“…”

Un Geom smiled as he received everyone’s gazes filled with suspicion.

‘Now it’s your turn to prove yourself. Chung Myung.’

Chapter 94: If you lose to those bastards, you lose everything! (4)

Chung Myung looked around as he climbed up the mountain.

‘She isn’t here, right?’

Chung Myung, who was quite nervous that Yu Yiseol would catch up with him, sighed deeply.

“Sigh… what am I doing?”

Chung Myung had nothing in this world he feared. In the past, when he was the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, there were people afraid of him, but he was never afraid of others.

Wasn’t the sect leader of the Shaolin sect even reluctant to meet him?

But now, that same Chung Myung was in a situation where he avoided a little girl.

“What am I being made to deal with?”

It would be so much simpler if he could just hit her on the head, wrap her up with a rope, and toss her off a cliff somewhere. But since she’s just an innocent nuisance, he can’t beat her up, right?

Huh?

What about Baek Cheon?

“That bastard came at me first.”

There’s a difference between a senior who picks a fight and a senior that’s a nuisance.

Well, for the first time in this life… no, for the first time ever, Chung Myung was avoiding others.

“What’s become of me!? Why do I need to avoid people this early in the morning!?”

Chung Myung, who stopped to take a deep breath, was ready to run up again.

‘Oh?’

He felt something.

“Yah! Yah! I knew this was going to happen! It’s useless to try fooling an old ghost like me! You can’t deceive…huh?”

Chung Myung titled his head.

This qi he was feeling was different from Yu Yiseol’s.

Yu Yiseol boasts a weird sense of non-existence; it was something that Chung Myung would have to heavily concentrate on feeling.

So, Chung Myung would listen for her footsteps instead.

However, what he was feeling now was too strong and clear to be Yu Yiseol. And…

“Two people?”

Not just one.

Chung Myung’s eyes narrowed, and he moved cautiously as he sensed the qi.

For two people to be meeting in this deep mountain so early in the morning. It felt like a conspiracy.

‘I need to see what they’re up to.’

Chung Myung’s eyes began to sparkle.

Swoosh!

His feet began to swiftly cut through the wind and accelerate. Chung Myung quickly halted and melded into his surroundings as he approached the area that he felt the qi coming from.

And then, he carefully snuck forward and stuck his head out to have a peek.

‘Huh?’

Chung Myung blinked his eyes. No matter how much he tried to double-check if his senses were right, the sight in front of him didn’t change.

One of the two figures was someone Chung Myung knew.

Baek Cheon.

It wasn’t strange for Baek Cheon to be here; after all, this was still Mount Hua’s territory.

But the other person standing there was unexpected, he wasn’t from Mount Hua, and the situation seemed strange.

‘Why is he here?’

Jin Geum-Ryong.

Jin Geum-Ryong, one of the Southern Edge Sect’s greatest disciples, stood opposite Baek Cheon with an odd expression.

‘Why are the two of them meeting here?’

It was definitely a conspiracy.

Chung Myung cautiously moved closer to listen in.

“You seem to be doing well.”

Jin Geum-Ryong smiled brightly and spoke to Baek Cheon. But Baek Cheon’s face clearly expressed his displeasure.

“You seem to be at ease.”

“Isn’t there a reason for that, Dong-Ryong?”

“Pffft!”

Jin Geum-Ryong and Baek Cheon both turned their gazes toward the sudden sound.

‘Ah, shit!’

Chung Myung desperately held his breath and concealed himself.

It was almost unbearable for Chung Myung to restrain his laughter when he heard the word Dong-Ryong. (Bronze Dragon)

The two looked at each other again. They probably thought it was just a passing beast.

Baek Cheon’s face contorted.

“Don’t call me by that name. I am Baek Cheon.”

“Don’t think of throwing away the name your parents gave you. No matter what anyone says, you are Jin Dong-Ryong.”

‘Ugh. Please, just stop already.’

Chung Myung clutched the floor and tried not to laugh.

‘Oh shit. I might die. Dong-Ryong. Baek Cheon’s real name is Dong-Ryong! Ah, my stomach might rip at this rate!’

Chung Myung’s body trembled and was cramped as he fought to hold back his laughter.

Baek Cheon’s face quickly turned red as if it would burst.

“It’s Baek Cheon!”

“Fine, Dong-Ryong.”

‘Wow, he is really losing it.’

Baek Cheon hated it so much that his face was burning red, but the other guy just kept calling him Dong-Ryong.

‘Such a bad personality.’

Whether or not he knew about Chung Myung’s internal evaluation of him, Jin Geum-Ryong continued to speak with a smile.

“Isn’t Mount Hua a great place to live? You look pretty good too, don’t you think?”

“What are you trying to say?”

“I just wanted to see you.”

A smile grew on Jin Geum-Ryong’s lips.

“To see what kind of an ugly life that little brother of mine who ran away from home to beat his older brother was living in Mount Hua.”

“You saw that two years ago, didn’t you?”

“I never get tired of kicking a defeated dog; not even a hundred times would be enough.”

Baek Cheon’s face crumpled.

This was Jin Geum-Ryong’s true character. He was merciless to those he considered weaker than himself. He usually disguises himself with a kind face, but he was rotten inside.

How long had Baek Cheon been bullied by him?

“What do you say? If you get on your knees and beg, I can accept you into the Southern Edge Sect.”

“Don’t spout shit.”

Baek Cheon looked straight at Jin Geum-Ryong.

“I am Baek Cheon, the Great Sahyung of Mount Hua’s second-class disciples. My dream is to make Mount Hua into a well-known sect that stands above the Southern Edge Sect. So don’t say such words in front of me again.”

‘Oh?’

Chung Myung looked at the two in front of him with shining eyes.

Let’s see.

So, these two are brothers, one Geum-Ryong (Golden Dragon) and the other is Dong-Ryong. (Bronze dragon)

‘… I really want to meet their father, at least once.’

He needed to meet the enemy that caused his belly such pain. What on earth did he think when he named his children like that!? That’s why Baek Cheon ran away!

Baek Cheon spoke with a growl.

“Since I know you’re just speaking hollow words, I’ll ignore that remark. After all, I know that even if I begged, you would simply mock me and act like it never happened. That’s just the kind of person you are.”

“Haha, being brothers is strange. You know me so well, despite being apart for so long.”

Jin Geum-Ryong, who had been smiling until then, suddenly changed his expression and turned cold.

“You made the wrong choice.”

“…”

“If you wanted to defeat me, you should have entered the Southern Edge Sect. Maybe then you might have had a chance, but you chose Mount Hua instead of the Southern Edge Sect? You fled to a crippled sect to defeat me? Hahahaha! Even a dog would find this funny!”

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

“Do not look down on Mount Hua.”

“Oh?”

“Yes, you’re right. The reason I joined Mount Hua was that you despised it. I will lead Mount Hua and defeat the older brother who ignored and looked down on me.”

“Such a foolish idea, so stupid that it makes me feel dumb for listening. It’s exactly like you.”

Ignoring the constant flood of spiteful words, Baek Cheon firmly said.

“In the beginning, I certainly was childish. But now, I really like Mount Hua. Living my life as Baek Cheon, Great Sahyung of Mount Hua’s second-class disciples is the most rewarding experience for me.”

‘Ohh?’

Chung Myung looked at Baek Cheon with a subtle sense of pride emanating from his eyes.

‘So that’s his story?’

He did say that he needed to grow stronger. So, there must have been a reason behind it, right?

Chung Myung felt a bit moved by Baek Cheon’s words.

‘Ah, this is so….’

“You think it’s rewarding to live as the disciple of a crumbling sect? In this ruined mountain? Has your mind gone astray?”

‘That son of a bitch!’

Hearing what this bastard had to say, Chung Myung grew furious.

‘I just need to punch him once!’

“Yes.”

Baek Cheon answered firmly.

“It might seem strange, but I understood once I stayed here. I’m not the sort of person who is happy living comfortably in a rich sect with nice food, clothes, and education. At the very least, this place needs me here. I can set a goal and help develop this sect. Mount Hua is a sect that has given me a goal to strive for. Furthermore, it is a home which embraced me affectionately!”

“Affection?”

Jin Geum-Ryong frowned.

“Such weakness. When I see you talking like that, I understand that you’ve lost your sense of reality. Let me tell you. You’re already finished. As a result of your pathetic choice, you will live the rest of your life in humiliation, forever left behind as a third-rate martial artist. Nothing more than a servant. Meanwhile, you will watch me rise as the future sect leader of the Southern Edge Sect from your withered hovel.”

“Well, I don’t really care. I am going to live my life regardless.”

“You’re going to live your life like trash. Well, at least it will be fun for me to watch.”

Jin Geum-Ryong said with a sly smile.

“But I’m not one to watch on the side for long. Rather than waste time waiting, I will show you tomorrow. You’ll see just how stupid it was for you to choose Mount Hua instead of the Southern Edge Sect.”

Jin Geum-Ryong tilted his head as if contemplating something before a wretched sneer covered his face.

“No, No. Maybe this was a good choice. After all, there’s no better combination for a ruined sect than an idiot disciple.”

“I don’t mind you insulting me, but your foul mouth has no right to speak of Mount Hua. Watch yourself, or I’ll tear that mouth of yours off.”

“… someone like you?”

Jin Geum-Ryong glared at Baek Cheon as he trembled in anger.

After staring for a while, Jin Geum-Ryong suddenly smiled.

“There’s no need to rush. The time will come when you realize it. Neither you nor Mount Hua will be able to make their marks on the world after tomorrow. I’ll make certain of that.”

Jin Geum-Ryong glanced once more at Baek Cheon before descending the mountain.

Baek Cheon sighed deeply as he stared at Jin Geum-Ryong’s slowly fading figure.

‘Can I do it?’

Jin Geum-Ryong is a strong man that always achieves his goals. Aside from his poor attitude, he was still more talented and greater than Baek Cheon.

Baek Cheon bit his lip.

‘I shouldn’t let myself be shaken.’

He is Baek Cheon of Mount Hua. One day, he would become the sect leader of Mount Hua and lead everyone into glory.

Baek Cheon, who was mumbling to himself, finally steeled his determination and turned around.

“Wow, look at this admirable kid.”

“Ah! Fuck! You scared me!”

Baek Cheon was so terrified at the sudden words that he fell backward on the floor. He was so shocked that he thought his heart would burst through his throat.

When he finally settled down, he saw Chung Myung nodding his head with a pleased expression.

“You, you… why are you here?”

“Dong-Ryo… ahh, Do-Do, Dong-Ryong.”

Baek Cheon’s expression crumpled when he heard Chuny Myung’s words, while the culprit himself struggled to hold back his oppressive laughter.

“… you heard everything?”

“Oh my, Dong-Ryong. I was amazed by your wonderful heart, which holds such pride for Mount Hua.”

Chung Myung nodded, while Baek Cheon sighed.

“Are you a ghost? I couldn’t even feel your presence.”

“Well, that is to be expected.”

“… I haven’t done anything wrong, but don’t tell anyone about this. Others might not think of this as a good thing.”

“Don’t worry, Sasuk. This is Chung Myung! I’m the man with the heaviest mouth in the world.”

“…”

Doesn’t that mean that his mouth can’t hold anything?

Baek Cheon wrapped his head around the idea of being caught.

No one except the sect leader and a few elders knew about this. But of all the people to find out…

“Hmm. So, Sasuk is Jin Geum-Ryong’s younger brother?”

“Even though we’re brothers, we don’t have a friendly relationship. Our mothers are different….”

Baek Cheon sighed and tried to talk.

“Since I was little—”

“Ah, don’t bother.”

“Huh?”

“I don’t have the time to listen to such trivial drama. It’s obvious. Whether he’s older or younger, you were defeated by your talented sibling and didn’t get treated well, so you ran away from home and came to Mount Hua.”

“… don’t just summarize other people’s lives.”

But it was right.

“You did well.”

“Right. So… what?”

Baek Cheon titled his head.

“I said that you did well. Coming to Mount Hua.”

Chung Myung had a different expression from before. It wasn’t the mischievous smile that scratched a person’s nerves to anger them. Rather, it was simply a gentle smile.

Then, Chung Myung spoke with a heavy voice.

“No matter your origins or what your story is, Sasuk is a disciple of Mount Hua. You weren’t wrong to abandon the Southern Edge Sect and choose Mount Hua; we will prove it.”

Baek Cheon couldn’t say anything.

This didn’t seem like a speech that should come from such a young child. Strangely though, when Baek Cheon listened to Chung Myung’s words, he felt his heart at ease.

“We’ll prove it? When?”

“When?”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“Today.”

And then he turned away.

Soon the sun would rise, and the conference would begin.

“Let’s run wild, Sasuk.”

He couldn’t hear the other part, but,

Now is the time to crush those bastards!

Chapter 95: If you lose to those bastards, you lose everything! (5)

The day of the Mount Hua-Southern Edge Sect conference had finally dawned.

Hyun Jong was quietly looking at the second and third-class disciples lined up in front of him.

Seeing the hardened and stiff expressions on the faces of these children, Hyun Jong felt his heart clench. Even the children lined up in front of him understood the weight of their burden at this conference.

Hyun Jong felt as if his heart would break.

He wasn’t sure when things had changed, but this burden should originally have been shouldered by the elders and the sect leader. However, at some time after the initiation of this conference, the responsibility of proving the sect’s worth and defending its honor passed onto the sect’s young disciples.

Hyun Jong believed that even the second-class disciples were too young to carry this duty.

Not to mention the third-class disciples.

Still, he felt infinitely grateful to the children who withheld all complaints and stepped forward despite their worries.

“Sect Leader.”

Hyun Young recognized the anxious atmosphere, and Hyun Jong slightly raised his head.

The sect leader had fallen into sentimental thoughts and left the children standing in silence for too long.

Hyun Jong coughed to ease himself out of his emotional thoughts and spoke with a soft voice.

“Everyone seems nervous.”

Hyun Jong looked at the children and shook his head.

“You don’t have to be so stiff. It doesn’t matter whether we win or lose. All you must do is use this as an opportunity to learn and grow.”

Hyun Jong made eye contact with everyone as he spoke with determination.

“No matter what the outcome may be, you are all the proud disciples of Mount Hua. All you need to do is remember that fact.”

It was crudely spoken.

It was a speech that didn’t rouse their morale or seek to inspire the students to defeat their opponents and bring glory to Mount Hua.

But those words eased the disciples’ tense minds, and their expressions began to soften.

Hyun Jong nodded when he saw that everyone had begun to relax.

“I will keep watching over you. So go.”

With that, Hyun Jong turned and walked away; Hyun Young quickly followed after him.

“You won’t go with them?”

“No matter how difficult this conference may be, there is no need for those who will watch and those who will fight to arrive together. The children must also have things to say between themselves. Let them have their time together.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Hyun Young signaled to the other elders and Un disciples before they quickly followed Hyun Jong.

As the second-class and third-class disciples sighed, one person stepped forward.

Baek Cheon.

He stood in front of everyone with a determined face.

“Today, we will fight the Southern Edge Sect.”

Baek Cheon’s gaze landed on Chung Myung briefly before returning.

“As the sect leader said, there is no shame in losing. What is shameful is failing to do your best. When we fight, we fight as proud disciples of Mount Hua.”

“Yes! Sahyung!”

“Let’s go!”

With a resolute expression, Baek Cheon led the second-class disciples. A fierce aura of determination emanated from the second-class disciples who followed behind him. Even Yu Yiseol, who was farthest back, showed a much more serious visage than usual.

“Ahem.”

Yoon Jong snuck out to the front as the second-class disciples headed off.

And the third-class disciples warmly welcomed him.

“What, does the Great Sahyung have something to say?”

“No, let’s just do this. Such days scare me.”

“Haa. Seriously, I heard fighting turns people crazy.”

‘These bastards…’

“Look at you bastards, thinking that I can act like Baek Cheon sasuk!”

“I get it. Let’s move already; my legs hurt.”

“If you’re going to be like this, let’s all say something. Jo Gul Sahyung. Go ahead and stand ahead of us. It will save some time.”

“Uh.”

Yoon Jong took a deep breath.

‘They were all such good kids in the past.’

How did things end up like this?

Yoon Jong turned his head and looked at the culprit.

Even though a massive event like the conference was happening, Chung Myung looked like he was dying from boredom.

“Chung Myung.”

“Huh?”

“Do you have anything to say?”

Chung Myung laughed.

“Is there anything worth saying?”

Chung Myung turned his head and spoke calmly.

“Let’s finish this quickly and go eat. Move it.”

Yoon Jong unwittingly smiled at Chung Myung’s casual remark.

“Come, you brat.”

He didn’t know about the others, but he was sure of one thing.

Normally, Chung Myung was a madman. But in times like this, Yoon Jong felt reassured by his presence.

“Let’s go!”

Yoon Jong took the lead and guided everyone to the conference.

Following him, Chung Myung’s eyes seemed to glimmer.

The Mount Hua–Southern Edge conference is an event created for both sects to exchange techniques and experience the other.

Of course, there is a deeper intent internally since it was a way for the Southern Edge Sect to intervene with Mount Hua’s growth and humiliate them. On the surface, however, both sects maintained the appearance that this event was held out of mutual respect.

Therefore, this event never entertained visitors.

Until now, only the members of both sects had gathered together to witness the exchanges.

And this event was no different.

At least, that’s what everyone thought before they arrived at the hall.

Whisper.

“…”

Hyun Jong stared with his eyes wide open.

After passing through Mount Hua’s gate, one would find the great training hall. Due to the nature of the event, they required a large space. Therefore, the conference was held here without exception.

Until now, all of Mount Hua’s and the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples would line up on the left and right sides of this wide area. Today, however, a rather strange scene was playing out.

“W-what are they…?”

An unknown crowd had gathered in the training hall, with more people continuing to pour in.

What was more bizarre was that they each held some kind of item in their hands. Every one of them was carrying either chairs or tables.

Hyun Jong was taken aback by the unexpected situation. Un Am quickly approached him with an urgent face.

“Sect Leader.”

“What happened here?”

“A massive swarm of people flocked to the front gate and demanded to see the conference for themselves. There were too many people gathered for us to refuse.”

“Uhhh.”

Hyun Jong shook his head.

“Did the Southern Edge Sect call them here?”

If so, the purpose was obvious.

Their goal must be to show how horribly they crush Mount Hua.

He didn’t notice at first, but upon closer inspection, there were many colorfully dressed middle-aged men. Among them were some familiar faces to Hyun Jong; he could tell that many of the people here were Shaanxi’s officials.

Even local celebrities were called, and all around them were people in official uniforms.

Considering their influence, once they witnessed the events here, they would spread the news all over Shaanxi.

‘This is bad!’

Hyun Jong, who felt a bit anxious at that concerning thought, spoke in a lower voice.

“Don’t you know that strangers aren’t allowed inside without permission?”

“But sect leader.”

“Aren’t their intentions clear?”

“I-it is true, but….”

“Huh?”

A low voice was heard in Hyun Jong’s ears.

“Sect leader, I don’t believe this is something we coordinated before, is it?”

Hyun Jong turned his head.

The Southern Edge Sect elder, Sama Seung, approached them with a slightly embarrassed face.

Hyun Jong paid particular attention to his ‘embarrassed’ expression.

‘Did the Southern Edge Sect really not do this?’

If Sama Seung had gathered everyone here, there was no reason for him to be so bewildered. He would have leisurely walked in with a grin.

Hyun Jong snuck a glance at Un Am.

“What happened?”

“I tried to stop them, but the person who brought them—”

“Is me, Sect Leader.”

Both Hyun Jong and Sama Seung shifted their sights to the new arrival and witnessed a familiar smiling face approach them.

“Elder Hwang?”

“Elder Hwang?”

Hwang Mun-Yak of the Eunha Merchant Guild.

“It’s quite exhilarating.”

Elder Hwang arrived, and the two representatives greeted him. Still, they each had their own doubts.

With a bright smile, Hwang Mun-Yak said.

“Since the conference is being held, I thought there should be some excitement, so I invited an audience.”

“Hmm.”

Hyung Jong frowned and was about to refute when Sama Seung’s response beat him to the punch.

“I don’t think it’s a bad idea. Since this will be the last conference, it should be alright to make it a grand event.”

Sama Seung held the power of the Southern Edge Sect.

Hyun Jong sighed.

If Elder Hwang had invited this crowd, and the Southern Edge sect agreed to it, it would be difficult for Mount Hua to oppose the decision. Was he going to tell those who just climbed Mount Hua to return with nothing to show for it?

‘I can’t do that.’

Word would spread that Mount Hua was too harsh to their guests. It would be even worse when considering the influence of the officials here.

‘It will be difficult.’

It would be difficult to deal with them.

In the end, Hyun Jong had to sigh and smile.

“Sure. Since you’re here, please enjoy yourselves.”

“Thanks for your understanding, Sect Leader. Well then.”

Elder Hwang smiled and turned around. The others who gathered also smiled and headed to the audience seats prepared by Elder Hwang.

Elder Hwang, who led the crowd, raised his head and looked at Chung Myung.

‘Will this be fine?’

Chung Myung nodded.

Exchanging glances, Elder Hwang was left with an awkward feeling.

‘This young disciple always surprises me. What is he going to do this time?’

It was none other than Chung Myung who requested that Elder Hwang gather the influential people of Shaanxi. Chung Myung secretly visited Elder Hwang and spoke to him in Hua-Um.

- First, I need you to gather all the famous people you can.

‘I did what I was told. I don’t know what will happen next, young disciple.’

Looking at Hwang Mun-Yak’s gaze, Chung Myung smiled.

‘The best way to taste success is with others watching!’

What’s the point of fighting each other when there’s no one around?

Even if they produced good results, no one would believe it, and the Southern Edge Sect can simply deny anything Mount Hua says. Therefore, he had to make sure that everyone could see the results with their own eyes.

“The preparations are done.”

“Huh?”

“No, nothing.”

How could anyone else know what he had planned?

Anyway!

‘My Sahyung! I’m using my head! Hurry and take back what you said about me being stupid!’

- Right, I suppose a small brain is still a brain.

“Can’t you compliment me!? How great would it be if you could praise me to my face?”

Jo Gul frowned and leered at Chung Myung.

“Why do you keep talking to yourself? Are you nervous?”

“…”

While Chung Myung sighed, the preparations were finished.

The chairs and tables were neatly arranged, the audience was seated, and the servants brought everyone refreshments too.

“It looks like it’s starting.”

Someone’s nervous voice could be heard.

Un Am walked to the middle of the training hall. Standing in the center, he looked around and clapped his hands.

Straightening his chest, he took a deep breath and loosed a solemn and hoarse voice.

“Then, let’s begin the Mount Hua-Southern Edge Sect conference.”

The atmosphere grew heated in an instant.